You're having a hard time because of me, right?
I hope you'll be happy, Sang Sik.
If you think about me a little bit,
you could let go some of your past.
I thought I had forgotten about it, but...
Then that's fine.
Let's not talk about the past any more for each other's sake.
I don't have...
the confidence...
to keep seeing you as if nothing happened.
I moved here because I wanted to be happy.
Certainly, there were many happy moments.
However, I realised that for his sake,
I could no longer stay here.
(Second to Last Love)
(Episode 14)
Hey, what happened?
She really did pack up and leave.
Did she say anything to you?
Me? Why?
You were the one that signed the lease with her.
You're right. Hold on.
Gosh.
"I'm sorry I couldn't say goodbye. I'll call you soon."
I didn't even know she texted.
Where were all of you?
We were at the stable. Ha Ni's not well.
Did you give him the bracelet?
Right. This?
Why do you have this?
I went to clean your study room,
and I saw Min Joo leave it behind.
What took you so long to give it to him?
You just left with all of your stuff just like that?
Yes.
What about your other stuff?
I put it in storage.
You're nuts.
It's not a problem having you stay with me,
but why did you run out of there as if you did something wrong?
I don't know, okay?
Do you know what you look like right now?
You look like a newly-wed...
that ran away to her mum's place after her first fight.
- What? - You and Jun Woo settled things,
and you confessed to Sang Sik.
It should be easy from now. Why are you running away?
It wasn't me who ran away, it was him.
I feel so sorry for him.
Life is short.
Why is he torturing himself with the past?
Try solving the next question on your own.
It's autumn already.
We broke up, remember?
Ye Ji, I found a good reading room.
Do you want to go together today?
Don't text me during class.
Are you done?
- Yes. - Yes.
Guys,
it's not a matter of speed.
You need to answer the questions correctly.
Life isn't about...
getting there faster than anyone else.
What's important is knowing...
exactly which direction you're going.
Sir, I want to go to the wash room.
Sir, I want to go to the store.
I'm so hungry.
Whose parents' turn is it for the volunteer day teacher?
- Ye Ji. - Ye Ji.
Bring someone next week to teach.
Okay.
Isn't this place better than there?
Yes. They have good facilities,
but it hasn't been promoted enough.
I think it'll be a good location for the characters to date.
Yes.
Then let's confirm on this and try to get more tourists there.
Chief Ko.
(Good luck, Chief Ko!)
Do you feel sick?
No, it's nothing.
Then where should we choose...
for the shooting location?
Did something really happen?
Chief Ko!
Are you going to work like this?
Well?
What is your relationship to Producer Kang Min Joo?
Why did you make a mess there?
What do you mean?
Why did you show them the boat? It's still under construction.
You people broke it.
The policy was that we would actively support...
any applicants for the drama project.
Support?
We should have omitted such dangerous sites from the list.
Even if they were picked, it should've been nullified.
I gave you the boat for you to revive it.
Yes. However, for something...
you used a lot of people's taxes for,
it was poorly constructed by your favoured contractor.
There was a lot to be investigated.
What did you say?
Are you saying this was due to poor construction?
We gave the job to a proper contractor.
You can look forward to...
how we'll promote it.
If you use extra money and fail to save it,
the Woori City drama production will come to a halt.
You won't be able to save your neck, either.
Keep that in mind!
Producer Kang. Producer Kang.
Good morning.
What happened?
Why did you suddenly move out?
Well, it just happened.
Do you know how worried we were?
- Who? - Sang Sik, of course.
And all of us, too.
I'm thankful.
Don't be.
Where are you staying now?
Let's go.
- Congratulations, Producer Kang. - Thank you.
Hello.
Our team was given the city project.
I'm sorry.
You must not know about this industry.
Drama production can fall through mid-way,
and sometimes they don't air even when it's complete.
Okay, sure. I'll do my best.
I hope you watch it when it airs.
Did you even listen to me?
The girl should leave by this point.
- Leave? - Why?
How can they stay together feeling like that?
That would mean that she didn't like him that much.
I agree. They want to be together, so why should she leave?
How can they stay together at this point?
It's a little uncomfortable and awkward,
but it's all in the past.
What's there to be awkward about?
Shouldn't it bring them closer together?
The man doesn't dare to even look at the woman in the face.
She has to leave him.
I wouldn't leave if I was her.
They should fight it together.
That's real love, and that's what she should do for him.
How come no one understands me?
Is this how kids think these days? Am I getting too old?
Jun Woo.
Do you work here?
Yes.
I see.
I heard about Min Joo.
Yes.
It must have been tough.
No, I'm fine.
How are you?
My health is better,
and I'm working on my feelings.
That's good. I'm glad.
I'm working hard in modelling,
and I'm getting acting classes.
Really? That's great news.
Min Joo introduced me to it.
I've never been so interested in something other than you.
Good. Min Joo will be someone that's better to you than me.
Jun Woo, you're still someone special to me.
Thanks.
Okay, that's good.
Okay.
Our press conference is in two days.
How can the male lead drop out right now?
We need to persuade him. We have to shoot the poster now.
- There's no point. - Pardon?
He's having legal disputes with his previous agency.
On top of that, he's a rookie.
He's not confident about acting with Na Joo Yeon.
Hold on.
What time is it?
Why isn't he here yet?
What should we do then? We don't have time.
What about our lead from the previous drama?
Isn't he preparing to shoot a different drama?
The director there is a friend of mine.
He was surprised at how long I've worked with that jerk.
He was complaining over the phone saying he wants to fire him.
Really?
That's true. Only you can control him.
How can we bring him right now?
We need something to persuade him with.
There is something.
Ambassador for Woori City.
Ambassador for Woori City?
Since we're producing a drama,
we need a new face to represent Woori City.
Sure.
What do you think about Wook Sa Ma?
Wook Sa Ma? The guy from the grape festival?
Yes. Thanks to him, we avoided a catastrophe.
Yes. The farmers were thankful to him, as well.
He'll appear in our drama...
and become the city's ambassador, as well.
Is that possible?
Whose idea is this?
Of course, it's Producer Kang's.
You two look cute together.
You should take it up a notch.
I have a date to go to.
- Ta-da. - My goodness.
I'm here.
Why are you late?
I was here 10 minutes before we were supposed to meet.
What? Then where were you all this time?
I was all the way over there...
watching you.
Then...
My goodness. I can't believe this.
- Gosh. - What's wrong?
You looked so lovely.
Actually, the thing is,
I was curious to see what you would look like while waiting for me.
Forget it. I'm embarrassed.
Isn't it nice here? Windy Hill.
Just like those pin-wheels,
we may look glamorous on the outside.
However, we come and go...
just like the wind.
We don't have much time left,
so don't go home tonight.
What?
Stay with me tonight.
Gosh.
What are you saying?
My goodness.
People are looking at us. Stop it.
They must be jealous.
Gosh.
Especially for today,
the popular star, Wook Sa Ma, is here to give you a special lecture.
Let's listen to the life he's led as an actor.
Let's welcome him with a round of applause.
Well, I have everything one could ever want.
There's the air that I can breathe with,
and the passion I can...
dream with.
Most of all,
each day grows increasingly harder to predict.
Each day grows...
increasingly harder to predict.
Since it's hard to predict...
You don't know who you'll meet and where you will go, right?
Yes, bingo. Life is a gift,
so don't waste it.
You don't know what will happen in the future,
so you should be faithful to your life now.
Live and cherish each day.
"Cherish..."
"each moment."
"Titanic".
Correct. It's the famous quote from the movie, "Titanic".
Give him a round of applause.
Why is he here?
It's Wook Sa Ma!
You're always so fast.
- Are you interested? - I'll think about it.
There's no time. I need you to decide now.
You have a better public image now because of the grape festival.
You can be the city's ambassador.
All right, I'll think about it.
- Wook Sa Ma! - Wook Sa Ma!
- Wait! - Hey!
Why did he come here anyway?
Did he leave already?
Hold on.
Excuse me.
- "Titanic"? - Yes.
Here.
What is this?
You should watch it on the road. It'll be fun.
Also, if you enjoyed it,
please give me a call.
Okay.
Listen, Director Kim.
I never said I'd quit.
I only did that because you wouldn't listen to my suggestions.
I'm not a robot. Why should I only do as you say?
I have a mind and a heart, too.
Forget it.
How annoying.
The grape festival...
would have been ruined if it wasn't for you.
- What is this? - We sent our grapes abroad.
I was so proud.
Since you're a global star,
I thought you were someone we would never meet.
However, I was able to help pay...
for my granddaughter's tuition thanks to you.
I was too busy working to care about dramas.
I cried so much as I packed the grapes to send to China.
It was tears of happiness.
I was so happy.
Really? He agreed?
Okay. Thank you!
Producer Kang.
Wook Sa Ma agreed to appear in the drama.
He'll be in our drama.
Really? How did he make a decision so fast?
Chief Ko went to meet him in person to settle it.
What? Really?
He says he trusts your your talent and ability.
He called the city and said that he's confident in making it a hit.
Really? That's great.
Producer Kang.
You should thank Chief Ko, don't you think?
(Toz Study Centre)
- Is this a reading room? - Yes, isn't it nice?
This is where kids study at these days.
Really?
Welcome.
We did a test on Ye Ji to see what kind of learner she is.
She's a visual learner, it seems.
It will be most effective for her to study in a place...
that's visually calming.
Will you prepare a room for her then?
Sure.
Hello.
- Hyun Seok? Is that you? - Yes.
Ye Ji, did you sign up here?
I didn't come here because of you, so don't mind me.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Hyun Seok,
you guys should try and get along. I don't know what happened,
but you can make friends with anyone at your age.
She's more than just a friend to me.
Right.
Did you make up with Hyun Seok?
No.
What is it then?
I don't know. I can't seem to forgive him.
All I need is a sincere apology.
I thought you said you'd never see a boy again.
Are you sure you didn't go there because of him?
No way. I'm only going to study there.
What is this?
- Hey, hey. - Wow.
You guys look good together.
Did you two go on a date?
No, we didn't. Give it to me.
Gosh.
Are you guys dating?
I said, no.
They why did she suddenly move out?
Well...
Did you fight?
You had a fight.
You are dating her, after all.
You're so sneaky.
What? Sneaky?
What's the problem? It didn't work out with Jun Woo anyway.
You should just make up with her. Why did you make her move?
That's not gentleman-like at all.
What?
I guess love is more difficult for adults...
since it even made her move out.
- Let's eat. - It looks delicious.
I guess Sang Sik is skipping breakfast again.
I know why he's fasting.
What do you know?
It's because of the woman next door.
What are you talking about?
Are you okay with it, Jun Woo?
What is it? Does it make you uncomfortable that I know?
There's nothing to be uncomfortable about. You're just smart.
I don't mind at all.
They're adults. They should take care of it.
Take care of what?
Sang Sik, are you skipping breakfast again?
Yes, I'm not feeling very good. Go ahead.
You should just apologise.
If you like her, just apologise and bring her back.
What are you talking about?
Nothing. You and Hyun Seok, men are all the same.
As I became an adult, I told myself "Not yet".
"It's not time yet".
I ended up being more careful.
However, as we live in the moment,
saying "Not yet"...
might be a placeholder in place of our fear and cowardice.
As I became an adult, I kept on telling myself...
"I should have done that" and "I shouldn't have done that".
I continuously look back at the decisions I've made.
Although the decisions may look like they are wrong now,
I must remember that they were the best decisions at the time.
Hello?
Yes. I'm nearby.
What are you two doing here?
Well, you know...
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
I don't know what happened between you and Sang Sik,
but how can you just take off like that?
There's still a lot of time before the lease is over.
If you feel uncomfortable,
just spend a few days out and then come right back.
It's not a simple matter.
Please just sort it out for me.
Actually, I have a problem.
What is it?
What problem?
It's because of Hoon.
We're preparing for his study in China.
I had to hand in an income lease contract, so I did.
Did you?
What did Sang Sik do?
What did he do wrong?
I'll be... I mean, all of us will be good to you. Please?
They say you eat with your eyes.
That means plating is that important.
These North European colours and simplicity...
help make the food taste even better.
What?
I have to take that.
Did you finish posting the photos?
Yes, take a look. Do you like it?
Oh, my. You're good enough to be a professional photographer.
I have a good eye, you know.
You're one talented woman, Writer Ko.
Hey, but why does this one only have my face in it?
What?
Well, I just happened to take those photos.
Did my handsome face make you keep pressing the shutter?
I should teach Sang Sik how to use social media.
Do you actually think he'll do this?
Even posting photos on the city hall's website annoys him.
He may find it confusing, but he should keep practising.
That way, he'll be able to know how she's doing...
even if they're not together.
Who?
That's a good idea.
Then I...
Okay?
Okay.
- Producer Kang. - Yes?
Are you on any social media platforms?
No. I used to use it, but I don't any more.
Why not?
It feels like a hassle,
and I don't feel too comfortable about sharing my life so openly.
My site has been taken over by those pop-up advertisements.
When she was super popular as a director,
she used to get as many comments as celebrities usually get.
We could post updates about the Woori City drama to promote it.
I think it's a good idea.
No one really visits my blog.
Shall I reactivate your account for you?
I think it's a great idea.
- To promote the drama? - Yes.
Shall we do that?
Social media?
That's right.
I mean, the Woori City song made you a star.
It'll be great for promoting Woori City.
Maintaining those things is a lot of work.
You can post about touristic attractions...
as well as safety issues for the citizens.
It'll also be a great way to inform people...
about fire hazards, heat waves and earthquakes.
- That's actually a good idea. - I know, right?
Just open an account first.
You have to keep doing it to get used to it.
I'll open an account for you.
Sure. Do it.
Here we go.
So she can't terminate the lease for you?
She said she won't be able to do it for a little while.
Just meet up with him and try to talk it through.
I already tried talking to him and everything else I could think of.
People often say that they're breaking up...
for the other party in the relationship,
but I just don't buy that.
You're saying that you broke up with him for his sake,
but you could've left because he didn't stop you.
Think hard about it.
- Just a second. - Okay.
Yes.
I'm with a friend now.
My gosh. Was that today?
Gosh, I completely forgot about it.
Yes, all right.
What was it about?
It was my student whom I told you about the other day.
I said I'd go to the city's education fair with him today.
Today is the last day.
I'm fine, so just get going.
All right. I'll see you at home, then.
Oh, right.
- Feel free to go in without me. - Okay.
- I'm sorry. - No problem.
What did you think of it?
I found it very informative and helpful.
- Thanks. - Hey, where are you going?
- My gosh! - Let's go grab another drink.
Gosh, seriously!
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Who is this kid?
Just continue along.
You two look so lovely together.
What's the age difference between you two?
She looks at least 10 years older than him.
Isn't he her son?
What did you just say?
Let's just go.
Where do you think you're going?
You just littered the street.
Go home. You two are drunk.
Ma'am. Don't hang out with kids like him.
Guys like us are available, too.
Gosh. Sir, please...
What do you think you're doing right now?
- Goodness. - Look at this kid.
- I shall teach him a lesson. - Hey, let's just go.
- Come on. - Hey, let go.
- I'll let it slide this once. - Let's go.
Those jerks, seriously.
They must be around my age. I'm embarrassed for them.
- Are you okay? - Of course.
You didn't get injured, right?
Yes. I'm fine.
Well...
Gosh.
(Friends you may know: Ko Sang Sik)
(Ko Sang Sik)
Gosh, I can't believe he's on here.
All of these photos were posted recently.
You should at least thank Mr Ko, don't you think?
I just want to thank you for what you did for Wook Sa Ma.
I thought I should thank you as the chief producer of SBC.
I'll wait for you in front of Cheonglim Station...
after work this Wednesday.
Hey, I'm so sorry!
I said I'm fine.
You should've stayed out for longer.
Why would I do that?
I don't want to hang out with him all night.
If you like him, you can.
I said he's just my student.
Oh, right. You said you don't like younger guys.
But...
he actually looked so manly today.
- What? - When we were walking,
drunk guys came up to us and started hitting on me.
"Leave her alone, will you?"
"What do you think you're doing right now?"
Good for you!
That must be why people date.
Have you heard from him?
No.
Are you waiting to hear from him?
I wanted to thank him for helping me with work,
so I sent him a message saying we should meet up,
but I don't know what will come out of it.
Breaking up is also part of dating,
so it's not over yet.
So you're here with your friends to watch the live show with singers?
Yes. A little while ago,
I looked up all the dramas you made and watched them all.
- You did? - Watching your dramas...
makes me get chocked up right here with emotions.
Unlike those dramas you forget about after watching them,
they all left me with lingering emotions.
That's why I'm even more fond of you now,
even though I already liked you before.
You're so cool.
So what is it that you want to talk to me about?
I think you should keep seeing my dad.
- What? - I have seen you two...
arguing and bickering at each other often,
but it wouldn't be bad to stay friends for now.
- For now? - Best friends never break up,
whereas couples and married couples can break up.
You're so mature.
Well, I've experienced a breakup when Hyun Seok and I broke it off.
Aren't you hungry? Eat with me before you go.
No, it's okay. You must be busy.
My friends are waiting for me, so I should get going.
Really?
All right, then. Get going.
By the way,
is talent donation...
- What? - Nothing. Never mind.
- Have a good day. - You too.
(Min Ji Sun)
What's the great news you want to tell me?
I've been chosen...
as the supporting model for Woori City's ambassador programme.
Seriously? The one Wook Sa Ma is in?
Yes.
I'm so happy for you. Congratulations.
I owe it all to you.
No, it was an open audition.
I'm not that good at acting yet, but I'm a great model.
Your wish has come true.
You said Woori City is like your second home.
Are you two out on a date or what?
Jun Woo.
Did something exciting happen?
Ji Sun has been chosen as a model for the city's ambassador programme.
I'm not the main model.
Still, it's huge.
Seriously? That's awesome.
Congratulations.
Oh, right. I actually have a favour to ask you.
Me too.
I wanted to talk to you...
because one of the characters in the drama...
is an amazing chef like you.
I was wondering if I could ask you to help us with food preparation.
I see. I heard it from Mi Rae, as well.
So you're saying that you need a food stylist, right?
That's right.
Sure, it sounds good.
Thanks so much.
Don't mention it.
I have to help you because we're neighbours.
Because we're neighbours?
And that's the favour I wanted to ask you.
Get some rest now.
What do you mean?
Come back home and get the rest you deserve.
I must say,
I have such caring neighbours.
All of your family members keep telling me to come back.
Except for one person, that is.
Oh, him.
You're doing great.
One more time.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Awesome.
(Ko Sang Sik)
(I'll wait for you in front of Cheonglim Station...)
(after work this Wednesday.)
Woori City Ambassador is here!
Chief Ko, we also picked up the posters.
That's great.
Take a few photos and send them to me via email.
- Sure! - Actually, it's okay. Hang on.
Let's see.
- Song Yi, move over. - My goodness.
Now, I will...
Chief Ko. You're on social media?
- Yes. - Really?
- Show me. - No, stop it.
Let's follow each other.
I'll be sure to find your ID.
(I'll wait for you in front of Cheonglim Station.)
He read my message.
- Hey, Ye Ji. - Ms Kang.
I'm sorry, but I have an urgent favour to ask you.
What is it?
We've had many of your parents join us...
for our talent donation event and tell us about their jobs.
Ye Ji told me that she invited a very special guest today,
so I'm very much looking forward to it.
Please come in.
Hello.
- Hello! - Hello!
Hi, everyone. I currently work for SBC Broadcasting Station...
as a drama producer. My name is Kang Min Joo.
- You're beautiful! - You're so pretty!
The repairs have been completed.
We also fixed all the parts that were poorly constructed.
Good. Thanks for your great work.
I also looked further into it and found out more...
about the materials getting swapped as well as the rebate.
Head Chief Shin certainly got a lot of kickbacks through this.
Are you going to let it slide?
No.
We have to revive this cruse ship first...
to get our finances back on track.
So do you have any ideas?
Someone suggested hosting the drama's press conference here.
Yes. One of our team members brought up the idea.
It's not a bad idea.
After that, we should turn it into a maritime or bird museum.
Then we'll host the press conference here.
Let's do that.
(Woori Natural Ferry)
(Hye Dam's Mother: Forest Middle School Mothers' Get-together, 4pm)
I didn't know my classmates would love your presentation that much.
Thanks for accepting my last-minute request and coming all the way here.
It was my pleasure. I had so much fun.
I really had a great time today.
I got to reflect back on my career path, too.
When I get home, I'm going to tell my dad...
that you visited my school today.
No, don't do that.
I did it for you as your friend.
Then you two should make up and be good friends, okay?
All right. You should go in now.
Okay. Have a great day.
You too.
This car is awesome.
Of course. You picked it for me.
This feels so nice.
I haven't been out...
for a drive with a woman...
like this for a very long time.
Don't let your business eat up your life.
Go out and have fun like this once in a while.
You should let yourself feel the change of seasons.
I know.
I always work alone in my office, too.
Why?
You must meet many people since you work in international sales.
Sorry?
I let my employees take care of those things.
I just work out a little and sign papers.
Right, that school.
Ye Ji's father is here.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's very nice to meet you. - Please have a seat.
- Hye Dam is doing well, right? - Yes, of course.
You're such a great dad.
- Thanks for joining us today. - He's awesome.
I wish my husband could learn from you.
I'm flattered.
Ye Ji would've been a happier kid if she had her mum around.
Why? What did Ye Ji do?
Well, her grades are great,
but she's been hanging out with bad kids.
- Bad kids? - Well, we heard...
that she's been hanging out with a different group of friends.
She's been going to concerts and even skipped the English contest.
I see.
That's okay. Kids can do those things at that age.
It sounds like Hyun Seok got tired of her, as well.
I heard that he broke up with her.
Well, that was...
I heard that Hye Dam has been making it clear...
to Hyun Seok that she has a crush on him.
You mean my daughter, Hye Dam?
No way.
You should talk to her when you get home.
- I should. - Yes.
Ye Ji must be so happy.
It sounds like you two converse a lot.
- I'm jealous. - Me too.
(Cheonglim Station)
I'll wait for you in front of Cheonglim Station...
after work this Wednesday.
It's raining.
The weather forecast was right.
- Come this way. - I didn't bring an umbrella.
- Thank you. Oh, right. - Yes.
I heard...
that Ye Ji brought a very special guest to the talent donation event.
She did? Whom did she bring?
I heard she brought a producer. A woman.
Apparently, everyone loved her presentation so much.
Oh, is that right?
Thanks. You didn't have to do that.
Wasn't the jjambbong so delicious?
Yes. On a rainy day, eating...
- jjambbong is the best. - Jjambbong is the best.
- You should go. - Ms Koo.
Well... Gosh.
Do you know that you were my first love?
What?
I'm just saying. Go in.
Take this umbrella.
Come on.
- Bye. - Okay, bye.
Min Joo!
- Thanks. - I meant to give you the key,
but I forgot.
You should've just bought an umbrella.
I wasn't in the mood to do that.
Why? Did something happen?
I thought I'd see him today, but I was wrong.
I saw him walking with a woman, sharing an umbrella together.
Seriously? Mr Ko did that?
Yes.
I'm sure you were mistaken.
No. I saw it clearly with my own eyes.
She must be just someone he knows.
He was being so nice to her. He seemed to be having a great time,
and it looked like they were clicking.
You're...
jealous, aren't you?
That is complete nonsense.
Then what is it?
I just...
didn't think...
that he'd be completely fine after what we went through.
Did you expect him to walk around looking as if someone died?
That's not what I'm saying.
But this is wrong.
Just call him.
Why should I?
You're waiting for his call.
- No, I'm not. - Yes, you are.
I said I'm not!
Ye Ji.
Yes, Dad.
By any chance,
did you invite someone...
to the talent donation event?
How did you know?
I didn't have anything prepared until the day of,
so I called Ms Kang just in case, and she came right away.
Oh, really?
I promised her that I wouldn't tell you.
- What? - She said...
that she did it for me as a friend...
and that there's no need for you to know.
Is that what she said?
You should call her and thank her for me.
Sure. I will.
(Kang Min Joo)
(Ko Sang Sik)
The number cannot be reached. Please leave a message after...
I didn't look at anything else. He said that he was a lawyer,
so I married him thinking that my life will be taken care of.
I had no idea that he'd cheat on me and leave me that quickly.
Hearing your life story is making me realise...
that you've lived one tough life.
Everyone at our age...
has gone through at least one crisis, you know?
I wanted to become a teacher whom students look up to,
but I've decided to just let it all go...
and do whatever I want from now on.
Teacher?
Pardon? Oh, what I meant was...
I used to dream of becoming a teacher when I was young.
- Cheers. - No.
I shouldn't drink any more.
Why?
Let's talk a little more.
I'm tired.
Let's go to bed.
You... You want to go to bed?
Are we not going to sleep? I have to take a shower, too.
Right. If that's the case...
You should wash up first.
Okay.
Are you stepping out?
I was just trying to find a good spot for this.
You should wash up, too.
Yes, I should.
This jerk. His phone is off, and he didn't even come home.
Mum. Did Dad not come home last night?
You don't need to know. Just go to school.
I know which gym he goes to. Shall I tell you where it is?
Do you really know?
Ae Kyung Sports Centre.
No, he doesn't work out there.
No? I saw a towel from that place.
- A towel? - It was with his workout clothes.
I put it in the laundry basket.
I'll see you later!
Oh, okay. Have a good day.
My gosh!
This is...
You're Min Joo's friend, right?
Yes, I am.
Have you seen my husband here by any chance?
Your husband? What's his name?
His name is Park Cheon Soo.
There's no one with that name here.
What?
There's no one with that name?
What is your name?
Why are you asking my name?
What are you doing, Ae Kyung? Get in the car.
I clearly heard him saying Ae Kyung.
Ae Kyung.
Gosh, Ae Kyung?
Then Wingless Angel is...
Min Joo's friend?
Are you sleeping, Richard?
No, not yet.
You should just sleep if you're tired.
No, let's...
We should do it.
What are you going to do?
Sorry?
Never mind.
Just a second.
(House ghost)
It's "Wingless Angel".
Ae Kyung.
Just go.
Sorry?
I'm tired, so I'm just going to sleep.
All right. I'll get going, then.
Good night. Have a good sleep.
Gosh, you fool!
You're a complete fool who can't even do anything!
Go in, or you'll be late for class.
It sounds like he's so inexperienced.
I like how naive he is.
Whatever.
I don't need that at this age. It's not exactly first love.
Apparently, I'm someone's first love.
- Who said that? - Oh, you know.
My old student I met when I went on that blind date.
Did he tell you that you were his first love?
All kids do that, you know?
They all have a crush on their teachers.
I see that both of you are dating now.
- Dating? - Gosh, no.
Don't deny it. I can tell that you two are over the moon now.
- We are? - We are?
You copycat.
What about you? What are you going to do now?
What do you mean? I moved out, so it's over.
Frankly, he's not exactly a good catch.
He's a widower with a daughter.
He also has a huge family.
She's right. Are you two friends or lovers?
You two work together,
but you're neither business partners nor colleagues in the same office.
He's just a person that helps me with for my drama, okay?
Goodness.
I'm home.
Honey, I'm home.
Gosh, you lazy bear.
What? A lazy bear?
Hey! Park Cheon Soo!
Where did you sleep last night?
Where did you sleep?
At the spa. So what?
At the spa?
Which spa? Which spa?
Get off.
Now, will you talk to me?
You'll talk only after I stay out all night?
Let's just not talk ever again.
That's...
Where are you going?
Feed me!
Darn it.
My gosh.
What brings you by again?
I came to work out.
You did?
- Yes. - Why suddenly?
To prevent ageing. No, actually,
I want to get stronger.
- Stronger? - Yes.
I want the bravery and strength to not lose,
no matter with whom I fight.
I see.
Good for you. Come with me.
(Ko Sang Sik)
(Kang Min Joo)
I'll wait for you in front of Cheonglim Station...
after work this Wednesday.
Wednesday?
It's Thursday today.
Hold on.
(Kang Min Joo)
Let's just go.
- Let's get drinks. - I'm in.
No one goes home early.
- Okay? Let's go. - Okay.
Come on.
You don't have to do that. Go inside and do your work.
What's wrong with you? We always did this together.
- I said to get out. - Get in here.
You were too busy when you were dating. Why are you helping now?
What?
I even cleaned all your caf's windows...
although I couldn't reach.
- Did you, now? - Why you...
I told you to wait so we can clean them together.
Hey.
Hey, Mi Rae. You...
What?
You beanpole.
What did you do while I was growing?
You eat two bowls of rice, too.
Stomp harder. Stomp.
Stop it.
- Are you okay? - No, I'm not.
Is this everything for the sites?
Do you not like them?
They're all okay,
but I need at least one special spot.
Then...
how about here?
(Woori City Suspension Bridge)
I'm not sure.
I need to go see for myself.
Now? Alone?
Everyone's busy preparing for the presentation.
See you.
Be careful.
Here are the documents.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Here. - Thank you.
Hello? This is Local Tourist Department.
Pardon?
Someone fell...
on the mountain?
Is the person badly hurt?
Thank goodness.
Would you please give me the name and number?
Yes.
Okay.
- What is it? - A tourist...
slipped on Gamak Mountain.
The ambulance is on its way,
but they questioned if something was wrong with the path.
Mr Ko.
Excuse me. What happened?
You'll need to block that off.
He was picking up acorns in there.
I see.
- Did anyone else get hurt? - No, everyone's fine.
You can't go in there.
It's illegal to pick up fallen acorns.
Illegal?
You're so inconsiderate.
You may think acorns are insignificant,
but it is food for squirrels, raccoons and other animals.
If you take all of them, they'll starve in the winter.
If you pick up acorns that have fallen,
you need to pay a fine. Do you understand?
- Sorry. - You can't do that again.
We won't.
If you're destined to meet, you're bound to meet.
No matter how hard you try to avoid them...
Even if you go around the earth 10 times.
If you're destined to meet, you're bound to meet.
No matter how hard you try to avoid them...
Even if you go around the earth 10 times.
(Second to Last Love)
You want to give your presentation on the cruise?
Something will go wrong.
We're with the inspection department.
Richard Park. I've got you now.
Go somewhere with me.
Are you heading home?
Where's Mr Ko?
He just went out to look for you.
Sang Sik!
Come back.
What must I give up?