bioskopkeren
Exactly. So let's talk about it inside!
- Let go! - What?
Do you feel guilty?
What's going on?
- Min Joo. - Ae Kyung.
Ae Kyung.
Richard?
Now, you show your true colours!
What? Richard?
- He's my husband! - Stop it!
What are you doing?
- Are you okay? - I...
Hey! Park Cheon Soo! Get over here.
Let go! Let go!
- Let go! - How could you?
- You little... - Stop!
- Let go! How could you do this? - Stop it.
Let go! Let go!
How could you do this to me?
Are you insane? What's wrong with you?
Who's calling whom insane? The two of you are insane.
How dare you have an affair!
An affair?
My goodness.
I'm going to lose my mind.
(Second to Last Love)
I can't believe this.
Are the two of you really married?
Explain yourself.
- That's not it. - Say it!
I'm sorry.
But please hear me out.
What for?
You've been staying out all night all the time after working out.
How...
How many times...
This is a misunderstanding. It's a misunderstanding.
Yes, it's a misunderstanding.
We only met a few times to talk.
All we did was talk. Nothing more.
That's right.
And I had no idea he was your husband.
I wouldn't have met a married man, had I known. I'm not crazy.
Say something!
You pretended to be single?
I'm worried.
How could this happen right after moving her stuff back in?
How could Cheon Soo meet Ms Kang's friend, of all people?
Come on.
I'm sure they were just acquaintances.
I'm sure there was a misunderstanding.
That's right. What was it that you wanted to tell me?
What did you leave in the comic book?
Did you read the comic book?
A little.
Did you feel anything?
What?
Did you feel anything flutter here...
or ache or something?
Don't make me laugh.
It's not like you drew it, so why?
It's because it's similar to us.
Like us? The comic book?
Forget it. Don't read it if you didn't yet.
Don't ever read it. Don't you dare, okay?
He's so annoying.
You still see me as a kid, don't you?
Oh, no.
I really didn't know.
I never saw him here, so how would I have known?
I'm speechless.
How could he act single?
You said...
you went to a hotel.
You talked about...
how he was too naive and you didn't want to be his first love.
That's right.
I'm shocked, too.
But we didn't do it. I sent him home that night.
Good going. Good for you.
How could a teacher...
A teacher?
He's a teacher?
You should've done your research!
How humiliating.
Please believe me.
It's not the type of relationship that you're thinking.
Then why did you see her?
Why did you pretend to be single and lie about your job to meet her?
A companion.
Because I didn't have a life companion.
A companion?
Are you out of your mind? What about my sister, Sang Hee?
Well,
people say spouses are your life companion,
but it isn't always true.
What?
People like you would never understand,
but the truth is,
many married couples out there...
aren't each other's companions.
It's not even like they are couples with problems.
There are so many couples...
who hide things from each other and are just a façade.
So?
Are you saying you and Sang Hee are nothing but a façade?
No.
That's not it.
A life companion...
should be someone you can discuss your life with.
If that's your spouse, that's awesome.
But it doesn't always have to be your spouse.
It can be someone else. That's what I'm saying.
It can be a friend of the opposite sex...
or a friend of the same sex.
Like a soul mate.
Devote yourself to your family.
Whether it be soul mate or companion,
you should create it within your family.
Then are Ye Ji, Mi Rae...
and my wife your life companions?
They have their own lives. What about you?
We're talking about you. Why are you dragging me into this?
A life companion walking on the same path...
and with whom you can talk about life.
I did it because I didn't have anyone like that.
It's been a while...
since I couldn't talk to Sang Hee.
Are you saying you were right?
No, I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
My friend really didn't know and make a huge mistake.
I'm terribly sorry.
I... I'm sorry.
I'm flabbergasted, too.
Goodness.
You're older than I am.
You took very good care of yourself.
Well...
I don't know how much I should believe about your relationship.
Anyway, about grabbing your friend's hair...
If you're ever in my shoes, you'll understand.
Of course. I understand already.
Whether or not my friend knew, she was definitely wrong.
It's her fault for not knowing.
- I'll talk to her. - Min Joo.
They'll never see each other again.
I...
My goodness. Go home.
Kang Min Joo.
- What? - I'm happy...
that you moved back in too, but you can't do this to me.
- What? - I know Sang Sik is important,
but your friend just got fooled by his brother-in-law.
How do you not care at all about me?
Wow.
Did I kill someone or what?
That's not it.
I'm the one...
who should get an apology from that family.
And you shouldn't get angry at me, but at that family.
A friend was victimised like this,
but you get mad at me and make my apologise?
- No... - Forget it!
Women don't care at all about friendship.
Their man is all they care about.
Ae Kyung!
You don't talk to me at all.
What did you like so much about her?
She's a wingless angel?
And I'm a house ghost?
Hey, Park Cheon Soo! Live with a human being.
Why do you live with a ghost and sleep with an angel?
Who slept with whom?
You treat me like a piece of furniture.
Conversation? You turn your back to me every time I start talking.
You bled me dry.
How good were you to that woman?
I want to talk to a human being.
I want to talk to a human being, too.
Do I speak in a foreign language?
I want someone I can communicate with...
and relate to...
Me too.
I'm a human being, too.
How did I live all these years trying to support you?
I couldn't stand it when you sold drugs...
on behalf of the principal's wife.
It hurts my reputation at school, and it's humiliating.
And the summers, too.
Just so you can make a few bucks,
you rent out our house...
and make our family live in tents in your brother's yard.
It's sickening!
Do you think I want to live like this?
The more you do things like that to save money,
the worse you make me feel!
We should live...
according to what we have.
Don't even think about...
sending Hoon to study abroad.
Sang Hee.
Are you okay?
Mi Rae.
I thought giving up my dreams...
and supporting my family what the right thing to do.
What is this?
How did it end up like this?
Don't cry.
Did your friend really not know?
Would she have done that if she knew?
She may have gotten married and divorced at a young age,
but she knows what's right and wrong.
What's wrong with your brother-in-law?
He isn't the type to do something like this.
Regardless, he lied to her about his job and his marriage.
My friend was the victim.
After all we went through to get back together,
must we argue about something like this?
I know.
How's your friend doing?
She was angry and disappointed in me.
In you?
She said I didn't understand how she felt when I'm her friend.
I must have talked like I was a part of your family.
Goodness.
Why did he do it...
when he has such a nice wife?
There must be a void that Sang Hee can't fill.
Still, they're married.
That's not right.
She may be my sister,
but I'm sure there was a problem with Sang Hee, too.
The man cheated.
Why do you think something was wrong with the woman?
He's the one at fault. He made a fool out of two women.
Of course, he was wrong...
since he lied about who he was.
But it wouldn't have come to this if Sang Hee had been better.
You'll never find someone more devoted to her family.
She gave up her dreams...
and devoted herself to her family.
I didn't think so before,
but maybe you're a bit of a macho man.
A macho man?
They say affairs late in life are scarier.
Are you afraid that I'd cheat?
Who knows? All men are the same.
My gosh.
How's the house?
I arranged it the best I could,
but if you don't like it, we can redo it.
No, I really like it.
You did such a good job.
It was like a surprise event.
This was the only thing I could do for you at this time.
Thank you...
for showing me how you felt first.
Please talk to your friend about my sister.
Tell her that she'll apologise in person later.
Married life doesn't seem that easy, either.
But if two people like each other,
it's better to get married and live together than to live alone.
I'll get going.
Anyway, don't think about going anywhere again,
and stay here, okay?
Okay.
He didn't just propose, did he?
Where should I put this?
Put it there.
Are you that happy?
About what?
You look extremely happy right now.
You're like...
a newly-wed decorating his house.
You punk.
You look good.
Don't lose her again, okay?
Okay. Thanks.
We're almost done. We should clean up now.
Okay.
Cheon Soo really messed up big this time.
How is Sang Hee doing?
She's a total wreck.
What were you doing?
Nothing.
(Houses for sale)
What are you doing?
I was just looking at some places. What?
Are you really moving out?
I'm just looking around.
How's Sang Sik?
He's energetic as always.
He blocked that hail storm...
with his body on that cruise, remember?
Exactly. Blame it on the cruise ship,
and make sure the production fee stays the same.
Yes, it's been set up already.
Of course.
The ship was damaged by the hail storm.
You had it renovated immediately before the drama was announced.
It was constructed poorly,
so it had many flaws even before the renovations.
We looked over the documents you submitted.
Mr Shin blamed the contractor.
If they had met the standards required,
the windows would not have broken or cracked from the hail.
Mr Shin isn't an expert,
so it is difficult to judge whether cheap glass...
or strong glass were used.
Then I guess...
you mean you need further proof or witnesses.
That's right.
But you undertook the renovations recently,
and the ship was damaged due to the hail.
We can't help but hold you accountable.
- What? - And the fact that you rushed...
renovations before the drama announcement...
makes us question your relationship with SBC's Kang Min Joo, as well.
The announcement event...
was intended to raise awareness of the cruise ship...
that was being wasted.
What is your relationship with Ms Kang Min Joo?
Is there something special?
Something special?
What do you mean?
I'm asking if your relationship is strictly professional,
or if it involves personal emotions.
Answer the question.
Yes.
She's the woman I love.
Hey.
How are preparations going?
Of course. Don't worry. It's all going well.
Woori City's drama production fee won't change.
Really?
I worked hard to get that.
So don't worry and proceed.
Thank you. What's gotten into you?
Let's have some soju tonight.
Why?
You agreed to have soju with me if I made sure the fee didn't change.
I'm super busy. You know that.
Why? Because of Sang Sik?
He should be busy lately, being audited and all.
Did you know that?
Is it because of that article?
Yes, it's because of you.
No way.
You announced the drama on the ship.
So what?
He's about to go on under because of that.
I heard it looks like he'll tell the world that you two are dating.
You should end it soon for his sake.
Why did you do it?
Why? It's obvious.
There's already a scandal about us conducting internal transactions.
Sang Sik.
- Yes? - Thank you...
for setting the judgement straight for the drama evaluation.
I didn't do it to be thanked.
If you leave things like this,
it'll be only natural that people think you let us use the ship...
for the announcement and the shoots because of your feelings for me.
Then how could I prove it isn't true?
You should've said our relationship was purely professional.
Why must I lie?
Goodness.
You're so stiff.
We're next door neighbours.
They can find that out just by running our addresses.
They can frame me easily if they wanted to.
Or...
you can give up on developing the cruise ship.
If we sell the ship now,
the corruption behind it will all be buried.
That's what Mr Shin wants and why he wants to sell it.
Our city must protect it.
They should be investigating Mr Shin, not someone like...
It's nice having someone on my side.
Then all I can do to help...
is to take less for the production fee.
Why would you do that?
Everyone worked hard for that.
Then what?
There are no answers in life.
I don't like the fact that someone like you is even suspected.
- Why? - Why? You're not like them.
It's also not the truth.
Are those the only reasons?
Because I like you.
Happy?
Then what happens to Chief Ko?
He'll take the blame all by himself.
Our team may be gone overnight, too.
What should we do?
Song Yi, why aren't you eating?
Is something wrong?
- Yes. - What is it?
It's because of Chief Ko's scandal.
But it's true that they're dating.
- With Ms Kang Min Joo? - Yes.
I shouldn't have gone to the movies with Chief Ko.
You watched a movie with him?
What was the point?
He ended it all right then.
I shouldn't have pleaded him to go.
I should've...
fought my feelings and resisted.
What is that?
We're living apart for now.
What?
What about Hoon?
He wants to stay at home with his dad.
- Traitor. - Obviously, his home is better.
Go back home.
Hey, Sang Hee!
Jun Woo, stop it.
I told you that's not it.
What is it this time?
This punk says he's moving out.
- Hey. - What?
He's looking for a new place to live.
- Why? - Why else? It's because of you.
In case you'd be uncomfortable. So that you'd be happy.
He's impossible.
No, that's not it.
Yes, it is!
Is something wrong?
Hello.
Hey. Be quiet.
Got it?
What's wrong?
It's nothing, so don't worry about it.
Are you sure it's nothing?
Yes, I am.
Why are you home so late?
- Did you have dinner? - Yes, I did.
That's good.
I need to talk to Jun Woo.
- Okay. Go in. - Okay, then.
What's going on?
That jerk. Selfish jerk.
He doesn't think about me at all.
Are you really going to do this?
That's not it. I'm really okay, but...
But?
What's the problem?
What did you say to me right here when you came from Canada?
When your appendix burst,
what did you say to me at the hospital?
The day I buried my wife,
what did you say to me in the car?
I know.
Fine.
Did you or did you not say that we are family and will never part?
Why don't you realise I'd be more uncomfortable if you leave?
Look,
I know I should leave for your sake, but...
That is not true.
Fine. Okay.
I wasn't thinking straight.
I looked around a little,
but I just couldn't give up this family.
So even if I make you uncomfortable, bear with me.
I'll keep wishing you happiness.
Okay.
You should've said that from the start.
Gosh, seriously. I just can't win.
I'm so sick of you all.
Let's drink.
Oh, wait.
What is it?
Are you all right?
Yes.
But seeing your face...
is reminding me of it and making my blood boil again.
I'm sorry.
If you're free, you should join me for breakfast.
No. I have to go eat breakfast with my son, Hoon.
Okay.
See you!
Hey, Tae Yeon.
Ae Kyung told you, right?
What? Today?
You girls are meeting him today?
Thank you.
I sincerely apologise for what my sister did to you.
So you're basically saying that I should never see him again...
and that I should stay far away from him, right?
I can't make such a request because you two are friends.
I'm just asking you not to visit for the next little while.
You're still treating me as if I'm guilty of adultery.
No, not at all. Cheon Soo is the one at fault, not you.
Exactly. You had no idea.
Okay.
Then let me say a few things as Min Joo's friend.
She's been completely fine alone so far.
I'm worried that people might think badly of her because of me.
I hope the incident doesn't affect your relationship. Be good to her.
I will, of course. Thank you.
And I'd like to thank you for telling me where her stuff was.
Oh, that.
Please make sure Min Joo doesn't run away again.
You must love her with all of your heart, okay?
Okay.
You probably don't know because you've never been married.
I guess my wife and I are going through ennui.
To be honest with you, I very much enjoy...
spending time with Ae Kyung.
Even if that is the case,
your wife can't stand it...
because it bothers her a lot,
so you shouldn't spend time with her.
You make dramas.
Can't you empathise with what everyone goes through?
That's usually the case,
but this is reality. Besides,
it involves my close friend.
You're probably more worried about this affecting...
your relationship with Sang Sik.
Right. That I can't deny.
Plus, I've become friends with Sang Hee, as well.
I know. But you know what?
I'm genuinely fond of her.
Ae Kyung and I have great conversations.
We're friends, and I feel comfortable around her.
Right, I get it.
However,
faithfulness is an important part of love.
Faithfulness?
Love that is all faithfulness and no love would be dreary, though.
Being faithful...
requires a lot of love.
Exactly.
So you know.
All right.
I'll try.
Is there a different spot you can think of?
The vehicle will have to spin as soon as it gets hit,
so we need a wider space.
This should be good enough, no?
Does the scene have to look that spectacular?
Are you kidding me right now?
This drama is for Woori City.
Oh, Producer Kang.
The shoot hasn't begun yet?
No. We're doing a run-through right now,
but I don't like anything I see.
- Hello. - Hello. Thank you for your help.
Producer Nam and I decided on the location together.
He wasn't happy with the original location,
so we came here, and he's complaining again.
- You made it. - Yes.
Gosh, this is seriously so ridiculous.
Producer Kang, could you direct the shoot instead of him?
When will the shoot start?
You should've told us to arrive after you're ready.
We've been waiting since very early in the morning.
It's because this is the very first shoot.
You two need to get comfortable with each other, so...
Producer Nam, spare me a second.
What did I say? We should've just started shooting.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologise to me. Just do a good job.
If you're that unhappy with the location, I'll find something else.
- Really? - That's what you need help with.
Also, don't push yourself to do too well.
How can I not? This isn't any drama.
We got the project after intense competition.
All eyes must be on us at the moment.
Besides, this is the first drama I'm directing.
Right, so you've got to relax. Don't feel pressured to do too well.
Okay. When I get stressed out,
I'll reach out to you for help.
I hope that doesn't happen.
And...
- just cancel today's shoot. - Sorry?
If you push ahead with it in this situation,
it won't turn out well.
Ki Cheol, you're the captain and the person in charge here.
In a few years,
no one will even give you any advice like I'm doing now.
You'll have to make your own decisions as you go along.
Pull yourself together...
and resume the shoot when you're actually ready.
Okay, I will.
Thank you, Producer Kang.
This isn't easy.
What? They want new locations for all scenes?
That guy is honestly a handful.
Who?
Producer Nam Ki Cheol who is directing the drama.
The shoot got delayed, so Producer Kang had to come.
Really?
I went through hoops with him to pick the locations on this list.
If they want to change it all up, the schedule will change, as well.
All right. I'll go through this.
Okay.
Goodness.
What's this?
Open it.
Why are you taking that?
The festival is going on now,
so please visit often and help us promote it.
- Sure. - Okay.
Hi. We're wondering if we go inside, what is there to see?
Oh, yes.
So this guy is a Korean philosopher...
named Yi I, also known as Yulgok.
So he is a Korean equivalent to Socrates and Confucius.
In here, we're celebrating his life and achievement.
- Thank you. We'll have a look. - Perfect. Thank you.
Ji Sun.
Hey, Jun.
You're doing a good job, right?
Of course. Did you bring the thing I asked you about?
Yes.
Here.
So these are healthy recipes you came up with.
I wrote down every single recipe by hand, so make sure to use them.
I will, of course.
This will help me be on a strict diet.
I'm only giving it to you because you represent Woori City.
I'm done here now. Do you want to grab a bite with me?
- Let's go. - Okay!
I'm here, Writer Ko!
- Hello. - Hello.
Here. Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Are the shoots going well?
Actually, it's...
Why? Is there a problem with the script?
No, not at all.
I think I'm having a difficult time because of my greed.
I cancelled the shoot and just came to see you.
Why did you want to see me?
I was reading the script,
and one of the lines you wrote really spoke to me.
Which one?
"In life, you ultimately have to trust yourself."
"If you can't trust yourself, you'll end up getting lost."
- Something like that. - Oh, that part.
I suddenly started missing you.
Well... Would you like to eat something?
Oh, shall we?
Mi Rae.
Jun Woo.
Are you two out on a date?
Yes, I guess you can say that.
We're not on a date. We met up because of work.
It's true that I came to see you because of work stress,
but I'm not here because of work.
You two look so lovely together.
You two look more lovely together.
You're both tall, and you have great chemistry together.
She's just a friend of mine.
That was delicious.
- What did you think of the food? - It was good.
I'll get going now. You should go in.
If I didn't have the event tomorrow, I'd love to have drinks with you.
Really?
That's too bad.
Jun.
Thanks for this. It'll be put to good use.
No problem.
Mi Rae, see you around.
Yes, see you.
Bye.
Have a good time. I'll get going now.
No, wait.
Call me if you have any questions about the script.
Okay.
By the way, do the two of you really live in the same house?
- Yes. - Yes.
I'll trust you, all right?
I'll get going.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Let's go. - Okay.
It looked like he had something to say to you. You should've stayed.
Why didn't you spend more time with Ji Sun?
What was that by the way?
It looked like a jotter.
It's my recipe note.
It has healthy recipes.
Why did you give it to her? Because she now models for the city?
I just felt bad.
Hey, you're giving her hope.
Why don't you date that guy? Producer Nam or whoever he is.
Stop it.
Why? Are you feeling shy about it?
Being attracted to someone isn't something to be ashamed of.
But...
what would you do if you confess your feelings to someone...
and end up ruining your relationship with that person?
I'm not sure.
Do you want to go to that comic book cafe we used to go to a lot?
- Comic book cafe? - Yes.
Doesn't it feel so good to be back here?
Yes. It feels strange in a very good way.
Coming here always sends me on a trip down the memory lane.
I know.
We read so many comic books here.
Yes. On the days that I ended up crying while reading comic books,
you came and read with me until sundown.
That's right.
By the way, why did you want to come here out of the blue?
No specific reason. I just miss the old days.
That means you're getting old.
I'm an adult now too, you know.
I need the first volume.
The fourth volume. I need it.
Why are you so slow?
Look at this. It's a dog. A puppy.
Look at this one.
This is you.
You're handsome.
What are you doing now?
Mosquito! I have to catch this mosquito!
This mosquito.
- I've got to catch this bugger. - Gosh, seriously.
My gosh. And?
I told her that she was being too heartless.
I get that Mr Ko moved all of her stuff for her,
but how can she take his family's side?
Getting back together wasn't easy for them, so try to understand her.
Hi!
What's this silence? Were you guys talking about me?
Yes.
"Love or friendship?" Something along the lines of that.
I'm sorry.
I should've asked you how you got to know Cheon Soo.
I should've listened to you and tried to understand you first.
Are you realising that just now?
This divorcee here has been acting as if she's a pro in this business,
but she was clueless.
- What about you? - What?
You got back together with him. Shouldn't there be some progress?
What are you talking about now?
You can start sharing the kitchen...
or...
knock down the wall between the two houses.
Or just get married.
Stop it, guys.
You've never thought about it?
Well, I'm content with how things are now.
I'm jealous. You're living the kind of life I've been dreaming of.
How will you face his family if they end up getting married?
Because of Richard?
It's not like he lives in that house.
His wife moved out because of you.
She's staying at Sang Sik's place now.
Seriously?
Then Richard must be alone at his place.
Why? Are you going to call him?
No.
Goodness.
Welcome to Death Experience.
This experience will allow you to understand the value of life...
Gosh, seriously.
Sang Sik, don't you think this is too much?
Those who think their lives are filled with problems.
The 10 minutes you spend in the coffin...
will give you a chance to reflect on your life and wrongdoings.
What is this by the way?
- It's your will. - Pardon me?
Sang Sik, please.
Just write it.
Gosh, it's not like I'm going to die soon.
Please lie down in the coffin now.
This is crazy.
Sang Sik.
Go in.
What are we doing now, seriously?
Just go in and lie down.
Gosh, this is insane.
This is just ridiculous.
Why do I have to do this?
How do you feel?
I'm sorry, Sang Sik.
You don't need to apologise to me.
From now on,
I'll be devoted to Sang Hee,
and I promise that I'll be good to her.
You said you can't communicate with her, though.
I should try harder.
I'll try to initiate conversations...
and repeat myself if she doesn't understand me.
If she goes off topic, I'll explain it to her.
We will close the lid now.
Sorry? The lid?
Why in the world are you closing the lid?
Sang Sik.
You're way too chatty for someone who is about to die.
Let's die peacefully.
Sang Sik!
- Please stay still. - Wait. Wait, please. Sang Sik.
No, this is wrong. Sang Sik!
Sang Sik!
I'm so done with making sacrifices.
I've been trying so hard to save and never spent a penny on me.
And what? You can't stand how stingy I am?
I'd like to get all of these.
Sure.
How did your afterlife treat you?
My life feels so futile.
All sorts of thoughts crossed my mind.
I really should not live like this any more.
Exactly.
Doesn't it feel like you've wasted your entire life?
Sang Sik...
What are you doing? Get up.
No. I'm just going to stay here.
What?
I'll stay in this coffin.
You can just go ahead and bury me.
Gosh, you're such a handful.
Hey, get up. Come on.
Just leave me alone.
Gosh, that's enough. Just get up already. Come on.
Goodness.
What did you write in your will?
I wrote that...
although I'm not a husband with great competence,
I'm grateful that...
she trusted and stayed with me until now.
What about you?
Me?
I wrote that I hope my family will stay healthy like now.
How's that your will?
It's just your hope.
Let's go.
Okay.
By the way, when's the Top 10 Chef party?
It's this weekend. Why?
I was just curious.
There must be many beautiful female chefs there, too.
There are a few.
Really?
Why don't you come with me?
No, why would I go there?
Don't worry because it's not a party for couples.
It's just a party where friends are invited.
Really?
Then shall I come, too?
If you want.
Ji Sun isn't coming, is she?
Why would she come?
She's your friend.
You're the closest friend to me.
I'm glad to hear that.
What?
It's nothing.
Gosh, these are heavy.
- These are heavy. - My goodness.
Give them to me.
Do you want to return all of these?
If it's too much,
I'll exchange them.
Okay.
Sang Hee.
Why are you so startled?
It's nothing.
Whose clothes are those?
Oh, I came to buy some clothes for Hoon.
I noticed all these clothes are on sale.
What brings you here?
I'm here to get groceries.
I see.
Do you want exchange this scarf, too?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Okay.
You didn't make up yet, but did you...
exchange everything to your husband's clothes?
Well,
I also got Hoon's clothes.
It's the same for everyone who's married.
It's a waste to spend money on my own clothes.
It's not like I earn money.
Many housewives are great at taking care of their family,
but I'm not like that, either.
That's nonsense. You've been a good wife so far.
You don't know anything.
I know by tasting Sang Sik's aged kimchi and bean paste.
How did you know? I made all of them.
That's what I mean.
Also,
my friend told me honestly.
There was nothing between her and your husband.
She thinks that it was a temporary...
escape for your husband.
Escape?
I wish I could also escape for a little while.
Since she's never had a family before,
she must think adultery isn't a big deal.
My friend was once married...
and went through a divorce.
Then she knows enough about life.
She really had no idea.
Please believe her.
That's why I hate my husband even more.
Goodness.
What? I didn't buy this.
Where's the receipt?
It's not on the receipt.
When you shop clothes for your family,
you can also get...
a scarf for yourself as a way to love yourself.
Thank you for saying that.
What are you doing?
What? Nothing.
What are all these?
Gosh.
These are all for Cheon Soo.
Well, I...
Why did you move out then?
Move back in.
Sang Sik.
- This. - What is it?
I picked it out at the shop, but I didn't buy it to save money.
Then our neighbour bought it secretly...
and put it in my bag, for which I'm grateful.
Really?
It's nothing big, but I feel so good.
It'd be great if my husband was like her.
Why did you buy him all these then?
He doesn't deserve it.
How can I help myself?
Give them to me. I'll throw them away.
No way.
Do you know how much they cost?
If you forgive him, move back in and talk it over.
Don't buy things like these ever again.
Goodness.
- It's delicious. - Isn't it?
It's great to be out like this.
There's nothing particularly special about youth.
Until your 40s,
you only get a taste of life.
Once you're over 50, you enjoy the real taste of life.
But weren't these couple shirts too much?
What?
We're on our way to get our couple rings.
- Really? - Yes.
You said you're having a hard time at City Hall...
with many audits these days.
I know.
People like Chief Ko shouldn't be put in a disadvantageous situation.
But even in my position,
I still face my difficulties.
Quit your job right away.
Then you should go travel with me.
Don't tempt me.
I still have dreams and aspirations.
Is it work or me?
Choose just one.
It's me, myself.
What did you say?
Goodness, aren't you Ms Na?
- Gosh. - Hello.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
Hello.
What on earth?
How could you thrust my hand away?
- I have a reputation to keep. - Forget about our couple rings.
Come on, Ko Bong.
Let's go.
Choose anything you like.
Goodness.
Don't you have to reschedule all the film shooting?
Yes.
Gosh, it's ramyeon.
I was about to make some.
It's special seafood ramyeon. Turn off the gas. It'll get soggy.
You said you wanted ramyeon since you ate oily food during the day.
Go ahead and eat.
What if your family sees us?
Who cares? Go ahead.
This is great.
Ms Kang, it's Ye Ji.
Goodness.
Wait a minute.
I have something to tell you.
Okay, have a seat.
Were you eating?
Do you want some?
No, I'm on a diet.
I made some to eat, but I don't want it any more.
What do you want to talk about?
I was thinking about asking Dad,
but I came here since I feel more at ease with you.
It's this.
Oh, this.
I don't believe what the article says. I trust Dad.
Of course you should.
I'm more curious about your relationship with Dad.
Well, I...
I'm happy that you moved back,
but I don't want to put a burden on you.
- A burden? - I don't mind...
living with my aunts.
In case you and Dad want to live together,
but are hesitating because of me,
I wanted to tell you beforehand that it's okay.
Why did you think that suddenly?
You moved everything out and then came back.
That means you and Dad became closer.
It's true, but you don't have to worry about that.
We can just be neighbours.
Really?
My gosh.
That must mean you haven't gone very far.
Gosh, I can't believe Dad.
What?
Anyway, you understand what I mean, right?
Yes, thank you for your thoughts.
Sure.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
- Sleep well. - Thank you.
I don't feel so good.
Ye Ji is very sweet.
What should we do about the ramyeon? It's probably soggy.
I'll make some more.
I'll look forward to it.
You haven't gone on a date?
No.
Plus, I also missed you.
What?
Do you want to go eat something else?
- Why? - You know the dentist...
I mentioned whom I had a blind date with?
- Yes. - Every time we met,
we had food like steaks and pasta,
so I feel like I have an upset stomach.
What do you want to eat then?
I want some spicy kimchi stew made...
with a lot of pork.
Why do you eat expensive steaks with her...
while you eat cheap food like stew with me?
It somehow turned out that way.
You don't like the idea?
Let's go.
I know a place that makes good kimchi stew.
You're so sensible.
I'll treat you today.
All right.
You can leave it.
We'll finish it faster if we do it together.
How was the ramyeon?
It was delicious but...
Was it too salty?
I don't think it's good as my seafood ramyeon.
Give it to me.
I'm not done with it. Give it back.
- Let's do it together. - I'll do it.
Gosh.
It was delicious.
You make it yourself next time.
It would've been better if some squid was added.
Now that I became an adult, I realised comfort in ordinary...
lives is much happier than a moment of excitement.
Shall we do some work?
We were supposed to shoot here,
but how about shooting it here?
- That sounds good. - Will it be possible?
We need to get permission from the residents, but it'll be easy.
We were supposed to shoot the wedding here,
but is there a better place?
How about here?
You don't understand women. That's too ordinary.
I think it'll be nice outside.
Outside? There's a place. Wait.
How about this place?
It's nice.
Why?
Do you want to get married at a place like this?
What are you talking about? Look for other places, too.
Now that I became an adult,
I realised how valuable it is to have a partner in life...
whom you can share your thoughts with.
(Woori City Hall)
Where's Song Yi?
What's wrong? What happened?
Check your desk.
What's this?
Goodness.
Did you call me?
I heard you went to the provincial government office.
Did something bad happen?
They want to handle...
the cruise issue before the press makes a big deal out of it.
When I reviewed and submitted...
your report on poor construction of the cruise and corrupted bidding,
they want to settle it down...
before the problem gets bigger.
I don't understand.
Didn't you notice as you were reviewed by the audit department?
Something that's deeply corrupted will damage Woori City Hall and...
the provincial government office, so they want to settle the case...
by making you take all the responsibility.
By saying that the hail caused damage to the cruise,
they want to blame you even though you saved people...
in such a natural disaster.
The production presentation held on the cruise...
wasn't based on your feelings for Kang Min Joo. Instead, it was...
a great coverage to develop a culture space for Woori City.
But they're trying to blame you for everything that has happened.
Hey, Mi Rae.
Why? Did something get published?
Take a look at this.
(A star government worker, Chief Ko Sang Sik...)
Isn't it Sang Sik?
What are you reading?
Sang Hee, come and look at this.
What is it?
Sang Sik?
Producer Kang.
- What is it? - Look at this.
(Will he be demoted or expelled?)
What is this?
They're blaming Chief Ko for the cruise incident.
Demote?
Expel?
Even with these,
do you still think I'm responsible for it?
Could you...
investigate a little more?
This is too cruel!
What happened?
(Report of audit results)
Demotion?
What do you mean demotion?
(Second to Last Love)
Do you think this would have happened if Min Joo didn't move in?
Gosh, stop it.
Doesn't my opinion matter to you?
He's suspicious. I bet he knows something.
For the first time, I wanted to get married.
- I... - Don't say it.
That's something men should say first.
You're not planning to send Hoon to study in China again, are you?
Can you live as part of my family?
Don't eat alone from now on.