Kang Min Joo.
You've gone through a lot...
after being born as Kang Min Joo.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
Watch her carefully.
You'll continue to be lonely,
but love yourself despite being alone.
I promise myself that...
I'll live well and be healthy.
Get ready.
In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- What happened?
-  Producer Kang.
- Producer Kang.
-  Oh, no.
- Oh, no.
-  Producer Kang.
Kang Min Joo.
Why did I waste my time on...
worrying about growing old alone if I was just going to die like this?
Goodness.
What's happening? Let me go.
Let me go.
Stay still.
I know how to swim.
My gosh, how stubborn.
You'll get yourself killed.
- Producer Kang.
-  Producer Kang.
- Is she alive?
-  Are you okay?
Hey, wake up.
Hey, wake up. Hey!
Producer Kang, please don't die.
I should have jumped off. I'm so sorry, Producer Kang.
Producer Kang.
- Producer Kang.
-  Move out of the way.
Producer Kang.
My gosh.
Hey, are you all right?
Producer Kang.
Are you okay?
She's alive.
Hey, go and get a blanket for her.
I'm sorry, Sir.
I forgot to remove it.
You forgot?
You being absent-minded could get someone killed, okay?
"The legislation on bungee jump maintenance must improve."
"More importantly,"
"government employees who are in charge of the facility must be..."
"educated well enough so that no one gets hurt."
A total of 140 accidents take place every year.
And these are the articles on those accidents.
Do you think doctors are the only ones who save people's lives?
We're the environmental facilities department.
People may die if we don't maintain the facilities.
Chief Ko, we've recently merged...
with the local tourist department, so we're...
So are you saying that...
earning money from local tourism is all that matters?
Do you mean you don't care about tourists' lives...
because we're neither in charge of safety nor maintenance?
Is this what everyone thinks?
- No.
-  No, Sir.
Hello, this is Local Tourist Department.
Pardon?
Tell me who's in charge of the bungee jump.
How could you not check the facility?
Who?
All right, I'll be on my way,
so tell him to stay right there.
Chief Ko Sang Sik?
Oh, my goodness.
Are you all right?
No.
I brought you some outfits.
Choose the one that fits you.
How's the filming going?
Did you stop filming?
Well, yes.
So what's happening?
I don't think bungee jumping is possible.
We decided to change it to another scene.
Then you should've done that earlier!
Please be careful.
My gosh. I brought something for your lower back support.
(Second to Last Love)
(Woori City Hall)
Yes, I understand. I'm sorry.
I'll make sure it won't happen ever again.
All right.
Tell Chief Ko to come to my office right now.
Chief Ko.
My goodness. You should still be resting.
I'm fine. Stay away for now.
What is it?
"What is it"?
Can you say that...
even after looking at my state right now?
Did you know that the actress could have died?
Is it common sense not to check the facility...
before our filming?
Common sense?
I don't know how you dare to even say that.
What?
This wouldn't have happened if you followed the rules.
If you were to film at a bungee jump,
you should have contacted the facility department.
You wouldn't have risked...
your life if you had followed the basic rules.
Why did you start filming...
at a site where we hadn't finished checking the facilities?
Accidents happen because of people like you.
We initially said we won't cooperate with your filming.
Is it common sense for you film at the site by force?
Are you saying...
that you're proud of putting my life at risk?
A government official who should serve the citizens...
should apologise first when something like this happens.
You talk to an adult like me in such a casual manner.
An adult?
You're not an adult.
You're a troublemaker who is no better than a child.
I'm not going to apologise, so you should leave right now.
What?
You make trouble every time I see you.
I can't do my job because I have to cover for you.
I don't even want to talk to a person like you,
so don't appear in front of me ever again, all right?
What kind of person are you?
I don't want to talk to you ever again, either.
Do you think I'm not capable of swearing and talking casually?
Please remain calm. He's the one who saved your life.
He didn't save my life. I almost died because of him.
Gosh, what are we going to do?
We have to film here again next week.
- Gosh.
-  Goodness.
He's not good enough to be a government employee.
My goodness.
- Goodness.
-  Producer Kang.
Whatever the case,
we're still government employees. Right, Chief Ko?
You must abide by government rules.
I had already signed the official document of authorisation,
so you should've followed my orders and taken responsibility.
I wasn't informed that they'd be filming at the bungee jump site.
We already gave them permission to film at the entire site.
You should have let them be.
I noticed that Cha Soo Hyuk is in charge of the bungee jump site.
Doesn't he work in your department?
Yes, he does.
What shall I do?
You need to take disciplinary action for what happened.
It's true that Cha Soo Hyuk is in charge,
but there's no reason for him to take responsibility.
How so?
He was checking maintenance according to his schedule.
But after the filming was permitted,
I should have given him specific orders, but I didn't.
I'll take the responsibility as well as the disciplinary action.
In that case, you will...
no longer have a chance to win an award from the prime minister.
Are you all right with that?
It's all right.
Okay.
Then please guide the production team...
with the remaining filming schedule.
Pardon me?
A drama?
I can't believe this.
Darn it.
My gosh. This is amazing. Goodness.
Isn't it incredible?
It is.
It's fun, isn't it?
Producer Kang.
You almost died, Min Joo.
We almost lost you there.
Gosh, stop watching it.
Wow, this looks amazing.
It's not amazing at all.
I don't know who he is, but he saved your life.
- Can we zoom in on his face?
-  Okay.
Stop it.
The invincible Kang Min Joo...
let go of herself to him.
You got that right.
My goodness. That's true.
Are you going to continue?
I'm sorry.
Why did you have to go all the way there?
I had to get the permission to film, but I also wondered...
what it'd be like to live there.
Why? Are you going to start farming?
Isn't it a great place to live if I'm going to live alone anyway?
Gosh, you're determined to live alone.
Don't be so picky about men.
If I had time to be picky, why would I even look for a place like that?
You talk like you're getting ready for old age.
Are you looking for a retirement home?
Are you really planning to move there?
She's beautiful.
Gosh.
Hello.
You could have just sent me an email.
Telling you this in person is the right thing to do.
It's my first piece of work anyway.
I have to read the script first...
to accept it as your first work.
This is the edited version...
where I applied all of your suggestions.
I'll take a look at the script since you're tired.
Forget it.
I'm going to read it in every detail at home.
You don't have to read it in such detail.
See you.
That workaholic. Take care of yourself first...
instead of going to a sanatorium.
A sanatorium?
I thought you were dead, but you're still alive.
What a great thing to say to a person who almost died.
You startled me.
You're not a police officer.
You should be aware of your position.
Do you want me to find a graveyard for you?
Let's see who dies first between us two.
Gosh.
- Here.
-  What is it again?
I don't want to look at it. It will make me throw up.
You should get married.
She was a nurse at a hospital when she was young.
She looks young and pretty.
Forget it. Give me a drink.
Do you...
have a problem down there?
I'm not old enough to look for a hospice worker yet.
Don't treat me like that when I'm being a friend to you.
That's right.
I killed him.
My goodness.
("As Long As It's Not You", Working title)
"If you want to know if you're living a good life,"
"ask yourself."
"It's not about whether your dream came true."
"It's about whether you're happy."
Yes.
I just arrived.
Shall I come inside?
Okay.
You can't even dream of living in a house like this in Seoul.
The air is fresh, the view is great and it's cheap.
It's quiet and peaceful.
There's a hospital nearby, and the police station is very close.
You have a good eye.
By the way, how many family members do you have?
I'll be living alone.
I knew it. I was thinking that you look very stylish.
You must be an eligible bachelorette with a great career.
Thank you for showing me the house.
Please don't forget to call me. I should get back to work.
Is this a house or a cafe?
We meet again.
Get on.
Aren't you going to get on?
You'll regret it.
You might fall off if you stay like that.
This is quince tea.
I made it because you seem tired, and you look like you have a cold.
Thank you.
It'll be hot.
Oh, right. Thank you for the other day.
If you're here for dinner, here's our menu.
No, I came to look at the house next door.
- You came to see the house?
-  Yes.
That house is pretty nice.
I know, right? I really like it too, so...
You should move there. Then we'll see each other often.
Do you live in this neighbourhood?
I live right here.
You must be the owner of this cafe.
I guess I might get another regular customer.
I'm relieved.
About what?
Well, I'm glad to have a good next-door neighbour.
You won't turn a blind eye when something happens to me.
What kind of things?
In life, you never know when you'll end up in an ambulance or...
At my age, it's...
Never mind.
You look very young, though.
I'm serious.
Whatever. I'll become your regular customer.
Excuse me.
- Just a moment.
-  Sure.
- Cheers.
-  Cheers.
We have to go to work tomorrow.
Stop drinking and go home.
He's talking like an old fogey again.
Fogey?
I said we shouldn't come here.
We should've just gone out for drinks ourselves.
When did I ask you guys to come here?
This place is my sanctuary, so don't ever come here again.
Yes, Chief! We'll remember that!
Let's never come here again.
Let's go! Come on.
Why are you kicking out my customers?
Those youngsters are livening up the mood here.
They called me an old fogey.
Right, so stop nagging them. It shows that you've gotten old.
Just change the music. It's way too loud.
Goodness gracious.
It's this Saturday.
What is?
That lady I told you about! The blind date.
Gosh, I told you that I'm not interested.
I'm doing more than fine.
Oh, my. Are you going on a blind date, Chief?
Why did you have to bring that up?
Gosh, Chief!
I'm sorry.
See?
Even my female colleagues treat me like this.
Those weird magazines definitely made things worse for you.
What magazines?
See?
Men are ridiculous.
Women are ridiculous.
Officer Cha.
You said you didn't want to join us for dinner.
We're all done now.
Where is Chief Ko?
Why are you here?
Why did you say that to the deputy mayor?
I heard you can no longer get the Prime Minister Award because of me.
Getting the award will guarantee a promotion as well as a bonus.
If you know that, be good to me. Don't cause any more trouble.
Please allow me to take responsibility.
Responsibility?
How will you do so?
I will gladly accept any reprimand.
Just work harder with that mindset.
- Chief.
-  If you cause another trouble,
I won't let it slide.
It's because of that incident, isn't it?
I know because I've heard enough about you.
You're a very responsible person,
and you try to take responsibility for anything that happens. That's...
Don't talk like you know everything.
Things like this happen because you work halfheartedly and clumsily.
Watch your mouth and behave yourself.
Please take my seat, Ma'am.
So you were in a different line of work before.
Here, I also see what you studied in university.
Have you given up on your dream completely?
My dream?
My family is my dream.
Hurry up! Get out of here now!
Don't let go of my hand!
Hello.
How much is this?
I see.
I'll get it next time.
This little...
Hey!
Help me carry this before I get mad at you.
I can't because my golden hands are too precious.
Golden hands?
These golden fingers will rule the world.
Golden fingers?
Just don't get faeces on them.
Your jokes are not funny at all.
You fogey. Fine, I'll carry one for you.
Yes, I'm an old fogey.
What are you up to these days? Why didn't you come home for days?
- I've been busy with work.
-  What kind of work?
- How's the job at the cafe going?
-  I got fired.
Mi Rae!
I work with guns these days.
- Guns?
-  I work at a gas station.
All right.
I hope you can keep that job at least.
They said they don't need me any more.
Why?
I put gasoline in a diesel engine.
- You fool!
-  Ouch.
I honestly don't know where you got your genes from.
It's because you're on your phone all day long.
Sang Sik, I'm a grown-up now. Stop lecturing me.
If you want to be treated like a grown-up, get a proper job.
Job? Steve Jobs? Apple?
- Shall I get a new phone?
-  Dear me.
You can't even pay your own phone bills.
Where's Ye Ji? She's not home yet?
No.
It looks like Sang Hee is busy meeting with Hoon's teachers.
- Mind your own business.
-  All right.
I can't breathe when I don't have my phone on me!
Stop! You old fogey!
- Old fogey?
-  Hey!
Stop, you old man!
Things like these can stay here. This one should go inside.
Please be careful with the floor.
Hey, Ae Kyung.
You've fallen off the face of the earth.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I moved today.
Really?
So the city girl has finally left Seoul?
That's right.
It's amazing here.
I feel as if I'm dreaming now!
You silly. You should've told us.
It's not like you know a buff guy who can help you.
I can do it by myself.
That's your problem. You're too independent.
How's your next-door neighbour?
He's a super handsome young guy.
He's also very kind.
A guy?
He's not a married guy with kids, is he?
Gosh, seriously.
When you visit me, you'll realise how stressful your lives have been.
The air here is so fresh.
Now, you just need a guy to live with.
Shut it.
From now on, I'll eat delicious things alone...
and take a walk and exercise all by myself here.
I'll grow old graciously!
My goodness, I'm tired.
Are you okay?
Gosh.
Goodness.
What brings you here?
My goodness.
I wanted to welcome you with this.
Oh, my!
My goodness.
Hold on. Oh, no! Goodness!
What is this?
It's rice.
I made rice with other grains.
I've been having digestive problems.
Just come over to my place for food.
Sang Sik, eat lunch before you go.
It's okay. I don't have time.
Gosh, why did you get changed all of a sudden?
I need to follow a filming crew around in the afternoon.
I've been told to monitor the filming site for a drama.
A drama?
This wouldn't have happened if they hadn't merged the departments.
Aren't you a chief? Why are they making you do such a petty task?
Something happened.
It's all because of that crazy woman.
What does that mean?
Gosh, it looks delicious.
You should eat before you leave.
It's delicious. I'll see you later.
Hello?
You have a guest. Go.
All right.
You're here. Please come in.
This must be where you live.
- It's connected to the cafe.
-  Yes.
Welcome to the neighbourhood!
Thank you.
Oh, my goodness!
It looks like a work of art!
Oh, my.
It's delicious.
It's so healthy, too!
I can eat this, right?
You already took a bite.
Come by often for food.
I should. You're such a great cook.
How did you make this?
(Comma's Cooking Class for Vegan Desserts)
If you want to know, you should check out the class.
It looked like you could use some help when it comes to cooking.
You teach classes at your cafe, too?
Once a week. It's free.
I teach healthy recipes...
for beginners and people who aren't confident with cooking.
Then it's perfect for someone like me.
How's your house?
I don't know who the former tenant was, but it's well taken care of...
and decorated tastefully, as well.
The person probably didn't want to move.
A few small things need repairs, though.
The first door of the kitchen cabinet won't close properly.
The hardwood floor will make a little squeaky sound, too.
The floor in the bedroom isn't even, so the bed won't be levelled.
I suggest you put something underneath to level it.
I used to live in that house.
Seriously? Then why...
I just feel comfortable living here.
I like the people that live here, and I'm pretty close to them.
I see.
Feel free to let me know if you need help with anything.
We're neighbours now.
Right, we're neighbours now.
My name is Park Jun Woo.
Hi, Jun Woo.
- I'm Kang Min Joo.
-  I see.
Kang Min Joo.
Preserve the site. Be punctual and safe. You must follow the rules.
Okay, we will do so.
This place will look incredible when the construction is completed.
A cinema in a cave.
If you screen horror movies here in summer, it'll be a huge hit.
What are all those things?
Those are our props.
In the drama, this cave is portrayed as where people come to make wishes.
They're sticky notes with couples' wishes.
I don't really care to know. Just make sure to clean up everything.
Okay, we will.
Please don't worry too much.
How can I not worry?
You're shooting the drama when the construction isn't even over.
You cannot go late. You can only shoot until 6pm.
I heard you. How many times are you going to repeat yourself?
We don't have enough time! Hurry up!
- Okay.
-  Okay.
Nothing will collapse or break here, right?
You're still going on about the bungee jump.
It could've killed a person. Our team manager, to be more specific.
Oh, the mayor is here.
Hello, Sir.
Sir, this is Chief Ko Sang Sik.
It's very nice to meet you. I heard you're great at your job.
- Oh, no.
-  Please don't be so modest.
I heard you're the one who came up with the idea...
of turning this useless abandoned mine into a cinema.
Oh, yes. We're working on it right now, but...
He has contributed greatly to making this city a better place to live.
- Spare me a second.
-  Sure.
I actually pestered him about coming here...
because I love this drama so much.
I see. I'm glad that you were able to visit today.
Please come with me.
Pardon me?
- Hello!
-  Hello.
- Have a good day.
-  You, too.
Gosh, don't embarrass me.
It's really fine.
Please take it back.
No, I don't want to.
You're putting me in a difficult position. Please take it back.
Gosh, you're the one who's putting me in a difficult position.
Goodness. What's he doing now?
My goodness.
Unbelievable.
You're here. Come this way.
He's the mayor.
Who's the woman beside him?
His wife.
Why?
Nothing.
Hello.
Oh, this is Producer Kang Min Joo.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Why is that woman here?
I'm a huge fan of your drama.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
By the way, when will the male lead come to...
Gosh, stop it.
What's wrong with being his fan? I love him, too.
I'll introduce you to him in a bit and get you his autograph, too.
Oh, my. Then I'll have no more wishes left!
Thank you so much.
Please show them around.
Yes, I'll guide you. This way, please.
Sure.
Well, then.
I'll get going, too.
The mayor is here. You should stay and watch the shoot a bit, as well.
No, it's okay.
See you soon.
He was going on about how we can't run late.
Why are they being so strict?
What are all those?
The mayor's wife told us to give these to the actors.
Goodness. She's making you guys do such ridiculous things.
Chief, take this.
- It's okay.
-  Just take it.
Oh, no.
Do you have anything to wipe it off with?
No. Gosh.
Goodness.
Gosh, let me do it.
Chief!
You're being like that again. Okay, just stand still.
It's okay. Please stop!
Stop it, please!
Stop making so much fuss! Stop moving. It got on here, too.
My goodness.
Stop moving, seriously.
- It's almost done.
-  What are you doing now?
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm okay.
You're really okay, right?
You should tell me if you're not. I'll help you.
What are you talking about?
Neglect of duty, demeaning dignity...
- and bribery.
-  What?
Shouldn't you avoid such things...
- as a government employee?
-  And?
You turned out to be such a rogue civil servant.
A rogue civil servant?
It's not like that.
Don't bother. Gosh.
You see, we're not civil servants.
Why do my staff have to go home right at 6pm?
We need more time to shoot. We'll extend the hours.
Under whose permission?
What if someone gets hurt like last time? Who will be responsible?
I will be responsible if you will cooperate.
Yes, please do that.
I have no intention of sharing my breath...
or any oxygen with the woman who goes unconscious.
Not even this much.
What did you say?
We already told you the hours. Make sure you follow it.
My goodness.
Unbelievable.
Cut. Okay, that's good.
Let's move onto the next scene.
Hurry up and take it down.
- Good job.
-  Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Bye now.
-  Thank you.
Bye.
Song Yi. I told you I'd call when it's finished.
- It's almost 6pm.
-  How much more do we have left?
- Just one scene.
-  Hurry up and finish it.
- Are they finished over there?
-  Yes.
Hey.
The shoot must finish at 6pm.
Call Soo Hyuk and make sure they keep the time.
- Yes, Sir.
-  Okay.
About that woman earlier...
Why is she so rude to you?
Maybe she finds me easy.
Why is this in here?
Ever since the merge, we're all so busy and are out all the time.
You must feel bad that you have to take care of things like this.
The chief of the local tourist department got a promotion...
while you're getting all the slack as soon as the merge.
Water? I'll get it for you.
It's okay.
Cut! Okay. That was great.
- All right.
-  Great job.
- Good job.
-  Good job.
Good job.
- Did Producer Kang leave already?
-  Thank you.
Good job.
Okay.
They just finished and wrapped up.
Really? Okay.
Yes. I heard that the shoot is over.
Why didn't they take this off?
Gosh.
Oh, no.
Hello?
Gosh.
(Restricted area)
Hello?
Hello!
There's someone in here!
(No trespassing)
Hello?
My goodness.
What should I do? My gosh.
What?
Where are you?
Producer Kang! Hello?
Hello?
Turn the car around.
Ki Cheol!
Hello!
What?
There's someone stuck in the cave?
Hello?
Anyone out there?
Save me...
Hello?
What? Everyone already went home for the day?
Chief Ko, here are the emergency keys.
What happened?
You should have checked properly!
They closed the cave, but someone was still inside.
I'm sure everyone came out. Who's still there?
That woman in charge of the drama.
That's impossible. I'll go.
- Forget it.
-  Chief Ko.
Chief Ko!
I can't believe this.
You should have checked properly!
(Automatic traffic violation enforcement)
Hello!
Over here!
Here! There's someone over here!
Here!
Are you all right?
Gosh.
You're so impossible.
How can they lock up without checking for people?
You can get hypothermia from the temperature drop.
Forget it. My team will come.
Don't be fussy. It's your fault.
No one told me it would be locked up.
You should have kept your promise.
I was only 10 minutes late.
You were 10 minutes too late.
How can you be so mean?
You should know when to say sorry or thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
What were you doing here by yourself?
- Producer Kang!
-  Producer Kang.
Producer Kang.
- Are you all right?
-  Are you okay?
I'm sorry. We should have cleaned up.
Because of our tight schedule,
we didn't get a chance to clean up properly.
Are you really going to keep this up?
I told you to make sure and clean up afterwards.
If you keep this up, you won't get to shoot any more.
- I'm sorry.
-  We apologise.
She was almost stuck in there all night.
Stop it. I should have rushed out earlier.
Give it to me. I'll throw it out.
Give it to me.
I'll clean up since I get your taxes to work.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
He's so uptight and obnoxious.
Did she clean all this up by herself after the shoot?
Gosh.
This should go in here.
This should go into recycling...
What? My goodness.
That's better.
What am I thinking?
He's a rogue civil servant that gives bribes and molests girls.
The hardwood floor will make a little squeaky sound.
The first door of the kitchen cabinet won't close properly.
The floor in the bedroom isn't even, so the bed won't be levelled.
I suggest you put something underneath to level it.
Gosh.
Hello, Mum.
I heard you moved.
Did you get home after work then?
Are you eating well?
Don't worry about me.
The move went well.
How is Dad?
We're living the life over here thanks to you.
I know you love work,
but do you plan on living by yourself there?
Yes.
Mum. Do you still enjoy living with Dad?
You guys fight all the time.
Even if you don't get married,
you should meet a man that cares for you.
I don't need it.
I'm doing fine all by myself.
You guys should take care of your health.
If you're going to scold me, I'm hanging up.
I got it.
Okay.
Seriously.
What is that sound?
It doesn't look like Jun Woo.
Who is that?
My goodness.
What are you doing here?
Jun Woo.
There's a ghost... I mean, a burglar in that house.
She's not a ghost. She just moved in.
What? Someone moved in?
Who? Why didn't you tell me?
I was going to tell you now.
You can greet her tomorrow. Let's go inside to talk.
Okay. Did you close up the shop?
Yes. I was about to go in when I saw you.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
That's better.
Gosh.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
-  Good morning.
Of course you're in a good mood...
as long as you're not stuck in a cave or something.
Isn't your place too far to commute to work?
That's why I like it.
I'll only work more if I'm close, and I'd get stressed.
What's this?
What?
- What is it?
-  Did you see it?
You saw it, didn't you?
("I Don't Love You Even If I Die" plagiarises a web comic)
I told you to meet with them.
Why does Producer Kang have to always clean up after you?
We already talked about this with Director Gook.
I did what I could already.
Gosh.
Producer Kang.
- Apologise!
-  Apologise!
I spent three years in my studio...
and I worked so hard...
without eating or sleeping...
for this web comic.
It was hard and lonely,
but I did my best to create the series...
for my beloved readers that were waiting for me.
However, without ever having to discuss the matters,
SBC illegally plagiarised my work...
and is airing the drama.
Instead of giving me an apology, they aren't even admitting to it.
Then need to cancel the drama right away.
I demand an official apology.
If they fail to apologise, I will be taking legal measures.
- SBC, apologise!
-  Apologise!
- Apologise!
Hey.
How far do you plan to go with the lawsuit?
Are you planning to continue with the drama?
- What do you plan on doing?
-  Please tell us.
Please answer our question.
Please, don't do this. Please.
It's dangerous.
Stop!
Be careful.
It's dangerous.
Excuse me. Open the door.
Open the door.
I'm from SBC. Let's talk.
Don't open it.
Open the door.
Open the door!
Writer Hwang.
- Why did she come?
-  Mi Rae.
I told you to stay in the studio.
Get down. Go back down.
Why are you here? It's so dangerous.
- My gosh.
-  You might accidentally fall.
Mi Rae. I'm telling you, get down.
Go down.
What do you think you're doing? Come down right now.
It's too dangerous.
I'm Producer Kang Min Joo of SBC.
Kang Min Joo? The one that kept calling me...
and begged me to meet?
That's right.
We won't settle. I won't drop the charges.
You need to cancel the drama and put up a letter of apology.
Is that all? Is that all you want?
That's right!
I understand. Just come down.
Are you admitting that you copied the web comic?
I need you to make that certain.
I'll talk if you come down.
Do you take us for a fool?
- Don't come down.
-  I won't.
You must know that it's hard to find evidence of plagiarism, right?
First, I apologise for our lack of communication regarding the suit.
However, what we can do is to...
avoid this from happening again. As a protective measure,
we'll pay you for any damages...
and support you in every way possible with your future work.
We never asked you to give us jobs.
We're not homeless. We won't negotiate!
- No way!
-  No way!
Is that it? We don't need it, so go away.
Writer Hwang. Will you really jump?
- No.
-  I trust that you won't be rash.
Do you want me to show you what being rash really means?
Well?
Writer Hwang!
- Why did she jump?
-  Writer Hwang!
Writer Hwang!
Are you all right?
My goodness.
Writer Hwang!
("I Don't Love You Even If I Die" plagiarism controversy)
(Web comic writer injured after suicide disturbance)
(Web comic writer attempts suicide)
Writer Hwang.
Must you really take such extreme measures?
That's why you should admit it and officially apologise.
I'm sorry.
I understand how you must feel when your creation is stolen.
I know nothing can compensate for what has happened.
There was too much damage done for it to be fixed.
If you'd like settlement money, we can meet your request.
Do I look like I'm putting up an act for money?
We just love our job. We post our work after many sleepless nights.
When we put it up, everyone copies it.
We never win the fight. We can't say anything.
They're like our precious children and they were stolen from us.
I don't want any more writers to go through this.
I see.
Our broadcasting company will get a lot of criticism for this,
but the drama will continue.
We haven't had this much profit in a while.
All we can do is give you compensation money.
That's it,
and I'm sorry.
Gosh.
It's better that you're honest.
Writer Hwang.
Actually,
the writer who developed and worked on that web comic...
is Writer Ko.
All I did was supervise.
She's the original writer.
If you want to settle or give her compensation money,
you should talk with her.
I'll drop the charges if she asks me to,
but I won't do it even if you come and talk to me every day.
Me?
How can I?
I don't know anything.
Is your name Mi Rae?
Yes.
I'm asking my seven fans.
If you take the lawsuit any further,
it'll only get more tiresome for you.
I guess so.
What should I do? What would be the best?
It'd be best to drop the charges for everyone's benefit.
I don't think it's right to drop the charges now.
Then what?
Is it too cowardly to take what they offer?
What do you want me to do then?
- Just fight them until the end.
-  She might die.
- Just compromise.
-  That's cowardly.
Take the money.
- It's too hard.
-  Figure it out yourself.
None of you are helpful.
Mi Rae.
It was so tough for her until now.
I know. I'm sure both of you had a rough time.
No, I still had fun.
I told her she should sue since it was identical to her work.
Other writers might get harmed by it, as well.
You're right. I'll make sure to never make the mistake again.
Okay, thank you.
That's why I need your help with this case.
If you can make the decision...
I don't have the power to make such a decision.
I also...
have a problem with making decisions.
Sorry.
You might want to talk to my legal guardian instead of me.
Legal...
guardian?
Yes. He's double, no triple times more cold than me.
He has the ability to make quick decisions.
You can talk to my brother and legal guardian.
Your brother?
Yes. I can't make a decision.
I'll drop the charges if he tells me to.
She's not even young.
She's over 30 years old. Why do I have to talk to her brother?
It's no time for us to be picky.
It doesn't matter if it's her brother or not. We need to beg.
Come on, Min Joo. Meet with him tomorrow.
I'm busy tomorrow.
Is my team doing okay?
That's not important right now!
You're finally showing your true self.
Jeong Sik. Who do you think I'm doing this for?
I know. I know that.
That's why I was really thorough with Writer Na's script today.
You should just focus on...
choosing what's more important to work on.
I'm already busy with what I have. Why should I focus on you?
I'm hanging up.
Did one of my lights go out?
Jun Woo?
Come and have breakfast.
Why did you set for three? Mi Rae never eats breakfast.
That's for our neighbour.
- What? Our neighbour?
-  Yes.
Hello.
- Good morning.
-  Come on in.
It smells delicious...
- Why is she...
-  Why are you...
What's this? Do you know each other?
Why...
Why is he here?
Because it's my house!
This is your place?
You better move out right now.
Yes. I want to get out of here this instant.
What's with you guys?
I paid to come in here. Why are you bossing me around?
I'm the landlord!
Who did I sign with then?
I'm so hungry.
Sang Sik, do you have food?
Jun Woo, pack up some side dishes for me.
- Okay.
-  How do you like your place?
How can you let just anyone move in here?
"Just anyone"?
Watch it!
What happened? Why are they fighting?
Why were you sawing at midnight?
How can you barge in here so early in the morning?
She has no common sense nor any manners. She's just selfish!
Brother!
What?
He's your brother? Really?
No, we're not real brothers.
I don't know what happened,
but let's just sort it out.
- No way!
-  Forget it!
Move out right now!
Fine, I will.
Why?
You're so loud, what's going on? I can't sleep!
Ms Ko Mi Rae?
I'm sleepy.
Hey...
How do you know my sister?
Your sister?
He's double, no triple times more cold than me.
He has the ability to make quick decisions.
You can talk to my brother and legal guardian.
No way.
Are you Mi Rae's big brother?
Yes.
I'm her big brother. Why?
(Second to Last Love)
Try some of this.
- It'll tighten it.
-  What?
Why did you eat this?
Because she gave it to me! She told me it would tighten...
You should keep a distance from her.
- I think she's nice.
-  What are you saying?
Don't do anything dangerous.
Also, don't even think about coming up here alone.
Are you worrying about me?
Are you single?
You should ask a man to do something like that.
No wonder you're single.