Goodness.
What's going on, Song Yi? What brings you here?
Chief.
What's this for? Why are you giving it to me?
Don't go on any blind dates.
Tell your friend that you don't want to be set up with anyone.
I...
like you.
I wanted to tell you how I feel before it gets too late.
So you can't go on that blind date, okay?
Goodness.
I'm here because I live here!
This is your place?
You're so loud, what's going on? I can't sleep!
Ms Ko Mi Rae?
I'm sleepy.
How do you know my sister?
Your sister?
He's double, no triple times colder than me.
He has the ability to make quick decisions.
You can talk to my brother and legal guardian.
How ridiculous.
(Plagiarism Scandal Surrounding "I Don't Love You Even If I Die")
How can I possibly ask him favours and negotiate with him?
- Hi.
-  Oh, right.
What you saw earlier was just...
What's the matter?
You two looked lovely together.
Well...
I have something to tell you, so if you're free around lunchtime...
I refuse to negotiate.
Spend that time to find a different house.
It's not about that.
You know what your sister does, right?
- The TV network I work for...
-  Plagiarism?
Right. That's what I'd like to talk to you about.
I'm realising that my new next-door neighbour is a thief.
- Pardon me?
-  You're a total thief...
who copies other people's works.
- Look.
-  Does this mean...
Woori City Hall has been helping a plagiarised drama?
My drama isn't...
When an accident takes place because of your violation of rules,
you must have the decency to apologise right away.
How could you make her try to kill herself?
You're one horrible woman.
Wait. Listen to me before you go on about...
Move out...
immediately.
My goodness.
(Second to Last Love)
(Episode 03)
Hey.
- Officer Cha.
-  Yes, Chief.
Get me last year's schedule for the event.
Sure.
- It's here.
-  Thanks.
Do you have a red pen?
- Here you go.
-  Thanks.
Can I also borrow your whiteout?
- Chief.
-  Chief.
- Why do you keep asking me?
-  You can just ask me.
Shall I do that? Okay.
Then pass me your whiteout.
Never mind. I have one here.
It's right here.
Right.
Chief, many people date their colleagues these days.
Don't overreact and just be natural.
You're making it obvious.
If it's ruled as plagiarism and goes to court, we might be able...
to buy some time, but our network's reputation will be ruined.
If we cancel all the exporting contracts and pay for the damages,
the total financial damage will be immense.
All of us will get fired, and the company will shut down.
Why does Producer Kang have to clean up the mess?
That's what I'm saying.
This is why people call her over to solve their problems.
Why did she volunteer to help Team Manager Han?
What is that?
- Oh, you're here.
-  Good morning.
Isn't that...
- a bribe?
-  What are you talking about?
I saw the mayor's wife...
The mayor's wife gave it to the male lead of the drama,
but he sent it to us for us to share.
- What is it?
-  Open it.
So was he trying to return this because he couldn't even deliver it?
What's so fun?
Officer Cha.
I'm sorry, but no one is looking at that area.
"That area"? Did you actually say that?
That alone can be considered as sexual harassment.
You get humiliated so easily.
(Letter of Request, Assistance Needed for "Love Is Bubbling Up")
I guess the shoot will continue throughout this week.
I must say that it's such a fun drama.
Why are you wasting your time watching that copycat drama?
- All of our help...
-  This one didn't copy anything.
You're talking about a different drama from the same network.
Are you sure about that?
Shall I look it up for you?
No, there's no need.
(SBC drama, plagiarism scandal)
("I Don't Love You Even If I Die")
(Cast)
(Producer Han Jeong Sik)
How did it go? Did you meet her brother?
Don't ask me. It got even more complicated.
Why? Who is he? Shall I meet him myself?
Forget it.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Gosh, let go.
The court will announce preliminary ruling in two days.
What will you do if it's ruled as plagiarism?
You should've looked into it more before jumping into it.
What's the point of grilling me about something that's already done?
It's not like I did it knowingly.
You're the only one who can resolve this situation.
Nothing is impossible to you.
The only thing we can do is to persuade her to withdraw the suit.
Run! Get out of here now!
Hurry! Come this way!
Don't let go of my hand!
Chief!
- Are you okay?
-  Yes, I'm fine.
What do you mean you can't do it any more?
Why on earth are you doing this?
It doesn't suit my personality.
It's not something I can do.
You work for the government.
You can't pick and choose your own tasks.
It's against government employees' code of conduct!
I'll gladly accept a disciplinary action.
I can no longer follow the crew around and help them.
I refuse to do so.
Song Yi?
What happened?
It's nothing.
What's going on? Did someone say something to you?
Yes.
Who?
You.
- Me?
-  You said I'm wasting my time.
I know that I'm just a contract worker,
but I only watched the preview of the drama.
It wasn't even 30 seconds!
Gosh, I didn't mean it that way.
I know that doing something unrelated to work is wrong,
but the fact that I like you...
shouldn't give you the reason to treat me however you want!
Okay, all right. I was out of line.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay now.
What?
I told you how I feel about you.
Now,
you can feel free to do this when you console me.
We can't do this. We mustn't. Okay?
Hello?
Yes, hello.
I'm your next-door...
No.
I'm Producer Kang Min Joo of SBC.
If you're calling about your shoots, I have nothing to say.
No, that's not it.
If it's about the house, we can talk later. I have to go.
Wait. Hello? Mr Ko Sang Sik!
Mr Ko?
Anyway, Song Yi.
- What I want to say is...
-  Is it because of a woman?
- What?
-  You're saying no to me.
Is it because you're seeing someone now?
What are you talking about? I'm not seeing anyone.
Then what about the blind date?
I'm not going on any blind date. Have you lost your mind?
Then we're good.
Listen to me carefully.
I don't know why you're doing this to me out of the blue,
but you can't be like this. You absolutely can't.
What is it that I can't do, exactly?
Did I ask you to do something with me?
I'm neither asking you to marry me now...
nor saying that we should live together.
I just told you my honest feelings.
Let's start by getting to know each other better.
Getting to know each other?
The reason why I'd like to speak to you isn't about the house.
I'd like to talk to you about your sister, Ms Ko Mi Rae.
(I'd like to talk to you about your sister, Ms Ko Mi Rae.)
Oh, hello.
- Hello.
-  I heard you're busy these days.
Where is Mr Han Jeong Sik?
You'll talk to me today. Please give it to me.
I don't want to.
I made the revisions based on Mr Hans's suggestions,
so I'll speak to him.
I'm the chief producer of the drama.
It's not like I'm a dog in your neighbourhood.
I don't want to go around asking everyone to pet my head.
Then I'll just end up plagiarising someone else's work and kill myself.
What did you just say?
I heard that a web comic artist killed herself because of you.
She tried committing suicide but didn't actually kill herself.
Are you not even able to comprehend articles properly?
Anyway,
your sensibility is... How should I put this?
It doesn't suit my style.
You don't understand what young women these days think and feel.
Ko Mi Rae.
You little... Wake up already!
Gosh, what is it?
Explain this.
(A Web Comic Artist Fell After a Suicide Attempt)
Come out right now.
Web comic?
Why didn't you tell me?
I couldn't tell you because nothing has been published under my name.
Is that why you copied the popular drama?
Goodness.
Who said that?
Tell me.
That woman who moved into the house next door?
Goodness. Who knew she'd be such a psycho when she looks so normal?
She was begging me to drop the suit.
Is she accusing me of that because she's at a disadvantage now?
The suit is coming to an end, so they're trying whatever they can.
Why did you tell her to talk to me without telling me a thing?
You were the only person I could think of at the moment.
Everything you just told me is true, right?
Of course. Do you think I'm lying?
Why would I? Look, I'm not scared of anything...
because I have nothing to lose.
They must think I'm a big joke.
How could they accuse me of plagiarising their drama?
Where is that woman now? Bring her!
What are you two talking about now?
I'm asking you what this is about.
When will the court's decision be made?
The day after tomorrow. How many times do I have to tell you?
If that's what the broadcasting company is going through,
then dropping the suit...
will never happen.
Gosh, please.
We can't do that. It should not happen.
The law will give us the right answer.
Why should we withdraw the suit?
As I told you, we will give Ms Ko a great opportunity in return to...
No. Don't even dream.
- Look.
-  My talk is finished.
Get this woman out of our place.
I'm sorry.
He has the ability to make the most accurate decisions quickly?
Sure.
You're very precise and meticulous.
You must be so happy to have such a wonderful, smart brother.
What a blockhead.
He's blocking her way and ruining her future.
It looks like...
you're the one who splashed muddy water into her future.
Her future depends on this.
If you withdraw the lawsuit,
I'll do everything in my power to help Ms Ko and her career.
She can come and work at our network if she likes.
It'll be a great opportunity for her to solidify her career as...
And what?
Will you make my sister become like you?
Is working like that what got you to where you are now?
With that chief producer title of yours,
you abuse your power over actors and crew members.
Then when things go wrong,
you hide in the back and try to come up with ruses...
and ideas to negotiate like a con artist.
Look. You're out of line.
I'm suggesting a proposal for both parties...
A proposal? We don't need such a thing.
If you made a mistake, take responsibility for it.
And do not involve my family in anything you do from now on.
What do you mean...
My family is doing fine now, so do not bother us.
I don't think you live in the area.
I haven't seen you before.
I moved here a few days ago.
Why are you drinking alone when you're that beautiful?
I know. Life is ridiculous.
By any chance, do you know Mr Ko Sang Sik...
who works at the city hall?
Yes, I know him very well. Why do you ask?
What is he like?
How shall I describe him?
I guess he's extremely by the book.
He never compromises.
No exceptions.
He's cut out to be a government employee.
He must have at least one flaw.
He has many flaws.
He's starting to lose hair, and he's single.
Oh, his weakness is his family.
His family is definitely his priority.
He takes great care of them.
But all of his family members are very quirky.
They're all a bit of troublemakers,
but he goes all crazy when anything happens to his family.
So be careful not to get involved in anything with his family.
If you do, you'll lose it.
So the drama filming crew you've been following around was...
That's right.
She's the chief producer of that drama.
She's a total troublemaker. Look what happened to Mi Rae.
You should stay away from her.
Gosh, Sang Sik. You're being overly sensitive.
I think she's pretty cool.
What are you talking about?
Why did you move out of that house anyway?
I like living with all of you here...
a lot more than living there all alone.
Goodness.
Sang Sik. Please let go of the past.
And stop worrying so much about your family, too.
You should enjoy your life.
You go ahead and enjoy yours.
This is my life, and I'm satisfied with it.
As you're getting older, you're starting to hide your feelings more.
Trying to be responsible all the time must burden you at times.
You'll know when you're older.
Right. I'm still a baby, so I don't understand those things.
I'll have fun for the rest of my life.
Don't take your life so seriously.
Tell them to come out.
Somebody must take responsibility for what happened.
They killed a hard-working employee and call it an accident?
- How can they just say that?
-  Mum, stop.
- Accident?
-  Mum, please.
- Please calm down.
-  Find whoever that is responsible.
How could this happen? How?
How is this possible?
My goodness.
Why did she drink so much?
Yes.
My blood was boiling because of someone,
so I drank a little.
Let go of me.
I know that you...
molest your female coworkers.
What? I molest who?
Look who's talking. You plagiarise other people's work.
- I'm speechless.
-  What are dramas for?
If you want to console and comfort the viewers through your drama,
you cannot copy other people's work like that.
Yes, sure thing.
You're so righteous.
I'm an irresponsible and reckless troublemaker,
so I just steal from other people.
I heard it's not even your drama.
Taking responsibility for your own life is difficult enough.
I'm not sure why you're being responsible for someone else's job,
but being nosy like that will only complicate your life more.
Thanks for your word of wisdom.
I guess your life is so uncomplicated...
because you always go by the book.
That's probably why your family is happy and well, too.
Yes.
That's exactly why you don't belong here, so move out immediately.
Look.
How long have you known me for?
How dare you judge me and criticise me...
when you don't even know anything about me?
You're drunk. If you want to talk, do it when you're sober.
You jerk!
This isn't no drunk talk.
Fine, I'm a thief, a crook and a con artist.
So what?
Gosh, seriously!
Are you out of your mind? Are you trying to molest me?
No, I was...
Oh, no. My hairpin.
- Gosh, this is...
-  I didn't...
Goodness.
Well, I was just...
Well... Listen.
Why are you doing this to me?
You told me not to bother your family.
Are you the only one who has family?
Is your family the only thing that matters?
Those who don't have family shouldn't even live, then.
You must be so happy to have a family to protect.
Do you think I live like this because I want to?
Please...
calm down. About the hairpin, I...
You're lucky I've gotten nice over the years.
Goodness.
I thought things would change when I become a grown-up.
I wanted to grow into an adult...
who is graceful, serene and relaxed.
"A thief moved into the house next door."
"You just hide behind..."
"and try to come up with ruses like a con artist."
What?
You jerk!
How could you...
I thought I'd find peace and maturity as I grew older.
The image of the adult I had in mind...
was nothing like this.
wasn't this.
When will my car be available? I signed the contract so long ago.
Please bring it to my place.
Get on. You can't carry those alone.
No, thank you.
Why not?
I don't want to have anything to do with your family.
What are you talking about?
And I'm not his family. That means you can come with me.
You still live with him.
Oh, right. Who installed the hardwood flooring?
I did it.
If you need to fix anything, I'll do it for you.
It's okay. I'll figure it out.
I'm on my way.
Don't just stare at the clock and wait for me. Do something.
You can sleep, read or watch TV.
Then dropping the suit...
We can't do that. It should not happen.
What are dramas for?
If you want to console and comfort the viewers through your drama,
you cannot copy other people's work like that.
Yes.
Jeong Sik.
Are you editing the episode for today?
How did it go?
- It didn't go well.
-  What?
Seriously?
We should just admit that we plagiarised and...
What in the world are you talking about?
I'm busy, so let's talk later.
Edit this out.
You guys are working hard.
What brings you here?
Team Manager Han reviewed everything and just left for the day.
You're sure that Jeong Sik left for the day, right?
- Yes.
-  Are you almost done?
Of course. It has to air soon.
Turn off the TV if you aren't watching it.
I'm going to watch the drama. It'll start shortly.
("I Don't Love You Even If I Die")
Why would you watch that?
- Because it's fun.
-  Fun?
- Doesn't it infuriate you?
-  Gosh!
- No! Don't do that!
-  This drama...
is based on the web comic "You're Not the Only One Who Loves".
We sincerely apologise for not being able to inform you of this sooner.
We hope you continue to enjoy the drama.
(Written by Hwang and Ko Mi Rae)
- Look!
-  What? Where?
- Why?
-  Gosh, right there.
(Executive Producer Jung Ki Oh)
(Written by Hwang and Ko Mi Rae)
Ko Mi Rae, Ko Mi Rae, Ko Mi Rae!
Ko Mi Rae, Ko Mi Rae!
Ko Mi Rae, Ko Mi Rae! Ko Mi Rae!
Look! Right there!
Ko Mi Rae, Ko Mi Rae!
(Executive Producer Jung Ki Oh)
(Written by Hwang and Ko Mi Rae)
Kang Min Joo, answer your phone.
Producer Kang, did you watch the drama?
They just announced the title of the web comic with an official apology.
Are you out of your mind?
This isn't a personal broadcasting station. What were you thinking?
Hey, where's Min Joo?
Hurry up and contact her!
There's a situation where someone has to take responsibility.
Even if there's a cost to pay for doing so,
at least once in your life as a grown up,
it's not that bad to take action and initiative.
Hey, Min Joo! What's wrong with you? Why did you do that?
You didn't even discuss it with me beforehand.
Min Joo.
You must think you're something.
I'm sorry.
Forget the apology. Let's hear what your reason was for doing this.
As you all know,
the original writer tried to attempt suicide.
I no longer wanted to ignore a life and death situation.
Min Joo.
You've become quite arrogant over the years.
What will happen to Producer Kang now?
Isn't it obvious? She'll have to take disciplinary action for this.
Does that mean she might get fired?
Let's get back to work first, okay? We have our own TV drama to work on.
- Okay.
-  This came for us this morning.
What's this?
Woori City says they won't let us shoot there any more.
They told us to find another city or department to work with.
Is he serious?
- He's so stubborn.
-  I totally agree with you.
Goodness.
Hello, Deputy Mayor.
Fine.
Since you were so strong about not allowing the drama team to shoot,
I sent them back after signing the papers.
Yes, I've been confirmed of that.
You also said there's a lot to take care of.
You know Chief Shin Seok Ki, right?
- Yes.
-  Starting today, he's been...
appointed as the director of the culture and economy bureau.
He'll be working with us from now.
Oh, here he is.
How is everyone?
Goodness, you look well.
It's nice to see you again, Chief Ko.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes.
Me too.
Producer Kang.
We'll be cooperating with another department at Woori City.
I know that. But what happened to you?
I was told to behave and wait.
They will make whatever decision they need to.
How can you be so calm about this?
Don't tell me you're quitting.
I'm exhausted now. Let's talk later.
Min Joo.
You worked so hard to stand where you are now.
You've gone through so much worse than this,
including what happened to Eun Ho.
Young Ae.
You're the reason I didn't give up until now.
Are you going to...
waste all your hard work just because of this?
Min Joo.
I'll see you later.
We didn't even get to have a drink together.
Min Joo.
Producer Kang.
Goodness, you look well.
It's nice to see you again, Chief Ko.
I look forward to working with you.
Subsection Chief Ko. Let me ask you again.
Please answer the question.
Is it true that Officer Shin here accepted that money?
Yes, that is true.
You jerk!
Hey, are you really my boss?
You should take care of your workers like a real boss!
You crazy jerk!
How clean are you?
Do you think your hands are all white and clean?
Just wait and see. I'll come and get you once I get out of jail.
Let me go. Let me go.
You jerk. Let go.
Seeing that he's still around even after that,
it's clear that he's probably as dirty as he was before.
(SBC Drama with Woori City, "Love Is Bubbling Up")
Hello.
Please take this.
What's this?
You registered my name as the writer for that drama.
No, I can't accept this.
I did what I had to do. It's me who has to make an apology.
Don't say that. Here.
Thank you.
Wow.
- Cut.
-  Cut.
It was okay, but let's just try it one more time.
One more take.
Let's go.
Cut. Okay.
Okay. Location change.
Thank you for your work, everyone. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Give me a hand, Eun Ho.
Okay. I'm coming.
I can't wait to get married.
I envy you.
My girlfriend started working at SBC starting a few days ago.
She wants to be a producer like you.
I proposed to her before anyone else could take her away.
You should come to my wedding. Come and see my beautiful bride.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Hi.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
You caught me again.
I was just trying to go up there.
It's dangerous. You're even wearing a skirt.
But wasn't this built for people to go up and see anyway?
Am I wrong?
Goodness.
Be careful.
It's not even fully constructed yet, and you're even wearing a skirt.
Please stop nagging.
My goodness.
Are you all right?
It's cool.
It's incredible here. How wonderful.
I made it.
Really?
That's impressive.
Goodness.
There's also a bird cage.
I think it laid eggs.
The name of the mother bird is Young Hee.
Is the father bird Cheol Soo?
You know well.
Why didn't you give them sophisticated names?
How about Harry and Sally?
Then they'd always argue.
Did Young Hee and Cheol Soo live happily ever after?
How would I know?
How do you know Harry and Sally?
I watch movies, too.
By the way,
here you go.
What is it?
Your hairpin broke last time.
I watched your drama.
I told you to take responsibilities, not make trouble.
I wasn't confident enough to be responsible,
so I made trouble instead.
Why did you make such a bold decision?
If there aren't any expedients or settlements,
we have to follow the rules.
No matter how much I try to deny it,
the truth is always revealed.
To make up for what you did, are you unable to go to work?
The worst thing that could happen is getting fired.
It seems like you've led...
a very comfortable life.
That's not true.
Compared to others, it may be true.
Why did you move to this neighbourhood?
You could have stayed in Seoul.
Are you trying to threaten me to move out again?
May I come here sometimes?
Come here sometimes and take walks.
Don't do anything dangerous.
You may not go enter the fountain again.
And don't you dare come here alone.
Are you being concerned for me,
or are you concerned about this place?
Obviously...
It sounds better than telling me to move out immediately.
- Let's go down.
-  I want to stay longer.
I'm a busy man.
All right, you go down first.
Min Joo.
- I'm glad I bumped into you.
-  Hello.
Isn't the house great?
It's all right.
You seem to have aged compared to the last time I saw you.
You have more wrinkles. But I know you can't do anything about it.
- Pardon me?
-  This is...
a special gift for your moving here.
Try it.
What is it?
It...
tightens you up.
What?
What I mean is...
it really tightens you up.
How do I explain it?
It's a supplement that's good for women who had menopause.
No, thank you.
Please accept it. Try it.
It's effective when you eat it for a long time.
I see. Thank you.
Sure.
- See you.
-  Bye.
Who are you?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Hey!
Hey! My goodness.
Goodness.
It's my car.
It's my new car.
Your new car?
Gosh.
If you're not a thief, why did you sneak into my house?
Aren't you going to talk?
I'm sorry.
You've only been apologising.
What's this?
That's...
Tell your mum to come.
Call her.
I don't have a mum.
What?
I said I don't have a mum.
What's going on?
Dad.
Did you...
call him Dad?
Yes, she's my daughter.
Ye Ji, what happened?
I had left something at her place.
When I went inside to take it,
this old lady caught me.
How unlucky.
- What? "Old lady"?
-  What? "Unlucky"?
Let me see it.
Go inside.
Now.
Is she...
your daughter?
What happened here?
As you can see, it's a car I got today.
Your daughter dropped a flower pot on top and...
He had a daughter?
Goodness.
(This is for the precious you.)
"It strengthens the immune system..."
"of women with menopause..."
"and relieves stress."
Gosh.
What brings you here?
Did you fix the floor?
- Not yet.
-  I knew it.
It's all right. I'll do it. You can leave it.
What are neighbours for?
It's all right.
What happened to your finger?
- It's nothing.
-  There it is.
I sometimes get hurt when I cook, too.
- Have a seat.
-  I said I'm fine.
Come and have a seat.
Your kitchen sink needs to be fixed.
The living room floor that creaks also needs to be fixed.
I'll fix it right away.
Here you go.
Let me know if there's anything else you need to fix.
I said I'll do it.
You don't have a boyfriend, do you?
You should ask men to do that.
Goodness. That's why you don't have a boyfriend.
Goodness.
What brings you here?
It's because of your car.
- Sang Sik.
-  Hey.
Why are you here?
- I came to fix something for her.
-  I see.
There's...
a good mechanic nearby.
Call this number. I'm sorry about your new car.
What happened?
It's nothing.
Ye Ji is here.
Finish fixing it quickly so you can come join us for a meal.
Okay.
Jun Woo, you should go.
It's okay.
I said I'll do it.
I'll leave after fixing this.
It's so loud.
Let me see it.
What's the big deal?
- Why would you hide it?
-  Let it go.
Hey!
Why are you so loud?
- Let's go upstairs.
-  Okay.
Ye Ji.
Come and sit here.
Good luck. You'll be fine.
Give it back.
Great job, Ye Ji.
Why would you embarrass yourself just for these photos?
I didn't know anyone moved in already.
I left it at Jun Woo's place before.
Why did you hide it at that house?
I didn't leave it here because you don't respect my taste.
I'm going to subtract the cost...
of the car repair from your monthly allowance.
- Dad.
-  And this.
Just leave this book here.
I'm your only parent, okay?
Will you hide and keep secrets from me or not?
As long as you don't nag me.
Will you or not?
I won't.
All right.
Why is there so much?
Look at his silly hairstyle.
Goodness.
(House ghost)
(The Grim Reaper)
- Thank you.
-  Hey.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
Since I move too violently...
every night after class, all the beads on my nail chipped off.
Oh, my goodness.
This is your first time at our shop.
What do you do for a living?
I...
do this and that.
- Wow.
-  You must own many businesses.
That's not...
Yes, I do.
Your wife must be so happy.
I want to get married soon.
Being married isn't always a good thing.
Rather than regretting your marriage...
or getting a divorce,
being single is more peaceful.
You're alone in life anyway.
You must've gotten a divorce like me.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
It's okay.
At this age,
I don't want to work, and I also feel empty.
I kept losing confidence.
I came here thinking I should at least take care of my looks.
You still look young.
Really?
You don't have muscles compared to your looks.
Make time to stop by.
You have to exercise by making time, not when you have time.
I can see that.
Hey.
Did you take your car to the mechanic?
Hello? I'm talking to you.
Why are you dressed like that when it's hot outside?
I'm going to see a dermatologist.
What's wrong with your face? Did you eat something wrong?
You told me not to get involved with your family,
but your family gets involved with me. Do you know that?
What's wrong with...
Gosh.
It happened after I took these.
Your sister, Sang Hee, gave them to me.
Is she still selling these?
Give them back.
I'm going to ask the doctor if there are any side effects.
Wait, why did you take these?
It's because she gave them to me. She said it'll tighten...
Immune system? Stress?
Goodness.
Wait...
Gosh.
You didn't come home when I told you to.
Why did you give these to her when you know there are side effects?
The thing is, I couldn't help it.
What do you mean?
My husband has been working as a teacher for a while,
but he isn't getting promoted.
He doesn't really...
get along with his superiors, either.
You know that already.
So what?
The school principal's wife sells these,
so how can I not do anything?
Where's Cheon Soo?
I don't know. He gets off work late these days.
He also works out of town often.
He doesn't answer my calls.
Then why bother doing this for him?
It's because I love him.
I love him very much.
I did it because I wanted my family to live happily.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Uncle Sang Sik, what's going on?
Mum.
I think my acne is getting worse because of these.
When did you take them?
They're only for women.
Really?
Hello, Min Joo.
What's wrong with your face?
What happened?
What did I tell you? Since you don't date,
you have hormonal imbalance which causes the skin to break out.
That's not why.
Then how did it happen?
It's all because of my neighbour.
- Neighbour?
-  Yes.
My skin broke out, and my car broke.
I'm frustrated.
Why would a new car break?
I don't know.
- My gosh.
-  What happened to you?
What's that?
You startled me.
You scared me.
What are you doing these days?
What do you mean?
I'm busy teaching children at school.
You don't teach this late.
Go home. Be good to my sister...
I mean, to your wife, okay?
You're done for if I catch you cheating.
Why would I cheat?
Don't worry.
By the way,
did she get in trouble again?
Go in and ask her yourself.
Come and see Ye Ji at her final match.
No, it's okay. She'll win even if I'm not there.
- Oh, no.
-  Don't get rid of them.
- No.
-  Sir, please.
Posting these up here is illegal.
Be quiet.
If you won't help me take these down, leave.
- He's so terrible.
-  My gosh.
- You're so bossy.
-  Goodness.
Why you rascals...
- Goodness.
-  My gosh.
Why do they like them so much?
What are you doing?
Oh, it's you. I was checking the street.
You're checking what?
For a district government worker, all public service is my duty.
If illegal posters are on the walls in my district,
it's my job to take them off.
That's amazing.
They're the most popular these days.
Do you even know them?
Of course I do.
You're treating me like an old man.
These are tickets to the concert on this poster.
If you have time this Saturday, go with your daughter.
Why would an adult like you give these out?
The band members came to say hello and gave me...
these tickets to promote their concert.
You're also popular among young idol members, are you?
I'm giving these to you...
because your daughter came to apologise to me.
Ye Ji did?
She was polite.
Do you want them or not?
If it's this Saturday,
I can't go.
Ye Ji is entering the final round of an English contest.
She must be very smart.
Not only is she smart,
but she's also talented in extracurricular activities.
She's smart because she takes after me.
I see.
Then leave.
Okay.
It seems like your face got better. I could be wrong.
Let's go to that concert together.
Gosh.
What's wrong with your face?
You must be under a lot of stress these days.
("Pretending To Be an Adult")
"Pretending To Be an Adult".
Tickets to an idol group's concert in a book about adults seem ironic.
Let's go to the concert together.
Why would I go to this concert?
Instead of pretending to be an adult,
listening to music without thinking like children...
can be therapeutic.
You seem to be stressed from work.
Okay, we'll go.
Ye Ji.
Is it today?
How did you know, Dad?
Your uncle told me.
Today's the final round of your English contest.
I see.
Yes.
Why do you sound so weak?
Aren't you confident? Shall I come with you?
No, I'm leaving.
Ye Ji.
- You can do it.
-  You seem a little imbalanced.
You told me to live up to your words.
You can do it. I love you.
I love you.
Presentation is just as important for healthy desserts.
Food's first impression is its presentation, not the taste.
That way, when you actually take a bite,
you can impress your taste buds.
Let's wrap it up for today.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Here you are.
This is something.
- Is it good?
-  It's good.
Start selling these today!
Sang Sik, it's me.
Hi. What's going on?
Ye Ji...
has disappeared. It's her final match soon.
- What?
-  She was here a few minutes ago.
Are you with her now?
Call her friends right now and ask them where she is.
Are you serious?
Are you sure about this?
What do you mean? Why not?
I feel guilty.
If your Dad ever finds out, I'm doomed.
I like everything about you except for just one thing.
- You're too good.
-  Ouch.
Did you find her?
Where is she now?
Where?
No. I'll go myself.
(Standing concert)
It's sold out.
What do you mean it's all sold out?
I'm not here for the concert.
I'm just going to find someone in there and leave right away.
I'm sorry.
What should I do now?
I've been counting days for this.
But what else can you do? You should go now.
She's right. There's nothing you can do.
Why is my great grandfather getting married today?
Hurry up and go.
What should I do with my ticket?
Hello? Are you there?
Can you hear me?
Hello?
Welcome to the concert of VIXX, the group of the century.
You are now about to see them.
Are you ready?
It's so noisy here. Goodness.
- Oh, no.
-  Can you hear me?
Hello?
Okay.
Let's countdown together.
- Five.
-  Five.
- Four.
-  Four.
- Three.
-  Three.
- Two.
-  Two.
- One.
-  One.
Let's go.
- Goodness.
-  Seriously?
Wait, what are you doing here?
Are you okay?
- Goodness.
-  What?
(Second to Last Love)
You haven't dated anyone in a while, have you?
- Min Joo.
-  Who is he?
I thought you were on a date.
Who will I go on a date with at my age?
Why not? If you like someone, you should date them.
This is much more complicated than that!
Lower your voice!
I really can't do this any more!
Do you want to join me for a drink?
- I love you
-  I love you.
- You spit on me.
-  My goodness.
My gosh.
It must've been hard living alone.
What does she know?
You must be lonely.
I don't like playing hard to get like the kids do nowadays.
Min Joo.
You're going out with me starting today.