- My gosh.
-  Can you hear me? Hello?
Hello?
Okay. Let's count down together.
- Five.
-  Five.
- Four.
-  Four.
- Three.
-  Three.
- Two.
-  Two.
- One.
-  One.
- My goodness.
-  Gosh.
What? What are you doing here?
Are you all right?
This is tonight's opening couple. Congratulations.
No way.
- Congratulations.
-  Congratulations.
- We'll guide you to the stage.
-  No.
- Why? Why?
-  Come with us.
- Wait.
-  Come this way.
Ye Ji! Ye Ji!
Are you all right?
What is going on?
We're doing the opening show.
What?
Please start us off with an opening dance.
- Dance!
-  Dance!
Come on. Let's get it over with so we can go back down.
Are you telling me to dance here?
What else can we do?
Hurry up.
How should I do it?
Wow.
Hurry up and get us down!
I was scared to death.
How can a woman have no fear?
What are you doing here anyway?
What about you?
Sang Sik. Min Joo.
What are you doing here?
It just turned out that way.
Dad.
Ye Ji.
Hello, I'm Ye Ji's friend, Kim Hyun Seok.
Come with me.
Let go of me.
This is so embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
How can you come all the way here?
You have the final English contest today. Why are you here?
Because I didn't want to go there, and I wanted to come here.
Are you joking me?
Just leave me alone.
You're pressuring me.
How dare you!
Do you know why you're so obsessed with me?
What? Obsessed?
It's because you don't date.
You should give all that energy and interest to your lover.
Since you don't have one, you're bothering me.
You need to focus on your own life now.
Just leave me alone!
Are you serious?
- Come on.
-  Let me go.
- That's enough.
-  Just let me go.
This is family business. You should step out.
Sang Sik.
Gosh, the concert is going to be over soon.
Hello.
Your name is Ye Ji, right?
Get out of my way.
I think it would be best for you to talk to your dad first.
This is so annoying.
Uncle Jun Woo, is this your girlfriend?
What?
If she is, take her away and shut her mouth.
- What?
-  Hey!
That little...
We have no choice. Just say that she dropped out.
If you found her,
you should try and persuade her.
It's no use. I know her. She's my daughter, after all.
All right.
I'll tell them that she withdrew.
Okay.
Gosh.
(Second to Last Love)
(Episode 04)
Ye Ji, didn't you have the English competition today?
- I gave up.
-  Ye Ji.
You're the guy who bought the ticket earlier, right?
Are they your friends?
Yes, Dad.
Dad?
No way. How can your dad come to a place like this?
Bo Gyeong had to leave because something came up,
and he bought her ticket to go in.
Really?
My dad's a music lover.
He has countless LPs at home.
Isn't that right, Dad?
Yes, sure.
Your dad is so awesome.
You're so cool.
- Buy us pizza!
-  Buy us pizza!
- Pizza.
-  Pizza? Okay.
- It looks delicious.
-  Wow.
Please have a slice.
Dad, you should have some.
It's all right, you guys have it.
- Thank you for the food.
-  Thank you.
Thank you, Sir.
To be honest, who do you think is the most handsome in the group?
I want to hear a guy's opinion.
My dad's not that big of a fan.
Why not? If he likes them enough to come to a concert,
I bet he knows their names.
Actually, he came to...
Ye Ji.
I promise to study them before coming next time.
I'll read their profiles beforehand.
What's gotten into you?
The next concert is in Busan, though.
- Right?
-  Are you going to go?
Sure. Why not?
- I'm so jealous.
-  I'm jealous.
Stop making fun of me.
I wanted to dance well up there, too.
You were good.
You're a dancing queen compared to Sang Sik.
I'm pretty bad myself, but he was...
Didn't it still help with getting rid of your stress?
- I guess it did.
-  See? Wasn't it a good idea?
Was her name Ye Ji?
She's not your ordinary kid. She's feisty.
She still grew up well.
They say daughters need a mother's care.
What happened to her mother?
Her mother...
died after giving birth to Ye Ji.
She was such a wonderful person.
Sang Sik had it tough.
How long have the two of you known each other?
Well, from when we were really young.
This is my hometown, and I used to live here too...
until I immigrated to Canada.
You said you studied there, right?
More so wander around than study.
Now let's talk about you.
What about me?
Why are you unmarried and still single?
Do you dislike men?
Men are great.
But at this age,
it's hard to meet someone.
Your age?
If he's a good catch, he's either already married...
or is with someone else.
I need someone who I can communicate with.
It's hard to find good conversational partners.
I had a good time thanks to you.
Does that mean it was a successful date?
If we walk around like this,
everyone would think that I'm the aunt and you're my nephew.
How about this then?
You don't like it?
My goodness.
What about this? Do you like it?
You must watch a lot of dramas.
It's from a documentary.
I don't like to play love games.
Let's...
date.
What?
What...
do you like about me?
When you like someone, you just like everything about them.
You don't pick and choose what to like.
It's not something you can pinpoint.
Well, you can start pinpointing now.
You should be more picky.
I don't want to. That means I don't like you.
If you do this again, I won't let you off so easy.
I won't get caught next time.
How can you say that?
I didn't get an answer yet.
That's enough joking around. Go inside.
Goodnight.
Hey.
She was your girlfriend after all. I was right.
What are you doing in front of the house?
I didn't do anything thanks to the two of you.
Gosh.
I saw your drama. I told you to be responsible, not make trouble.
Why did you make such a bold decision?
If there aren't any expedients or settlements,
we have to follow the rules.
To make up for what you did, are you unable to go to work?
Hey, Ye Ji. Goodnight.
- Sweet dreams.
-  I'm off to bed.
I told you not to drink from the bottle.
You can drink from the purifier.
- Don't you have a girlfriend?
-  Don't joke around.
You should go on blind dates while you're still young.
I should work harder to support you while I'm young.
I won't be able to work later.
I can take care of myself.
Do you call today taking care of yourself?
I know you had high expectations for the English contest,
but the one I was up against is the kid who always comes in second.
Don't tell me you did this on purpose.
That kid is a lot more desperate than I am.
That's when I knew that I lost already.
What's that?
I'm interested in a lot more stuff other than math or English.
The world is a huge place, and there are so many interesting things.
What will you become?
What I become isn't important. How I live is what's important.
My goodness.
I can take care of myself.
But you need someone to go to the hospital with.
Watch what you're saying.
I won't bother you when I'm old. Enough nonsense. Go to bed.
You'll be so lonely sitting alone on my wedding day.
You little...
(Resignation letter)
(By admitting to plagiarising the web comic, I have damaged...)
Let's see.
In a month, I normally use about...
2,000 to 3,000 dollars.
If I send my parents money,
in a year, it'll cost...
The insurance plan costs me...
Is this all?
I'll be penniless in five years.
By then, my age will be...
Gosh.
I'm so embarrassed.
Why did you come so late? You're so bothersome.
I couldn't sleep.
You must still be young.
Right.
Why didn't you go on your blind date?
I put in all that effort.
Hey, it's you again.
We're about to close.
Really?
The lights were still on.
You can't even drink. Why are you out at this hour?
Did you make up with your daughter?
There's nothing to make up.
She doesn't listen as she gets older.
She's all grown up. Why would she listen to you?
It's her life.
She should lead it herself.
You've never been married, have you?
Not...
yet.
Don't say that if you're not a parent yourself.
She may look big, but she's still a child.
She doesn't know anything about life.
Still, you shouldn't intrude so much.
She'll only get delinquent if you do.
Kids these days are different from us.
You don't even have a kid. What do you know?
You're a real stuck up.
What?
To me,
she looks like a perfectly healthy teenage girl.
It's normal for girls her age to like concerts.
Her life won't change just because she missed one contest.
Are you serious?
Do you think all I do is make her study?
You know, ageing is not all that bad.
I get to feel and understand things I never got to before.
That's why I like it.
I'm talking about the things we didn't see in our 20s and 30s.
Right, but there are things you can't see any more with age.
I thought it might get on your shirt.
Yes, thank you.
Do you want to drink together?
They don't have any customers, and it's just us.
Okay. One drink won't hurt.
I like this music.
I think I still like the music from our time.
It'll stray away now
Deep into the back of our memories
- The conversations we've had
-  The conversations we've had
- Still stay in my heart
-  Still stay in my heart
- Now it'll leave me
-  Now it'll leave me
- With a memory and a smile
-  With a memory and a smile
- Just like a sunset
-  Just like a sunset
- I love you
-  I love you
- I only have you in this world
-  In this world
- I scream my lungs out
-  I scream my lungs out
- But only the sunset answers back
-  But only the sunset answers back
That's how it is.
I can't tell which idol is which these days.
When I was in school,
I used to know all the foreign bands like Scorpions, Air Supply,
Pink Floyd and Bon Jovi.
I can't keep up any more.
That's why...
your daughter thinks you're old and calls you an old man.
Don't you know how popular old man jokes are these days?
"Old man jokes"?
If I peel a banana,
would you find me appealing?
Hold on.
Aren't you glad...
I have an orange?
Guess what time it is in Indonesia.
Indonesia?
Is it 4pm?
How do you say you're not sure in Japanese?
I'm confused.
What about in Chinese?
That's it.
- Tilting.
-  Tilting!
What about in French?
- It's vague.
-  In German?
It's uncertain.
What about in Ghana?
Ghana?
I don't know.
- You just spat on me.
-  My goodness.
- Gosh.
-  I'm sorry.
I already know all this, but why is it still so funny?
That's what I'm saying.
Gosh.
I think we drank too much.
You're right.
Actually,
I've never been as...
scared and uncertain...
about the future like today.
Are you talking about retirement?
Yes.
Retirement.
I made...
so many decisions until now.
I had self-respect...
for coming all the way here. On the other hand,
I asked myself if that's as far as I can go.
I also felt shameful.
It's best to believe that all of your choices were right.
If you don't, you won't have anything left behind.
I guess so.
Pay the bill and come out.
Me?
I'm a poor civil servant.
You should pay since you earn so much money.
I might become jobless soon.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
What the...
You're not...
giving me a piggyback, are you?
Are you confused again?
You're too old to carry with my arms.
Too old? What kind of old person does this?
I'm so good at drinking.
I've never once lost...
a drinking competition with men.
I would walk home straight and sleep on my bed.
Sure you did.
It's because you got too old.
Old?
My brain stopped ageing at the age of 30,
and my heart stopped at 20.
When did I become an adult?
Why are you mumbling into my ear? That's ticklish.
Are we far away?
We're almost there.
Then let me down.
Also, let's consider that this never happened. Okay?
My goodness.
It must have been tough for you to be alone.
It's hard as it is for me to take care of myself.
What do you know?
You must be lonely.
(Resignation letter)
No, stop...
- I only have you in this world
-  I only have you in this world
Why are you mumbling into my ear?
My goodness!
Gosh.
Why did I do that?
What is this?
I tried making it the way you told me yesterday.
Really?
It's too salty.
What should I do?
Preparing the shellfish is the most important.
Seafood is already salty.
They cook at different times, so you also have to put them in order.
Try it.
It's so delicious.
- Wow.
-  You dance well,
but your cooking is horrible.
What did you say?
I told you, didn't I?
She's Uncle Jun Woo's girlfriend.
Let's slice this zucchini now.
Why is she here?
Goodness. What is going on over there?
Why are you up at this hour?
I heard Jun Woo made spicy fish soup.
Jun Woo! What are you doing?
I'm hungry. Let's eat now.
What brings you here at this early hour?
I'm here because I don't want to eat alone!
Oh, right. Is your face all right?
It's better now.
What are you two talking about?
This family loves trouble.
Ye Ji crashed her car, Sang Hee ruined her face,
and I...
We're such troublemakers. Gosh, I'm hungry.
Hey, come in.
It's good to see all of your family members eating together.
There are so many of us, right? Please have a seat here.
Yes, thank you.
Hello.
Gosh, I'm relieved. Your face looks so much better now.
I went through so much trouble thanks to you.
Things always get worse before they get better.
It's part of the detoxification process, not a side effect.
Shut it.
Just eat your food.
Okay.
By the way, why does everyone seem so uneasy today?
Well, if it's because of me...
Gosh, don't say that.
Everyone, I have an important announcement to make.
Her name is Kang Min Joo. Her age is...
Why are you doing this?
Let's move on. She's a producer at the drama department at SBC.
Seriously? You're a drama producer?
Oh, my. That's so cool.
Ye Ji, I'll tell you more about those things later.
So what's the announcement?
Min Joo...
is my girlfriend as of today.
What did you just say?
So it'd be greatly appreciated if all of you can be considerate...
and respectful towards her.
All right, let's applaud.
Wait a second.
What is the matter with you?
It's all right. There's nothing wrong with it.
It's not all right at all.
Gosh, what is going on here?
My name is Kang Min Joo, and I moved to the house next door recently.
Many things have happened already, but I hope all of us can get along.
I'll see you later.
Wait, Min Joo.
You literally just met her. Do you date anyone you meet?
She's not anyone.
Min Joo!
Wait, Min Joo.
How can you do that?
You didn't consider my opinion or feelings at all.
They're like family to me.
I apologise if I upset you. I was just...
Forget it.
I don't know what I did to make you get the wrong message,
but stop this nonsense already.
Goodness.
I'm in a bind.
Gosh!
Goodness gracious.
All right.
Excuse me.
- Me?
-  Do you see anyone else?
What is it?
Ride your bicycle carefully when you pass by people.
That's a bicycle lane. You should walk on the pavement.
It's narrow, so I...
Well, I guess not everyone can walk on that lane.
What are you talking about?
"Do you date anyone you meet?"
Am I a pebble everyone stumbles upon on the street or what?
You must've come across as so easy.
That's why you got drunk and got dragged into that situation.
What did you just say?
You passed out because you can't even drink well.
I have no idea how you've been able to live alone all these years.
I can't believe it. It's a mystery.
I know I drank with you once, but that doesn't mean...
you can think of me as a joke.
- What?
-  Guys must like me...
because I'm still quite attractive.
I can't really stop guys from falling for me.
Don't you think so?
Gosh!
Look at you. Is this how you snatch guys?
Gosh, that woman!
Goodness.
- Hey.
-  What's going on?
Where are my team members?
Gosh, you startled me.
Just fire me. I don't want to do my team members any harm!
What are you talking about? It's a considerate gesture.
They didn't even want it! It's abuse of authority.
I stopped them from transferring you to the branch in the countryside.
All right. I'll just quit, then.
Wait, Min Joo!
They'll fire me if you quit.
No one is as capable as you are.
That's also why I'm able to keep my position.
You know that I've done more than enough.
I think my passion for making dramas is going away, too.
And to be honest, I'm not as energetic as I used to be.
We need an explanation for the plagiarised drama.
I completely understand how you're feeling.
You did the right thing. I'm not saying what you did is wrong.
Come up with an idea for a drama that people will love.
Then everything will go back to normal as if nothing happened.
I made so many decisions until now.
I had self-respect...
for coming all the way here. On the other hand,
I asked myself if that's as far as I can go.
I also felt shameful.
Don't get all emotional and submit a letter of resignation.
Just put up with it and don't quit.
That's not losing. Look at the bigger picture.
Come in, Chief Ko.
I summoned you urgently because I have something to tell you.
- Have a seat.
-  Okay.
The business support department should be in charge...
of managing all events related to Woori Grape Festival.
The local tourism department will work on site at the events.
Hang on. My department came up with the idea for the festival.
I know, but the situation has changed due to the merger, though.
The merger?
My department's plan for the festival was chosen,
so my team should be in charge of managing the events.
I know how hard your team members worked for it.
You're probably reacting like this because of the incentive.
Let's revisit the issue after the festival.
Head Chief.
Compensating the employees for their hard work is very important.
However, what is more important is...
the fact that no one else knows the information my team shared...
and what they did for the residents better than my team members do.
Such knowledge can't be fully transferred.
Lower your voice!
How dare you raise your voice in front of the deputy mayor?
Send all files related to Woori Grape Festival...
to the business support department.
Chief. I thought we were in charge of the project.
Why should we? This is ridiculous.
We skipped our vacations and pulled numerous all-nighters for that.
To contribute to enriching the local community...
You think I don't know that?
Let's be grateful that the festival isn't being cancelled.
Preventing damage to the residents...
is more important than getting our team's work recognised.
Still, this is crazy.
Oh, you're here.
- Producer Kang.
-  Producer Kang.
- Tidy up and clean the space.
-  Okay.
All right. Our lives depend on coming up with good ideas.
- All of you are aware, right?
-  How can they do this?
The company should thank us for sending out the notice.
How can they demote us?
Exactly. Someone is obviously responsible for all of this mess.
This isn't a demotion.
Are you belittling the strategic planning team?
We're so happy that Producer Kang is here now.
I agree. Both Strategic Planning Team 1 and 2 are doing so well.
It's always our team that gets in trouble.
- It is obviously a demotion.
-  Goodness.
Hey, explain to her so that she understands. Have a good day.
Have a good day.
Gosh, that sly slacker.
Goodness.
We just need to plan a good project.
As you get older,
the distinction between good and bad becomes increasingly vague.
Please move over.
Sir!
- Gosh!
-  What are you doing now?
Being righteous puts you at a disadvantage.
If you're prickly, you get hammered.
If you fall victim to injustice after doing something right,
you compromise your principles in order to survive...
and say that it's the reality to make yourself feel better.
Until when...
Until when do I have to live as an adult like this?
(To Min Joo, I'm sorry.)
Jun Woo!
Could I get her bill?
Is this all?
This is her fifth order.
Jun Woo, I'll explain.
I tried ordering everything on the menu, but nothing is good.
I was going to force myself to eat, but the dishes taste so horrible.
You can put it on my card.
I will, but we unfortunately have to...
put this customer's name on our hotel's blacklist.
Your blacklist?
- That's crazy. What did I do?
-  Sit down.
Take this and buy whatever you want to eat,
whether it's street food or something from a hotel restaurant.
I didn't ask you for money! I just want to eat something you made.
I can't do that for you any more.
How can you do this to me?
I've become anorexic because I have not been able to eat your food.
You always call me for help when you get yourself in trouble.
I'm so tired of this now.
- Jun Woo.
-  There's someone I like.
So don't call me any more.
What?
I'll change my phone number, too.
No, don't do that. Don't!
Be responsible for your own life from now on, please.
Jun Woo! Jun Woo!
Tae Yeon.
- Yes.
-  We talked about your profession.
So is that how old you're turning this year?
Is that all you want to know about me?
You keep asking me my age.
Well...
I'm sorry, but I will get going now.
No, I'll get going first.
I'll get the bill.
Goodness. What is this ridiculous situation?
Gosh.
Did you say that someone stopped by?
Yes. He said that we have to take meticulous care of this car...
because the owner of this car is very fussy.
And who is that?
Mr Ko Sang Sik who works at the city hall.
I'll call you when everything is done, including polishing.
You can pick it up then.
I fought the urge to submit my letter of resignation.
Thank you.
I guess you worry about anyone you meet.
Ma'am! I'll get what he's eating. A large size, please!
Chief.
What is it?
I don't think I can ever become a public official like you.
Why would you want to become like me?
You always go by the book, and you're known as a man of integrity.
You're like the most ideal public official.
You even know how to butter up people now.
Why did you decide to take the civil service exam?
You used to be in a different line of work.
Because of the stable monthly salary. Are we good now?
What kind of work did you do before, then?
Don't waste your time asking about useless things.
Just take good care of the farmers participating in the festival.
What's this?
All public officials get seven dollars per each meal,
but you ordered the large-sized portion.
He's really something.
This one is much better.
What brings you here?
I'm here to take a look at kitchen supplies, as well.
Do you really think this one is better?
Yes. It suits your kitchen much better.
Okay. It's so convenient to have someone who decides things for me.
I have good taste.
Well, did you get my text?
Yes.
I'm sorry. I sincerely apologise.
Well, it actually didn't upset me too much.
But I wasn't thrilled, either.
What is it, then?
I'm just saying that it's better than having...
nothing happen.
Why did you decide to take the civil service exam?
What kind of work did you do before, then?
Hurry up! Get out of here now!
Don't let go of my hand!
(Operating Room)
Thank you for today.
You picked out the dishes for me...
- and carried them for me, as well.
-  It's my pleasure.
I hope every day can be like today.
Then I'll think of you...
like a little brother and talk casually to you now.
Then we'll become close more quickly.
You should go in.
Hey, Eun Ho. Look.
Isn't this such a great purchase?
I picked it out for you.
I have good taste.
- Come in, guys.
-  Look at the actor here.
There we go.
What are all those?
The farmers who are participating in the festival sent them for us...
to taste the grapes to thank us.
Return them immediately.
- Pardon me?
-  If you want to taste them,
pay for them during the festival.
How can you bring these here?
Has he lost his mind or what?
It's not like these cost tens of thousands of dollars.
We carried them all the way here.
Return them to the farmers right away.
Yes, sure thing.
- Hurry up.
-  Goodness.
Grape Festival?
Yes. It's organised by Woori City,
and they want to invite the actor.
So what's been decided?
He has a shoot around there anyway,
so he'll stop by the event and do an autograph signing.
He'll also participate in the grape stomping event.
- He'll do that?
-  Yes.
- That's awesome.
-  Producer Gang!
My surname is Kang, not Gang.
Well, you're as ruthless as a gangster when it comes to scripts.
I heard the bad news, though.
Because of the plagiarism incident,
I heard you got transferred to the strategic planning team.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work with Mr Han.
You can talk to me from now on.
What?
Gosh, why do we keep running into each other?
If you patronise me again,
I'm transferring to another broadcasting station.
You'll be patronised at other places if you don't change.
How could you say something so offensive that easily?
The emotions of the female character are fake.
- It just doesn't make sense.
-  You've never dated, have you?
You aren't dating now, are you?
It's been a while since you've dated, right?
That's why you say such a thing.
What did you say?
Gosh.
Min Joo, are you getting off work?
Wow, he's so handsome.
Is that a camping vehicle everyone dreams of?
Who is he?
He's...
That's why I'm so impeccable.
I know exactly when to appear.
Why did you bring this car?
Are you speaking to me casually now?
Does it make you uncomfortable?
No, I like how friendly it sounds.
You asked me where to find ingredients.
Today's the day.
Can we also get ingredients that have strange names?
Of course.
Why do we need this car when we're shopping for groceries?
This is for work.
I've travelled all over the country with this car.
A wanderer who stays at other people's houses?
You could say that.
Look at him with his family.
You mean Sang Sik?
Of course.
We go on a trip together sometimes.
Do you want to join?
No thanks.
Where's the market?
We're almost there.
Don't worry too much.
Once customers find out about you through this festival,
you'll be able to sell other related items.
We're also making long-term plans,
so it's important to make the festival successful.
Without this festival, we would have thrown away all these grapes.
We'll trust and follow you.
Please help us out.
You're the ones helping me out.
Come on, Ma'am.
Show us the ones you've hidden.
Be quiet.
I'll sell these first.
Didn't your granddaughter like the cake I baked?
That's right.
Wait a moment.
You're so good.
These dates with seeds are sweeter and tastier.
Dates?
It's a dried date.
Let's see.
This is the one.
Who is she?
Oh, isn't she pretty?
Is she your aunt?
How can you sell a lot when you say things like that?
Chief Ko.
Yes?
What are you doing?
It's a photo that proves we're working outside.
You look great in that hat.
Gosh.
Focus on your work.
Chief Ko, try this. It's so delicious.
No thanks.
You told me to check everything.
You have to try it to know it's the best quality.
What are you doing?
The skin is more nutritious.
Goodness.
Chief Ko, come over here.
What is it this time?
Hurry up.
What's going on?
What?
Stop it.
Didn't you see the valve?
I can't see anything.
Move out of the way.
- Move out of the way.
-  How nice.
It's so refreshing.
What's going on? What are you doing?
You already turned it off.
What?
Oh, no, you're all wet.
Wasn't it really refreshing, though?
It was very refreshing.
Aren't you too wet?
What are you looking at?
I didn't look at anything.
She's so exhausting.
I'm playing hard to get right now.
What's with the face?
"It's natural for an older woman to like a handsome young man."
Is that why?
What's wrong with that?
Don't worry. I won't refer to you as an older woman.
I'm an old lady.
Old lady? That's not bad. It sounds quite friendly.
Someone must really want to talk to you.
Is it your girlfriend?
I hate being misunderstood.
I'm popular, but I don't date two people at once.
I don't think two people would suffice for you.
I only like one person right now.
If you continue, it'll get uncomfortable between us.
Why will it be uncomfortable?
It's a teacher and student relationship.
I'm teaching you how to cook.
Right.
Does that mean there will be a difference in status, too?
Then there's too many obstacles between us.
Gosh.
Do you take the bus here?
Yes.
Chief Ko.
How do I look?
The hat is a little too big.
Gosh.
Chief Ko.
When you interviewed me,
what was your first impression of me?
Why do you ask that?
I'm just curious.
I thought you'd be...
meticulous and hard-working.
I'm not talking about that.
Did I seem cold, intelligent,
or thoughtful? I'm talking about that kind of stuff.
I see.
I thought you'd be meticulous and smart.
Goodness.
Sang Sik.
Hello.
Hello, Song Yi.
I like you, Chief Ko.
What?
Hello.
Hello, you must be returning from somewhere.
- Yes.
-  It's for the Grape Festival.
We were preparing for it.
Are you coming from somewhere?
We went out to relax.
Are you two on a date right now?
Was she the employee who gave you a bouquet in front of your house?
Yes.
Really?
People might think you're dating someone your daughter's age.
What?
Why not?
What do you mean?
I thought you were on a date after receiving a bouquet.
It wasn't a date. We were out for work.
You seemed quite close.
Speak for yourself.
Me? What about me?
Come on, Sang Sik.
Never mind.
What's wrong with spending time with someone like her?
- What did you say?
-  She's not underage.
She confessed her love to you by giving you a bouquet.
Who would I date at my age?
What's wrong with that age? Why isn't it possible?
Gosh.
You can date if you like each other.
What's wrong with that?
You're getting worse.
Family is important, but your life is more so.
- Don't you think?
-  Of course.
What?
Chief Ko, we checked all the received goods.
Thank you.
Did you see the weather forecast?
Yes.
It's supposed to rain.
Why would it rain when it's so sunny out?
We don't know when it'll shower,
so prepare the tents.
Prepare enough raincoats and umbrellas, too.
Here. Stick this on the back of your car.
What is this?
Chief Ko brought it for me to stick it on your car for free.
I wanted to let you know.
(This car was just washed. Keep a safe distance.)
Please come to today's Grape Festival.
Hey.
Oh, hey. Hello.
Hello.
You must be very busy.
Everyone was excited about a celebrity coming today,
but he can't make it.
Have a good day.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Never mind. Bye.
(This car was just washed. Keep a safe distance.)
I don't like her every time I see her.
I just have a bad feeling about her.
(Woori Grape Festival 2016)
He was supposed to come,
- but he didn't.
-  I know.
Did they trick us or what? There's nothing to see here.
- We came here to see him.
-  I know.
Did they lie to us?
How long do I have to wait?
Min Joo.
You should go in. What are you doing here?
I was doing a dessert tasting event here today.
Really? Is it finished?
People snatched the dessert so quickly,
but the festival isn't over yet.
Is that so?
This wine was made with the grapes from our city.
- I really like its fragrance.
-  Thank you.
Chief Ko.
Come here and have a drink.
It's okay, I'm fine.
Deputy Mayor Na, please pose for the camera.
Please take a photo of us.
(Experience grape stomping)
What are you doing?
Are you going to do this?
Yes, it looks fun.
Put them on and come in.
Everyone, come in here.
Mothers, come in with your children. Over here.
Over here.
- It's fun.
-  Come in.
- Come and stomp the grapes.
- It's fun.
-  Come in.
Come over here and try it. It's fun.
Come in.
Don't just watch. Please join us.
Be careful. You might get hurt.
Be careful.
(Woori Grapes)
It's suddenly raining.
Come this way.
(Woori Grape Festival 2016)
Come and take a raincoat.
- Everyone, come here.
-  Come and take a raincoat.
- Here.
-  Take a raincoat.
I knew this would happen.
What do we do? Customers left because the celebrity didn't come.
What if the festival we prepared...
turns out in vain?
This is held by a different department anyway.
They'll take responsibility if it fails.
They'll probably blame us for it.
They made us work so hard for the festival.
How horrible.
- Goodness.
-  My gosh.
Are you all right?
- You're soaking wet.
-  I'm all right.
I'm worried about the festival because of the weather.
Don't worry too much.
The basic events of the festival are finished.
What remains is the sales.
You should leave first. I'll report to you after I wrap it up.
- All right, please take care of it.
-  Certainly.
Please hurry up.
I'll go help them now.
Go ahead.
- Did you get soaking wet?
-  I'm all right.
Sang Sik must have worked hard to prepare this.
Your phone is ringing.
I'll go look around over there.
What should we do?
You should go if it's an urgent matter.
I'll stay until the rain stops.
I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. I'm fine.
Then I'll call you later.
What are you doing here? You should leave.
Is this all you have to take care of?
It's dangerous. You should leave.
Let me help you.
I'm done.
Gosh.
- Put this on.
-  It's okay.
Put it on. Just listen to me.
- I said I'm fine.
-  Here.
Chief Ko, please come this way.
Okay.
Leave now.
(Daegok Village Vineyard)
- Can you hold it?
-  Okay.
- I'm going to that side.
Are you finished with everything?
What are you still doing here?
Can you leave now?
Of course.
Let's go together.
I'm already wet anyway.
This won't work.
Why not?
You can date if you like each other.
What's wrong with that age? Why isn't it possible?
Family is important, but your own life is more so.
What are you doing?
Run!
(Second to Last Love)
Don't make me a swindler when I'm not.
Don't do anything. It's my work.
Why do you treat me so strictly?
Otherwise, you'll make trouble everywhere.
You must've fallen for Min Joo on the day she moved.
No, even before then.
I'm being honest.
What is this?
What's wrong with me?
If you don't do anything,
nothing will ever happen.