I can...
certainly look after a garden.
I moved all the way here because I wanted to try these things.
Like this.
Why was I so busy...
when I was young...
to try anything?
Now, I've become an adult who can't challenge herself...
because she's afraid of what other people would think.
People keep looking at me.
Don't worry about other people.
Who cares if they look?
Starting now, you're the centre of the world.
And then you do this.
Lift it up.
Like this?
Yes.
Gosh.
Goodness.
I can't do it.
It's okay. Try one more time.
You're doing well.
Be careful.
This is so fun.
Try it again.
Let's go.
This is great.
(Second to Last Love)
- Are you all right?
-  I'm going to be sore later.
You could've done better if you weren't so scared.
Do you want to come again tomorrow?
No, I really can't do it.
Right.
I have cooking class today.
Cooking class?
- You're teaching?
-  Yes.
We're having a dessert party later.
I'm sorry I took so much of your time.
No, it's you who made time for me.
You should come. I know you wanted to learn cooking.
It's okay. I don't have the time and I'm busy.
Is that the reason why you never got to try what you wanted?
You brought this out...
because you don't want to live like that any more.
You're right, but it's really hard to do.
Just take baby steps and take it easy.
You'll regret it if you push it to later again.
My dad bought it three years ago when he was interested in cameras,
but he didn't even take pictures of my graduation. It's almost new.
Three years? That's old. I'll give you 350 dollars.
Is he crazy?
Does he know how much this is?
Go buy it from someone else.
420 dollars.
500 dollars. That's the lowest I can go.
Thank you so much for coming all the way here.
I'm so lucky to have a good neighbour. Now, Hoon has a teacher.
Oh, it's nothing. Is he inside?
Of course. He's been waiting for you.
Hoon, your tutor is here.
- Hello.
-  Hello, you must be Hoon.
Do you take after your dad? You're very handsome.
I take after my mum.
I see.
We're very lucky to have her, so you better behave.
All right.
I'll go get you some fruits.
- Make yourself at home.
-  Okay.
- Please sit here.
-  No, I'll just sit here.
What is this?
The lens...
You broke it.
Why did you put it there?
Pay me 53 dollars to fix it.
No discounts.
Hey!
- Hello.
-  Welcome.
It's so hot.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
-  How are you?
Are you waiting for someone?
- How did you know?
-  Don't you know me?
I can tell how you're feeling just by looking at your shadow.
Min Joo promised to come.
Our neighbour?
Are you two really dating?
If she shows up today,
I hope to make today our first day.
- The first day?
-  The first day of going out.
If she comes today,
it means that today is the first day of our relationship.
Why do people care about those things?
And why do they count such number of days?
How do you define a beginning of a relationship?
Do couples try to come to an agreement if they think differently?
Can you just pick any day you want?
Yes, that's exactly what I did. Are we good now?
I'm a fool for telling you these things.
Gosh, you little...
I see some new plants. Did you buy them?
I did, of course. Do you think they just sprang out of the ground?
My goodness!
- Move over, please.
-  Gosh, seriously.
Hey. It's you, Mi Rae.
Hi!
What... What brings you here?
Why do you think I'm here?
I came to see Jun Woo.
Have you had dinner yet?
Yes.
Oh, aren't you going to Uncle Jun Woo's dessert party today?
Just focus on one thing at a time,
whether it's studying or exercising.
What now?
I'm done!
Ever since she moved up to grade eight, she's turned into a brat.
We have a member whose birthday is today,
so we'll make desserts that are perfect for birthday parties.
Who's going to assist me today?
Over there. The new member.
Come on out. I won't give you difficult tasks since you're new.
Go on.
I haven't seen Jun Woo's desserts in so long.
Ji Sun. Jun Woo's class began, so I should get going now.
Sure. See you later.
It's delicious.
We have to save these desserts for the party later.
There are so many of them. I'll just eat one.
I don't want to be petty about food, either.
But if Jun Woo finds out...
Just tell him that I'm here.
I won't interrupt his class.
These are mined carrots and pecans.
This is coconut.
If you use these ingredients together,
the texture and the nutty taste...
will be greatly enhanced.
Due to the texture of carrots,
even those who dislike the sweet taste of carrots will like this.
Please add soy milk in it instead of milk.
Gosh! Oh, no!
Okay, I got it! Goodness.
How much soy milk should I add?
Three cups, please.
Sure!
What in the world are you doing here now?
You actually changed your phone number.
That's why I'm here.
Don't you have any pride?
I told you that you're being a nuisance to me.
It's that woman, isn't it?
- What?
-  You said you're seeing someone.
The one who was assisting you.
I could tell from the way you were looking at her.
I mean, how would I not know?
Just bear with me for just a month.
A month?
My old agency got in touch with me.
I'm going to go back to modelling...
and walk the runways again.
So let me stay here for just one month.
I'll just stay by your side.
Think of me as a part-time helper.
You're going to work here for a month?
Leave immediately and don't come back ever again.
I might actually call the police if you show up like this again.
If you hate me that much, just be nice to me so that I'd leave sooner.
You're a jerk.
You're so horrible.
Jun Woo.
People are waiting. Come on.
All right.
I'll be right there.
Sorry.
I apologise.
Don't worry. It's okay.
She's pretty, but she looks a bit old.
Excuse me.
Were you just talking about me?
Did you finish reading that?
Yes.
Then I'll take it.
Wait, I'm not sure if you can take that with you.
I'm a fan of his.
Do you like this guy?
Pardon me?
Have you tried soy sauce bibimbap?
It's his speciality.
No.
What about bulgogi japchae?
I haven't tried that, either.
Okay.
Look.
Why are you asking me those things?
What was that about?
She looks so young, too.
And why is she so tall? Goodness.
I'm not sure if this is the right time to tell you this, but...
Jun Woo's girlfriend?
What are you talking about? You're not making much sense right now.
I saw him when I was on a blind date a few days ago.
He was being so cold and rude to a young lady.
It looked like they were intimately involved.
What I'm saying is that what you know about him now...
may not be everything.
Okay. Let's talk again later. Bye!
I'm sorry. I made you my assistant and couldn't pay attention to you.
Don't say that. I'm sorry I'm not good enough to be more helpful.
Then promise me that you'll attend every class.
I'll try. It's more fun than I expected.
By the way, it looks like you have a lot of fans.
Fans?
A tall lady said that she's your fan...
and took the magazine that you were in.
Oh, really?
Good for you.
Have you ever made a special dish for someone?
Well, I've lived long enough to have done it at least once.
I'm good at making ramyeon. Don't underestimate me too much.
I must try your ramyeon.
For whom have you cooked, then?
Well, in my case,
I always cook for my family and customers.
Also, when I was living in Canada...
Never mind.
Who is it? Why did you stop in the middle of talking?
Today is our first day.
What are you talking about? Our first day?
You don't need to know now. Thanks for coming today anyway.
See you.
All right. See you.
Today is our first day.
I saw that you planted those seedlings already.
Can I raise these seedlings if you don't mind?
No, you can't.
Gosh, seriously. I can do a good job. I won't kill them.
Are you confident that you won't kill them?
Of course!
Oh, right. I saw this notebook, too.
I just have to follow these instructions, no?
That's not everything.
If you're unsure about anything, look it up on the internet.
Really? So you're letting me...
take care of this garden, right? Don't change your words later.
Think of it as my act of kindness for a resident.
For a resident?
That's right.
You're a resident of our city now.
Yes. Thank you.
An act of kindness for a resident?
A project for promoting Woori City?
Yes. Let's come up with ideas that can help us this summer.
We need something practical that can be done right away.
Social media is certainly the way to go.
We won't have to do much if we use social networks effectively.
Let's do that, then.
What's important is how we'll utilise which social media channels.
What will our content be and how will we share it?
How about we come up with a song for Woori City?
- A song?
-  That's right.
We can use our mascot, the squirrel, to let people know of our song.
Such tactic is frequently used in election campaigns.
A drama about Woori City?
Min Joo.
I want you to take this on.
Director Gook.
I know that I'm in the planning team now, but if you make me do this...
What's wrong with this project?
You're asking me to make a drama that promotes the city hall.
That is not true. How many times do I have to...
Give it to someone else.
You're really not going to take it, right?
Director Gook, I'll do it.
Shut it, you silly.
She doesn't want to do it.
An opportunity like this doesn't come by easily.
All broadcasting companies have their eyes set on this.
And you're saying no?
I guess she didn't know.
You're so out of touch with what's going on.
Min Joo, it looks like no one tells you anything any more.
If another network ends up scoring this project,
I'll be fired.
I wasn't aware.
Then I'll review the proposal and think about it.
"Woori City Song".
So you're suggesting that we should make a song about our city.
Yes. Those are some of the ideas...
that we came up with today regarding boosting tourism this summer.
I like the idea. I'm actually a good singer myself.
- Pardon me?
-  Let's make a great song together.
Okay.
But as I mentioned to you the other day, I'm not sure about the drama.
Head Chief Shin will be in charge of the drama project,
so you don't need to worry about it.
By the way,
why do you hate dramas so much?
Do you really never watch them?
That's right. I'd much rather watch the news and shows...
about current events as well as documentaries.
Where should we go for lunch today?
I'll eat at the cafeteria.
Oh, is there something you need to discuss with me?
No, not at all.
I don't have much appetite these days,
so I was asking to see if you have any recommendations for lunch.
I see.
Well, if that's the case...
Do you like naengmyeon? I know of a good restaurant.
Which one is better between this...
- and this blazer?
-  Pardon me?
Which one suits me better in your opinion?
Well...
For what you're wearing now, I think this one will be better.
Then I'll wear the other one.
Did you say that you know of a good naengmyeon place?
- Yes.
-  Then text me...
the restaurant's address.
Last but not least, I hope you enjoy your lunch at the cafeteria.
I will.
- Have a great day, Sir.
-  You, too.
- I hope you enjoyed the food.
-  Yes, thank you.
The wait won't be too long.
Hello, Ma'am.
- Are you here alone?
-  Yes.
- Why do you ask?
-  Please come with me.
Sure.
Please take this seat.
Is this the only table that's available?
Yes. Come and take order from Table Number 13!
Hello, Ma'am. What would you like to order?
I'd like a bowl of mulnaengmyeon.
I'd like mulnaengmyeon with no ice.
- I'll get mine without ice, too.
-  Sure.
You can take it. I don't need it.
No, please leave it here.
I never said that I don't need it.
I apologise. I thought you two were together.
The naengmyeon here is more delicious without it.
Gosh, seriously.
Please try without it first.
Adding all sorts of things...
ruins the authentic flavour of the buckwheat noodles.
How is it?
It's a little bland,
but it's not bad.
Eating bland things are good for people at our age.
How old are you? Why do you assume that we'd be around the same age?
We're both ageing. Who cares about 1 or 2 years of age difference?
The fact that you're eating this here alone at this hour is enough...
for me to assume that you're an old lady who is bored and lonely.
Did you just call me an old lady?
I look at least five years younger than you!
Well...
I just thought that your blazer looks too old-fashioned.
What did you just say?
My goodness.
Hello.
Yes.
I'd love to work with you on a drama about Woori City.
I'd love to, but I don't think I can commit to it now.
Please let me know if another opportunity pops up in the future.
Thanks for thinking of me,
but another network approached me about it already.
It looks like we will be competing against each other.
You're so out of touch.
It was announced today,
but everyone in the industry found out about it a few days ago.
All right.
Yes, okay.
Producer Kang.
Can I be honest with you?
Of course.
People at work are saying that you're not like you used to be.
No one would obviously want to work with you on it.
What do you mean by that?
People are saying...
that you're not as good as you used to be...
and that you've lost your zeal and drive due to your old age.
You've been rejecting all the good ideas.
So it looks like writers are avoiding to work with you.
I see.
All right.
No, no.
Thanks for telling me.
If we drag it on like this, it won't even get scheduled for next year.
The two of you should negotiate or come to an agreement.
Can one of you give in, please?
You don't even have another writer in mind for co-writing this with me.
Producer Kang, did you take on the drama about Woori City?
What are you talking about?
The drama about Woori City?
When will I debut as a director, then?
Also, what will happen to Writer Na?
Why are you so worried?
You'll be able to debut if Writer Na's script turns out well.
Producer Kang, you can't do this to me.
You made me work like a dog,
but you're working on something else behind my back?
She'd never do that.
It's not true, right?
- I'm thinking about it.
-  Goodness!
Producer Han has already started on the next drama.
Producer Kang, you might end up losing your job at this rate.
Have a good day.
Wait.
My goodness.
Let's see.
(Ms Na Choon Woo, your order for the lingerie has been shipped.)
What's this?
"Women's sexy chiffon lingerie"?
"Ms Na Choon Woo."
Na Choon Woo. Who is Na Choon Woo?
- No, no.
-  Gosh!
- My goodness.
-  No, I was just...
Unbelievable!
Right. That's when my phone got switched with hers.
"Flaunt your sexy charms all you want..."
"and enjoy a steamy night."
Gosh, this old lady is a piece of work.
The battery is dying.
What? This blazer looks old-fashioned?
That ridiculous old man.
Goodness.
I do not answer telemarketing calls.
Wait, hello? Is this Ms Na Choon Woo?
Who is this?
You ate naengmyeon at Bimatgol for lunch today, right?
Who are you?
Why are you stalking me?
Who would be stalking a grandmother like you?
I called to tell you that our phones got mixed up.
What?
No, this is mine. What trick are you trying to pull?
Then hang up the phone and look at it carefully.
My gosh.
What is he talking about?
This is... It's that pervert from the restaurant!
They say that you're not as good as you used to be...
and that you've lost your zeal and drive due to your old age.
You've been rejecting all the good ideas.
So it looks like writers are avoiding to work with you.
Mi Rae.
Hello. Are you coming home from work?
Yes. What are you doing here?
I'm just studying people.
People?
Yes.
I tend to have a closed mind if I stay at home,
so I hike up the mountain sometimes...
and ride on the subway even when I don't have to go anywhere.
But then I run back home when I get sick by the crowds.
That could happen to people who work at home.
It's good to be focused on your career,
but you should try to be more social.
- Hey, hey!
-  Hey, it's here!
Hurry! Come on!
Really? Right now?
Yes, hurry up.
If we don't go now, there won't be any left.
Hey, can you hold onto this for a minute?
What is it?
The new ones are on the shelves.
I have to go buy a bunch. Let's go!
- Hurry!
-  Let's go!
I'll be here.
(Love and Cooking, Written and illustrated by Ko Mi Rae)
(Go and wash your hands. I'm holding a knife.)
Good job, good job.
Good.
I was waiting and you didn't come, so I took your laptop home.
I'll see you at home.
Thank goodness.
Mr Ko.
Yes, hello.
Why didn't you come out yesterday? All the mums got together.
Didn't Ye Ji tell you?
No, she didn't. What was it about?
It was just a gathering for mums with daughters.
We gave advice to each other while sharing information.
If you have another meeting, please let me know.
How is Ye Ji these days?
My daughter told me that Ye Ji often goes to the library with Hyun Seok.
She told me that they even download music for each other.
I see. Thank you for letting me know.
Okay. See you later.
Bye.
We can't French kiss yet,
but we can kiss.
What? Kiss?
No, no.
I'm happy with just holding your hand.
Really.
I don't mind this much.
Ye Ji...
What's wrong?
Why her?
This is annoying.
Gosh.
Hold on.
Why do I have to run away?
Kids these days are such troublemakers.
- Hey, excuse me.
-  My goodness!
Gosh.
What... What is it?
What was that about just now?
Are you being coy or acting innocent?
Coy?
Acting innocent?
I know you saw us.
Yes, I did.
- So what?
-  Don't tell Dad.
Why would I tell him such a thing?
What do you mean, "such a thing"?
Gosh, you adults.
Then why are you asking me not to tell him?
Because my dad is old-fashioned.
It's nothing, but he'll think it's a big deal if he hears it from you.
In any case, I don't want to be in trouble.
So just pretend you didn't see it.
Isn't that my aunt's computer?
It is.
Why do you have it?
Because she left it with me.
Give it to me then.
It's okay. Tell her to come and get it herself.
Anyway, you'll keep it a secret. Right?
A secret?
What will you do for me then?
You're so mean.
What do you want?
Here.
Thank you.
Mi Rae.
Don't you want to work with me?
What do you mean?
I'm asking you if you'd like to make your web comic...
into a drama with me.
Me?
No. How can I work on a drama?
Although the order was mixed up,
you already had your previous work become a drama before.
Actually, I saw your latest work earlier today.
What? No one is supposed to see it yet.
I just started recently, so...
It's pretty fun.
I'm making an official offer to you.
No, I can't do it.
If I do it, I'd have to talk to other people,
have meetings, try to get along,
and make compromises and stuff.
That's right.
It's a good opportunity for you to become more social.
Don't be afraid and think about it...
before making a decision.
Another decision?
No, I... I don't want to do it.
Thank you anyhow.
Gosh.
Hey, I'm coming in.
Okay.
All you do is roll around in your room.
Did you come here to scold me?
No way.
Shouldn't you find a proper job now?
Proper? Are you saying my job is improper?
I know how hard you work,
but life isn't about just working hard.
You need luck and also people that give you opportunities.
What is this? What have you been listening to?
What do you mean?
They say opportunity strikes only three times in your life.
You don't have much time left.
You little...
Get lost. Go. Leave.
You!
Hold on. Three times? How many times do I have left?
Gosh.
I just talked to my aunt.
I'll do my best to persuade her until she says yes.
You have to promise you won't tell Dad in return.
Just coming in?
Hey, I have to ask you something.
The leaves on these cherry tomato plants are wilting.
It's so strange.
Oh, dear.
This one has aphids.
Aphids?
Will this plant die then?
You should save it.
Just spray some vinegar water on here.
Vinegar water?
How much of it?
Wait here for a minute.
- Sang Sik.
-  Hey.
You're here, too.
What is that?
This one's mine,
and this is a present for Min Joo.
Why would you...
Why do you think? Now, we can wear it together.
You can wear it for the motorcycle or the skateboard.
I think it'll look great on you.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Ye Ji.
Ye Ji?
Open the door, Ye Ji.
Ko Ye Ji!
What is it? I was listening to music and didn't hear.
I see.
Why did you lock your door?
Sometimes I want to be alone and uninterrupted, too.
Were you on the phone?
No.
Are you going to keep me standing here?
What is it about?
I just...
- Anything new?
-  Like what?
- Maybe you're being bullied or...
-  No.
Dad, I'm in the middle of talking with my friends.
What is it about?
Come on.
All right.
You can talk to me any time you want.
- Okay.
-  All right.
Who is it at this hour?
Gosh, I'm awake now.
Who...
Who are you?
Hold on. Hold on.
I'm a family of the owner.
Why are you lying?
Excuse me, there's someone here!
Hold on, hold on.
Hold on, I'm...
I'm the landlord's brother-in-law.
Why don't we go in and check?
Ko... Ko Sang Sik!
Please...
- Please, hold on.
-  My goodness.
Please quiet down.
- Hey, neighbour. It's you...
-  Dad.
Honey.
I should have told you in advance.
I'm sorry we surprised you.
I thought I was going to die.
It's just for tonight. Just tonight.
They'll find out everything by tomorrow morning.
I have no idea what's going on.
What are you doing at this hour?
As long as we set up the tent, Sang Sik won't kick us out.
Tent?
- Oh, no.
-  I told you to be careful.
Don't you know?
Do we have to live like this every summer?
All of my friends go abroad on trips...
and vacations.
We always rent out our place for money.
Hoon, keep it down. It's just for 15 days.
Just think positively and consider it as making memories.
All right, enough nagging.
Prepare the blankets. I'm sleepy.
- I'm tired, too.
-  Okay, okay.
These mosquitoes.
Where's the spray?
Min Joo.
Hey, Min Joo.
I'm sorry to wake you. I packed so much stuff,
but I forgot to pack the insect repellent. Do you have one?
Thank you. Have a good night.
Ma'am.
Ma'am?
Hello. I'm Park Hoon.
I'm sorry, but could we borrow a bottle of water?
I won't ever forget this.
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
I had too much water.
It's urgent. Can I use your washroom?
What is that?
Ko Sang Hee.
Ko Sang Hee!
What are you...
- Gosh, my back.
-  What is this?
Why are you guys coming out from there?
Well the thing is, last night...
We were going back and forth, then...
She told us to just sleep there.
What?
Hey.
Did you sleep out here?
Can't you tell?
Did you let them sleep in your house?
Yes, it turned out that way.
Why would you do such a thing?
Last night...
I had no other choice.
Sang Sik, don't yell at her.
Be quiet.
- Take care.
-  Wait.
Since you let us sleep at your place, come have breakfast.
I'm all right.
I didn't get to sleep at all.
Everybody, come follow me.
Right now.
See? He told all of us to come in.
Yes. Let's go inside for now.
Well, I...
- Come on.
-  Gosh.
This is awkward.
Let's eat.
- Thank you for the food.
-  In any case,
I'm sorry to have inconvenienced you because of my family.
Yes. I moved here to get a peace of mind.
This is your whole family, right?
I guess so, but I'm not sure.
Who knows when one might pop out of nowhere?
Come on, Sang Sik.
That's it. This is all of us.
Take your tent away after you finish breakfast.
I have to go to work.
My friends are staying for just a week.
Can't you be understanding? I'm trying to make money.
Accommodation is expensive during summer vacation,
and they've been looking forward to this all year.
That's no reason to cause inconvenience to our neighbour.
I told you.
I knew we'd be kicked out this summer.
- Hey.
-  Hoon.
It's not a big deal. We're neighbours.
Right, Mi Rae?
I'm sorry?
Why are you asking me?
Right. Mi Rae might get a job at a broadcasting company.
Really?
Is this true, Mi Rae?
No, no.
No. I haven't decided yet.
What is this about?
I gave Mi Rae an offer.
I asked her to work with me at our company.
I'm against it.
- Why?
-  It's a no.
You'll only get hurt while working at a place like that.
"A place like that"?
What are you trying to say about my work?
All they care about are ratings and commercials.
It's the most commercial-focused job in this capitalist society.
For someone like Mi Rae who focuses only on creativity,
it's a place she could get hurt.
On what grounds are you saying this?
My family...
isn't interested in television shows nor dramas.
Well, I love it.
The thing is,
if you don't watch it you kind of forget about it.
- Isn't that right, Honey?
-  That's right.
Of course. Our family don't watch dramas at all.
I watch the news, Hoon watches games,
and my wife watches the shopping channel.
She's addicted.
This is all your fault.
Come on, we're having a meal with our neighbour.
Shouldn't we talk about food, hobbies or ideal types?
Ideal types?
I'm fine as long as it's not...
a civil servant who has no idea what his family is thinking...
and is stuck up and stubborn.
Same goes for me. I hate women that lived alone for a long time...
and only cares about herself.
I'm sorry, but I'll excuse myself.
What's wrong with you guys?
- Don't leave like that.
-  No, sit down.
Sit down and eat.
How can he talk bad about my job after I let his family...
sleep in my house?
What?
We obsess over ratings? We're capitalistic?
My stomach hurts.
Why do I suddenly feel...
I'm so stressed.
What on earth happened?
Come on, tell us now.
- Goodness.
-  Goodness.
You know,
my period started. Thankfully,
it wasn't menopause. My period was just irregular.
Really?
Bravo.
See? I told you to get a checkup.
Between menopause and an irregular period,
did you switch from being a person to a woman?
To congratulate you on becoming a woman again,
let's cheer.
Okay.
- It's all because of skateboarding.
-  Skateboarding?
Jun Woo taught me how to skateboard.
Have you asked him...
about the woman I saw last time?
Gosh, why are you jinxing a couple that's doing well?
He must have lent some money to her.
It didn't look like that.
How can I ask him directly? I'm not his girlfriend.
Didn't he count that day as your first day of dating?
You're slow-witted and old-fashioned because you can't even...
understand that.
That's right. I'm old-fashioned who's losing her senses.
I'm already treated as an old lady.
What's wrong now?
If you get a project with Woori City,
it won't be that hard for us to escape from this place.
What are you going to do about not having a writer to work with?
We have Ae Ri.
Are you going to work with her?
There's one more, but I'll have to meet her. Before that...
What?
Since we don't have a good writer,
we need a good actress.
Which actress? Everyone's scheduled for their next drama.
Joo Yeon.
Do you mean Na Joo Yeon?
Yes, why not?
Come on. She'd never do it.
She'll be loyal at least.
Cut. Let's take a break.
Bring me my phone.
Oh, my. Producer Kang.
Goodness, have you been well?
I'm always the same.
You must be popular. You're dominating all the commercials.
No, it's tiring because young ones are getting competitive.
You're still unrivalled.
Have a seat.
It's okay. You should sit.
Okay.
What brings you all the way here?
Well...
You see, there's this drama...
that I'm producing.
I have to tell you more about it.
When are you free?
Did you wait until now just to tell me that?
You should have called.
I did, but you didn't answer.
Really?
I didn't know because I don't have your number saved.
Is this about the Woori City drama?
How did you know? Did someone else call you?
Of course.
Many people called me to try and win something hard to get.
So are you considering it at all?
I'd consider it based on our friendship,
but you should consider your age.
It needs to include current trends,
but if you produce it, do you think anyone would select it?
What do you mean? I'm still fine.
That was during your prime.
I'm not the Joo Yeon...
who used to cry for being scolded for my bad acting.
Shooting dramas is exhausting,
so I want to focus on movies.
You're still a rude brat.
What did you say?
Do you know why so many dislike you?
It's because of that tongue.
You can lose your career by saying something wrong in this industry.
If you want to continue working,
don't think about fixing anything else...
but that tongue of yours.
This is unbelievable.
Why did she come here just to make me angry?
Move that away from me!
- Thank you, everyone.
-  Thank you.
You don't know how to move your body.
Why can't you do that move?
Can't you do this?
Do it like this.
He's a little old, after all.
I'm old?
Stop it.
Chief Ko was the cutest like a squirrel.
I was impressed that you could write songs.
That's nothing.
Let's rehearse more...
and upload it on the homepage or the blog to see how people react.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
Mi Rae.
Hello.
I'm sure it was a difficult decision.
Thank you so much for coming.
No, I'm the one who should thank you.
Let's talk inside.
Wait.
I'd like to make it short and talk here.
I thought about it a lot,
but I think it's better that I don't do it.
If it's because of your brother...
No.
I don't want to give him a hard time for my sake.
What do you mean?
You should tell me a definite reason...
Actually,
my brother had a bad experience with a broadcasting station.
A bad experience?
Well, what I mean is...
There was an accident that he doesn't want to remember.
Does that mean he opposes you of working...
because of something that happened a long time ago?
How frustrating.
I told you my decision, so I'll get going.
Mi Rae.
Are you just getting home?
Yes. Is your brother home?
Yes, he got home just now.
Where is he?
Go up...
way over there.
What kind of room is this?
Gosh.
How did you get in here?
The door was open.
You have so many records and movies.
This is my space, so please leave.
I have something to tell you.
I'd like to apologise for what I said before.
I didn't mean to offend your job,
but I don't want Mi Rae to work for a broadcasting station.
She doesn't like being in conflicts with people...
and has never worked in such an environment.
She came all the way to the broadcasting station.
She wants to do it,
but she can't because she's concerned about you.
I definitely warned you...
not to pull my family into your business...
or come near my family.
I don't know what happened in the past,
but you're holding your family back because you're stuck in the past.
I don't know what Mi Rae told you,
but it's none of your business. Just go on with your life.
Being the head of a family doesn't give you a crown.
You stop them from doing anything like it's for their own sakes...
when you're being suffocated by being surrounded by family.
What gives you the right to say that?
You think so highly of yourself.
You think you're competent and talented, right?
- What?
-  Who are you to give a chance...
to Mi Rae? She doesn't want it.
You're so frustrating.
Does that make you happy?
Is that why you don't want anything to happen...
and overreact whenever something happens?
Is that why you have...
treated me harshly so far?
That's nonsense. Get out now.
- Mr Ko Sang Sik.
-  Get out.
Fine. Keep living like this.
Hold down your family...
while being stuck in the past and giving up your whole life.
What did you say? Keep being selfish like this.
In the end, no one will be there for you like right now.
Hui Soo.
Hui Soo, wake up.
Hui Soo, wake up!
Hui Soo.
I'm sorry.
I'm too late.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
Wake up.
Open your eyes, Hui Soo!
Hui Soo.
Hui Soo!
I'm sorry.
You think so highly of yourself.
You think you're competent and talented, right?
Keep being selfish like this.
In the end, no one will be there for you like right now.
Where are you?
I'm still out.
Why?
Your lights were out.
I called because I was worried about you.
Now,
I have someone who worries about me.
Of course.
But why do you sound so down?
Is something wrong?
There must be since you're not answering.
I don't know what's going on, but stay strong.
You can do it, Min Joo.
(Forest Study Room)
- Pardon me.
-  Yes?
Which room is Ko Ye Ji in?
Wait one moment.
Let's see.
Ye Ji didn't come today.
Ye Ji, where are you?
I'm still at the study.
Is that right?
Why?
I was worried because you said you'll be late.
Dad, I'll come home after studying a little longer.
Don't worry and go to bed first.
- Bye.
-  Ye Ji, wait...
Yes, Mum.
Min Joo, can you talk right now?
Yes.
What's wrong with your voice?
Is something wrong?
No.
I called because I was thinking about you.
Are you crying?
Of course not.
What's wrong?
Your dad keeps being forgetful.
He went for a checkup and...
No, never mind.
Is it...
something like dementia?
No.
Your dad is still healthy.
It happens with age.
The test results will come out in a few days.
I'm still healthy though.
This is why you need someone when you get old.
Come visit me...
- or shall I go there?
-  No.
It's a waste of money to travel.
Take care of yourself.
Mum, I'm healthy and successful, so don't worry about money.
I've been working so hard.
Of course, I'll keep being successful.
Okay.
It can't be dementia.
Talk to you later.
For what have I been striving all this time?
I thought...
this was the right way to live.
What's left...
is a pathetic wound.
Are you hurt? Let me see.
I'm fine, don't mind me.
Here.
I'm fine, so let me go.
Ever since becoming an adult,
I couldn't express my pain.
That's because I have to stay strong and keep going forward.
No.
It's okay not to stay strong.
It's okay to rest for a while.
Don't do anything right now.
It's okay to do that.
(Second to Last Love)
Nothing happened last night, right?
- Why would anything happen?
-  That's a relief.
"That's a relief"?
It wasn't my brother.
Mi Rae disappeared.
She took all her belongings and ran away.
An accident?
Emergency room?