Do you have disinfectant at home?
If you don't, I'll bring you some.
Come here.
- Where?
-  Just come with me.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I was too harsh on you.
It's okay.
I also mistook myself as a competent and talented person.
I only said that because I was upset.
I didn't mean it for you to blame yourself.
I'm not. It's the truth.
I feel like I'm falling behind.
People treat me like a has-been.
I think the problem with you is that you work too passionately.
That's why you keep on falling.
Take a break. No one will arrest you.
Ask them to give you time off for your leg.
What if I really fall behind then?
People are making fun of me these days.
It's okay to hear that at our age.
It's normal.
That's why I should try harder.
That way, I won't fall.
You have to rest well in order to avoid falling.
Don't try to run. Just walk.
I'll try.
Actually, I've been practising something with my staff.
I'm the only one that keeps getting it wrong.
They call me old-fashioned.
What are you practising?
We're trying to promote the city.
I'm going to be singing and dancing.
I know how well you can dance. I saw that at the concert.
Why are you bringing that up?
I wish I could see what you practised.
Do you have drinks instead of coffee?
I think you drank enough already.
It won't change much even if I drink more.
What kind of music do you like?
I like anything old.
You're like a DJ.
There are so many films, too.
With this many albums, I wonder what you did before.
Did you have a different job?
It's just a hobby.
You should go home and sleep.
I'll go when I finish what you gave me.
About the garden,
I did what you told me to with the vinegar water,
but the leaves turned white and it looks worse.
I sprayed some more, but it turned even more white.
What?
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
That's why I'm telling you now.
Don't tell Dad.
It's nothing, but he'll think it's a big deal if he hears it from you.
What will you do for me then?
You have to tell me right away next time.
Don't try to decide on your own.
That's the right way to raise one.
All right, I will.
I asked her to keep it a secret.
How can she tell him already?
(Second to Last Love)
(Episode 7)
Cheers.
I hope I didn't make a mistake.
Gosh.
Jun Woo. Jun Woo.
- Hey, Sang Sik.
-  Where are you going?
Min Joo's place. She seemed to be upset yesterday.
I thought maybe we could go for a walk together.
Hey!
She's probably sleeping in. Just let her be.
She's sleeping? How do you know?
It's still early. How can she be up already?
You said something happened yesterday, right?
She could have had some drinks.
Do you think so? I'll give her a call.
A call?
The number you have called...
She's not picking up.
Maybe she's sleeping.
Right. You should go on your own.
I better do that. Do you want to come?
No. I'm feeling a bit sore.
Go and come back fast. We'll have breakfast.
- Okay.
-  All right.
Why did I...
I must be crazy.
- I...
-  Hello.
- Did you sleep well?
-  Why didn't you wake me?
You were sleeping so soundly.
Nothing happened, right?
Of course not.
You're sure?
Well, I was drunk, so I don't remember anything.
I'm glad. Bye.
You should be careful.
- Okay.
-  Bye.
Glad? She's glad?
I think the problem with you is that you work too passionately.
That's why you keep on falling.
You have to rest well in order to avoid falling.
Don't try to run. Just walk.
He seems like a good guy...
the more I see him.
Give it to me. I'll set it.
You guys, too!
- Okay.
-  Okay.
Don't any of you have manners?
I told you, we should make eye contact during meals.
- Okay.
-  Kids are like that these days.
We can't compare to when our parents were alive.
I was looking at textbooks.
Didn't you say you studied at the library until late yesterday?
Well, there's no end to learning.
What's the point of starting then?
Of course, it's hard for you to understand since you never started.
I prepared something special for Ye Ji...
since she studies so hard.
Amazing. I'll only eat this since I'm on a diet.
Diet? For who?
What's wrong?
- Eat.
-  Good morning.
Good morning, Sang Sik.
Hurry up and sit down. Get ready faster tomorrow.
You weren't at the library.
Where were you?
I was with Hyun Seok.
I'm asking you where you were and what you did with him.
It was our 50th day, so we ate with our friends and talked.
50 days? What is that?
Sang Sik. It's a thing these days.
You guys dated for 50 days already?
Bring him home. I want to see him.
You dated him for 50 days?
Why did you lie to me?
How can I ever talk to you about anything?
Especially about Hyun Seok.
You haven't dated in so long. You wouldn't understand.
What did you say?
- I wouldn't understand?
-  No!
Well, I haven't dated in a while either.
Maybe it runs in the genes.
Why did you give them such bad genes?
Come on.
Look who's talking.
Also, get rid of that tent outside.
You're not homeless. Why would you put up a tent...
Ye Ji.
You better watch your actions. Understand?
Okay.
What do you mean?
Jeong Sik is doing a drama project for the city?
Do you remember the proposal about bringing in new writers?
The one we all voted for.
Yes. You guys voted against me, and I was embarrassed.
Anyway, I think they're preparing with that proposal.
Why would Director Gook ask me and ask Jeong Sik, as well?
That's what I mean. It's weird.
What's wrong with your leg?
Did you get hurt?
I fell.
What?
- Anyway, I'll be there soon.
-  Producer Kang.
Producer Kang?
What's happening?
Is it broken again?
What?
I wouldn't understand?
And she's been dating for 50 days?
Gosh.
Yes, Writer Hwang.
Thanks for considering me, but I should work on my own now.
I decided not to go to the broadcasting company.
It's because of family reasons.
Yes, it's a good opportunity. I want to do it, as well.
But it just turned out that way.
I'm sure another huge chance will come in my life.
Mi Rae, can you come down and help me?
Okay.
I'll call you back later. Bye.
When I was young, I thought...
you would know how to do everything once you become an adult.
However, now that I'm an adult,
I realised that nothing will happen...
unless you take action for yourself.
Mi Rae even came to see me at work.
She's interested,
but she can't accept the job because of you.
I don't know what happened in the past,
but it's making you tie down your family.
You didn't leave yet?
No. I'm leaving now.
Why are you coming down from there?
I went to Ye Ji's room.
Why?
Mi Rae.
Do you want to try that job?
What job?
The offer from our neighbour.
Do you want to do it?
No, I'm not going to do it.
I can tell that you want to.
I said, I'm not doing it.
I'm not interested. I told you.
I hope you earn a lot of money by going through all this.
Hoon has no future here.
I better send him to China to study next year.
I already told you. Studying is not his thing.
His dad's blood still runs in him.
Yours, as well.
While we're on that...
You never got a loan from work, have you?
- I'll give you interest if you...
-  Are you still sleeping?
Wake up. Wake up.
Don't worry about Ye Ji.
It's normal to have a boyfriend at that age.
We should let Mi Rae go, as well.
She's 35, and all she does is draw alone at home. She'll die a virgin.
She needs to have a social life.
Even if it's tough, she needs to work with others.
It'll be fine.
I'm going to work.
I'll make kongguksu for dinner tonight.
I make it better than Mum!
Your knee hurts. Why are you wearing heels?
Thanks for your concern,
but someone like you...
wouldn't understand women.
Wait.
Regarding Mi Rae...
If it's about her, let's forget it. I'll consider it never happened.
That's not it.
I was hoping to ask you to look after her.
If you're still open to working with her, that is.
Then tell her to come out right now.
May I?
I can't guarantee if we'll work together for long,
but it's important to give it a try.
You should still wear runners.
You keep changing your mind about everything.
Don't go back on your word again.
I won't. I'll send her over.
Joo Yeon, as long as you sign with me,
I'm certain I can get this rolling.
You've seen the character, right?
If you use this chance to change your image,
it'll only be a matter of time before you go to Hollywood.
Okay. I'll send in my agent.
Producer Kang.
- What is this?
-  What do you think?
It's the script you threw out like garbage when everyone else liked it.
Are you sending her to Hollywood...
and kicking me out of work?
How can the both of you stab my back like this?
I guess there really is no loyalty in this industry.
This is why I said we should meet outside.
I'm not scared of her.
Anyway, sign it. Okay?
What happened to your leg?
("Oh Hae Jin, The Love Psychologist")
"Woori City drama"?
Director Gook.
What is it?
Am I a spare?
What do you mean?
That's impossible for the great Kang Min Joo.
We're not a car repair shop.
If anything, I'm the spare. Isn't that right, Director Gook?
Well the thing is...
- I...
-  Don't you trust me any more?
Did you think I wouldn't be able get the city drama project?
Is that why you ordered Jeong Sik to do the same thing?
Calm down.
- Have some water.
-  Yes.
I didn't even start,
but all the writers declined already.
Even top stars I discovered and supported declined my offer.
I was declined by everyone!
Really? You...
Director Gook.
I know that recently,
some of the ideas I threw out were made...
into dramas at other channels and were very popular.
I know that.
Ever since I started working here,
my dramas were always rated the best.
I would get so many commercials and get 30 to 40 percent ratings.
I can't just die like this. I won't allow it.
I know you won't.
You're still good, so don't worry.
I'm not doing this because I don't trust you.
To be honest, what if we really don't get this project?
Our company's name is on the line.
I'll succeed no matter what.
I'll show everyone that's talking behind my back.
I'm going to get this project no matter what.
Chief Ko, you're a lot better now.
I agree. Did you practise by yourself at home?
Chief Ko, why isn't the drama project led by our department?
Chief Ko went through so much trouble the last time...
we helped out with a drama.
Still, the drama can make Woori City known globally.
I think that broadcasting companies are competing to get the project.
It's become a huge project.
We're busy with other projects.
We're in the local tourism department.
We should be the ones working on that project.
Song Yi, isn't it because you want to see celebrities?
That can definitely be considered as sexual harassment in the workplace.
Sexual harassment?
(We're looking for part-time helpers who are interested in cooking.)
(Comma)
Hi.
Jun Woo. Jun Woo.
- Hey, Jun Woo.
-  Did you order nakji bibimbab?
- Look over there.
-  Yes.
- What's the matter?
-  It seemed delicious.
We use kidney beans instead of sausage.
Also, the tofu scramble replaces scrambled eggs,
which enhances the texture and compliments the broccoli inside.
Then what about this one?
That one is raw zucchini noodle pasta.
What should we do?
I don't know. Just leave her be for now.
The noodles are made of zucchini, which is like Italian squash.
It may look like a salad,
but it's actually very filling and keeps you satiated for long.
- Oh, really?
-  It looks nice.
Hey, Sang Sik.
I came to Jun Woo's cafe to help him out with the lunch crowd.
What? The broadcasting station?
Now?
Gosh, what am I doing right now?
I must be out of my mind.
What happened? Is my sister-in-law okay?
She's getting surgery now. Please wait a little bit.
Sang Hee, what should we do? What's taking Sang Sik so long?
Jun Woo, you're here.
Where's Sang Sik? Is he not here yet?
What's going on? What happened?
- Sang Sik, please.
-  Let go of me!
- Sang Sik.
-  Sang Sik.
Why are you dressed like that?
You should've put on something more proper.
What's wrong with this?
You can do a good job, right?
I don't know if I'm doing the right thing.
I don't think what I'm doing is right.
Let me say this again.
Don't give up on your dream because of me.
Do your very best at whatever you want to do.
Are you going on vacation or what? Why did you bring so much stuff?
I need everything I brought today.
You're so quirky.
I could've taken the bus alone.
Call me if anything goes wrong, and take care of yourself.
Am I enlisting myself in the army? I'm not a kid.
Don't worry and get going now.
- Ko Sang Sik?
-  All right. Go in.
Best of luck.
Why does Chief Ko get disgusted every time he just hears "drama"?
I know, right? It's almost as if he's allergic to the word.
He must have some sort of unfavourable memories about dramas.
Unfavourable memories?
It could have something to do with his ex-wife's death.
According to rumours, that's when he became super responsible.
I heard he took the civil service exam after she passed away, too.
Then what kind of job did he have before that?
I asked him, but he didn't tell me.
I'm not sure what he's trying to hide.
They say that you mustn't ask men about their past.
What the person is like now...
at this moment is what matters.
Come in, Mi Rae.
Everyone, say hello.
She's Ko Mi Rae, the one who wrote "I Don't Love You Even If I Die".
Pardon? You mean the web comic that Producer Han plagiarised?
Yes, that's right.
The one who didn't withdraw the lawsuit and caused you trouble?
Gosh, stop it. It's all in the past.
All in all, she's the one who made Producer Kang get demoted.
You got demoted?
Aren't you guys going to greet her?
Welcome. I'm Oh Young Ae, and I'm a producing director.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm inexperienced, so I'll have a lot to learn.
Please help me out.
I'm waiting for this project to work out...
so that I can debut as a director. My name is Nam Ki Cheol.
My life depends on the tip of your pen.
My life depends on it, too.
I'll do my best.
- Hello.
-  Hello. Welcome to the team.
- I'll work hard.
-  Thank you.
This is Writer Na Ae Ri.
She's written online romance novels.
She'll be creating the plot and co-writing the script with you.
I see. Hello, Writer Na. I'm honoured to work with you.
Are you nervous?
You look so frightened right now.
Is this your first time visiting a broadcasting station?
She is always that rude...
and blunt.
I see. She's a rude person.
That's okay. I don't really care about what other people say.
That girl and I are obviously not going to get along.
How am I going to write the script with her?
I was very worried about having to work with someone like me.
I'm glad to know that you're so different from me. Nice to meet you.
By the way, what's in your suitcase?
Oh, this?
All right. I'm ready to work now. Shall we have a meeting, then?
- We'll focus on promoting the city.
-  Come in.
Yes.
In addition...
What can I help you with, Chief Ko?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm sorry to interrupt. I'll come back another time.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Don't mind me.
Do you know Chief Ko?
No. He looks a lot like someone I know,
so I mistook him for my acquaintance.
Hurry up! Get out of here now!
Don't let go of my hand!
I trust that you'll make an excellent drama for Woori City.
Thank you.
Do you know that man, Chief Ko, well?
Of course. He and I have a bit of history together.
Is that right? You should tell me about it over drinks.
Have you and Chief Ko crossed paths in the past?
Yes.
"Paradise of the Youth".
("Paradise of the Youth")
Have you watched any dramas?
I used to watch dramas all the time when I was younger,
but I haven't watched many recently.
I think I watched all of Producer Kang's dramas, though.
That's probably why. I see elements of romantic comedy throughout this.
It's so funny.
Really? Let me see.
Read it.
Then what's your favourite drama of all time?
Obviously, it's "Paradise of the Youth"...
No, that's not true. I don't have one.
"Paradise of the Youth"?
What's wrong? It's fine.
Producer Han Jeong Sik was the director of the drama.
My favourite is Producer Kang's "Story of the Lovers".
It's my absolute favourite drama of all time.
All right. Let's start the meeting.
Okay.
I'm totally counting on you.
- Seriously.
-  Don't you worry.
Hold on a second.
You're Ko Sang Sik, right?
Gosh, how long has it been? It's so nice to see you.
What brings you here?
I'm here because of the drama about Woori City.
You have a great job now. Why didn't you keep in touch with me?
How have you been?
Good. I've been doing great.
Oh, Mr Shin and I went to high school together.
I see.
Chief Ko, I didn't know that you used to be a drama producer.
He used to be my assistant.
Anyway, I'm happy to see you doing well.
Working for the government is the best.
It was wise for you to quit. Being a drama producer...
at this age is so tough.
I'm working on the drama about the city, so help me out.
It looks like I'll get to see you often from now on.
Don't you think so, Mr Shin?
Take care.
Does he think that he's an actor or a Hallyu star?
All of his photos are taken with young women.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
Why did you get up? I'm here now.
Iced latte, please.
Have a seat.
Give me my phone.
Why are you so impatient?
I couldn't get any work done because you took my phone.
You must know if you peeked into my phone.
I don't know. I turned yours off.
I let you answer your calls on my phone. I'm sure it wasn't too bad.
Give me my phone now.
Goodness gracious, this woman.
Here. Take it.
My goodness.
So are you saying that you still don't know...
who I am or what I do?
You probably never go out unless you're dressed up from head to toe.
If you get a pimple on your face, you must stress about it all day.
I can tell what a woman is like at a glance.
A woman?
I'm a woman, of course. However...
You nag a lot, too.
You try to put up a tough front, but you feel...
empty and lonely.
Your life will change dramatically if you could undo just one button.
Poor you.
Goodbye, then.
What was that about?
Did that womaniser just turn me down?
A woman?
We're used to them pestering us while drama shoots are going on.
I'll be glad if there are no accidents.
The KBN drama, "Paradise of the Youth".
Goodness, you're bringing that up again.
Rumour says that it wasn't an accident.
Then are you saying that it was intentional?
It was an accident...
where the electrical over-stress on set caused a fire.
That's how it was reported in the media, too.
We can't fully trust the media.
Someone died because of the fire,
but no one took responsibility for the accident.
- Really?
-  Weren't you the director?
I wasn't there when that happened. The production assistant was there.
Then was he the person in charge when that happened?
Of course.
In the absence of directors,
assistants are responsible for everything, so do your job properly.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
It's not my brother.
My brother didn't do it!
Boss, where are you going?
If it's a delivery, I'll take care of it.
Jun Woo.
Are you stepping out to see that woman?
I hope you're not here when I'm back.
I'm sorry.
I really mean it.
I pestered you and caused trouble because I wanted to see you.
I came to Korea because I missed you,
but you didn't even want to see me.
I acted like that because you kept ignoring me.
- I'm really sorry.
-  That's enough.
If you like someone, go out with her.
If you love someone, go ahead and marry her.
Think of me as your friend, please.
No. Just think of me as a girl you know.
A girl I know?
Why is a girl I know apologising to me like this?
I'm going to leave in a month.
I want to apologise for what I did...
so that I can move on, too.
Help me get over you by letting me stay by your side for now.
Please.
Please let me know if anything happens to Mi Rae.
Does he think this is a kindergarten?
She works with me in a small office. Nothing bad will happen to her.
I assure you that nothing will happen, so please stop worrying.
You were here.
It looks like you're hurt quite a bit.
I'm fine.
You're not fine. Let me take you to a doctor. How did it happen?
I got drunk and fell on the street.
It's just scratched and bruised a little.
Producer Kang! Are you in there?
Yes, I'm here. What's the matter?
- Is Writer Ko there, too?
-  What?
No, it's just us here.
Writer Ko is gone.
We stepped out to get coffee,
and she packed up everything and left before we got back.
What did you just say?
What happened?
I don't know. As far as I know, nothing special happened.
She's not answering her phone.
Keep calling her.
I told you to just stay at the office.
Don't worry about me and just go find her.
My goodness.
I'm glad. I'll trust you.
Have a great day.
Where did she go?
Min Joo, can you talk right now?
I'm on my way to bring you lunch.
I want to surprise Mi Rae, so don't tell her.
What if she just grabbed a taxi and took off?
She's so quirky.
- Are you sure nothing happened?
-  Yes, I'm positive.
But why do we have to find someone who ran away?
If we don't find her, our future will be doomed.
Do you want to become a director when you retire?
I'll go this way. You should go that way.
- Okay.
-  Writer Ko!
Min Joo, what happened to your leg?
Nothing. Did you see Mi Rae on your way here by any chance?
Mi Rae?
Over there.
Where is she going?
Min Joo, are you okay?
What's her condition like?
She has weak knee cartilage.
Cartilage?
It's common amongst middle-aged women going through menopause.
Here, you can see some cartilage deterioration in her knee.
It's damaged, too.
I think you should be hospitalised for treatments.
It's not that serious at all.
Just stay here and get the treatments you need.
You have early-onset osteoporosis, too.
You may need to get surgery if it gets worse.
Mi Rae isn't answering her phone.
I said she's not answering her phone.
Stop worrying about her, and get your knee treated first.
What is this mess, seriously?
Why are you refusing to be hospitalised?
I can't afford to stay at the hospital right now.
Hey, did you get a hold of Mi Rae?
No. She's not answering our calls, and we can't find her anywhere.
Where are you now?
I'm at a hospital.
Hospital?
Hello.
Hey, Jun Woo.
Hey. Has Mi Rae called you by any chance?
No. Why do you ask?
Mi Rae...
suddenly left the broadcasting station.
- What?
-  I saw her leave.
Why didn't she call me?
Where are you now?
While looking for Mi Rae,
Min Joo got into an accident, so I'm at the emergency room.
The emergency room?
Please get some rest. I'll look for Mi Rae.
How can I be hospitalised when she's missing?
Please stay calm and get some rest.
- Okay.
-  Thank you.
- Did you hear that?
-  I can't believe this is happening.
I really look sick.
You look sexier with those clothes on.
Are you teasing me?
Why? Were you embarrassed in front of me?
No, I felt ashamed.
I like your being honest like this.
By the way, aren't you hungry? It's past dinner time.
I'm fine, so you should go.
Why would I leave you alone?
There's no one to stay with you.
I've already been alone on an ambulance once.
This is nothing.
Stay here for a minute.
Sang Sik, where are you?
Why aren't you here?
Hui Soo was in an accident.
She's in surgery now.
Oh, my.
Sang Sik.
You must have worried a lot. It wasn't a major accident.
What happened? Why are you hospitalised?
Well,
I have something called chondromalacia patellae.
Apparently, my knees have gotten weak.
That's obvious at our age.
Anyone over 40 ages and their cartilage becomes weaker.
Don't you know you recover more slowly once you hurt yourself?
Ageing...
Why would you run when you have weak knees?
I told you she was looking for Mi Rae.
Stay out of it.
Are you here to scold me?
What happened to Mi Rae?
Didn't you say she was doing well at work?
Everything was fine when I sent you the text message.
The meeting went well, too.
But just when I went to the restroom...
Min Joo didn't do anything wrong.
She probably left because she couldn't adjust well.
There's nothing wrong with Mi Rae.
Broadcasting stations are strange.
What did you say?
You said nothing would ever happen.
Then why would she pack her things and run away?
Gosh.
It's Mi Rae.
Mi Rae, what happened? Where are you?
I'm sorry. I should have made my decision more carefully.
I'm sorry for making everyone worried.
My colleagues may sound harsh, but they're not bad people.
Where are you now? Everyone's worried about you.
Be quiet, Ha Ni.
Ha Ni?
Are you with someone?
If it's difficult to get along with people,
there are other ways to work around that,
so don't make quick decisions. My goodness.
Hello?
Where are you?
Mi Rae?
Gosh.
Why did you take away my phone?
Where is she? Who is she with?
She apologised, but she didn't tell me where she was.
Who is Ha Ni?
What did your colleagues do to her that she ran away?
Are you blaming my colleagues?
Why would she run away, then?
Do I have to watch over Mi Rae all day long like she's a kid?
That's why I asked you to take care of her.
Goodness, please stop.
- Gosh, my leg.
-  Are you okay?
Don't worry about Mi Rae.
Just take care of yourself.
Stay here and take care of her.
Are you leaving?
She apologised, but she didn't tell me where she was.
Who is Ha Ni?
Here's your medicine.
Make sure to take it on time.
Okay, you should go now.
Why do you keep saying I should go?
I'm going to spend the night here.
- What?
-  Why not?
I've always lived alone. Being alone is better for me, so you should go.
I don't want to leave.
I'm also worried about you.
My friends will stop by my house and bring me extra clothes,
so don't worry and leave.
Do you mean your friends from your housewarming party?
Yes. Let me know if you get a call from Mi Rae.
Don't worry.
I'm going to bring her to you.
Thank you, Jun Woo.
Don't mention it.
I guess I really got forced into taking a vacation, didn't I?
Although, I did get scolded by Sang Sik.
Don't worry so much about what he said.
He's sensitive about his family.
According to Mi Rae,
he had a bad experience with a broadcasting station.
What happened to him in the past?
Well,
there was an accident.
He lost his wife that day.
I see.
Then...
I can see why he'd be sensitive.
I think I know where Mi Rae is, so don't worry so much.
Where's that?
I shouldn't have gone near a broadcasting station, right?
Are you there again? I know where you are.
Just wait until I see you.
If you know, just let me be.
Mi Rae.
Come here.
Sang Sik.
I'll teach you a lesson today.
I said I'll talk to you later. Why did you come here?
Do you know how much everyone is worried about you?
You're finished once I catch you.
Come here.
Where are you going? It's dangerous.
Hey.
Gosh.
Stay where you are. Once I catch you...
That's dangerous.
Hey, stop.
Mi Rae.
Don't follow me.
Stop right there.
Leave.
Just wait until I catch you.
That's dangerous.
Stop it.
Hey.
Don't come near me.
- My goodness.
-  Stop.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
How can she be okay?
She almost died because of you.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm okay.
Don't scold her so much.
How can I not?
I can't handle her.
I said I'm sorry.
Why did you run away from the broadcasting station?
I'm sure she had a reason.
Just because.
"Just because"?
Mi Rae, feel free to talk to me about it.
That way, I'll be able to find a solution.
Well,
your colleagues said they were going to get some coffee,
so I went to the cafeteria, too.
I wondered who it could be.
So Ko Sang Sik is your brother?
He's currently working at Woori City Hall, isn't he?
I guess families are alike,
seeing that you're also working in this industry.
Do you know my brother well?
Of course I do.
Tell him to let it go now.
Tell him to stop feeling guilty about what happened in the past.
My brother didn't do it.
Of course not.
It was only an accident.
Mi Rae.
- Mi Rae.
-  Yes?
What on earth happened?
Did you meet someone?
Well,
I heard some employees...
saying that producing a drama is really difficult,
so...
I got very scared.
Drink slowly.
Anyway, I'm very sorry.
Do you really not want to come back to work?
I don't think it's something I can handle.
Look at that.
He won't leave his mother's side.
That's Ha Ni.
She gave birth to a pony not so long ago. Aren't they beautiful?
You're right.
Mi Rae.
Yes?
At first,
everyone needs help.
Did Ha Ni run fast from the start?
There's no one who can run from the beginning.
At first,
I was very scared, and I had a hard time, too.
I thought my dream had finally come true,
but I also had doubts on whether or not I could continue working.
I wasn't sure if it was the right thing to do.
Why?
When I first started work,
I was so excited to hear...
that I got hired.
But I lost someone I loved only after then.
We were about to get married.
At that time, I was an assistant producer,
so I didn't get to have any personal life.
I couldn't be there to say goodbye to him.
That's when I started to have doubts about this job.
I couldn't see the point in working.
I went to work while crying every day.
I went to the editing room while crying.
I wanted to run away then, but I had nowhere to go.
Somehow I ended up here.
I didn't think you would've had such an experience.
People all get scared and want to run away.
It's not just you. I was like that, too.
However, I just didn't have anywhere to go.
I didn't have the courage to quit, either.
Mi Rae.
It's okay to be scared.
I won't tell you to be brave.
It's okay to feel scared. There's nothing wrong with that.
Just know that...
there's someone by your side who understands...
what you're going through.
Are you crying?
I'm just sweating.
It's hot.
Feel free to tell me whenever you're scared or having a hard time.
I'm more of your neighbour than...
a drama producer.
Okay.
Thank you for saying that.
Goodbye.
Why won't you listen and go home with us?
Spend some time alone. Come when you're ready.
Sang Sik.
Yes?
I'm sorry...
for making you worried.
It's fine as long as you're okay.
Are you okay, Sang Sik?
Of course.
Goodness.
I lost someone I loved only after then.
We were about to get married.
All he did was work hard, but you killed him overnight!
How can you call this an accident?
- An accident?
-  Mum.
Bring me the person who was in charge!
Tell him to come here!
How could this happen to my son? How could this happen?
How is this possible?
I have a lot to apologise for.
Well, I'm the one who told you that things were going well...
without knowing that Mi Rae had disappeared. It's my fault.
How are your knees?
Are you sure it didn't get worse after you fell again a while ago?
I was startled then, but I'm fine now.
Did you get a scratch?
It's okay. It's only a scratch.
By the way,
I didn't mean to,
but I overheard what you said to Mi Rae.
Is that so?
It's all in the past. It's okay.
You must have gone through a lot.
When someone who's always been around is no longer there,
it's difficult to get through each day.
Come to think of it, the same happened to you.
I still feel like I lost my wife yesterday.
Anyway,
thank you for everything you did for Mi Rae today.
So you're being discharged from the hospital tomorrow?
Yes.
Let's go in now.
Wait.
There are some things that you just know because you're an adult.
I know how this man is feeling right at this moment...
even if I don't put a stethoscope over his heart.
There are some things that you don't know even when you're an adult.
What is this woman sitting next to me about to tell me?
I can't even make a guess.
Sang Sik.
Do you...
like me?
(Second to Last Love)
Am I the only one who remembers it? In this room, we...
When I'm attracted to someone, I won't hold back any more.
Ye Ji is already hanging out with a boy and...
They... They... Why didn't you tell me about it?
Shouldn't things become easier when you get older?
You should be able to tell right away...
if you're meant to be with the person or not.