Wait.
Sang Sik.
Do you...
like me?
What are you talking about?
I asked you if you like me.
Why would you ask me that all of a sudden?
Is it too sudden?
Whether I like someone or not,
it's not important at all.
Nothing will change.
Why not?
Even if I like someone,
it won't change anything in my life.
That's why there is no point in liking someone...
or not liking someone.
It's all meaningless.
I understand what you mean.
Of course,
I think that way sometimes, too.
I sometimes think that I'm too old to fall in love.
However,
you won't know if it'll change your life or not unless you try it.
Even if your life doesn't change a lot,
your heart can change.
What's wrong with liking someone?
To think that I won't have those kinds of feelings again...
makes me feel sorry for myself.
I'm not sure.
I'm used to this life already.
I decided not to live like that any more.
Just like the dramas I make,
I'll like someone as much as I want when I do.
I'll wait for him with butterflies in my stomach.
When I hold his hand,
my heart will race. I might even get jealous.
That's what I plan on doing.
That's...
You're single and unmarried, so that's possible.
Why are you asking me that all of a sudden anyway?
Take this injury for example.
Why would you put your life on the line with the horse going wild?
Is this...
just you doing your job again?
Isn't it a human instinct...
to help those in trouble?
Are you saying that...
you don't have...
any feelings for me?
Well,
it's natural for a man to help a woman in need.
Helping a neighbour is...
a duty and also common sense.
I'm glad.
I was worried that...
I might feel pressured if you actually liked me.
Why would you worry about that?
I didn't want us to be awkward.
You're the strange one to feel awkward with me.
Maybe you're the one who has feelings for me.
No way.
Gosh.
That was harsh.
Since I hate being awkward, let's be friends.
- Friends?
-  What's wrong?
You don't think a man and a woman can become friends?
Don't tell me you're that old fashioned.
I'm not that bad.
Good.
Here.
Let's be friends.
Gosh.
Seriously?
(Second to Last Love)
(Episode 8)
Friends?
We're friends?
Hold on.
My goodness, I didn't know that.
Cheers.
What should I do?
She doesn't even remember it.
This is huge problem.
They grew up a lot, didn't they?
Yes.
I was here with Jun Woo when Ha Ni was born,
but she's a mum now.
Time sure flies.
All of my horses here grew up healthy thanks to Chief Ko.
He paid a lot of attention to us.
I'm so thankful.
I'm also growing up well thanks to my brother.
Are you still friends with Jun Woo?
Of course.
You two were friends since you were small,
but you're adults now.
Don't you guys have something going on?
No way.
You know what we're like.
You never know.
There's Jun Woo.
Hey, Ko Mi Rae.
- Hello, Sir.
-  Hey.
I made this. Have some.
You always bring me food.
Hurry up and take her.
Of course I want her around,
but her brother will be worried.
Okay, I'll snatch her away.
Why did you come? I told you not to.
Hey, Ha Ni.
You're so big now.
You should have brought some alcohol.
Do you want some? I can get some right now.
Forget it.
What happened at the broadcasting station?
It took a lot for Sang Sik to agree to this.
Are you really not going back?
It's awkward not to go back after hearing Min Joo's story.
What did she tell you?
Min Joo...
seems to have a broken past.
A broken past?
- Min Joo does?
-  Don't ask me any more.
Of course she has a past at her age. You do, too.
Forget it. I'm done.
What? You hardly ate.
What are you doing? Let's go home.
That smells.
It's a stable. What do you expect?
Do you like it that much here?
Why not go to a hotel?
I don't have money for that.
I like it here. It puts my mind at ease.
You're like a filly.
I'm more experienced than you think.
You little...
Just leave. I'm going to sleep. I'm tired.
What a troublemaker.
Gosh.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm going to take a break before going back.
This isn't some hotel.
I guess you're an adult now.
You used to tell me everything whenever we came here.
I want to be alone.
I guess today isn't the day.
Don't make us worry so much. Come back tomorrow morning, okay?
Got it?
I got it.
I wanted to congratulate you on your job.
I was happy to see you finally work on something...
you really enjoy.
I really wanted to tell you that.
What are you making? It smells so good.
I made abalone porridge for Min Joo.
She's so lucky. She gets to have Jun Woo's porridge.
It's nothing.
I made a lot, so have some for dinner tonight.
All right. You should go see her since she's alone at the hospital.
Okay.
Aunt Mi Rae didn't come home last night.
- I know.
-  What happened?
She started working with our neighbour, didn't she?
Is she working overtime already?
Ask Mi Rae yourself.
Honey, please drop off Hoon.
Why won't you have breakfast? You look so down.
Give me my bag.
This? Here you go.
- I'll be back.
-  Okay.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
Have a good day.
Good luck!
- Thank you.
-  Bye.
Min Joo.
My goodness. Why did you come?
You should rest for a few more days. Why are you getting discharged?
I even made porridge for you.
Why did you go see Mi Rae yesterday?
You need to rest.
I'm fine now.
Let's go.
We have lots of time, so we'll take it slow.
I better go to the office.
Like that?
No, not today. I won't allow it.
Who was the man that stayed with me when I was sick?
Eun Ho.
I'm reminded of Eun Ho when I look at Jun Woo.
Even including all of my feelings from back then.
What is it? Does it hurt somewhere?
No.
The local tourist department will focus on the city promotion,
while developing tourist attractions.
As for the drama project,
Head Chief Shin will spearhead it.
Great work.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
Thank you.
Chief Ko. Take a look at this.
The business support department got a bonus...
for working on the Woori Grape Festival.
My staff think your team should take it...
for a team dinner since you worked hard on the ground that day.
Team dinner? No, thank you.
Come on. It was raining cats and dogs,
and you guys worked so hard on it. Take it.
Are you looking into the internal spy that made a deal with...
a company that sells cheaper imports instead of our city's grapes?
Chief Ko, what are you talking about?
If you're too busy, I can ask the police for you.
Go head. I hope you do.
You won't take this bonus, then?
I'd rather not take it to avoid getting on your boat.
What? What did you say?
On what grounds are you saying this?
- Chief Ko.
-  Yes?
Are you saying the culprit...
behind switching the grapes during the festival is...
You should stay out of it.
Is this going to be all right?
You're not young any more.
If you keep this up, a promotion is out of the question.
Half of our middle-aged lives are full of failures anyway.
It's not so bad to age like this.
What's with the head chief anyway?
Starting today, it's the real thing.
I'm nervous to do it in front of our citizens.
I'm confident. I think it'll be fun.
Here's yours.
- Thank you.
-  Good luck.
Shall we head out?
- Yes!
-  Yes!
(Happiness Concert)
- Hello.
-  Welcome.
What's going on?
As you can see, we decided to go with...
the strings quartet for the promotional event for this year.
You can go back to your desks.
But Head Chief Shin, we worked really hard.
Did you say Ms Han Song Yi wrote the song?
Yes, Sir.
This is why you're on contract.
You'll never become full time at this rate.
If you don't want to be kicked out before your contract is up,
you should be more creative...
instead coming up with things like that.
What you just said is an insult to my staff, and an act of contempt.
That's why you should stop bothering us and go back in.
This is an order!
No, Chief Ko.
How can you go to work like that?
You should go to work, too. People will be upset if you're closed.
I have someone working there.
Do you? That's a relief.
I'm not sure if it's a relief.
What do you mean?
There's something about it.
I'll tell you later.
What about Mi Rae? Did she say anything?
Don't worry about her.
I bet she'll go back.
How do you know that?
I grew up with her. Of course I know.
I see.
You two must be close.
Don't misunderstand, though.
We're just friends.
Friends?
Can a man and a woman...
be friends?
Of course.
All right.
I think so, too.
Go have some of the porridge at home, and take it easy at work.
Okay. I will.
Song Yi.
Even though I'm a contract worker,
I was proud of my job, and I did my best.
I know.
What do you know?
You don't know anything.
On your first day here,
I know you stayed behind after everyone left...
so that you could study our work processes.
I also know that you come in earlier than others...
to clean their desks.
You're also the one behind stocking up our supplies.
Even during the grape festival, I know you were...
more tedious than me at picking out the products.
Chief Ko...
I know it all. So don't let someone like him hurt you.
But...
I've closed my heart on you, too.
Me?
During the grape festival,
I saw you run away...
in the rain...
with SBC's Producer Kang Min Joo.
What?
Run!
That's because there was so much rain.
I mean, why do I have to explain this to you?
You guys aren't what I think you are, right?
Tell me you're not.
No, it's not like that.
Then what was it?
It was just...
We're just neighbours and friends.
Friends?
Yes.
Chief Ko.
I had no idea.
Song Yi.
Song Yi, please...
Someone will see us.
- Chief Ko.
-  Song Yi.
Song Yi, don't do this. We're at work.
- Song Yi, please.
-  My goodness.
Song Yi.
Hold on.
Producer Kang.
Mi Rae.
I can't believe you're here on your crutches.
You should have took more time off.
There's no time for that. We better hurry back after we eat.
This is what Ae Ri wrote, and this is what I reorganised.
Hold on.
Before we proceed, tell me why I have to...
work with Ko Mi Rae.
She may look sloppy and incompetent...
on the outside.
However, her perspective towards people...
is so warm and beautiful.
I want to steal it away from her.
Then what is it that she has and I don't?
I see.
Being unsanitary?
No.
She's curious about things no one cares about.
Observational skills.
You're actually pretty cute.
- How old are you?
-  35 years old.
You look really young for your age.
Then...
I'm older than you.
Why are you lying? You guys are the same age.
Gosh.
Who cares about age at work?
Writer Ko, you can just call him Producer Nam.
I'm not an official writer yet.
Okay, Producer Nam.
All right, let's start the meeting as we eat.
Look right here.
Yes?
Mi Rae went back to work?
No, I'm glad.
Okay.
How long has it been? It's so nice to see you.
What brings you here?
Why do you think? I'm here for the city drama project.
What a nice place you work at. Why didn't you tell me?
Are you saying the famous Na Joo Yeon...
is on Producer Han's drama?
- Yes.
-  How can he do that?
You used to be his assistant. He wants to beat you so badly.
Gosh.
If they get picked, is it finished for us?
- Bingo.
-  Who is Producer Han?
It's him right there.
Producer Kang. I heard you were in the hospital.
Are you okay?
You should have rested longer.
- Let's go work.
-  Okay.
Okay.
Writer Ko.
I thought you packed up and left.
Did something happen?
Not at all.
You're not a coward like someone I know.
Good luck.
A coward?
I plan on doing that.
There's someone I want to beat.
Who?
- Me?
-  We'll see...
who gets the drama project.
Good day.
She's just like her brother.
Give me the money to repair the camera.
- What if I don't?
-  Come on, it's not much.
If it's not much, why are you asking me for it?
53 dollars is a lot of money for me.
You're the first student to rip money off of me.
- Here.
-  Gosh.
I said, no discounts.
Three dollars.
I don't have change.
Even delivery makes us fight when we sell used products.
- Delivery?
-  Delivery fee included.
You're lucky I'm not taking interest.
Hey.
I'm Hoon. Park Hoon.
Yes?
He can't come to dinner?
Of course something came up.
I have a life too, you know.
No, no.
I don't want to meet someone like him again.
I'm hanging up.
You got dumped.
Are you still single?
Just focus on your book.
What's wrong?
Is this...
made by the owner here?
Why do you ask?
It's a little salty.
Oh, no.
How did you know?
Did you...
make this?
I told you not to take customers without me.
Hey, how can you leave your store like that?
Hello.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Sir.
It was break time, so I was cleaning when a customer came.
Hey, what is going on?
You should feel thankful...
that she's making business while you're away.
Why are you abusing your power on this beautiful young lady?
I'm not.
He is.
He's abusing his power because I like him more.
Ji Sun.
Anyway,
you're always leaving the store these days.
What's gotten into you?
What are you talking about?
He's right.
Your next door neighbour.
Kang Min Joo.
Am I right?
Who? Your next door neighbour?
Come with me.
His next door neighbour? She came to my bar before.
What do we do with Sang Sik?
What's wrong with you?
I'm just saying the truth so that there aren't any misunderstandings.
He seemed close with you.
If you keep this up, you'll be out in a day, not a month. Understand?
You said you wouldn't get involved even if I like...
my neighbour or anybody else.
You said you would just remain as a friend.
That's right, I won't get involved.
I won't.
I'm happy as it is now.
I'm happy to see your face every day.
Now, I can finally breathe again.
You're obsessed.
If you want to get away from me, stop thinking that way.
I'm trying, too.
I'm thankful that you let me stay here.
Don't say anything stupid to other people.
If you do that again,
I won't go easy next time.
Remember that.
He's still at it with her?
Hello, Min Joo.
What happened to your knee?
Your cartilage?
The emotional shock must be bigger.
That's why you need to exercise a lot.
I haven't seen you at the gym.
Working out can't stop you from ageing.
You can't stop it, but you can delay it.
Look at that.
That sushi has been going around forever.
This is the fifth time.
It looks like me.
I went on countless blind dates and job interviews,
and now I'm old and wilted.
No one would ever choose me any more.
In the end, I'll go bad and get thrown out.
- Gosh.
-  Goodness.
I thought I would never come down from my high heels.
Now that I'm older, I don't care about fashion.
I love low and comfortable shoes.
I ask myself what I've been doing, too.
I'm just as lost as I was in my teenage years.
If I'm this old, it should be different from then.
But I'm still worried about the same problems.
It feels unfair.
I'm afraid this will last until I die.
We should at least marry before we die.
No, no.
Marriage isn't the answer. No way.
Then at least let me date.
How is it going with your next door neighbour?
- Which one?
-  My goodness.
Of course it's Jun Woo. Why would I talk about the civil servant?
Min Joo. It's about Jun Woo.
I'll only tell you what I saw.
Do you remember the mysterious woman I told you about before?
I saw her working at his cafe.
She was all over him.
She begged him to let her stay in his life.
She looked really into him.
His past lover?
That's suspicious.
I guess that's what he meant earlier.
Did you know?
He told me that he would tell me later.
I thought you were finally getting to date.
Nothing is easy.
I wonder if Min Joo...
is planning to marry Jun Woo if things go well with him?
Why don't you ask her directly if you're that curious?
All of these boys look the same to me.
That is not true at all.
Bigbang.
G-Dragon, Tae Yang, Dae Sung,
Seung Ri and T.O.P. There are five members.
T.O.P is the name of the drink. It's pronounced as "Top".
I know, "Top".
This is read as "Bap".
It's B.A.P.
Gosh, E.X.O has so many members.
It's EXO.
You should've studied English this hard when you were in school.
When I said T.O.P, you corrected me and said it's "Top".
So I read B.A.P as "Bap", and you said it's B.A.P.
Then I said it's E.X.O, and you're saying it's EXO.
What do you want me to do, seriously?
This is exactly why Ye Ji can't talk to you and thinks...
you're incapable of love.
You think love is like cancer, don't you?
I'm trying, okay?
All mums think of those boys as their own sons and love them.
Do you not do any housework at home and watch TV all day?
Stop wasting your time and look after Hoon.
On that note,
I want to talk to you about taking out a loan under your name...
to send Hoon to a school in China.
Gosh, I'm so sick of this. You're going on about it again.
I'm sick and tired of this. My goodness.
Yes. I'm coming to pick up my laptop now.
Goodness.
My gosh!
What are you doing now?
Don't make me talk because this won't be easy.
Let me down. I'm heavy. What if we end up rolling down together?
It's exhausting, isn't it?
Yes.
Park Jun Woo.
I like hearing you calling my name.
Shall we...
try seeing each other?
While making so many romantic dramas and melodramas,
I've realised that our reality can't be like dramas.
Whether it's love knocking on your door...
or you falling passionately in love, love doesn't come by easily in life.
Love shines the most when it's between two young people,
and that's still the kind of dramas I make.
That area isn't good for education, so the real estate prices are bad.
By the way, what kind of supplements do you take these days?
I don't take any supplements.
Everyone goes to yoga classes to lose weight,
but I think walking is the best.
Especially hiking. It's excellent.
Which mountain do you go to?
The little hill in front of my house.
For people in my generation, love has lost its place in our hearts...
before we even realised it.
However, I regained the desire to be in love again.
It's because coming across someone who likes me this much...
may never happen again in my life.
You really meant what you said earlier, right?
Then we're a couple now.
Well, what I meant was...
that we should spend more time together...
to get to know each other better.
It's the same thing.
No, it's different.
How is it different?
You need to be with the person to get to know him or her better.
Is there a generation gap between us or what?
Being with the person means that you're in a relationship.
Getting to know each other is...
What is it? Just testing the waters?
Being able to get out of it easily if things don't go well?
Yes, something like that.
You need to learn more about me,
and I also don't know a lot about you yet.
So you're scared.
What?
What you're saying is that you're scared of jumping in.
Yes, I admit.
You'll find out when you're older.
Meeting new people isn't easy.
Getting into a relationship is even more difficult.
Why do things become more difficult as we age?
Shouldn't things become easier as we get older?
With age, we gain experience and ability to make better decisions.
We also learn to trust our intuition,
so you should be able to know right away...
whether you're meant to be with the person or not.
So what do you think?
You're so handsome.
Gosh, seriously.
I'm quite good-looking, aren't I?
Goodness.
Tae Yang, Seung Ri, T.O.P,
Dae Sung and G-Dragon. Bigbang.
- Hello! Have a great day.
-  Hello.
Hello. Good morning.
Block B has... Right. Block B's members are Zico, Tae Il,
Jae Hyo, B-Bomb, P.O...
P.O...
Gosh, what are they doing in the car?
(This car was just washed. Keep a safe distance.)
EXO... EXO has...
(Let's sing "Woori City Song" together.)
All right. Will everyone be able to do it here?
What can we do? We have no choice.
Song Yi, best of luck.
Thank you.
All right, everyone. If we give up,
"Woori City Song" will disappear into history forever.
Yes. If our performance doesn't get any feedback, that will be it.
Let's think of this as our last chance and do our very best.
We're like independence fighters.
A secret organisation.
Let's do this. Let's march on, fight and win. We can do it.
- Okay.
-  Sure.
- Let's march on, fight and win.
-  Let's march on, fight and win.
- We can do it!
-  We can do it!
Producer Kang!
Hello.
Where are your crutches?
I'm better now.
Are you really okay now?
If not, I can just use the crutches or get hospitalised again.
No, you have to work with me.
I overcame my indecisiveness and decided to do this with you.
Thanks for saying that.
I really mean it.
Knowing that someone needs me made me so happy.
I always felt that not many people can understand me,
but I feel like I have someone on my side now.
I'm grateful to know that my sincerity reached out to you.
Also, I wanted to talk to you about Jun Woo.
He seems immature and carefree,
but he actually has a mature soul who has an wounded heart.
He feels lonely easily, too.
He doesn't fall for someone easily, either.
Hearing that he's into someone...
makes me so happy and grateful...
"You should be good to him." That's what you want to say, right?
Yes. I'm sure you'll be good to him, but I just wanted to...
Jun Woo is very lucky...
to have such a great friend like you.
No. We fought and beat up each other while growing up together.
He's like the bane of my existence.
Hey, Jun Woo!
Look at this. I like seeing the two of you leaving work together.
You should've called.
I was worried that you'd decide to work for longer if I called.
I'll take the subway.
You're so smart.
Why? Join us for dinner.
- No.
-  I don't want to.
See you later.
But...
Get home safely!
Bye!
Shall we get going, too?
I feel so sorry.
My new neighbourhood is a strange place.
I don't feel alone even when I'm by myself.
I feel as though I'm with people even when I'm alone.
There's more humanism than melodrama.
That's what this neighbourhood is like.
- Let's support Woori City together.
-  Let's sing together.
Woori City is the best!
- The forest has a nice breeze
-  The forest has a nice breeze.
Let's sing together!
I judged you by your looks and didn't think you'd be this friendly.
What do I look like?
You look like you've never had to lift a finger.
You look destined to live a comfortable life.
I met Jun Woo, so I could be...
happy for the rest of my life.
Why is Jun Woo so cold to you by the way?
I mean, you're so good to him.
I guess he doesn't like me.
What are you talking about? You two looked so lovely together...
when you visited him a year ago.
Things can chance overnight in romantic relationships, you know?
You sound so knowledgeable.
He's treating me like that now,
but I guess things will get better soon.
You're optimistic, too. I like that.
What's this?
I washed my husband's trousers without even checking the pockets.
I guess he works out these days.
What do you mean?
What's this thing from a fitness centre?
He doesn't work out at all.
He stays home all day even when I ask him to go to the spring with me.
The only exercise he does is breathing.
My classmates created a group chat.
Group chat?
Don't kids do it to bully classmates?
It's a serious social issue these days.
It's not about our classmates.
It's about you.
Me?
What did I do?
I'll show you the chat room, but don't be shocked, okay?
What is it about?
Why would I get shocked over kids' chitchats?
My gosh.
What is wrong with him these days?
He has such thick skin.
Will he really be transferred to a different school?
- Nice!
-  No, no.
That rumour has been going around since last year.
He'll probably stay here forever.
I want him to be gone soon.
Goodbye, Captain.
Goodbye.
Don't let it get to your heart.
It's only a small number of our class.
I won't, of course.
This is nothing. These silly kids.
Goodness gracious.
Gosh, are you okay?
Pardon?
Yes.
I'm fine.
What's the matter?
I feel so little and insignificant.
Life feels so futile right now.
When I was younger,
I just thought I should do better next time.
But as I'm getting older, I find myself thinking,
"Will I be able to do better next time?"
I don't feel confident.
It sounds like you've been running at your full speed.
Being an adult is more difficult than we think.
You have to reward yourself here and there...
in order to keep running without tiring yourself out.
Reward myself?
Meeting someone like you who really understands me...
is a reward for me in and of itself.
Thanks for saying that.
There were moments in my life...
that I shined as brightly as them.
I'll see you later!
- Honey. Wait a second.
-  Yes.
Wear this.
- Did you make it?
-  Yes.
- Oh, my.
-  I put a pendant on it, too.
"Sang Sik".
- Is it a little loose on you?
-  No, it fits perfectly.
I love it.
- Ta-da.
-  Look at that!
You made two?
They're our matching bracelets.
These bracelets will bring us luck.
Only good things await us.
Of course. Let me see.
Sang Sik and Hui Soo. They look amazing.
Those moments are all in the past now.
However,
my family is shining brightly in their place.
Hello.
Have we met?
We met during Jun Woo's class the other day.
Don't you remember?
You're the one who took the magazine Jun Woo is in, right?
Yes.
I work here now.
I'm helping Jun Woo out.
I see.
It looks like his taste in women has changed a lot.
He never used to be interested in older women.
It sounds like you're very into him.
Yes. Since your job is making dramas,
you're quick at figuring out what's going on.
I hate ultra dramatic soap operas.
Especially for what we have going on here.
I'd hate to see that kind of plot unfolding.
What exactly do we have going on here?
Don't worry.
I won't grab you by the hair at least.
It sounds like you watched a lot of Korean dramas in Canada.
Min Joo.
Ji Sun, what are you doing here?
I'm Min Ji Sun.
You live next door, so I thought I should introduce myself.
See you around.
Are you all right? Did anything happen?
Nothing happened.
She's pretty and cute.
Goodness.
I don't get kids these days. Gosh, seriously.
I think that's Ye Ji.
What? Where?
That little brat...
She was going on about how I'm incapable of love,
and she's already...
I can't let it slide.
Let's just go unless you want to be called a fogey again.
Things will get very awkward if you pull over now.
But still...
What should I do with her?
I really want my dad to start dating like us.
Then you might get a stepmother. Will you be okay with that?
I'm all grown up, so it doesn't matter.
I have my own life,
and my dad needs a bit of love in his life.
These days, it's hard to find a family that is as tight as yours.
Who'd dare to try become a part of it?
Someone like my next-door neighbour...
who's single and around his age would be perfect.
Then you should befriend her first.
She's not right for him.
Why do you say that?
She doesn't keep her words and is disrespectful towards me.
Plus, Uncle Jun Woo announced to everyone that he's dating her.
You should go home now.
I'll walk you to your door.
It's okay. I'll get in trouble is any of my family sees us.
Why? Are you embarrassed of me?
So are we keeping our relationship a secret?
I think it's too early to tell everyone.
Why do you think that?
No specific reason. It's just how I feel.
That... That little rat...
I must teach him a lesson.
Actually,
I've been upset because I think Hae Dam likes you.
That's not true. You're mistaken.
I'm not interested in her at all.
I know that.
That's why I'm spending time with you like this.
That little...
What should I do?
Go in.
Hey, you're home.
Where's Sang Sik?
He's dealing with an emergency because of Ye Ji.
What? What are you talking about?
- Sang Sik, there you are.
-  Yes. Give it to me.
I'm home.
Hi, Ye Ji. Were you at the library?
- Yes.
-  Hey, it's really late.
Be careful when you come home late at night.
Will Hoon ever go to a library in his life?
The air is bad inside libraries.
You sound so pathetic right now. My goodness.
Sang Sik, pass me the watermelon.
Dad.
Get changed now.
What's going on?
I want to talk to you.
Go ahead, I hear you.
What have you been doing lately?
What do you mean?
I go to school, private classes and the library.
I'm not talking about that.
Are you busy dating someone?
Who told you that?
It's not important who told me.
I can't believe you're already...
Dad, I'm 15 years old.
I liked someone when I was in elementary school.
I also liked someone in kindergarten.
You didn't say much then, so why now?
That's because...
you're all grown up.
Why are you wearing something so short?
It's summer. What can I do when it's so hot?
You'd better not see that rascal Hyun Seok dressed like this.
Gosh, I can't take this any longer.
Where are you going again?
Ye Ji, Ye Ji.
Goodness.
What's going on?
Ye Ji...
and that boyfriend of hers...
Did she kiss him?
They must have, don't you think?
I thought you trusted her.
Trusting and being concerned for her are different.
People will think it's all because she was raised without a mum.
Come on.
You should get her a mother, then.
Even if you don't get married again, you should at least date someone.
You're all hopeless.
Ye Ji.
Do you want me to expose your private life by saying...
that you are dating Uncle Jun Woo on social media?
You should've kept your promise like an adult...
or you shouldn't have made a promise at all.
You should have been clear on your judgement and action, no?
Are you done?
Please speak if you have anything to say.
Let me make it clear.
I've never exposed your private life to anyone.
Even more, I've never talked about you to your father.
I saw it with my own eyes and heard it with my own ears.
- What?
-  I heard you talk about me.
That's why Dad said...
you shouldn't judge on your own and told you to tell him next time...
so that I can grow mature and be healthy.
That's the conversation you had in his study.
Wait.
I don't know why you're accusing me,
but the first thing is to find out where the misunderstanding started.
You told my dad that you saw me kiss Hyun Seok.
What are you talking about?
What?
You kissed him? It's not the other way around?
What are you talking about?
Ask your daughter yourself.
You didn't tell me about it when you saw that?
How could you fool me by teaming up with my child?
Who fooled who?
Silence could also be a lie.
Pretending not to know is worse.
Goodness. What are you talking about?
At her age, she can do that with her boyfriend.
"Boyfriend"?
Do you kiss your friend?
What?
What I mean is...
Well... I mean...
She's still a child.
She's only in middle school.
If you saw something like that, you should have told me.
What do you mean?
She didn't do anything wrong.
They kissed...
They smooched...
Well... They... Why didn't you tell me?
What's wrong with a kiss...
They can smooch if they want.
Are you saying that carelessly because she's not your child?
Children can also like someone and express their love.
They can hold hands if they like each other.
What's wrong with a kiss on the cheek?
She isn't young. At her age...
No, my child can't do that!
Nobody can touch my child!
- Dad.
-  You can't say that when...
you have no child of your own.
Don't even say things like that.
Why are you scolding her?
Just scold me.
Okay, follow me.
Goodness.
Gosh.
By the way, you're cool.
You're a contemporary woman.
"A contemporary woman"?
Where are we going?
Just follow me.
Dad.
Did Ye Ji scold you?
Yes.
More than her, Chief Ko scolded me.
What?
By the way,
about Ji Sun...
Ji Sun?
She likes you a lot, doesn't she?
It's just that...
when I was in Canada,
I worked as an assistant chef at her house.
Her family was quite wealthy,
but she's the only child of divorced parents.
I felt bad to see her alone,
so I made a lot of Korean food for her.
Few years ago, she lost her parents in an accident and came to see me.
Have you tried soy sauce bibimbap?
It's his speciality.
No.
What about bulgogi japchae?
I haven't tried that, either.
Okay.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I wanted to tell you beforehand,
but I didn't want you to misunderstand. I'm sorry.
She'll go back to Canada in a month.
She says she wants to slowly part with me.
It's hard to understand, isn't it?
No, I can understand.
What? You don't feel jealous, and you're not suspicious?
Must I feel that way?
You're too nonchalant.
I should have told you beforehand, then.
Anyway, Sang Sik should make up with Ye Ji...
since she's going through puberty and is sensitive.
I think he's the one going through it.
Why is that?
"Do you kiss your friend?"
What is he talking about?
What is it?
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
Like what she said, what's wrong with expressing...
my feelings honestly?
You're still too young for that.
Should I be of certain age?
Then when can I hold hands and kiss someone?
Is it written in a textbook or the law?
Why should you make the standard?
It's not me. When you become an adult,
you can do all those things.
I'm not a child.
I'm becoming an adult, to be exact.
When I was young, you complimented me for being mature.
Now, you're talking as if becoming an adult is a bad thing.
That's right.
Becoming an adult isn't always good.
There isn't a set time to date someone you like.
Anyone can like someone at any age.
Does it happen only during a certain age?
Does it happen so easily?
All that matters is that I know how to control my feelings, no?
Ye Ji.
To be honest,
I'm scared to see you...
mature every day.
Are you scared that I'm becoming an adult?
It's not that.
I don't know how to treat you...
when you continue to mature day by day.
I'm flustered and scared when it comes to that.
I've never practised it.
It's my first time.
Starting from your birth...
to you turning 5 or 10 years old...
Even when you become 20 or 30 years old,
you'll always be my first.
Just when I'm about to get used to your age...
Just when that happens, you start maturing again.
It's always my first...
to see what's going on with you, so it's interesting and new.
But I also wonder if I'll be able to do well.
"Can I keep up with my daughter who's changing so much?"
I'm scared that I might not be able to do a good job.
I have to understand you more because you don't have a mother.
Or at least, I want to be the best father there is.
But unlike my determination,
I'm worried that I might not be able to keep up.
Ye Ji.
Here, your mum and I talked about something.
While you were...
growing up inside your mother's womb,
I said that...
when you're born, every day will be strange at first,
but that I'll treat you well.
I made a promise with your mum.
Even if...
I'm awkward and can't keep up with how fast you grow,
I hope...
you won't hate me or get disappointed in me.
Goodness.
You're all grown up.
Do you kiss your friend?
Oh, no.
There isn't a set time to date someone you like.
Anyone can like someone at any age.
Does it happen only during a certain age?
Does it happen so easily?
Sang Sik.
Do you...
like me?
May I come in for a minute?
Sure, come in.
What brings you here?
Is it only me who remembers?
That day, in this room...
That... Well... That's...
So you already knew.
Whether I like someone or not,
it's not important at all.
Nothing will change.
Why not?
Even if I like someone,
it won't change anything in my life.
That's why...
you didn't say anything...
because nothing would change.
It won't change.
Min Joo.
Didn't you say silence is also a lie?
To be honest, I...
I started...
dating someone.
I thought...
I should tell you.
Okay.
That's good.
Is it...
really good?
You said you wanted to give your all to the person you fell for.
That's right.
I'm going to.
Then,
see you.
Wait a minute.
This...
is very similar to mine.
There's no way.
Mine has...
"SS" engraved on it.
I lost someone I loved.
I was about to get married, too.
Don't let go.
Don't let go!
(Second to Last Love)
I'm your first priority from now on.
Jun Woo is everything to me.
Don't play games with your life.
How do you know Chief Ko?
You've forgotten about him, right?
I'm talking about Eun Ho.
Don't I look great with him?
You do.
You'll move aside for Jun Woo?
- Have you sinned or what?
-  I think so.
If this unlucky prediction is true,
it'll be difficult to endure it.