I started...
dating someone.
I thought...
I should tell you.
Okay.
That's good.
Then,
see you.
Wait a minute.
This...
is very similar to mine.
There's no way.
Mine has...
"SS" engraved on it.
I lost someone I loved.
I was about to get married, too.
- Sang Sik.
-  Don't let go.
Don't let go!
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Where...
did you get that?
My wife gave it to me.
I see.
Then...
I guess it's something similar.
Didn't you grab me because you had something to say?
No, it's nothing.
I see.
It's a lucky bracelet.
Only good things will happen to us from now on.
Of course.
Sang Sik, Hui Soo.
It's pretty.
I don't know what it is,
but Eun Ho...
was clasping onto it.
(Second to Last Love)
(Episode 9)
Should we...
take a break over there?
- Should we?
-  Yes.
I used to play here a lot when I was a kid.
This must be a memorable place for you.
I used to hate it here, though.
Why is that?
After having a fun day here and the sun starts to set,
all of my friends' mums came...
and took them away one by one.
- They went home for dinner.
-  Let's go home and eat.
I was so jealous of them back then.
I was left alone...
and wondered why my parents were always so busy...
and why they didn't get along.
I resented them.
That's whey I decided...
to become someone who makes delicious food.
I wanted to make food...
for people that are alone.
Is that why you invited me when I moved in?
Food is all about sharing.
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
Hello.
It's nice to see you two working out together.
I wanted to go for runs as soon as I moved here.
I'm finally doing it.
We went on the regular route you and I go to,
and she really liked it.
Good idea. It has great views.
Yes, it was really nice.
The spring water was really fresh.
I see.
- I better get ready for work.
-  Let's go.
- Bye, Sang Sik.
-  Bye.
- Bye.
- Wasn't it hot?
-  It was okay.
Kang Min Joo.
I hope...
she's not who I think she is.
I hope I'm wrong...
about this ominous feeling.
- Right.
-  What?
Give me your phone.
- My phone?
-  Yes.
(Park Jun Woo)
Why did you save me as Park Jun Woo?
What should I save it as then?
Think about it and then edit it.
I'll check later.
I saved my number as number one.
When you're in an emergency, just press one.
From now on, Park Jun Woo is number one...
to Kang Min Joo.
You should go in.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
(Woori City Chief Ko's day)
This is crazy.
Look at how many people saw the video.
Chief Ko's a star now.
Song Yi, when did you take Chief Ko's videos?
I took them whenever...
he was working or running an event.
I didn't know people would like it this much.
Isn't it more popular because he keeps getting it wrong?
I don't think people would have liked it as much if he was perfect.
"Chief Ko is so humane. He's the best."
"What a hard worker. Go Chief."
"He just keeps on making mistakes. It's so funny."
Everyone's complimenting him.
I guess everyone likes him just like me.
Local Tourist Department. You did great.
Bravo, bravo.
The video of Woori City went viral,
and it was also introduced on the newspaper and the news.
Thanks to that, there are more tourists now,
and the businesses are booming again.
One more thing while we're on the topic.
Starting today, you will participate in the city drama project.
The drama project?
That means we can be a part of the drama project, right?
Of course.
With Head Chief Shin here, you'll help with the planning,
production and promotion.
As you already know, this project is an extensive event.
We need more people, so I've asked the deputy mayor.
After seeing what you've done, we decided to work with you.
I hope we get along.
Deputy Mayor.
Chief Ko, I need to speak to you about this project.
Come with me.
Have a good day.
What?
What are you doing?
You should have just run me over.
What?
He might be just a fling for you,
but Jun Woo is everything to me.
If I die because of you,
you'll live your life feeling guilty.
Jun Woo would never be able to forget about me, either.
Are you insane?
I want to be remembered even if that's what it takes.
You wouldn't understand.
- Listen, Ji Sun.
-  Of course you wouldn't.
You wouldn't know unless you've lost someone before.
I do know.
I had to let someone I love go before me,
and I suffered enough to be tempted to follow him.
You're still young...
to be able to put your life on the line for love.
- What?
-  When you lose someone you love,
you feel like you'd go crazy at first.
It hurts so much that you want to die.
But after a while, you can eat.
In no time, you'll be laughing again.
If you're alive, you'll live on.
Sometimes if you keep living,
you might even meet someone else.
The dead is the one at loss,
so don't be like this. Don't joke around with life.
It's just too foolish.
I want to be remembered even if that's what it takes.
You wouldn't know unless you've lost someone before.
Don't look at the clock.
Let's only live in the moment.
Okay?
(Resume)
I saw that you used to be a drama producer before.
I think you'd be the best fit for Woori City's drama project.
All I did was assist for a few years at the studio.
In any case, your degree and experiences...
are in the same field.
Can you please participate in the screening evaluation?
I believe someone like yourself will be very fair.
Ever since then,
I tried so hard to get away from the industry.
This is very similar to mine.
As if there is an invisible tie,
have I been pushed to a dead end where I can't avoid it any longer?
Our female lead will likely be Na Joo Yeon.
We found a good story from a new writer.
We'll hire a star writer to write the script.
I'll direct.
Great. What about you, Producer Kang?
Here.
Let's see.
A writer who hasn't debuted?
She's a nameless web comic artist?
Nam Ki Cheol is directing?
How is this going to work?
We plan on going to the city hall to interview them first.
If you don't make this, your department will be split.
I'll either send you to the suburbs, or to different departments.
You're trying to push us down even more? That won't happen.
I hope so, too.
You don't have a chance with that shabby of a group.
We might be shabby or we might be "The Avengers". You'll see.
I should go visit Woori City, too. Maybe I'll visit your new house.
Can I go?
Okay.
Don't visit her place.
Why not? Of course I should, we're close.
Don't think you can act that way just because you're married.
She has a boyfriend.
A boyfriend? Who?
Her next door neighbour.
What? Her next door neighbour?
Do you really not have any feelings for me?
Nothing at all?
- No.
-  They why were you so nice to me...
in Canada?
- That's...
-  Why?
Did you feel sorry for me?
Because my parents were fighting all the time...
and I was left alone?
Because you...
were like me.
You were like a child left alone in the playground.
I saw my childhood in you.
Jun Woo.
On top of that,
I was thankful that you ate and liked everything I cooked.
So...
I wasn't nice to you because I felt bad for you.
I did it for myself.
It wasn't out of sympathy.
It was only to comfort myself.
I'm selfish, right?
That's fine.
Us lonely people can live together.
No.
It hurts me more to see you.
You obsess over men saying it's love, and you depend on them.
It scares me because I feel like I'm seeing my mum.
Jun Woo.
I'm sorry.
I hope you'll find your own life and move on.
I mean it.
Then are you considering marriage with Jun Woo?
Marriage? I never even thought that far.
Then that's how much you like him.
To be honest, I'm not sure yet.
I don't know how much I like him.
I'm not sure...
if I like him at all.
Are you kidding me?
First,
if you want to find out if you like him or not,
imagine being in bed with him.
If you can't picture being with him, then he's out.
If you can, then you're good.
Well?
Can you imagine being with Jun Woo in bed?
I don't know. People will talk bad about me.
It's not like you're committing adultery.
People will talk bad about me if they knew.
Hey. Men date girls that are 20 years...
younger than them, and they even get married.
What's wrong if it's the other way around?
You're biased.
It's a lot of pressure, though.
I'm not a fan of Jun Woo.
Of course there's the age difference,
but it worries me that his ex-girlfriend is around.
Everyone has a past.
You can just clean that up.
I'd love a younger man.
I'm okay with everyone except for younger men.
How can I keep up with a young guy?
Just thinking about it makes me tired.
She's shaking.
I'm sure we'd break up when I get old.
What's the point?
It'd feel like walking on manholes with killer heels every day.
Actually, I'm not that confident, either.
That's why you should meet someone you're comfortable with.
Someone you can talk to like a friend.
Someone you can lean on time to time.
Where on earth are they?
Forget it.
A woman should always...
have their heart flutter in order to feel alive.
Don't you agree?
I don't know. Let's do a toast.
If you don't want him, let me have him.
Gosh.
There are no hand-me-downs in love.
Cheers.
You'll give her up for Jun Woo?
Give her up?
She lost someone she loved in her past.
I'm sure she went through a lot.
I know how that feels.
Of course you do.
Now that she met Jun Woo,
I hope things work out for her. I mean it.
Did you commit a crime or what?
Yes.
I think I did.
But...
if this ominous feeling turns out to be true,
it'll be really hard for me to deal with.
I'd feel so sorry to her.
There's something going on, isn't there?
In any case,
she just started a new life with Jun Woo.
It must have been a hard decision.
I don't want to ruin it for her.
Do you know what kind of person is the most annoying?
People who act like they're something they're not.
They act caring and more mature. But it's all an act.
That's the most annoying kind.
Your spitting on me.
Gosh.
Excuse me,
do you have this in a single packet instead of this 1 plus 1 deal?
They all come in sets. I don't have any single packets.
It's too much for one person.
You just moved in, right?
You live at Chief Ko's place.
Yes. There are a lot of single-person families these days.
I don't know why they would make this so big.
Do you want me to take it out?
No, I'll just take it.
Honey!
What's wrong?
Honey, why were you outside?
- Who... Who is that?
-  Hurry.
Did he stalk you?
Let's go inside. Let's hurry to my door.
We suddenly got a slew of visitors.
Our town isn't usually like this.
You must be really surprised. Look at that cold sweat.
Thank you.
Why are you wearing such a short skirt?
You must be going somewhere.
I'm sorry.
- My goodness.
-  Sang Sik.
What happened?
- Min Joo.
-  Jun Woo.
There was a strange man stalking her.
A strange man?
No, don't worry.
It's fine now.
- I better go in. Thank you.
-  No problem.
I was just on my way to pick up something.
You should go.
Okay.
- Min Joo.
-  My goodness!
Are you all right?
I didn't mean to surprise you.
You came in so suddenly. My heart dropped.
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure to knock or ring the bell next time.
Did you go get groceries?
Yes.
I was seeing my friends out...
and went to grab some groceries.
Don't go out by yourself late at night.
You should go with me when you get groceries.
Are they still together?
Just leave it. I can put it up by myself.
I'm almost done.
Gosh.
What happened?
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
- Did you touch something?
-  No, I just...
I just plugged in the pot to make you coffee.
The fuse must be out.
The fuse is out.
What should I do? It's too late.
You'll have to fix it tomorrow.
What?
Are you scared because it's dark?
No way.
Gosh.
What was that?
My goodness.
No way.
It can't be.
I can stay by myself. I'm not scared.
Didn't a strange guy follow you earlier?
You must be anxious since you don't have electricity.
I'll leave as soon as I see you fall asleep.
How can I sleep when someone is around?
It's not like I'm a stranger. Why can't you sleep?
I'd be too uncomfortable to sleep.
Are you uncomfortable with me?
No, the thing is...
You must be having weird thoughts.
Don't worry.
Just lie down. You must be tired.
You must be tired, too. You should go home.
No way.
I'm going to sleep over.
Stop joking around and leave.
Fine, I'll go in a bit.
- My gosh.
-  You're so awkward.
Gosh.
What do you like about an old lady like me?
What do you like about living alone like this?
I didn't...
particularly want to be single.
It just somehow turned out that way.
After a while, I just got used to it.
Now,
it's harder for me to imagine living with someone else.
Do you plan on living alone forever?
I'm not sure.
The older I get,
being alone makes me nervous.
However, I can't make that an excuse to get married.
This is why I like you.
What?
Most people are scared of being alone and lonely.
So they can't even break up with people they don't love any more.
Most people are scared of being alone, as well.
But you're different.
Who are you referring to? Ji Sun?
Well, she's one of them.
Is there someone else?
My mum.
My parents got divorced when I was a kid,
but she could neither move on...
nor be alone.
I felt bad for her, but I also thought,
"Why is she like that when she's an adult?"
I couldn't really understand her back then.
I think...
that case is a little different.
It's not different at all.
She ended up meeting someone else...
and is fine now.
Is she in Canada now?
Yes.
Well,
I wasted your time by telling you useless things.
I should go now.
All right.
Just stay there. You don't need to walk me out.
It'll wake you up.
Okay. Good night.
I'll fix the fuse tomorrow.
When will I get another chance like this?
What are you talking about?
Sweet dreams.
Good morning!
Hello.
- Did you come alone?
-  Yes.
- Where's Jun Woo?
-  He went to pick up ingredients.
I see.
Did you come here for a walk?
Yes, sort of.
If you want to exercise in the morning, let's do it together.
Why would I do that?
Pardon me?
What I mean is that...
I don't want to interrupt you two having a lovely time.
What's there to interrupt? We'll just be exercising together.
Are Young Hee and Cheol Soo doing well by the way?
They're still glued to each other. It's so lovely.
I know, right? Being together must be better than being alone.
What about you? Are you going to live alone forever?
Well... I have my family, you know?
What about after everyone leaves?
I mean, both Mi Rae and Ye Ji will get married eventually.
Then I'll get to live alone and enjoy my freedom.
I'm sure that the thought of living alone...
scares you from time to time. Am I wrong?
Well, I can't really deny that.
I want to talk to you about Jun Woo.
He's a great guy.
Please take good care of him.
We grew up together since we were very young,
so he's like a brother to me.
There isn't really anything I can do.
Dating someone at this age feels awkward,
and it's definitely not easy.
But why are you telling me this all of a sudden?
It's because...
we're friends.
- Right, we're friends.
-  Yes.
Yes, we're friends.
Attention, everyone.
We must get the drama for Woori City.
I know that all of you have your own goals,
but a rough road will be ahead of us if we don't get this project.
I have no idea what will happen to us.
So please stay focused,
and let's do our best. Got it?
- Yes!
-  Yes, got it!
All right.
Oh, my. This room is great.
Mi Rae, which room are you going to use?
Which room? I'm not sure.
I'm going to use this room, so you should find another one.
There aren't that many rooms. Shouldn't we be sharing rooms?
I can't share my bed with anyone.
I'm very sensitive.
I see.
Wow, this room is awesome.
Writer Na. You two will be sharing this room, right?
There's a couch in the living room. I can sleep anywhere.
That's not right. You two should exchange opinions and...
We can do that during meetings.
You should still share the room and spend time...
I'm not sensitive, so I can sleep anywhere.
Gosh, I'm so sick of this tension.
- We should do it properly.
-  Absolutely.
Hey, Chief Ko!
Please prepare thoroughly for the drama for Woori City.
I was just at the provincial office because of that project.
- The provincial office?
-  I wanted to review our budget.
I see. Oh, right.
I want your department to take care of this as soon as possible.
- What is this?
-  You know the cruise ship docked...
at the shore of Woori Forest Town, right?
Yes. The city has neglected it for a while,
so it's become useless.
You should restore it...
and use it to attract more tourists.
The business support department...
pushed for an unreasonable amount of increase in the budget to...
You should follow your superior's order and take on the task.
You're obviously not being a good example to your subordinates.
Have a good day.
You too, Sir.
Chief, this is like a bomb that every department has been avoiding.
The entire sum of money that has gone into this project is...
We'll be blamed for everything if we take this on.
Let's go.
But...
This is so frustrating.
I'm hungry. Goodness.
He should be here by now.
Who's coming?
He's here.
Welcome!
Hello, everyone. I'm here to deliver your food.
What brings you here?
I ordered lunch for everyone.
You're that guy. You're Producer Kang's boyfriend.
These days, girls love guys like you who are great cooks.
- No, no. I hope you enjoy it.
-  Thank you.
I know you're busy. You didn't have to do this.
Gosh, I'm sure he did this because he wanted to see you.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
You're young and good-looking. What do you like about Producer Kang?
Well...
She's so inspiring and beautiful.
She's much more attractive than young girls who talk thoughtlessly.
I apologise.
It's fine. Let's eat, everyone. Here.
It looks so delicious. Thanks!
Were you surprised to see me show up like that?
No, it's fine. Thanks so much for doing that.
Do you really mean it?
I actually feel a bit uncomfortable when you visit me at work.
I see.
Call me next time to give me a heads up.
Okay, I will.
I won't show up randomly any more.
I'll call you and ask you first.
Is Ji Sun watching the cafe right now?
Why do you ask? Does it bother you?
No.
She's saying all those things,
but I'm sure she's heartbroken inside.
I see. So you're not bothered by her,
but you're worried about her.
Breaking up with you...
must feel like being cut off from the entire world.
She must feel as though everything is over for her.
How can you understand her so well?
Because I used to be like that.
With your first love?
Yes.
Back then, love was my everything.
We had decided on a date for our wedding...
and even sent out wedding invitations.
Really?
Then what happened?
There was an accident.
I ran to the hospital in shock,
but he was already...
It must've been so hard for you.
You said that Ji Sun also lost her parents...
due to an accident, right?
You've been her support system, but you left her, as well.
Her coming all the way here and not wanting to let you go...
is only natural. I understand it.
However, being good to her now...
might make things worse for her.
Anyway, don't worry about her too much.
She probably just needs a little bit of time...
to find a way to become a real adult on her own.
It's in a pretty good shape.
Why did it stop operating?
Operating it is costly,
and there isn't anything special about its routes.
You brought your camera, right?
Yes, I did.
- Take photos of the front.
-  Okay.
- Take photos of over there, too.
-  I will.
He's so cool.
What a handsome guy.
You're not taking photos of me now, are you?
No!
Then are you taking photos of an airplane or what?
Look over there.
I think it's Chief Ko.
You're right.
Sang Sik!
- Hey.
-  I guess you're here for work.
Yes. What brings you here?
We came here to have a meeting.
Mi Rae said that it's quiet here.
Jun Woo delivered lunch for us, too.
Oh, did he?
You're working on the drama for Woori City, right?
Yes.
I saw the video clip of you on the internet.
- You're a celebrity now.
-  I saw it, too.
You were so cute and funny in it.
- Hello!
-  Yes, hello.
Hi, Song Yi. I haven't seen you in a while.
I know, right?
Are you here to see Chief Ko?
No.
I'm here for work, too. I just bumped into him.
I see.
Then do you mind taking a photo of the two of us?
A photo of us? What are you talking about?
It's so beautiful here.
When will I get to take a photo with you at a place like this?
- But...
-  You're a celebrity, you know?
Please just take one good photo of us.
Give me your camera. I'll do it.
It's okay.
Please take a good photo of us.
Sure.
Why do you want to take a photo all of a sudden?
Please stand closer.
- Gosh, seriously.
-  Just stay still.
We don't have much time, so please hurry.
Oh, okay.
All right. In 1, 2 and 3.
Thank you so much.
Don't Chief Ko and I look good together?
Yes, you do.
See? People can sense the chemistry between us.
What?
Chemistry.
Sang Sik, we'll get going. Have a great day, Song Yi.
Have a wonderful day.
- See you later.
-  See you. Have a good day.
What is the matter with you?
I wanted to take revenge against her.
Revenge?
You said that you two are just neighbours,
but I felt it.
I felt that strange air...
between the two of you.
What are you talking about?
It was my intuitive hunch as a woman.
It felt awkward, but it seemed like a chemistry at the same time.
So I put on a show intentionally.
Goodness.
Wait up.
He really fixed it.
- Hey, Jun Woo.
-  Hi.
Did you get home from work?
Yes, I just got in.
Thanks.
My place is no longer dark thanks to you.
You're welcome.
I hope you didn't forget about the class today.
It'll start shortly. Come and meet me here.
- Now?
-  Yes. Why?
Nothing. I'll be there soon.
- It's delicious.
-  Isn't it so tasty?
By the way, isn't Mr Park so attractive?
I'm so curious to find out what kind of woman he'll end up marrying.
He's totally my type.
We're still single, so we can be hopeful.
I'm sure he has a girlfriend.
Someone who is very cute and pretty.
Don't you think so?
Yes, definitely.
All right, everyone. Thank you for all of your hard work today.
We didn't do much. Thank you for all of your had work.
Mr Park. You have a girlfriend, right?
Girlfriend? She is my...
- No, it's not me.
-  Goodness.
Mr Park, stop kidding us.
Seriously.
You even have a great sense of humour,
and you also care about us so much.
It's hot in here. I'll be right back.
Can I not tell people about us?
What will they think?
Who cares about what they think? We like each other, so all is good.
I can't even tell them that you're my girlfriend?
What's the matter?
Frankly, I like hearing all this from you,
and it makes me feel better, but...
I'm not saying it to make you feel better.
I'm very serious right now.
Your judgement might be...
clouded by your emotions right now,
making you think that I'm better than who I actually am.
What...
What do you mean by that?
I'm nothing special.
I'm just an old woman.
Where did your confidence go?
Don't pay attention to what other people say.
Doing that becomes hard at my age.
When I was young,
I could grab a hot potato in my hand fully knowing that it's hot...
and that it'd burn my hand.
But I don't do that any more. I don't want to do it, either.
Then...
what do you do now instead?
I wait until it cools down...
to make sure that I don't burn my hand and that I'm safe.
I'm becoming less reckless and more cautious as I age,
and I avoid jumping into dangerous things at all cost.
Okay.
I guess I was too self-centred.
Boss.
Everyone is leaving now.
Okay.
It's possible that what I missed was...
not someone I can love,
but feeling the emotion of love itself.
Is the class over now?
Put on some music for me, Sang Sik.
You silly.
Here we go.
How is it? Do you like it?
Yes. I've always liked...
your taste in music.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No.
Jun Woo.
I find it very difficult...
to be with Min Joo.
What?
I liked how she's maturer than me.
Well, I still like her, of course.
But is it because she's older than me?
I don't think she likes my way of doing things.
That's not possible.
You're so good to her. What more would she want?
I might be too young for her.
There could be a generation gap.
However, you're...
like an old man inside.
Goodness.
Jun Woo.
I'm really...
happy to hear that you started liking someone.
You've never liked Min Joo.
That's because I didn't know much about her back then.
When you like someone,
you often get into conflicts with that person.
There are also bad things about that person.
You find out things that you don't like about them.
Right now,
I think you're in the process of getting to know each other.
Thank you.
I'm the one who should thank you.
Why?
You're still young, and I was afraid...
you wouldn't date anyone.
Goodness.
Why does age matter in dating?
My only wish is that you'd find someone nice.
Gosh.
Hello, Mum.
How's Dad?
It's still in early stages,
so he won't get worse as long as he gets regular treatment.
I really hope so.
I'm here for him, so don't worry about your father.
Why do you keep calling when you must be busy?
I just wanted to talk to you and Dad.
I must be getting old, too.
Don't talk about getting old in front of me.
You're still young.
Aren't you feeling that way since you only work and don't date?
Perhaps. It's been so long since I dated someone.
I think my heart is broken.
If it's difficult to find someone you like,
date someone who treats you well and loves you very much.
Then the rest of your life will be easy.
Really?
Do you really think so?
Honey, will you be home early tonight?
- Why?
-  Why?
It's because you're home late these days.
I think Dad exercises after work.
He even has muscles here.
Exercise?
I just thought I should regain my stamina.
I guess he works out these days.
What do you mean?
He doesn't work out at all.
He stays home all day even when I ask him to go to the spring with me.
The only exercise he does is breathing.
That must be why. You should have told me so we can go together.
What kind of exercise do you do?
I go to a health club near the school.
I didn't even know. I should get you some herbal medicine.
Don't waste money on useless things.
You're not anything useless.
Come home early tonight since I'm making samgyetang.
I want baeksuk made with Korean chicken.
You're so tactless. Stop interfering.
Do you know what day is today?
Of course I do. It's the day to submit class evaluations.
We're leaving now, Sang Sik.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Sang Sik, why did I get married?
Don't start that already. See you.
Gosh.
Come on, everyone, get up.
Come on.
- Gosh.
-  Do you know what time it is?
You're here already.
My stomach hurts.
Gosh, I'm in a hurry.
I'm in a hurry.
Could you close the door?
What are you doing?
Writer Na said she's in a hurry.
What?
Goodness.
Come this way.
You can wash here.
You look even cuter early in the morning.
Song Yi.
Why did you call me here?
Well,
I know it's possible,
but don't you think it's wrong?
What do you mean?
He's a widower,
but how could you and Chief Ko...
It's not like we're getting married.
I'm dating him right now.
Is Chief Ko...
fine with dating someone who's almost as young as his daughter?
I'm not underaged right now.
Plus, why do you think Chief Ko shouldn't date?
As a person in charge of official duties...
and considering how things are in the office...
Has my dating Chief Ko stopped you...
from carrying official duties?
This is strictly my personal life.
Please stay out of my business unless this is out of jealousy.
Please excuse me.
More people would empathise if I select the female lead character.
A woman who's waiting for someone to love.
Any other opinions?
I don't agree with it.
It's not that she's waiting for a man to love.
Her missing the feeling of wanting to love sounds more convincing.
I agree with Writer Ko.
Writer Ko, you aren't familiar with dramas.
I like dramas and watched many of them.
Watching and writing are different.
You keep saying...
Please don't argue here.
Okay, let's think about that part some more.
You used to be good at playing the piano.
That doesn't matter any more.
My fingers are stiff now that I haven't played it for so long.
I wonder if I'm just getting old.
Come on.
You should start playing again.
Hoon will be a senior in high school next year.
Cheon Soo should become a principal before he retires, too.
I have to support them. I can't play the piano.
You need to have your own life.
Everyone will be fine on their own.
I really wish that was the case.
I wonder why I got married.
(Sang Hee's wedding anniversary)
Isn't today your wedding anniversary?
You're the only one who cares for me.
Doesn't Cheon Soo know?
If he knew, I wouldn't regret getting married on a day like today.
It must have been hard after you got divorced.
Of course,
but I'm fine now.
Don't you feel lonely?
You feel lonely whether you're with someone or not, right?
That's right.
How long has it been since you got divorced?
Well, I...
- Pardon me.
-  Please go ahead.
(House ghost)
Marriage requires...
many sacrifices, responsibilities and pressure.
At times, you have to say things you don't mean.
It's like a thick mask.
I wonder how I should live so that I don't regret it.
They say life ends while you hesitate.
Bernard said that.
It's a famous quote.
Cheers.
I'll stop here because I have to teach tomorrow.
We finally started talking.
Let's go now.
Have one drink at least.
- Sang Hee.
-  Aunt Sang Hee.
- Mum.
-  Sang Hee.
Where's your dad?
He isn't home yet.
Today's their wedding anniversary.
Dad is so horrible.
(Last summer items on sale)
What are you doing?
Hello.
Are you checking the streets like you mentioned before?
That's right. I'm checking banners like this...
and signs that get in the way of pedestrians.
I'm here to meet someone.
- I see.
-  Have a good night.
See you.
- Jeong Sik.
-  Hey.
Look who it is.
Hello.
Do you know each other?
How do you know Chief Ko?
- In the past...
-  In the past,
I met him at an event in Woori City.
Well... Yes, that's right.
How do you know each other?
We met because of a plagiarism issue regarding a drama.
Oh, right.
You're Ko Mi Rae's older brother.
He's my neighbour now.
He lives next door.
Then is he the guy...
What's wrong?
- What?
-  Well, then.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Here you go.
Cheers.
Are you dating your next door neighbour?
What are you talking about?
Never mind.
How did your filming of Woori City go?
I just took a look around.
What's going on?
Why don't your socks match?
Really?
Can't you distinguish between navy blue and grey?
This is how I am.
Goodness.
Actually, I got divorced.
- What?
-  It's been about a year.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want things to get awkward.
What would get awkward?
Divorce?
Min Joo.
You've forgotten...
about it all now, right?
- What do you mean?
-  I'm talking about Eun Ho.
Why are you bringing that up?
I was just thinking about the past.
How boring.
- Are you just getting home?
-  Yes.
Ji Sun.
I may be saying it...
out of concern...
Out of concern?
What I'm saying...
may be out of too much concern.
I see. It's okay. Go ahead.
It's about your stay here for a while.
I know you talked about it with Jun Woo,
but I don't think your staying here...
will help you in the future.
Thank you for your concern.
I know what you mean.
However,
this is the only thing I can do right now.
Okay.
While you stay here,
I hope you'll come to a decision.
Thank you.
See you later.
"SS".
This...
is very similar to mine.
There's no way.
Mine has...
"SS" engraved on it.
Where...
did you get that?
My wife gave it to me.
Stop it and sit down.
I said I'm fine.
You shouldn't concern yourself with our wedding anniversary.
Things like this can happen in married life.
Ye Ji, how can you be so cruel?
You celebrate your anniversary with your boyfriend.
Why should I be forgiving on a day like this?
Cheon Soo must be busy today.
He doesn't even know what day it is today.
Is this ready to eat?
No, I have to make the sauce.
Sit down and wait a little.
I'll finish up and bring Sang Sik over.
Let's have a drink together, okay?
Let me do that. Give it to me.
Stay in your seat on a day like today.
("Paradise of the Youth")
Pardon me.
What brings you here?
By any chance,
have you seen this before?
I thought it looked exactly the same.
Where...
did you get it?
My boyfriend...
had it when he died.
I mentioned him before.
Is that so?
I don't know what's written on it.
It looks like a name.
- "SS" is...
-  What was...
his name?
Eun Ho.
His name was Jang Eun Ho.
No!
Sang Sik.
Sang Sik, get out of there.
Don't let go!
Don't let go of my hand!
Hold my hand.
Hold tight, Eun Ho!
Eun Ho!
Don't let go of my hand!
- Sang Sik.
-  Eun Ho!
Eun Ho!
What's wrong?
Actually...
Sang Sik.
Min Joo.
(Second to Last Love)
What did Min Joo come to ask you?
Is it something between you two?
I like this place. I won't ever leave.
It's so hard to love.
I don't want to break up. It hurts too much.
With me...
I'm disappointed in you. With an employee like your daughter...
What?
I think Sang Sik...
likes Min Joo.
I already know.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?