Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
I'm hungry! Something delicious!
Why I ought to...!
Don't treat him that way.
Goodness, okay.
Of course, I'll do as you say.
Good job today.
Please keep up the good work.
You're building the religious community, right?
Of course.
Don't get foolish ideas now.
Just think of the townspeople.
It must be great that you're so popular.
My Ji-sun must be so happy in heaven.
Hallelujah.
Yes.
How could you ask me to be with Satan?
How could you ask me to work with the devil?
Just what... is your plan?
Father...
Pastor, don't cry.
If you cry, you're a baby.
I'm not crying.
If you laugh while crying, you get hairy down here.
Poor Sung-ho....
I'll protect you.
I trust you.
I do.
I will send you to heaven.
That feels refreshing.
It's good!
It's the best!
I'll buy you more.
If you want more, I'll buy you more.
You're the best, pastor.
You're an angel!
Sung-ho.
You can become an angel too.
Really?
Why are you doing this?
Get up!
I told you I'll kill you if you come back here, you bastard!
That reckless bastard.
Bastard, stop right there!
I heard he stabbed him in the stomach.
Goodness!
How scary!
(Save Me 2)
(Episode 14)
What's this "T"?
Why is it so chaotic here?
Why isn't the scene being preserved?
This is a mess.
Who allowed them in?
I'm the chief here and he's...
I understand.
I'll contact you if we need you.
What do you mean?
Do you know this neighborhood?
You can't treat us like this if you're going to question people.
Okay.
Don't disturb the crime scene.
Let's go outside and talk.
You call yourself a police officer and yet...
Be thorough.
He's not from around here and he doesn't have his wallet or cellphone...
I think it will take some time to figure out who he is.
Are you sure he's an outsider?
I'm sure.
He came to our station to ask for directions.
Chief, all the security cameras in the motel corridors are all fake.
They say the one at the entrance was broken early in the morning.
Just one?
Jeez.
It's because the neighborhood's a dump.
A dump?
A dump? It's not because it's a dump!
It's because it's a crime-free neighborhood!
- Why did...
- Hey!
- Did someone really die in there?
- Yes.
It was very vicious.
He was stabbed multiple times here.
Is this a horror movie or what?
Reality's scarier than movies these days.
Anyways, who died?
Go away!
You can't stay here.
You can't stay here!
Please go away! Don't spread rumors! Go!
Sir.
Did someone really die?
Who was it?
I need to talk to you for a second.
Please go back to your houses now.
He's an outsider.
Did an outsider recently come to your cafe?
Goodness! That bastard...!
A crazy bastard came to my place.
Tell me more.
I never saw him before but he made a mess at my cafe and he hit me.
But Min-cheol showed up and saved me.
He made a mess at your cafe and Min-cheol stopped him?
Sir.
If it wasn't for Min-cheol, I would've been beaten to death that day.
Okay....
Jeez.
Hey!
You!
Hello!
Fasten that!
Yes, sir.
You...
You were here on a delivery last night here, right?
You brat.
Look carefully.
You delivered that, right?
Yes.
What time was that?
I think it was past 2 a.m.
2 a.m.?
Are you sure?
I left work right after making the delivery here.
Anyways, did he really die?
You said you had a headache.
Are you okay?
I took some medication so I should be fine.
I'm going to get some air and head over to the bus stop.
Okay.
It's time to pop open this!
Young-sun!
It's me! Young-sun!
Pastor?
We're going to go somewhere nice at night.
It's a welfare foundation in Seoul.
I brought you 2 months' worth of pay in advance.
Ma'am.
You need to return to school.
Will you just stop here?
It must be great that you're so popular.
Hallelujah.
Pastor.
Young-sun.
What's wrong?
I remembered.
Elder Choi... sold me there.
He gave me some strange drug too.
Elder Choi...
He used me.
Don't worry. Nothing happened.
I had hoped that you wouldn't know.
I thought it would make things hard for you.
So I didn't tell you.
(Wanted for Fraud - Choi Kyung-seok (55))
Choi Kyung-seok.
That's right.
He's not an elder.
He's a scam artist with 12 priors.
We need to report this.
Why haven't you reported him yet?
As you already know,
most of the townspeople gave their entire fortunes for the religious community.
If he's arrested now,
then the religious community won't be made.
I couldn't let that happen.
Because of the townspeople.
Because of the religious community,
Ms. Lee was saved and she was able to go to heaven.
She didn't have to worry about Sung-ho or the baby.
She passed away in peace.
The task that the Heavenly Father gave me...
I will finish it, no matter what.
Please join me.
If you want,
I'll do anything to help...
Thank you, Young-sun.
Min-cheol!
Min-cheol! Min-cheol!
Min-cheol! Get up!
Hey, wake up!
- Min-cheol!
- What?
That man died.
Who?
The guy who hit me!
You know that thug!
He died at the motel!
- The motel?
- Yes.
I heard he was stabbed.
- Jeez!
- No way.
He really died?
You know...
I guess people really shouldn't do anything bad.
You'll be punished for them someday.
He was killed at a strange place.
He was killed like an animal.
My goodness.
How scary.
We're almost there.
You scared me!
Don't scare me like that!
I'm sorry, sir.
The bus is here.
I brought the money we collected in cash yesterday.
Okay.
Why do you keep collecting it in cash when it's so inconvenient?
It would be easier to wire transfer.
You fool.
Do you know why I haven't been caught when I have been wanted for 4 years?
Don't leave any evidence behind.
I see.
Goodness.
Let's go work.
Welcome!
- Hello!
Thank you!
Welcome!
Is there something wrong?
I want to go to heaven.
I gave you all of my compensation money.
Good job!
That's fine.
But...
These two don't have anything.
I want to get on that bus and go to heaven too.
Elder Choi, is there a way for us?
Please wait a little, ma'am.
(Ji-woong)
Yes, bring me a document and hurry over here.
Yes.
Heavenly Father makes the impossible possible.
Oh, my!
- Amen!
- Amen! Amen!
(Promissory Note)
Did you read it all?
You just need to stamp it right there.
Hurry up and stamp it so we can all go to heaven.
(Creditor, debtor)
I can go to heaven now too!
Good job!
You're not going to do it?
If you don't feel comfortable,
then it's fine.
- I...
- Stamp it so we can go together!
I need to ask my kids.
I'll do it next time.
Yes, go ahead. It's fine.
Then let's get on the bus now.
Let's go.
Follow me.
What happened to this bastard?
The phone you are currently calling is turned off right now. Please leave a...
Sir.
I think he ran away.
No, this bastard wouldn't just leave without getting his money.
Then should I go check the motel?
Go to the city and find out where that bastard ran away to.
Tell Ji-woong to take care of the rest.
Yes, sir.
This bastard.
The phone you...
Ma'am!
Please tell me more!
I told everything to the detective already!
A person died!
You should answer when the police asks you a question!
Fine!
What do you want to know?
When did that man come here?
It's been about 3-4 days.
He told me he was staying here for a week.
So I even got paid in advance.
Then exactly when did he come back last night?
Do you remember?
I remember.
He came back past 1 a.m.
He ran to the second floor.
And then Kim Min-cheol followed him right after that.
Goodness!
How scary!
Kim Min-cheol?
Are you sure it was him?
Yes!
Kim Min-cheol, that bastard!
Hey.
Make sure no one enters here.
Stop! Stop!
Sir, we have a suspect.
They say they found Kim Min-cheol on the footage.
He's wanted right now.
We need to find him first. Let's go!
Hurry! Hurry!
Here comes the makgeolli!
Makgeolli's here!
This is very cold right now.
- Chil-sung, are you really not going to go with us?
- Yes.
I guess Mi-sun's very tired after yesterday's congratulatory service.
So I'm going to let her rest today.
I'm going to get her favorite food too.
Goodness! We have a great husband in Wolchoo-ri!
Goodness, here comes our savior!
- Pastor!
Pastor!
Believing in you is like believing in God.
You know you're the only one we trust, right?
Yes.
Young-sun, you're going too, right?
Yes, my mom and I are going.
Good, good.
Hey, Chil-sung.
You should go with us too.
We already know where we're going.
Please just take a picture for us.
Okay. Don't worry.
- I'll send you one.
- Yes!
Shall we all take pictures on our cellphones?
You'll miss your hometown when the town is submerged.
You should take pictures so you can look at it whenever you miss it.
Wow!
We didn't even think of that!
- You're the best!
- Yes!
- I'll take it.
- Let's take it!
Hey, hey.
- Be in the middle.
- Goodness.
Okay.
1, 2, 3!
I'll take one more.
Okay! 1, 2, 3!
You should join them too.
I'll take it.
Shall I?
Hurry up and join us!
- Let's take a picture!
- Hurry up!
Goodness, the sun is going to set at this rate!
Goodness!
- Hurry over!
- Okay!
- Let's do it.
- Here I go.
1, 2, 3!
One more time. Smile! 1, 2, 3!
Let's go.
Where's Elder Choi?
He's been on his cellphone over there for a while.
I see.
What is going on with this bastard?
Elder Choi.
I think everybody's here.
Let's go now.
Not everybody's here.
We shouldn't make the elders wait.
What's wrong with that bastard?
This is pissing me off.
Min-cheol, where are you going?
This won't do. I need to find out what's going on.
I have a bad feeling about this. Shouldn't you just stay in hiding?
No, no.
Min-cheol, where are you going?
This won't do. I need to find out what's going on.
I have a bad feeling about this. Shouldn't you just stay in hiding?
No, no.
Yes, who is it?
We're the police.
I have a few questions to ask.
What should I do?
Yes, give me a second.
Yes?
You know Mr. Kim Min-cheol, right?
Kim Min-cheol?
Why?
He's a suspect for the motel murder.
It's been a while since I saw him.
I see.
Excuse me!
Excuse me! What are you doing?
You can't do this!
What are you doing?
Stay still.
A detective can't just do this!
You're being ridiculous!
What are you doing at a single woman's house!
Kim Min-cheol! Stop right there!
You bastard!
Hey!
Stop the car! Stop the car!
It's Kim Min-cheol.
That rat.
Where did he hide?
- Go this way.
- Yes, sir.
This is driving me insane.
Kim Min-cheol!
I didn't do it!
You bastard.
He's not around here.
Jeez! Just where did he go?
I'm sure he didn't get far.
He's not over there too.
Kim Min-cheol had a history of murder and assault.
I'm sure he's the killer.
- So call me right away when you see him.
- Yes.
We'll patrol this area.
Okay.
Ask for backup.
Yes.
It feels like we're going on a trip, right?
Pastor, Dane!
- Dance!
- Get up! Get up!
Please sit. Please sit.
You shouldn't do this inside the bus!
Pastor!
They say that man's dead.
I think he was murdered.
The police are here too.
What's wrong with me again?
We have a baby. Our baby.
Let's go home.
Hurry up and run away! Hurry!
(Wolchoo-ri Religious Community Construction)
You can get off now!
Watch the steps!
Please follow me.
Is it here?
Oh, my!
It's so nice!
Like this?
Oh, there it is.
So that's going to be Sung-ho's house.
- You're right.
- Sung-ho's house.
You see your house there, right?
The place where they dug up the dirt. Go play there!
My house's the best!
We're in heaven!
My goodness!
- That's Chil-sung's house, right?
- There?
Yes, over there.
You're right.
That's my house next to it.
Chil-sung.
This is heaven.
This is your place.
It feels like God's gift.
Choi Kyung-seok.
You think he'll back down?
Just trust me.
God won't forgive him.
I was going to cook for you.
This is your job.
I'm going to start swearing.
It's so good!
I'm glad.
Here we go.
Be careful! It's hot!
It looks so good!
Here. This, this.
Cheers.
Honey, let me roll this up for you.
Try this.
How is it?
It's nice and savory, right?
Yes.
Oh, right!
I forgot to show you this.
This.
This is our place in heaven where we're going to live.
[OnDemandKorea Ver]
OCN E14 'Save Me S2'
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Okay, gather around now!
Gather around!
Sir!
Thanks for your hard work.
He's the construction manager.
Hello!
Welcome!
As you all know, everything's made of the best quality and it's Eco-friendly.
So we're being very careful.
We're using Hinoki cypress for the interior.
So it smells great!
As you can see here, in the middle of the religious community,
the church will be here.
It's a place to communicate with heaven.
Yes.
And in the surrounding areas,
we'll have a gym, library, and a pool.
We'll even have a medical center!
Yes, that's right.
The areas around the religious community are truly great.
And each house is a single family house, of course.
It will be easy to think of it as a townhouse which is considered the best in Gangnam.
It sounds great!
Yes, yes.
And we'll have big windows.
So the sunlight will be...
Okay.
It seems like we went through most of it.
I'll make sure to make your house completely broke so just wait and see.
You.
I heard you got into a fight with that man from the motel.
Yes, that's right. We got into a fight and I followed him.
You crazy bastard, stop following me!
You're dead meat, you bastard!
You bastard, I told you I'll kill you if you come back.
Do you know what room that bastard who just went up is staying in?
I don't know!
What's wrong with you?
That's ti.
I know.
The motel owner said you went outside in 5-10 minutes.
So there's no reason for me to be chased by the detectives right now.
You're wrong.
You were the last one seen in the motel security camera.
And based on your criminal history....
Everybody will think it's you.
This is crap.
Go.
Just leave!
Where would I go?
You know I'm not the killer! Do something!
You idiot!
You know I'm older than you but you still talk to me with no respect!
That's why you...!
Let's go.
Why did you help Kim Min-cheol?
Because he's not the killer.
Since when was that important?
You tried to send him jail by making up crimes before.
I wonder who the real killer is.
Delivery.
Hey.
Why did it take so long?
Hurry up!
Yes.
Hey, where are the free dumplings?
There's no such thing.
Hey, that's a given when you order sweet and sour pork.
The countryside people are so stingy.
What?
Hey, are you going to bring me the fried dumplings?
Fine.
- Bring it, okay?
- Okay.
Hurry up and go!
Yes.
It's past 2 again.
I need to get paid more.
Who's doing that?
What's wrong with you?
What the hell!
Who's doing that! I ought to kill you!
Damn it!
It's open! Come in!
You should've brought it earlier.
Leave it there.
What the hell!
Satan!
You sinned because you didn't repent when you were given a chance!
You sinned because you went against God's will!
You dirty Satan!
I am punishing you for also taking advantage of our Heavenly Father!
Evil soul.
You were judged by God's will.
And executed.
We're going to heaven soon.
Chil-sung.
Chil-sung, you were home?
Chil-sung!
Mi-sun.
Chil-sung, Mi-sun's cold...
Chil-sung!
Look.
My Mi-sun...
Come look.
She looks pretty, right?
She has a million dollar smile.
Mi-sun's dead.
I guess she was very happy after she gave her testimony yesterday.
She was in a hurry to go to heaven.
So she left first.
I've never seen Mi-sun so happy before.
This is all thanks to this.
It's all thanks to the water of life.
What happened?
Stop.
Chil-sung, stop.
Chil-sung, please stop.
Let's go out. Let's go to the hospital.
Let's go to the hospital.
Okay, okay.
My Mi-sun's the happiest right now.
Mi-sun.
I'll join you soon, okay?
Get a hold of yourself.
Chil-sung, what's wrong with you. Please stop.
Chil-sung, look at me. Look at me.
They're all frauds.
They're a cult and they're scam artists.
They fooled you and you were fooled.
Get a hold of yourself! They're scam artists.
What's wrong with that?
I'm so happy and at peace right now.
Who care if they're a cult or a group of scam artists?
Why is that important?
Here I have...
I...
Chil-sung!
Chil-sung, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you? Chil-sung!
Chil-sung!
Hello?
This is Wolchoo-ri Chil-sung Supermarket...
I did it for fun.
Be quiet.
Kim Min-cheol is the suspect.
The police are after him.
This is good for us, right?
Of course.
Of course!
This is helpful.
Okay, everybody.
How do you feel now that you saw the religious community construction today?
We feel great!
Yes, that's right.
A place to connect with heaven.
Today's your last chance!
Time does not wait for us!
You will miss your chance if you don't grab it.
They said life is a continuous cycle of choices.
Your life depends on what kind of choices you make!
Today, heaven gave us one last chance!
I want to live there too!
Hallelujah!
(Admission Application)
- Everybody else, please make a decision soon!
- Who needs an application?
- Give me one too!
Over there! Hallelujah!
- Yes!
- Give me one too!
Yes! Hallelujah!
God bless you all!
The pastor will take care of us.
Everybody.
I have some urgent business to take care of.
So I'm getting off first.
I hope you have a safe trip home!
- Thank you!
- Good work!
Ms. Kim Mi-sun died on June 20th at 21:37.
She was dead when she arrive here
so the current time is her time of death.
Why did she die, doctor? I thought she just had a cold.
I saw her medical records
and she was in the last stage of lung cancer.
Her cause of death was lung cancer.
I don't know what else to say.
Doctor, what's wrong with Chil-sung then?
It seems like seizures from shock.
But I think we'll know more after we get his CT results and other test results.
Let's wait a little more.
Thank you.
Chil-sung, are you okay?
Chil-sung.
Give... me some water.
Okay, wait a little.
Heavenly Father.
I believe that my Mi-sun is in heaven.
Thank you for allowing my Mi-sun to step foot into heaven.
The happiness Mi-sun didn't have here on Earth...
Please take care of her so she can have that happiness in heaven.
Chil-sung.
I brought water.
Stop and drink some water.
Why...
Do you not want me to be happy?
I want to pray.
Please don't bother me.
Please...
...allow me to live as your servant all my life, God.
Goodness, hello!
Hello!
Goodness, what brings you here?
Yes, I was in the neighborhood so I dropped by to see you.
I see.
Please have a seat here.
Yes.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
A cup of water is fine.
Yes.
Something happened in the city.
It's a mess right now.
Thank you.
I heard there was a murder.
Yes.
An outsider died at the motel.
I don't know why an outsider came to the countryside.
Goodness, that's unfortunate.
You should catch the killer soon.
The suspect is Kim Min-cheol.
Goodness!
Is that so?
Jeez.
Hey!
That's crooked!
That!
Bring me the wanted poster! Hurry!
- Yes.
- You should put that up well.
See! It's wrinkled!
Jeez.
(Wanted for Fraud - Choi Kyung-seok (55))
We would get a special promotion if we arrest even one guy here.
You should put this up well. It's wrinkled.
Sir, I'm sorry but I have some urgent business to take care of.
I...
Something urgent came up.
I'll see you next time.
- I see.
- Goodbye.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Take care!
Hey.
Bring me the evidence bag.
Why?
So I can send the fingerprint to forensics.
Bring me the documents.
We're leaving here tonight.
Don't worry, Young-sun.
I'll make Choi Kyung-seok back down.
He already took the religious community donations.
There's no reason to keep him around.
Young-sun.
Just trust me.
Yes.
Things won't be hard for you from now on.
You can't forgive him, right?
I'm talking about Mr. Kim Min-cheol.
Kim Min-cheol...
For all of my life...
I won't forgive my dad.
But you know what?
Kim Min-cheol's a lot like my dad.
I think of my father when I see Kim Min-cheol.
I really hate that.
Once the religious community's built,
you won't have to see him.
Don't worry.
Heavenly Father.
It was once a hard path.
But thank you for letting me go down that path with Young-sun.
Thank you once again for giving us the vision of the religious community.
Thank you, Heavenly Father.
Thank you for letting me meet you and the pastor to be reborn.
The pastor saved me.
The pastor showed up when I felt I was alone.
Even when I was fooled by a man who's like the devil,
he saved me.
From now on, I will live only for you and the pastor.
Thank you for saving me through your disciple, the pastor.
I love you.
Sleep well.
Yes.
- You should go in too.
- Yes.
Young-sun.
Don't leave my side, okay?
Yes.
I'll stick next to you.
Don't do this.
Please don't do this for Young-sun's sake.
You shouldn't commit any more sins!
Hey.
I mean, pastor.
I have a favor to ask you.
Okay?
Please just leave Young-sun alone.
I beg you.
Sir.
We're all children of God.
You were briefly seduced by Satan.
But you can come back as God's child again.
Sir.
I know how you lived your life.
The world is tough.
You had to fight and overcome it.
That was probably the world you had to live in to survive.
I understand. I really do.
I'm not the only one who understands you.
Our Heavenly Father already understands too.
You can rely on me and trust me from now on!
You can live a happy life!
Leave Young-sun to me.
That's the only way everybody can become happy.
That's what Young-sun wants too!
Do you know that Young-sun tried to commit suicide because of you?
There's something Young-sun confessed to me.
"Our Heavenly Father helped me realize that I was born to be loved."
"Could you help my brother have this hope like I did?"
"My brother had a harder life than me."
"At one point, I resented him but now I want to give him hope."
"Even if everybody says he's a bad guy,"
"there are still two people in this world who love him."
"Heavenly Father and me."
"Pastor."
"Please help my brother come into God's embrace."
Sir.
Please get up.
Just like God forgave you, I also forgive you.
You're not a bad person, Min-cheol.
She never said that.
It's okay, Min-cheol.
Please get up.
No, that's not it.
She never called me brother.
Pardon?
Young-sun never called me her brother in her life, you bastard.
Do you get it now?
How dare you make up such lies?
Who are you, you bastard?
She called me that before.
Damn it.
I went overboard, right?
You found out.
You bastard.
Have you lost your mind?
You rat!
You scumbag!
You crazy bastard! You're worse than the scam artist!
Come here!
- Come here!
- I'm different!
Don't compare me to that scumbag, Choi Kyung-seok.
I'm not like that man.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Save Me 2)
What did you ever do for Young-sun?
Young-sun doesn't need you!
What's the cause of death?
It looks like wounds from taking meth.
People show signs of hearing and seeing things.
Kim Min-cheol's in town! Hurry up and find him!
Choi Kyung-seok might come before Kim Min-cheol.
We will catch him tonight, no matter what.
Was it you?
It's the price of your sins.