Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(EPISODE 7)
How would you catch a rat...
living in your home?
Why does someone so young have...
such a huge car?
It's as big as my bathroom.
- Who are you?
- Where's the other car?
A rich young man can't have only one.
This is it.
I heard there's one that isn't black.
Something nice and bright. Like red.
I told you already.
This is his only car.
Han Se Kyu's the son of a rich, well-connected man,
so I won't get a warrant.
But that makes him...
a scared little mouse that doesn't know much.
Just a little nudge...
and he will spill.
You are right.
He's an amateur.
He won't have hidden his tracks completely.
His own house is too risky,
so he must have hidden it somewhere private...
that others don't have access to.
Somewhere private that others don't have access to.
It can be moved at any time...
and has enough space to hide stolen items.
A car.
I don't know anything.
I just did as I was told.
(POLICE STATION)
- Open that.
- Look.
Get out.
We have a reliable witness and evidence.
Will that get us a warrant?
Even if he is the Chief Prosecutor's son.
Get inside.
Han Se Kyu.
You're under arrest for the Gaesu-dong break-ins.
Be still.
You have the right to be quiet...
and the right to an attorney.
Your father knows a lot about law, but he can't help you.
Your prints were all over the stolen items.
Another suspect of the high-profile...
Luxury Home Break-In Case...
that had our attention for weeks...
was arrested this afternoon.
The suspect is the son of the Chief Prosecutor at Seoul's...
Central District Prosecutors' Office.
The suspect had ties with the sons of the victims...
and used the friendship to gain access,
which shocked the community.
My client had stopped...
eating and drinking since Oh was mistakenly arrested...
for the crimes he had committed...
and was contemplating about turning himself in...
when he was arrested.
The victims wish to settle out of court,
and since this all began with...
the curiosity of a misguided youth,
we hope that the judge will hand out a reasonable sentence.
I don't get it.
Why did you ask for...
an espresso at a karaoke bar?
How come? Why?
How could they not have an espresso machine?
You embarrassed us all.
They don't know the importance of an espresso machine.
Look at all of this.
We should be looking into this one.
Where's Detective Cha?
Where is Soo Hyun?
Who is it?
Who are you?
Hello.
I'm on the long-term Cold Case Team...
with Detective Cha, and my name is Park Hae Young.
Oh.
So you are Soo Hyun's colleague?
Yes.
Okay, come in.
Please come in.
Please sit down.
Would you like coffee or tea?
Either is fine.
Hey! I got you.
- Humans!
- My gun is bigger!
Attack!
What?
You haven't seen a sick person?
Detective Cha...
called in sick.
You were there too.
I'll be right back.
Take a nap at the night duty room.
That's why we need an espresso machine.
Our long term Cold Case Team should...
invest in one.
That's out of the equation.
Which one is it?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I won!
Gosh.
Okay, okay.
Quiet down.
Go play in your room.
Rock, paper, scissors!
- My goodness.
- Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Don't they drive you nuts?
It's okay.
They're so loud.
It's an apartment.
Wow, it's so big.
I mean...
none of Soo Hyun's colleagues have ever visited before.
- I see.
- Please go ahead.
Excuse me, but...
how old are you?
Why would you want to know?
Why did you change?
It must be really busy for him to come and get me.
No, it's not that bad.
That hurt.
- Let's go.
- You are sick.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm sure he came for a good reason.
Yes. Well...
it's actually important and we need Detective Cha's help.
All right.
Tell me...
how old you are before you go.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Okay.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Why do you keep staring?
Are you okay?
Maybe you need to rest more.
Did that look like resting to you?
What is it?
Do you ever regret it?
Being a police officer is a dangerous job.
What's with you?
You face criminals all the time.
You won't have a normal marriage life.
It's okay. Just pull over.
- What?
- Pull over on the side.
Don't slack off while I'm gone.
I expect a meticulous plan for the next investigation.
Han Se Kyu from the Break-In Case...
was proven guilty, but...
considering this is his first offence and...
that he is in deep remorse,
he was sentenced to 6 months in prison with 2 years of probation.
(EX-CON MURDERS A MAN WITH A GRUDGE OVER HANYOUNG BRIDGE INCIDENT.)
I wasted my time.
If I knew you'd be back here,
then I wouldn't have cleared your charge.
That man...
He paid for what he did...
and I'll pay for my crimes.
It's only you who's still in here.
Everybody involved is living their life again,
but why are you still in here?
Why do you keep doing this?
The real bad guys will forget about everything...
and move on with their lives.
Why... Why are you still here?
Darn it.
Goodness.
I heard Oh Kyung Tae died here while serving his time.
There it is.
(OH KYUNG TAE, 1958-2005)
(PARK SUN WOO)
There's not even a tombstone.
Is this it?
We can't do much for convicts...
without family or relatives.
Even if you change the past,
some things remain the same.
The world...
will always be unfair.
There he comes.
Hey, where's Chief?
How come I can't reach him all day?
- Hey, get over here.
- Look.
It says Han Se Kyu broke in out of curiosity.
What kind of crazy person breaks in to three houses out of curiosity?
- Hey.
- Not only that,
some items are still missing.
They're not investigating properly.
- Where's Chief?
- This is not the right time.
Chief.
What happened?
How does this make any sense?
What are you doing?
We do as we are told.
What do you mean? It's not like you did anything wrong.
Shut it.
You've seen a detective being transferred before.
It's Han Se Kyu, right?
There's something more to it.
That lowlife wouldn't do this out of curiosity.
What's the real story?
Do you know where Jinyang is?
Yes, it's the new city that's being built, right?
The team that was in charge of Hanyoung Bridge incident...
did some background investigation on Sekang Construction Company.
They found clues leading to...
corruption charges involving the congressmen and the corporation.
There's over several billion dollars involved.
Also...
the three houses that were broken in have something to do with it.
What's more important is...
that I don't know if Han Se Kyu was aware of that,
but the stolen items contained...
a conclusive evidence for what went on.
Even after knowing that,
the prosecutor terminated the trial?
Keep still and pretend you don't know anything.
This case...
is far bigger than the Police Squad can handle.
- But still, we...
- You're still here.
Hi.
You're early.
Say hello.
This is Kim Beom Joo and he will be taking over.
Say hello, everyone.
This is Kim Beom Joo.
Look after them for me.
You're getting kicked out for not keeping them under control,
and you want me to look after them?
No wonder you ended up like this. You're too soft.
Don't worry, though.
I'll keep them under control.
Sir.
Wait...
Are you Lee Jae Han?
Do you know who I hate the most?
An idiot who runs around thinking he has something others don't.
Just one of them...
makes everyone look bad.
I would love to lie low,
but you people just won't let me.
It stinks.
We deserve an award for jailing Han Se Kyu.
Instead, our boss gets fired...
and the higher-ups replaces him with one of their hounds.
I'm guessing they're trying to hide something.
Don't worry.
I won't let you down.
I'll stir things up.
A bracelet of natural pearls and platinum.
A pair of diamond earrings.
They're here.
Is this it?
A blue diamond necklace.
Blue diamond necklace?
- Is it not here?
- I can't find it.
- Is it gone?
- It's not in here.
It's gone.
Of all the things that Han Se Kyu stole,
something could be used to prove...
someone else's corruption.
The missing item.
A blue necklace that was taken from...
Congressman Jang's home.
You haven't been home in a month.
Remember this.
Congressman Jang and the other gentlemen...
settled under the condition that you return everything you stole.
I'm sure you know,
but make sure you don't...
tell anyone about these conditions.
There he is.
I'm Shin Dong Hoon.
Han was released...
under probation this morning.
Some say it was a slap on the wrist. What do you think?
He stole from you. What do you have to say?
Well, I'm pretty sure...
the judge made the right decision.
Make way.
You suffered a big loss. Can you forgive him?
Did you retrieve your missing items?
I'm Detective Lee Jae Han...
from the Police Squad.
You settled out of court...
before you got everything back.
You are so generous.
- Move.
- Step aside.
- Get out of the way!
- I'm not done!
- Make way!
- Move it.
Wait!
Let go. Congressman!
- Congressman!
- Congressman.
- What's the rush?
- Please say something.
Why did you show leniency to Han Se Kyu?
Wouldn't it have been nice if you'd shown...
such generosity to Oh Kyung Tae as well?
Or did you have...
no choice but to release Han...
because of the blue diamond necklace?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Thank you for your work.
- Congressman!
- Please say something.
- Please wait.
- Say something.
- Congressman!
Why are you out in the cold?
What about you?
How is your cold?
Don't even mention it. It's embarrassing.
Look after yourself.
Don't get sick or hurt.
You need to take care of your health if you ever wanted to get married.
Do you want to die?
I was kidding.
Do you remember what we said?
About what?
If...
you got a message from the past,
I asked you what you'd do.
You said that...
you'd give it a try...
rather than not trying and regretting.
Even if it makes a mess.
But...
I think you're wrong.
It's best...
to ignore those messages.
Things could get...
really messed up.
Lieutenant Park? It's Lee Jae Han.
Are you there?
We arrested Han Se Kyu.
I know.
But that's not all.
He didn't do it out of curiosity.
A blue diamond necklace is missing.
That item...
is part of a bigger issue.
Detective.
You said that...
we should never have...
gotten in touch.
Lieutenant.
I don't know...
how this came to be and why you and I came to talk.
But I think we should stop.
What do you mean?
We can't change the world.
Don't you agree?
We'll only make matters worse.
An unrelated...
police officer almost died because of us.
Wait.
You should know.
Find out where the missing necklace is.
Kyung Tae suffered because of what Se Kyu did!
Please...
stay safe.
Lieutenant. Lieutenant.
I don't know what went wrong,
but if someone committed a crime,
they must pay for it...
regardless of how much money they have.
That's what the police is for.
Lieutenant...
Lieutenant!
(LEE JAE HAN, 1989-2001)
(INVESTIGATION REPORT ON DETECTIVE LEE JAE HAN OF HOMICIDE DIVISION)
Silly face.
It's been a while...
since I've heard that.
Shall we talk about old times?
The walkie-talkie that Lee Jae Han carried all the time,
you remember it, right?
The one with the yellow smiley sticker.
You placed that sticker, right?
Are you ready?
Yes, Sir.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Oh, it's going!
Gosh.
I'll do it again.
Goodness.
Listen.
As you let go of the clutch, press on the accelerator.
- Got it?
- Yes.
I'll try again.
It's finally moving.
Turn the steering wheel.
Okay.
That way. Stop, stop!
- Hit the brake!
- Brake!
You almost crashed.
I'm sorry.
Reverse.
Reverse. I said reverse.
Okay.
Reverse?
Stop right there.
Okay.
Parking mode.
Get off.
He's mad.
Yes.
No, he's not.
One, two. One, two.
- Get in.
- Yes, Sir.
Stop laughing.
- Pay attention.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
It's going. It's going.
She's good.
It's going. Gosh.
Hey.
- Hey!
- Yes?
You said you were ready?
You're not even close.
Gosh.
Just get rid of her.
She's helpless.
She's pretty though.
It's moving.
See? Look.
She can't even drive a diesel car. Why is she in Homicide Division?
We can assign her a driver.
It's not like she can afford it.
We said we'll rotate being drivers.
Why is it always me?
You're the best driver here.
Anyhow...
- help her with the car.
- Car, car!
- Hey, hey.
- Just watch her drive.
- Hey, hey!
- Goodness!
- Slow down.
- Hey, hey!
- Hey.
Hey! Hey!
Get out!
- We have a meeting today, right?
- Yes.
- When are we starting?
- We'll start right away.
There you go.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Have some coffee.
Here's your coffee.
I made it just the way you like it.
I only drink coffee in a can.
Stop acting like...
a waitress.
Why are you serving coffee and not investigating like a real detective?
- Hey.
- Who are you trying to impress?
Get back to work.
- Give me the page at the back.
- Okay. Hold on.
We have his face and MO.
We don't know his whereabouts so we can't catch him.
There must be a way to find out.
Did he not return this?
Hey, don't touch that.
That's his good luck charm.
A good luck charm?
What about that walkie-talkie?
You're well-known in the forensic team.
You are always there when a new skeleton is brought in.
But...
it's not just you who's looking for Lee Jae Han.
- Pardon me?
- Park Hae Young is...
also looking up on him.
Park Hae Young?
He asked me...
if I knew Detective Lee Jae Han from Homicide Division at Jinyang.
How would he know Jae Han?
None of his relatives have anything to do with Jae Han.
Hae Young was a teenager when Jae Han went missing,
so they can't have met.
Hae Young...
even asked someone from HR...
to get him a copy of Jae Han's personnel file in secret.
If they knew each other,
he wouldn't have done so.
They are strangers...
with no ties whatsoever,
but he's looking into Jae Han's past.
Isn't that strange?
Shouldn't you keep tabs on your team?
You're here early.
Good morning.
You stink. Did you shower in alcohol this morning?
Merci beaucoup.
- It's fine.
- Gye Cheol.
A new pasta place just opened up.
How about cream pasta for lunch?
I can't take cream on a hangover.
You look too bulky for pasta anyway.
I need soup to sooth my stomach.
How about offal soup?
You have gross taste for someone your age.
Get lost.
Offal soup's the best for hangovers.
You are so not on my level in many ways.
What about Hae Young?
Don't even ask him.
He always eats alone. To look classy.
Omurice.
Omelette?
What?
Why? Don't you like omurice?
With ketchup?
Hello, Soo Hyun.
I was waiting for you. I researched...
How about looking into this case next?
Park Hae Young.
Are you...
Is this the long-term Cold Case Team?
Yes, it is.
Detective Cha.
Do I know you?
We met once, long ago.
You don't remember me.
You came by with a male detective 20 years ago.
His name was Lee Jae Han.
Detective Lee Jae Han?
Why?
Do you know him?
Oh.
I know another detective with that name.
I'll let you two talk.
I saw you on TV recently.
You solved the South Gyeonggi serial killings.
So what?
You're the only one...
I could think of who can help.
20 years ago,
my fiancee died.
Her name was Shin Da Hye.
Oh dear. She was a beauty.
What did she do?
She wanted to act.
- Okay.
- We met when I was...
working at a studio.
A bit more.
Change the lens.
Hey. Hey, you.
Don't just stand there.
- Snap out of it.
- I'm sorry.
- Change the lens.
- Okay.
It wasn't easy...
but she worked hard.
Then she suddenly killed herself.
She was found in a lake. She left a note behind.
So...
why exactly are you here?
Please...
find her.
I see.
Wait, what?
You want us to find a woman who died 20 years ago?
Yes. She killed herself 20 years ago.
That's what I thought.
I took this...
20 years ago on the last day we met.
We used to date at this cafe often.
Da Hye.
Ever since she died,
I went to the cafe sometimes.
20 years have passed,
but the cafe is still there.
A few days ago...
I went there, out of habit.
Welcome.
This is the photo I took that day.
I think she's still alive.
Please find...
Da Hye, or whoever this woman may be.
A few days ago,
a young woman came to a store with a diamond necklace.
A pear-shaped diamond.
I thought it could be the one from the break-ins.
This one.
Yes, this is the one.
Who brought it?
She looked about 20.
Yes, I'd say she was about 20 years old.
A 20-year-old woman...
Can I see the tapes from your security camera?
That's her.
- This woman?
- Yes.
Hello.
Well...
Yes?
I want to sell this.
Where did you get this?
It was a gift.
Your boyfriend must be rich.
Why do you want to sell it?
If you aren't interested...
Wait.
Eight bills.
Eight...
thousand dollars?
You have no idea what this is, do you?
This is worth...
at least 80,000 dollars.
What's that next to the box?
- What?
- This black square.
Oh, that?
It was in the box.
What's this?
Isn't that a floppy disk?
A floppy disk.
They detected a large-scale...
corruption scandal regarding the development of Jinyang City.
Of all the things that Han Se Kyu stole,
something could be used to prove someone else's corruption.
Do you have it? Did she take it?
She took it.
Did she leave anything? Like a contact number?
She did leave a number,
but it didn't exist.
- It didn't exist?
- No.
I had my doubts that she'd leave a valid number,
and I was right.
People who bring stolen goods would never leave a contact number.
Then...
Kim Beom Joo, you scumbag.
I'll take the contact information.
Let's delete the security footage.
Sure.
These are the documents from the head office.
Forget documents. Get out there and catch the perp.
You lazy punks.
Gosh.
Are you doing any work?
Soo Hyun.
- Yes?
- Come to the parking lot.
Let's practise driving.
Oh.
Sure.
No one cares if you're not at your desk, right?
Is that true?
The women's night duty room has a phone, right?
Yes. It does, but...
why?
I need to find a phone number.
- Watch the road.
- Yes, Sir.
The last two numbers are likely wrong.
Call them all,
and find the one that has a woman in her 20s.
Is that all?
Hey!
What? Do you not want to do it?
No, Sir.
Different phone numbers. A woman in her 20s.
That is enough information.
This is a top secret...
between the two of us.
Yes, Sir.
Hello? A bathhouse?
How old is your grandchild?
24?
It's a grandson?
Hi, kid. Thank you.
An aunt? A grandmother?
No, thank you.
This isn't a prank call! Don't hang up!
I found them.
Of the 100 phone numbers with 2 different digits,
there were 24 residences.
Of them, only 5 had a woman in her 20s living there.
Shall we head into the city then?
- Me?
- The handle!
- Look straight.
- Yes, Sir.
You should stay in the car.
I found them.
I want to see who we are searching for.
But who are you searching for?
(JINSOO-DONG 238-5)
Thank you.
He isn't that old.
I heard many young people get Alzheimer's lately.
I know.
We should've found him a good hospital or something.
The photo did look similar to his late fiancee.
According to the angle and lighting of the photograph,
completely different people can look alike.
Of course.
That's not all.
How could he not forget 1 person for 20 years?
That's nonsense.
Not unless they ran off with your money.
He may not forget.
That's impossible.
People come and go all the time.
Don't be like that.
What?
You too.
- What?
- This case.
I'm against it.
So am I.
The body was already cremated.
- That's right.
- There isn't enough...
scientific evidence.
There may be evidence at the cafe where the photo was taken.
Why are you doing this again?
Think of how many people go in and out every day.
There couldn't be any evidence remaining.
We won't know until we look.
Forget it. Forget it.
Don't bother with other people's love lives and...
let's take Oh Dae Han's case.
This is a true cold case.
If what he says is true,
the body found in the lake was...
an unidentified body.
That makes this a cold case as well.
Gosh, she is impossible to talk to.
What about you, Lieutenant Park?
- You're against it, right?
- Of course, he is.
Kids these days aren't into devotion.
How do you know...
Detective Lee Jae Han?
Why are you interested in my senior officer?
Senior officer?
I used to work with him back in the day.
Why did you go to her funeral?
- Are you interrogating me?
- I'm asking because of this case.
Why did you go to Shin Da Hye's home?
I'm sure it was for the investigation.
Right?
I don't know the details,
but he said he was looking for the stolen goods.
The stolen goods?
Did you ask him which one?
He was looking for a blue diamond.
The stolen goods went missing.
It's a diamond necklace.
It hides...
a bigger secret.
Detective Lee Jae Han was...
chasing that stolen good all by himself.
This case is related to Han Se Kyu.
You're making me nervous. Why are you asking so many questions?
Was that after the real thief Han Se Kyu...
was arrested?
You're right.
You won't take on this case, will you?
Right?
I'll clean up now.
Let's do it.
Shall we vote on it?
- I'm in.
- I'm out.
I'm also out.
- I'm in.
- It's 2 for 2. It's done.
May I...
I'm in as well.
Who are you to vote?
He's our rookie.
So it's 2.5 to 2.
I'll meet with Yoo, so you gather the evidence.
Get Shin Da Hye's bank and credit card records.
You come with me.
Hwang Ui Kyeong, get over here.
- Get over here. How dare you?
- I'm sorry, Sir.
What is it?
I told you, I don't work with people who have secrets.
So, tell me the truth.
There you go again.
How do you know...
Lee Jae Han?
I told you. He has the same name as someone I know.
I thought you were going to meet with the family of the deceased?
I should meet with the detective on the case, right?
I'll go first. I'll see you later.
Don't forget to eat.
He asked me...
if I knew Detective Lee Jae Han from Homicide in Jinyang.
I heard you were the detective on the unnatural death case.
What brings you here?
I received the case file from back then...
and I had some questions.
I read that a fisherman found the body...
and that the body was identified using ID found in the wallet...
in the pocket.
It's as it says.
The body must have deteriorated significantly.
How was the family so sure it was their family member?
They said the clothes and items found on the body was hers.
But I don't understand something.
Shin Da Hye's home was in Seoul.
It's an hour and a half away.
Are you saying she came all the way here in her pyjamas and a jacket?
You're right. I thought that was suspicious too.
I thought it may not have been a suicide.
That's why I requested an autopsy,
but the family adamantly refused.
The family did?
I hear you still take care of your mother.
Yes.
I'd like to meet her.
I can go to your place.
Mother is ill,
so she's in the hospital.
Then...
may I visit her at the hospital?
I'm afraid not.
She is very ill...
and is in the ICU.
I heard you're the one who identified...
Shin Da Hye's body.
How were you sure that...
the body was Shin Da Hye?
Her height and hair length were the same as my sister.
She was wearing her clothes, too.
May I see...
some of Shin Da Hye's belongings?
No.
We burned them all.
Excuse me?
You burned everything that belonged to her?
Yes.
It was too hard on my mum.
I'm sorry I wasn't of help.
It wasn't a suicide.
Most suicide locations are...
places that hold meaning or in close proximity.
But Shin Da Hye and Migang City have no relation.
Plus, if she went to the lake in order to commit suicide,
it would've been premeditated, not spontaneous.
But...
she was wearing pyjamas and a jacket.
Nothing makes sense.
It is very likely that...
somebody killed Shin Da Hye and made it look like a suicide.
The family, too.
The detective requested an autopsy,
but the family adamantly refused.
They are definitely hiding something.
What did you find?
I checked the tables, chairs, doorknobs, everything.
We have dozens of fingerprints that overlap, so we can't find anything.
I told you, we wouldn't find anything here.
Are you going somewhere?
May I help you?
I told you, I really didn't know the stolen goods were here.
You know this woman, right?
What was her relationship with Han Se Kyu?
She had the goods that Han Se Kyu stole.
She frequented this house, right?
Was she his girlfriend?
That brat was a total player.
He just played her.
Where is everyone?
Stop right there.
Are you okay?
Get the flashlight.
Get over here.
Those little brats were so dirty.
I got sick from cleaning up after them time and time again.
Did she come after that?
After the thefts. When the stolen goods were here.
She came once, alone.
Alone?
That's when...
Shin Da Hye took the stolen goods.
Are you sure you checked everything?
I checked the table, the four chairs...
and even the dust on the floor,
but there's nothing.
Excuse me.
Does this book belong to the cafe?
No, a customer left it here.
That's right. That woman who was sitting there left it.
Be careful.
He was right.
(SHIN DA HYE)
This woman held...
all the clues to the case.
Shin Da Hye...
did not die.
(SHIN DA HYE)
(SIGNAL)
How can you find someone who's been hiding for 20 years?
What if I killed her?
It's Han Se Kyu.
How does it feel to get bit by a hunting dog?
Let's see who wins, me or that hunting dog.
I can't remember.
Should I cuff you to help you remember?
Why should I care?
What were you doing?
I ordered the investigation.
Did you find a floppy disk?
You sound just like that detective.
What about the fiance?
Did you find Da Hye?
I won't forgive you.
How dare you?
It's time to prove what you did...
in that house.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU