(All characters, places, companies, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(August 30, 2018, The first encounter)
"Bring Coach Kim!"
"Shall I rip your lips off?"
"Get on a wheelchair."
I can relate to the storyline.
I'm very excited and nervous at the same time.
I'll give my all for this.
I'll do my best.
I think it'll all be fine as long as I do well.
I hope you love our drama.
(They started off by showing how determined they were.)
(November 23, 2018, The first episode)
Action.
(Sky Castle became a bigger issue every time a new episode aired.)
(The drama caused a huge sensation.)
(It recorded the highest rating among the history of cable shows.)
(Why was Sky Castle so popular?)
You're the best. I love you.
(It criticizes the reality of our country's education system.)
The only goal of education is to get the kids into university.
He got into SNU's Med School with extracurricular activities.
I'm the top student!
What's the secret behind getting good grades?
I'm not the one who destroys their families.
It's the parents.
What is the happiness and success...
that parents want for their children?
And do the children want the same?
(Enthusiastic veteran actors)
Don't trust yourself.
Kwak Mi Hyang!
I'll take everything.
(The acting was gripping and captivating.)
You just study.
This is a crisis.
Please.
Mother!
Mom.
Love him loads and loads.
Let's escape the fiery pit!
(It'll be remembered for a long time.)
Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
(Shall we go behind the scenes?)
Open.
(Welcome to Kwak Mi Hyang's home.)
Do you recognize this place?
Do you know why we're here dressed like this?
You must trust us completely.
Do you?
- Yes, I do. - Good.
Some have not watched it at all,
but no one can watch just one episode.
Sky Castle is the talk of the town.
That is why we prepared a very special program.
That's right. We go behind the scenes.
Will you take the risk?
Ms. Kim, I can take the risk.
You'd better.
I said I can.
(Lee Sang Min)
(Jang Seong Kyu)
(Behind the Scenes at Sky Castle. Can you take the risk?)
I just loved the drama.
I watched the premiere,
the rerun, and the second rerun. It was always on my TV.
- It is so fun. - It is.
For those who need something to...
fill in the emptiness that the drama has ended,
we invited four of the main cast.
Please join us.
(Totally excited)
We got to meet these people at last.
Hello, Professor Cha. Come on in.
- Professor Cha Min Hyuk. - Hello.
- Hello. - Take a seat.
- It's so great to meet you. - That's right.
Could you please greet the viewers?
Hi, I'm Yoon Se A, and I played Noh Seung Hye.
It's nice to meet you.
(I'll show you my other side.)
(Awesome Seung Hye)
Hello, I'm Kim Byung Chul, and I played Cha Min Hyuk.
This looks so unfamiliar.
Hello, I'm Soo Han's mom, Jin Jin.
I played Woo Yang Woo, Jin Jin's husband.
I'm Jo Jae Yun, and it's nice to meet you.
(The introductions got us excited.)
Nice to meet you all.
As an avid viewer, I feel so nervous right now.
I just don't know how I'll manage to get through this.
First, I'll ask if you can tell how popular the drama was.
Of course. I got calls from a lot of people that I missed.
- I see. - This drama was a gift to me.
And when I'm out frolicking in the street...
You're "out frolicking"?
Gosh, Seung Hye got us started.
- Keep going. - I'm worried now.
"Give me an autograph. Let's take a selfie."
I haven't felt this fever in a while.
- Right? - That's right.
(Just like in the drama)
We'll dive into all things Sky Castle...
which we divided into a few subjects or classes.
The first subject is Korean.
Do you know the four-syllable nickname your fans gave you...
My nose is running. I'm so sorry.
- I'm sniffling. - Right?
It's cold in here. Colder than you think.
- Then... - There's no heating.
It's very cold.
I'll ask you, Professor Cha.
When you opened the door and said...
"Honey."
(He was left alone in the house in episode 18.)
When you said, "Honey."
You sound exactly like him.
- You shed tears and snot. - Yes.
Was it because you felt cold or...
I think I had a runny nose because of the tears.
- It's method acting. - Right here.
(Snot before tears)
What a mess.
- We used the second take. - I see.
After the first take,
I wondered whether or not to blow my nose.
- But I didn't. - I get it.
So the snot appeared before the tears did.
The director said that if we have a runny nose,
they'll erase it in post-production,
so he always tells us to cry all we want.
You took that way too literally.
(I'll go on trusting you.)
Professor Cha, Byung Chul, we'll start with you.
Do you know your nickname?
- What is it? - "Pacul Min Hyuk".
(Pacul Min Hyuk?)
Mercul, Mercul.
You've never heard of it.
You mashed up two separate nicknames.
Oh, dear.
That's a new one. "Pacul".
You're "Mercul Min Hyuk".
- I'm "Starlight Seung Hye". - That's right, you know.
I'm "Line-crosser Jin Jin".
- "Line-crosser Jin Jin". - Yes, "line-crosser".
Professor Woo?
- "Spine Yang Woo." - "Spine Yang Woo."
I talked about a slipped disk for seven episodes.
- For seven episodes... - He was bedridden.
I was always in bed or getting beaten up by Jin Jin.
- I hit and scolded him. - It was so rough.
Let's watch the scenes with the fantastic dialogue that...
got the characters their nicknames.
(The Queens' Memorable Lines)
Shall I rip your lips off?
- The lips. - That's it.
- Gob Mi Hyang. - That's a hit.
Too bad your daughter's a brat.
How dare you. Shall I rip your lips off?
(Surprised)
I heard that even the actors repeated that line on set.
- Yes, yes. - Yes.
She's not like a monster who cares only for grades.
Shall I rip your lips off? Who are you calling a monster?
She says it so well.
Gosh, that's scary.
What are you doing? Hey, Kwak Mi Hyang!
- Let go! - That must've hurt.
I lost a clump of hair.
- Did you really? - Yes.
Am I base? Am I?
Shall I treat you how Kwak Mi Hyang would?
The scene after that.
- Jin Jin's so pretty. - Don't say that name again.
- I'll rip your lips off. - The next cut.
She's pretty. She's pretty even then.
It's as if rose petals should fall from the sky.
- Like in a commercial. - Yes.
She's pretty.
Oh, Ms. Kim.
(Ms. Kim)
(Is she calling me?)
To make my daughter successful.
That is more important to me than anything.
I just want Woo Joo to be happy.
Don't be such a hypocrite.
However successful your husband is,
however successful you may be,
if your child's a failure, so is your life.
Just what a terrible thing it is that I'm doing.
- Such unfortunate circumstances. - I know.
(Suh Jin will do anything for her daughter.)
But Yeh Suh.
That's it.
I just can't give up on your life.
- Many moms empathized with her. - Right.
(Teacher Joo Young)
- Ms. Kim the coach. - She's here.
- That's her. - You must leave it to me.
- You must trust me. - She lost a lot of hair.
After that scene?
She emphasizes trust a lot.
I asked if you mean you'll take the risk, ma'am.
Yeh Suh has a fragile mentality.
Doubt and question even the problems that you know.
Snub and ignore everything that inhibits your success.
- Even if that's your mom. - This scene.
Let Hye Na into your house.
I told you to let Hye Na in.
Only the result...
will prove your worth.
When your parents are at their happiest,
- you shatter everything. - The look in her eyes.
(Tempted)
That is true revenge.
(The intimidating glare)
Honk, honk. I jumped out of the way at the sound of the car horn.
- "Honk Honk"? - What?
She's "Honk Honk Sue Lim" because of that?
Power is a virtue.
(Sue Lim's first day at the book club.)
This is an utter comedy.
This book club. Is it really what the kids want?
Are you not giving them a hard time...
to satisfy your own greed?
What? My goodness.
We should look after our kids. We should protect them.
- She provides an ideal. - Yes.
We are moms.
Yes. Because we're moms.
You will be punished.
I will end your malice.
Wait and see.
(She doesn't waver.)
- She didn't even blink. - Don't worry about such nonsense.
Don't cross the line.
Is she the 38th parallel? Why can't I cross?
- The 38th parallel? - Did you make that up?
- You cross the line. - It was in the script.
(Jin Jin reacts so well, so what's her famous line?)
My gosh. What's that?
- My gosh. - My gosh.
(The interrogative exclamation)
(He's envious.)
What's this about blocking messages?
My point exactly.
- "My point exactly." - My point exactly.
- They're all different. - My point exactly.
- There are so many. - Different nuances.
My point exactly. Four fried chickens.
I want chicken. Buy me chicken.
- I'd love to shoot a commercial. - Right?
She pulled my hair so tight that my eyes slanted up like this.
- I could even see behind me. - I made up that part.
- That was improvised? - Yes.
- No way. - This too.
I can't keep my eyeballs open.
You really couldn't, could you?
- I really couldn't. - How did you manage?
The director wouldn't yell "cut", so I said that out of anger.
(Spinning around)
Darn it, I almost winced.
It's become a habit.
You're my precious son.
(Even rash Jin Jin is a mom with strong maternal instinct.)
Mommy...
will die without you.
Okay?
(I won't forget that.)
(Starlight Seung Hye)
- How beautiful. - The stars are shining.
Don't study on a night like this.
This is amazing.
It's a different world.
See? Isn't it a winter wonderland?
Too much attention is a problem too.
Everyone here is rich and entitled.
That was the only way to erase your feeling of inferiority.
(That's nonsense.)
Everyone but yourself is an enemy!
If you don't kill, you will be killed!
Do you want to die? Do you?
- He lost his voice that day. - I bet he did.
He started trying to be funny after that.
We were the original funny couple.
No.
Do you realize you're being overly anxious about their grades?
As they say, what kills you in the desert...
isn't the heat or your thirst, but your anxiety.
You should believe in them and be supportive.
Since you have no respect for the housewife,
you need to know how tiresome it is to prepare each meal...
- and how thankful it is to be able - I really agree with that line.
to eat dinner that is made with heart.
I'll help you realize that first.
You should only compete with yourself.
Competing with others makes you lonely.
I believe true success is living a life...
where you're not lonely.
- I can relate to every situation. - Do you agree?
Agreed.
(Our mom is the best!)
Which part was the most memorable?
Nothing can beat that.
Nothing can beat "Shall I rip your lips off?"
It's such a vulgar way to curse at someone.
It was so shocking.
But once I kept saying it, it became quite addictive.
I've heard a lot of people say...
"snout" or "trap".
But I've never heard anyone say...
"Shall I rip your lips off?"
I heard you guys often used that expression on set.
I wanted to use that expression often,
but I couldn't dare say it to my senior actors and actresses.
So I'd suddenly say something and say...
"Should I rip my lips off?"
- That's what how I'd use it. - You used it on yourself?
She used it on herself.
We joked around like this and had a fun time.
We've seen a couple of flashbacks earlier.
Do you remember if there were any ad-libs...
that ended up becoming popular?
I always added ad-libs to my lines.
- Always? - Yes.
Later on, I had to voluntarily stop saying my lines...
because the director would keep the camera running.
"Cut."
(Jin Hee is the best.)
"This is the end. Cut."
Do you remember the huge fight we all had?
- Yes. - The really huge fight.
Half the curse words I said during that fight were ad-libs.
I'd love to hook you up to a dogsled...
and drag you about...
so your eyes flip and lips rip off.
Yes!
My line was only written until "dogsled".
After that, it was all supposed to get bleeped out.
I changed the lines so that they didn't sound like curse words.
I was originally going to say "poke your eyes out".
But I felt like it might get censored.
So I said "so your eyes flip".
- That's so detailed. - What's the difference?
- It's very detailed. - So I ended up saying...
"so your eyes flip and lips rip off".
I refined it a little.
I heard "My goodness"...
was written differently on the script at first.
Oh, right.
On the script, it read, "My goodness, goodness, goodness".
But because my character...
is very impatient, I couldn't say all that so quickly.
- Right. - So...
that's why it ended up getting shortened into "My goodness."
She can use that for any kind of conversation.
You can probably use it abroad.
I can say "My goodness" when I'm hungry.
- I can use it when I'm happy, - She's so good.
and I can use it when I'm sleepy.
- Even when you pass away. - "My goodness."
- She's good. - Then Professor Woo would go...
(Shut that mouth.)
The script would say "tongue rolling sound".
(He adds a gesture to the sound.)
That was part of my ad-lib.
The biggest ad-lib was calling her "Jin Jin".
- Jin Jin. - Yes.
Jin Jin.
(He called "Jin Jin" so many times throughout the drama.)
Gosh, my back.
What about you two?
He did a lot of physical ad-libs.
He'd extend 1 line into about 10 lines...
by showing his actions very meticulously.
He did a lot of ad-libs with his actions.
(She suddenly starts hosting the show.)
(Flustered)
- Are you sleeping? - She's like his spokesperson.
- Yes. - Spokesperson.
There's a scene where I get dragged out of the house by my sons.
And the script only said I'll be getting dragged out...
and that I had to struggle.
And it was my job to choose how I was going to struggle.
So I had to think about those little things.
He'd think about which arm or leg he's going to use at what point,
and what kind of sound he's going to make.
- You planned all that? - No, I wasn't that meticulous.
And because of that,
I couldn't even look at him because it was so funny.
- Did you have to hold it in? - Of course.
I had to do my best to stop myself from laughing.
I'm sorry.
(He has a lot of respect for the talented actress.)
There's a scene...
that I really tried my best to get a high rating.
What was it?
(There's a scene where the two actresses had to fight.)
My gosh, let me go.
What do you think you're doing? Stop being vulgar!
This is what Jung Ah said.
"Na Ra, I want to make your eyes rip like this."
"Can I do that?"
So I told her to go ahead.
I said I'm willing to do anything...
for the rating.
So she actually pulled on my hair very intensely.
According to Jung Ah,
she pulled Na Ra's hair...
just enough for her eyes to slant upwards.
But she got greedy...
and held Jung Ah's hands and pulled them higher.
You pulled her hands?
She's the one who made her eyes rip.
She made herself look like that.
Jung Ah told me that she looked really funny...
close-up.
She said she wanted to rip my eyes, but she kept pulling here.
But this part doesn't do anything to my eyes.
So I asked her to start pulling from right here.
But she wouldn't, so I pulled her hands...
and did this.
You fought a little back when you were young, didn't you?
Were you a bully back in high school?
I told you that I'm refined.
It's just that it all came out so naturally.
Normally, people get flustered when someone pulls on their hair.
- But I knew how to react. - It seemed so natural.
So that's why I thought...
You guys actually talk similar...
to the way your characters talked...
on screen.
We're so used to it now.
- It must feel natural. - Yes.
I used to be very refined.
- Used to be? - Yes.
I used to be very calm and refined,
but I became very bright after I took on the role of Jin Jin.
(Laughing)
Byung Chul, do you talk like Cha Min Hyuk?
No, we're not very similar.
Min Hyuk tends...
to yell a lot.
But I'm very aware of my surroundings.
Yes, he's very gentle and calm.
- He's a yes-man. - That doesn't sound good.
- But... Why? - No, it's nothing.
This is how I am.
- They'll break up soon. - You're going to break up soon.
- It won't work out. - They'll break up soon.
He's still in character right now.
That's why he seems so rigid.
But he's normally very gentle, and he does everything for us.
Now, it's time for math class.
Now, let's take a look...
at the highlights of Sky Castle based on numbers.
(Mathematics)
(As popular as it was,)
(Sky Castle created a lot of highlight scenes.)
(The cast showed solid acting skills.)
(The storyline reflected the issues of today.)
(And the directing was near-perfection.)
(What are the best scenes of Sky Castle?)
(Best likes: 11,594 likes, Episode 15: The Battle)
I'll rip your lips off.
Who are you calling a monster?
Rip what off? That's so base.
You vulgar woman.
What? "Vulgar"?
(They assume Yeh Suh and Se Ri were involved in Hye Na's death.)
Hey. Come over here, you fool.
I need to rip off your lips first.
- My gosh. - Stop it.
(They start with a quarrel but end up getting into a fight.)
I felt so upset back then.
You were so amazing, Byung Chul.
- It's like you're still married. - My gosh.
I was so scared back then.
(The scene of the battle was very frightening.)
This scene.
(The actors and actresses really put in their all.)
(You're not really fighting, right?)
(Stop)
That pillow made everyone quiet.
I think we should begin with this scene.
"The Battle".
Some people even call it a dogfight.
I feel like it would've been really funny to shoot that scene.
Let's say Byung Chul and Joon Ho...
- are shooting a scene right now. - Yes.
We'd be behind them reacting to the scene.
We'd be lying down and saying...
- "Look at them." - Yes.
We'd be like this.
- "This is so fun." - They're so mischievous.
- "This is so fun." - "This is the best."
(They're still in the middle of shooting "The Battle".)
(This is so fun.)
This is the behind-the-scenes.
(How was the shoot of "The Battle"?)
(They're all nervous before the huge incident.)
("The Battle" has finally begun.)
His pushing his head onto his chest was an ad-lib.
(Most of the scenes were improvised.)
That hurt, didn't it?
He really pinched his lips.
(He may be acting, but it really hurt.)
Joon Ho, doesn't fake it.
(Joon Ho, doesn't fake it.)
(You can already tell how terrifying it was.)
(This is what it actually looked like on TV.)
(Take it off.)
- "Take it off." - "Take off your glasses."
- "Take off your glasses." - That was an ad-lib as well.
(They stop the shoot because the nosebleed makeup got erased.)
- I remember. - The nosebleed.
(Nosebleed makeup)
Hey!
(They act very passionately and realistically.)
(And their chemistry was just as important.)
It must be essential to have good chemistry.
Yes.
My gosh, what's that? That's not fighting.
That's not fighting.
(Struggling)
Jung Ah is a lot taller than me.
My goodness.
So however much I tried to grab her hair, I couldn't.
The script said we should both pull on each other's hair.
- And... - They were doing this.
when I got up, her hair was a complete mess.
But I never even got to pull on it.
And it turns out she tossed and turned herself.
Because her hair was so fine, she made a mess of it herself.
I really liked this line.
"You jerk! Se Ri is..."
- "a club MD." - MD.
You jerk!
(Se Ri is a club MD. She's into planning, marketing,)
(and hosting customers. She's a professional.)
(This dialogue shows how much Min Hyuk loves his daughter.)
"She's a professional!"
- When he said "professional", - He spat.
he spat.
- And we were watching them fight. - "This is so fun."
We could see his spit flying across like this.
(This is where they sat to watch the fight.)
(Professional)
(Take my spit.)
She's working so hard.
That's right.
That's how he tried to step away,
and she had to improvise by wiping her face.
We didn't do just one take.
Later on, he started to collect spit so he could spray it.
(Feeling guilty)
- Did you see that? You saw that. - I did.
He had to do it again.
I'm collecting spit even as we speak.
It was a lot of fun.
We just have to mention this scene.
It's the scene that kick-started the rating rush.
The ratings started off at 1.7 percent,
but this scene shot it straight up to 8.7 percent.
(Memorable Scenes, Episode Four, Suh Jin Goes on Her Knees)
Ready. Action.
(How the scene was shot)
I believe we're done talking.
Just a moment, Ms. Kim. Five minutes.
No, just one.
She's down on her knees.
I heard that the ratings spiked at this scene.
I'm so engrossed already.
I never got to meet Ms. Kim.
- Is that true? - Yes.
If that were ever to happen,
are you willing to take that risk?
(Suh Jin agrees to do anything to get Yeh Suh into SNU's Med School.)
Even if a tragedy befalls like it did to Young Jae's family,
will you still accept the risk?
- I asked if you'll take the risk. - She's good.
That glare.
Yes. I will.
I'll take the risk. I will.
[VIU Ver] jTBC E01 SKY Castle Special
"Behind the Scenes at Sky Castle: Can you take the risk?"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Han Suh Jin's facial expressions)
- When she turned around. - Her expression changes.
(Even the actors are impressed.)
We all lie.
I heard they shot this in one take.
Everyone was so emotional at the moment.
This scene made me jittery. "What would I have said?"
I kept wondering what I'd have said.
It was so engrossing.
As a viewer who watched from episode one onward,
Suh Jin goes to Ms. Kim and then slaps her.
Yes.
(Suh Jin blames Joo Young for Young Jae's mom's death.)
As a viewer, I thought the story was progressing too quickly.
I thought the story was moving on way too fast.
But when Suh Jin went back and went on her knees to beg,
- I realized how it all fit in. - That's right.
Our director's famous for his fabulous endings.
He's really good at that.
- I believe that scene was the end. - Yes, of that episode.
Seeing Suh Jin go on her knees convinced all the viewers.
You mentioned while we were watching that clip...
that you never got to see Ms. Kim.
- I never did. - Me neither.
- This is what we want to know. - That's right.
We only texted each other.
I text to ask if her hair's okay.
She texts back to say she's losing a lot, and it's hard on her.
I wanted to meet her but never got to.
You haven't texted her yet either?
We have a group chat room.
I'm always nice to her because I'm scared.
(Acting cute to survive)
Is she cold and aloof even in the chat room?
- Her? - No.
Our chat room is hilarious.
We type like we're in character,
and you can almost hear us talk.
- That would be fun. - For example,
Suh Jin's real-life daughter, the actor's daughter...
drew each of our characters.
She did such a fantastic job that I said...
"My gosh, you should send her to SNU's Med School."
Ms. Kim said, "I'll take the responsibility."
(Laughing)
(The 3 Scenes the Viewers Most Empathized With)
I'll bring your dinner to the study.
Today...
(Seung Hye prepared a special meal.)
It's extra spicy.
Extra spicy.
(I want mild flavor.)
Son.
(Maternal Jin Jin Hee)
Sometimes I wish that you'll become a doctor like your dad.
But when I see you suffer,
If you look into Soo Han's eyes, he's just so adorable.
He's so sweet that you just want to hug him.
To be honest, even I don't know what's right.
I'm sorry.
(After she finds out her daughter pretended to be at Harvard)
(Seung Hye's confession made the viewers cry.)
I really don't know.
I thought my priority was to raise the kids well.
(Seung Hye had given up her dream.)
So I gave up on my dreams.
I feel like my life is an empty shell.
I was just overjoyed whenever they got good grades.
(Many parents empathized with her.)
I'm the one to blame.
I think that many parents sympathized with parts of the drama.
One special scene is the one with the spicy cup noodles.
Wasn't that improvised?
The director of photography gave me the idea.
- Director Oh. - Really?
The script mentioned a certain brand,
but we aren't allowed to say the name.
- It was a good idea. - We talk about being spicy.
I just loved the idea.
Other than you, Jae Yun,
the others are still single.
It can't have been easy acting moms and dads when you're single.
Because I'm still single...
and don't have a child,
I had strong doubts about whether...
I could honestly portray a mom.
So I told myself I'd do what my mom did for me.
When I was a child, she would scold me,
and then at night, she'd hold me in my bed.
I thought of the times when she then apologized.
I was really afraid at first.
- You were afraid? - Yes.
I was a troublemaker like Se Ri growing up.
Although I didn't go to the lengths she did,
while I was shooting the scenes where I'm out looking for her,
I kept seeing my own mom.
That's right.
What about you, Byung Chul?
While portraying Cha Min Hyuk,
I wondered if I could be a better dad than he.
I found myself thinking about that.
I could see myself feeling the urges that my character did.
Rather than approach the kids as a parent,
I thought I should treat them as a separate individual.
Someone who isn't too connected to me.
I thought that if I were to approach it that way,
then maybe I could make up for my lack of actual experience.
(The Sky Kids' Favorite Scene)
Yum Jung Ah finds out that Kang Joon Sang is...
She's so cute.
Hye Na's father.
She goes into the dressing room...
and cries in silence.
She didn't say a single word,
but her facial expressions and the sound of her crying...
was enough to portray exactly how she felt.
That was the most memorable scene for me.
After watching that on TV, I mentioned in our chat room...
that Jung Ah was just amazing.
The scene where I argue with Yeh Suh...
in the corridor and say, "Your dad is my dad."
Your dad is my dad.
Professor Kang who gave you those great genes is my dad!
After that I say, "Do what you want. The milk's been spilled."
Try putting that back in the cup.
The milk's been spilled.
- Even the kids... - Aren't they amazing?
They're the best.
I remember smashing the glass and china.
- I think he was traumatized. - He pulls that down. Oh, dear.
- Her treasures. - For that,
I had to pull it down and break everything in one go.
- That's my most memorable scene. - There's no second take.
We had just one shot.
- It was dangerous. - Hey!
You 60-percent fool broke all these expensive plates!
How dare you when you're so dumb?
He looks scared.
I lock horns a lot with my dad.
There's a scene where I cry and plead with him.
You made me think that only kids who get good grades are worthwhile!
There's a scene where Yoon Se A screams.
(Seung Hye's furious with Min Hyuk)
- Hey! - Wow.
It was like she was a real mom.
I felt like we were a real family.
- That kid. - At that moment.
Don't touch my daughter.
It was the day I smashed the pyramid.
The pyramid scene we did with Dad.
We'll only film your torso.
Why is... Is this when I say my line?
Why is the world a pyramid?
Earth is round.
- I loved that line. - Me too.
(My precious pyramid)
(Ki Joon rebels and smashes the pyramid.)
Why is the world a pyramid?
Earth is round. Why is the world a pyramid?
To us, that pyramid...
symbolized all sorts of pressure.
I was given a chance to break that.
I was so grateful and I had fun shooting that scene.
I thought it was a very important scene.
Fortunately, our dad helped us through it.
We managed well.
What are you doing? Let go.
(The special scenes were full of fun and energy.)
That was great.
We watched it all before, but it's still amazing.
- I still get sucked in. - Right.
He got kicked out. What happened next?
I found out in the drama.
He went outside and opened the garage door.
He did everything he could to get back into the house.
(Min Hyuk desperately wants to get back indoors.)
The director gave me the idea.
You want to be funny.
I can tell you now that...
over half of my character came from the editing...
and music that was added in post-production.
- What? - Hang on.
Are you up to something right now?
What's going on?
Who is this cute person?
She just said "Who is this cute person?"
They're still like a married couple.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
I have so much to say.
I feel like we should shoot 12 episodes of this.
(Laughing)
The behind-the-scenes of Sky Castle.
- 12 episodes? - Should we do it?
Exactly.
Let's shoot 12 episodes of it.
- We can't end it with just one. - Exactly.
We should use the same background music.
The popularity of Sky Castle...
created a whole new kind of sensation...
on the internet.
(Sky Castle)
It became the most searched word on the web.
It even made people come up with a new term called "Castlers".
And it even appeared on the news.
This is a very popular drama these days.
This popular drama shows the obsessiveness...
of private education among the upper class...
It brought about a lot of analyzations and controversies...
and caused a huge social issue.
(A lot of contents analyzed the drama in many different ways.)
- It even appeared on the news? - Really?
(Students from SNU made a video about it.)
(And even psychiatrists tried to analyze the characters.)
SNU's Med School graduates made a lot of contents.
It didn't end there. So many people even made parodies...
which shows how popular the drama was.
We will now share the videos...
that stirred up the internet.
(Who are you?)
("Men on a Mission" also did a parody of Coach Kim.)
(Scared)
(I asked if you can handle it.)
He's so good.
(Coach Kim looks a lot different under the bright light.)
(Sky Castle was popular among many celebrities.)
He's good.
- I just got goosebumps. - The one on the right is Yoo Ah In.
- I got goosebumps. - What?
Ho Dong is dressed as Yoo Ah In from "Veteran".
(She's weak-minded.)
(Bada made a music video of "We All Lie".)
(She even reenacted Kim Joo Young's appearance.)
Bada, the singer,
even made a music video of "We All Lie".
(She even reenacted Kim Joo Young's appearance.)
(Don't I look similar?)
(Each celebrity made a parody video according to their individualities.)
(The comedian, Kim Ki Soo, did a makeup tutorial on Kim Joo Young.)
Can you fully trust me?
We all lie
(Makeup tutorials were as popular as the parody videos.)
I'm going to try putting makeup on like Kim Seo Hyung.
(Coach Kim's Grim Reaper Makeup)
These are Kim Seo Hyung's eyebrows.
Makeup youtubers were mainly focused...
on Coach Kim's Grim Reaper Makeup.
Are you threatening me?
You must fully trust my makeup.
This part is important.
(Due to the popularity of the drama...)
A famous Youtuber, Korea Grandma, also transformed herself...
into Kim Joo Young.
Coach Kim, do you think my kid can become a mukbang youtuber?
She made a lot of people laugh by pretending to be...
a mukbang youtuber coach.
Eat a lot. Only think about yourself.
Just think about mukbangs. Eat up.
Keep eating.
Cut the nonsense, and shut your mouth.
Grandma, I can't eat anymore.
You punk, you already finished everything.
- I told you to order jokbal. - She's a very famous youtuber.
On top of that, people even created webcomics.
There are those who rule and those who are ruled over.
Those who give orders and those who obey.
- They drew it really well. - That's good.
- My gosh. - She looks so similar.
- Shall I rip your lips off? - Goodness.
("What goes around, comes around.")
And the most popular kind of video that people created the most...
were impersonations.
Let's see how similar they sound.
Ma'am, you must put this tree in your house.
You want to bring that tree into our house?
Mom, do you think that makes any sense?
If my grades go down, it's all your fault.
You must fully trust Rudolph, ma'am.
Shall I rip your lips off?
Why hold a party?
What's the use of being the top student...
when she's as rude as anyone can be?
When do you want the surgery?
What do you think about...
asking Professor Cha, your neighbor?
(This is an impersonation of Woo Yang Woo dancing...)
(when he's suffering from a herniated disk.)
Jin Jin.
My goodness.
That's exactly my point.
If you want to climb to the top of the ladder...
How am I going to eat those green onions? They're not cooked.
It's green onion soup.
Green onion soup.
Since you have no respect for the housewife...
I'll help you realize that first.
What?
Shall I rip your lips off?
(This is so funny.)
The drama may have ended,
but the parodies will continue...
forever.
- That was fun. - How nice.
Have you seen any of those videos?
I saw the one made by the dubbing artist.
- Yes, me too. - She did a lot of impersonations.
It was my first time seeing the other videos.
- Aren't they fun? - They really are.
- I only showed you a little. - They're incredible.
- There are so many. - There are a lot more.
There are so many.
Byung Chul, can you impersonate any of the other...
actors or actresses on the show?
Well...
He needs to gather energy...
- starting from his joints. - Sorry for putting you on the spot.
(He can't wait to hear it.)
"Rip what off?"
There's a scene where I say that.
I'll rip your lips off.
Rip what off? That's so base.
You vulgar woman.
He talks with a tune.
"Cha Suh Joon. Cha Ki Joon."
He talks with a tune like this.
I should've learned that.
You're very detailed.
Cha Suh Joon.
Cha Ki Joon.
My character did a lot of impersonations in the drama.
And the director kept wanting more...
and eventually asked me to try impersonating Cha Min Hyuk.
But because he's a guy, it was really hard to sound similar.
- What was the line? - "You cannot escape the pyramid..."
"You cannot escape..."
No, this isn't right.
- It's hard. - It's hard.
He's shaking his head.
- As long as you live in this world. - Can you show us?
"As long as you live in this world."
That's how he talks.
I can't say it like that.
That's why you did this.
Yes, that's why I just did this.
"You cannot escape the pyramid..."
"as long as you live in this world."
- Yes, this is what I did. - It was a great scene.
Why is that a great scene?
(Professor Cha gets worked up for the first time.)
A lot of people said I looked like you.
You guys keep talking nonsense.
Is there anything special when it comes...
to impersonating Jin Jin Hee?
My character talks with a rhythm.
"That's exactly my point."
You need to flip the sound a little.
- "That's exactly my point." - "That's exactly my point."
- You're scary. - "That's exactly my point."
Four chickens.
- I can impersonate Sue Lim. - She's really good.
"I let Woo Joo..."
"take private math lessons because he wanted to."
"But I never made him do anything else."
(She sounds just like Lee Sue Lim.)
Now, it's time for Yeh Bin.
You're good.
"My mom doesn't even know why I ran away from home."
My gosh.
You're so good.
- My goodness. - You're incredible.
The fans of Sky Castle...
made so many speculations.
And we're here to resolve all of your curiosities.
Yes, first of all,
I'm sure you all want to know how they are in real-life on set.
So we secretly received a report...
behind their backs.
Here's the first question asked by one of the viewers.
"Is Seung Hye and Min Hyuk actually dating in real-life?"
- Don't be flustered. - Look at his face.
If your face turns red, that's a yes.
I really want to say something.
(What are you trying to say?)
(Zip your mouth.)
- I should keep my mouth shut. - Yes.
- Why? - You don't need to.
- Can I say it? - Sure.
- Really? - What is it?
It's nothing much.
Byung Chul and I are friends.
And I could see that his heart was fluttering at times.
- We'd joke about it sometimes. - Don't get swayed.
They have such great chemistry.
- The way they look at each other... - They seem so loving.
is so cute.
So I went up to Byung Chul and asked "What do you think about Se Ah?"
I asked him what he thought about her.
And with that exact smile on his face...
- He smiled like that and said... - He always smiles like this.
- It's not something he does for me. - He smiles at you sometimes.
He smiled at me and said,
"I'd love to date her."
(Shocking news)
- We want you guys to date. - We really do.
(Now, all that's left is Se Ah's answer.)
(What will she say?)
He said, "I'd love to date her."
(Shocking news)
- We want you guys to date. - We really do.
(Now, all that's left is Se Ah's answer.)
(What will she say?)
But before she answers,
let's take a look at video footage first.
I guess something happened between them.
(Awkward)
- Hello. - Hello.
(It was the first day of the table-read.)
I'm Kim Byung Chul, and my character...
in Sky Castle is Cha Min Hyuk.
I'm Yoon Se Ah, and my character is Noh Seung Hye.
I hope you all love the drama.
- I hope you love it. - Please watch our drama.
Try being cuter.
(He acts cute.)
(They already seemed pretty close starting from this day.)
You're very good.
The making film?
Min Hyuk's shoulders are so broad.
It's different.
(Min Hyuk is embarrassed.)
Isn't he cute?
(Isn't he cute?)
This is a long time ago. It's when we first started shooting.
- Yes, it's during the beginning. - She's following him.
You normally follow someone's behavior when you're in love.
Can I talk more casually with you?
Haven't you already started doing that?
I thought you did that a while ago.
Your lips look like my dad's.
- Really? - Yes.
Was she making a joke?
I think she really meant what she said.
I did that?
(She touches his lips.)
(Are they really in love?)
- People say you're so handsome. - Did I touch his lips?
I think so.
- Do you not think so? - No.
- Do you want to take a photo? - A photo?
- I'd be honored. - Let's do it.
Those two are not there to work.
(Lovey-dovey)
They went there to play.
(Love is in the air.)
(Sky Castle, Cha Min Hyuk, Noh Seung Hye...)
(Slapping)
(He needs to hide his handsomeness.)
Oh, is that what it meant?
(He makes sure she's warm.)
There's something going on.
(Even when the entire cast is present,)
(she doesn't hesitate to show him affection.)
Did you kiss him?
- I did? - You did.
I kissed him?
What is going on?
Do you call each other?
We were filming on my birthday.
He changed our vault password to my birthdate.
What?
Hold on.
It was 0101.
I guess he was feeling pressured.
He called me to congratulate.
So I said, "Sing a song for me."
- And... - No way.
He didn't hesitate for a second and sang for me.
(Her heart's fluttering.)
At that time,
- Look at him. - my friends were at my place.
- So... - Did they hear him?
Yes. And he asked, "Were you not alone?"
Anyway, I loved it.
- It's so romantic. - I know.
Goodness.
- Happy Birthday to you - It was heartwarming.
I'm curious about his tone.
Happy Birthday, dear Se A
- Of course. - I said that.
I think I said, "dear Yoon Se A".
- How romantic. - Why my surname?
- I can't remember. - We're not strangers.
Anyway...
(Someone please stop her.)
As a fellow man in his 40s,
being able to sing that song for someone right away...
- is not easy at all. - Right.
I feel like we could expect some good news...
from them.
(These two showed great chemistry as a married couple.)
(We hope to receive some good news soon.)
This one was given to us...
by one of the cast members.
Apparently, there is an alien among the cast.
Let's find out.
I think my mom is an alien.
- I'm an alien? - She's an alien.
She is strong and has a loud voice.
And when she lifted her hair, her left ear was missing.
That's why I think she's an alien.
Oh, my.
(Soo Han, take a better look at it.)
(Do you see my ear?)
I didn't see it.
(Let us check.)
Woo Soo Han!
(Afraid)
I had a nightmare!
Just go to bed!
It's important!
(Laughing)
Good!
- I knew you'd be funny. - They're hilarious.
Is that more important than me?
It is!
(She sure does have a loud voice.)
She's so loud.
She's already checking how to enter.
(She checks her position.)
Your body...
is our body.
It hurts.
(Now, we will reveal her charms.)
I can actually hear the sounds.
- This wasn't planned. - Goodness.
Tell someone else to do it.
It's not easy for a woman to hit like that.
- She did this. - It hurts.
How dare you?
I thought those sounds were edited in.
She hits well.
(You hit well.)
- Maybe she learned boxing. - Right?
You're really good. Did you learn boxing?
Did you learn?
Tell us if you did.
I didn't.
(Embarrassed)
She looks so frail. Oh, my.
(That's a full swing.)
Okay?
I didn't know I hit you that much.
You little...
(She also harasses them with props.)
(Laughing)
- Goodness. - Does she always do that?
(She runs well in her high heels.)
(She runs like Usain Bolt...)
(in her high heels.)
- Wait for me. - You're very agile.
Isn't it difficult to run that much in high heels?
(She keeps running.)
She could be an alien.
I think she is an alien.
(Worried)
What should I do?
(You will still adore me, right?)
She looks so lovable.
(She is an adorable alien.)
No matter how much she hits you, you won't be able to hate her.
I said something that wasn't planned,
and it was, "You're pretty."
Your testimony is very different from your son's.
He called her an alien.
But you think she's beautiful.
Thanks to him, it helped describe our couple.
Before then, I was just a wife...
who was always scolding her husband.
But after his line,
- people started to love us. - Right.
- Thank you. - Just watching the footage,
I can see that you guys filmed in a friendly atmosphere.
How was it?
It was even better than that.
You guys just saw the tip of the iceberg.
- Right. - It was so fun.
Oh, no, your back. Oh, no.
That's good.
She's really beautiful.
You went to Anyang Arts High? I went to Kaywon High.
- Suh Joon went to Anyang. - I used to live there.
Where?
Step over me.
Don't!
(I will protect my daughter.)
(Behind the camera, she is mischievous.)
(Joo Young, will you take responsibility?)
(They look very friendly.)
- Come here. - It's okay.
- It's all right. - Wear it.
You could catch a cold.
Just wear it, you punk!
(Teamwork is the secret to their success.)
They gave me heat packs when it was cold...
and even gave me a blanket as a present.
Also,
when I struggled with acting,
they would help me by giving advice.
I really like them.
I joined the team late,
so for me, it was awkward.
They approached me first...
and asked whether or not I had eaten yet.
I really loved them.
It truly felt like I was their daughter.
It was heartwarming.
He bought me food often.
He really did.
There is a Chinese restaurant nearby,
and he bought me various dishes.
Every time our family eats, he's the one who pays.
My entire family,
my father, mother,
Ki Joon, and Se Ri...
all grew on me.
This is our last shooting,
and I think it'll be very difficult to say goodbye.
My goodness. He doesn't say things like that.
- Right? - He just left that day.
It's touching when those who don't usually express things do it.
- You're already tearing up. - I know.
Say something to your kids.
First, I'd like to say something to our oldest kid, Suh Joon.
(He's the eldest?)
Wake up!
You're rock bottom. You get zero points.
He loves our daughter as if she's our baby.
Se Ri!
(Don't misunderstand.)
(These two love each other like real father and daughter.)
To our daughter.
You truly did a good job expressing such complex feelings.
You did so well...
that we were so proud of you while watching.
Suh Joon.
You said it'd be hard to say goodbye.
But I'm glad it seemed like it wasn't too hard.
And Ki Joon.
You are so cheerful and funny.
Also, your acting had the depth which isn't common...
in kids your age.
I hope we all stay in touch.
Good work, guys.
(Everyone is touched.)
He's such a gentleman, right?
- Should I say something too? - Sure.
- Make it short, please. - All right.
Dear Soo Han.
I'm going to cry.
Me too.
This was your first project.
You did a terrific job.
It was so touching when you said...
that I felt more like your mom than your actual mom.
- His mother will be watching this. - My goodness.
- Oh, no! - We're sorry, ma'am.
- Sorry, ma'am. - We're sorry.
- I'm sorry for tearing up. - That's what he said.
It's probably a temporary emotion that he felt at that time.
Since you've become well known through Sky Castle,
I'm pretty sure that you will get more work.
I hope we meet again once you become a fantastic actor.
Next time we meet, instead of meeting as mother and son,
let's meet as an older sister and her younger brother.
I had such a great time, and you did so well.
(He is proud.)
If teamwork was the secret to a successful production,
the secret to the drama's success was that it stimulated...
the viewers to deduce certain things.
Several scenes and props...
encouraged the viewers to analyze and infer.
Here they are.
Castlers analyzed the characters' actions, lines,
and even the props while they waited for the next episode.
Why is this world a pyramid?
Their inferences came second only to that of Sherlock Holmes.
Let's look at some of them.
First one was the apple.
- The apple? - Right.
- What could it be? - What is it?
Castlers claimed...
that the director's intention was hidden in this scene.
They compared the apple...
to the fruit of knowledge in the Bible.
They predicted that...
Hye Na will meet the same fate as Adam...
after eating the apple.
Castlers predicted Hye Na's death...
through the apple she bit.
(They predicted her death through the apple.)
(Shocked)
This was...
Wasn't the ending amazing?
- It shocked me so much. - That was the end.
I was shocked to the bone.
There was another scene that caused a controversy.
It was the dragonfly.
(Their second deduction came from the dragonfly.)
Coming in second is something to be proud of as well.
Hye Na loses to Yeh Suh in an unfair battle...
and cannot accept the result.
(Hye Na suspects Yeh Suh of cheating.)
Enraged, she heads somewhere.
A dead dragonfly was found in Hye Na's place.
(- Is Hye Na going to die? - What does this mean?)
Castlers talked about how dragonflies are born...
in the summer and die in the fall.
They suspected Hye Na's death once again.
(This wasn't the first time a dragonfly was spotted.)
This wasn't the first time a dragonfly appeared.
(A dragonfly was found on a teapot.)
Before Hye Na's death,
a dragonfly was spotted on Suh Jin's teapot.
Also, Suh Jin's sandglass was analyzed by them.
(The sandglass seemed to be significant.)
They believed this was a foreshadowing...
of someone's death after some time had passed.
Were all these hints...
foreshadowings intended by the director?
The truth will be revealed soon.
They inferred all that. That's fascinating.
Isn't it?
We infer many things together.
This isn't something you can guess at once.
- They watched it several times. - Castlers?
They're amazing.
They need to be applauded. Thank you.
Actually, there was a spoiler for the ending.
It was very detailed.
Which one of those deductions did you think...
was baffling?
I had one.
There were rumors that I was going to die,
and that Soo Han would die.
It was a scene where I was hugging him.
Our family photo appeared,
and his face was blackened.
The light didn't shine there.
Because they couldn't see his face, they believed...
that he would die.
They suspect every single detail.
And they said I'd die because I knew...
Suh Jin's secret.
- Goodness. - It was baffling.
Is it because you talked a lot?
- So they killed me. - Oh, my.
Someone asked me,
"It's the history teacher, right?"
(That's original.)
I had to remember who the history teacher was.
(The history teacher had strife with Hye Na.)
Chairman of the board's niece.
(What? I'm the culprit?)
Since we didn't know who the culprit was,
- we had a debate as well. - Sure.
At Suh Jin's place,
there is a helper named Kang Young Sook.
Usually, the other helpers don't have...
- specific names. - Right.
But that woman had one.
- I see. - So we thought it was her.
(She was a candidate.)
(She also had strife with Hye Na.)
Get out.
Get out now!
(I'm innocent!)
- I thought she was it. - Right.
Right.
She also gave Hye Na...
- a hard time. - Right.
So we thought she had something,
and that she killed her.
- You guys did? - Yes.
It was the director's intention to make everyone...
try to guess and deduct things...
from these scenes.
We will reveal it to you.
- Really? - What was...
the director's response?
Let us find out.
(Curious)
What was the director's response?
Let us find out.
(Curious)
(What was the secret...)
(behind the scene...)
(where she bit off the apple?)
That part was already in the script.
Many people shared their thoughts on it...
and even mentioned the fruit of knowledge.
First, I put that scene in to show that only the true daughter...
would be able to leisurely eat an apple...
and roam around the house as if it was her own.
It started out that way,
but I began to find other meanings as I was filming.
(What is the truth behind the dragonfly?)
That was strictly a coincidence.
We do prepare thoroughly for our scenes,
but depending on the nature of the set,
we may not be able to do exactly as we've planned.
She was next to the window during the rehearsal,
and we spotted the dead dragonfly.
I knew beforehand that Hye Na was going to die,
so it gave me an odd feeling and decided to film it.
I didn't plan it out to have a significant meaning,
but our audience came up with various interpretations.
That's when I realized that the owner of this drama...
was not us, but the viewers.
It wasn't intentional either.
(Were there anything that was intentional?)
Ready. Action.
- Action. - Action.
(Sky Castle was made with the best team of staffs.)
(Now, they will reveal the hidden intentions.)
For every single scene I watched,
I could feel that our synergy was powerful.
I wondered when I'd be able to work on another project where all...
the staff and actors would have great chemistry.
Try to talk more smoothly.
Every time I start a new drama,
I devote myself completely to it.
(The secrets will be revealed.)
- Ready. - Ready.
Cut. Good.
(The Secret of the Castle)
(First secret: the set's design)
(The characters lived in flashy houses.)
(The luxurious props grabbed the viewers' attention.)
(What is the secret behind the interior designs?)
There are five different characters,
and I wanted to portray each of their desires.
(A grandeur that attempts to veil one's past weakness)
(The color black which reflects Min Hyuk's authority)
(An interior design which goes against the previous authority)
(Freewheeling and flashy)
(Second secret: the soundtrack)
(The song, "We All Lie", always made the viewers anxious.)
(It was considered to be the best ending song.)
(What is the secret behind the soundtrack?)
I really enjoyed seeing that every character was two-faced...
and pretended to be good people.
I thought about the keyword for this drama,
and it was "lies".
While composing the song, I had that keyword...
in my mind and made such a song.
(Schubert's "Erlkonig" was Joo Young's theme song.)
(Is there a secret behind this?)
Before I received the script for episode 13,
I had already chosen this song as her theme song.
And then, I read the script...
and found out that the writer wrote,
"Kim Joo Young is listening to "Erlkonig".
The fact that we both thought of the same song...
is quite fascinating.
(Third secret: mise en scene)
(Through various camerawork and artistic scenes,)
(the drama grabbed the viewers' attention.)
Overall, we filmed a lot while circling the actors.
The camera moved in accordance with the characters' emotions.
We did that so that the viewers could...
empathize and assimilate with the characters.
I want to kill Kim Hye Na.
We used mirrors and other reflective devices...
to portray the characters' other sides.
Sometimes, we even used 3 to 4 reflections...
to depict the characters' true feelings, inner feelings,
and even those inner feelings' innermost feelings.
Every time they had to decide on something,
we used such reflections.
Ready.
- Action! - Action!
(Fourth secret: directing)
We'll start off far away...
and then dolly in until we zoom into your face.
(A high-quality drama was made.)
(What is the secret behind their filming directions?)
There is a message in this drama that's aimed at...
all the parents who are raising and educating their kids.
I wished that they would watch this drama of all people.
We tried not to seem like we were teaching them,
so we put in some humor.
In order to prevent this drama from being easy to predict,
we really gave it our all and focused on the details.
- You should use your body too. - Okay.
I thought he'd be perfect,
(He's acting with her.)
Suh Joon, you need to show that you're not enjoying your meal.
Count how many grains of rice there are with your chopsticks.
- Okay. - Count your rice.
Try to pick out one grain out of all the grains.
I'm going to do a close-up later.
- So make sure it doesn't show. - Okay.
You were being emotional earlier.
Okay.
(This is how the close-up scene was made.)
Go ahead and kill me.
They try to hide...
their enormous greed as they talk.
And in order to portray that,
I decided to focus on their facial expressions.
And as we reached the middle part of the drama,
we decided to switch from facial expressions to hand movements.
People can't lie with their hands.
And the actors and actresses understood that very quickly.
So they did a very good job.
(Director Jo Hyun Tak leads the drama shoot...)
(with this meticulous directing skills and laughter.)
- "By the way." - "By the way."
"By the way."
(What's the most memorable scene as the director?)
The main character of this drama is Han Suh Jin.
And Yum Jung Ah portrayed the delicate emotions...
of how determined Suh Jin was to send her daughter...
to SNU's Med School even if that meant she needed...
to overcome her conscience or any other obstacle that got in her way.
I still can't stop thinking about that even after the shoot.
It's still deep in my heart.
Please save...
Yeh Suh, Coach Kim.
I feel like I'll sometimes think about those scenes...
when I'm alone even after the shoot is over.
(What would you like to say to the viewers of Sky Castle?)
Thank you so much.
Every single viewer is very precious to me.
What's the ultimate goal of life?
Is it being successful? The answer is no.
It's the happiness you feel as a family,
and the happiness you feel with the people around you.
I hope this gives you an opportunity to think about stuff like that.
(Think about the happiness that comes from the people around you.)
First of all, I'd like to thank the viewers.
Your love...
enabled us to passionately shoot the drama until the end.
I was able to realize...
that I was being loved...
Gosh, what's wrong with me?
I was able to realize how much I was loved and how precious I am...
by watching the results on TV.
And I feel like we received so much love thanks to that.
I'd like to sincerely thank you for that.
I received a lot more love than I deserved thanks to this drama.
I was so happy and grateful.
I'd like to thank Na Ra for putting up...
with my giddiness and immature behavior until the end.
Thank you.
(Touching and warm)
I'd like to say something.
As a viewer of the drama, I'd like to thank the four of you.
You made me look forward to every Fridays and Saturdays.
And I'm very grateful to all of you for giving me so much joy.
I'm sure the other viewers feel the same way.
(And the last story...)
Thanks to your love and attention,
we were able to cheer up until the end and finish the shoot.
I wish you all a happy New Year.
And thank you very much for loving our drama, Sky Castle.
This won't be the end. We'll surely meet again.
And I'd like to thank the staff for everything they've done.
I'd also like to thank the viewers...
for allowing Sky Castle to have a rating over 20 percent.
Thank you.
I hope the three of us will get to meet you again...
- through a lot of other works. - Good luck.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for watching...
And supporting our drama...
Until the very end.
- Bye. - Bye.
I'd like to thank all the viewers...
who watched Sky Castle. Thank you!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
We're done now.
- It's all over now. - Great job.
- You did so great. - My goodness.
It's so pretty. Thank you.
- Great. - Professor Cha.
Thank you.
- Great job. - It's so pretty.
- Professor Woo. - Goodness.
- You did great. - Thank you.
Sky Castle!
- Good luck! - Good luck!
Thank you. I got a bouquet.
Great job.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Great job.
- You did great. - Goodness.
- You did great. - You too.
Congratulations.
We finished shooting 20 episodes.
You did great.
1, 2, 3.
Okay. It came out great.
- Thank you. - You did great.
- Thank you. - I'm not done yet.
1, 2, 3.
- Great job, everyone. - Great job.
(Thank you for watching Sky Castle. I hope you're always...)
(full of love and happiness. From Writer Yoo Hyun Mi)