There's a Native American proverb...
that says if you repeat a wish more than 10,000 times,
it comes true.
I'll marry that man.
I definitely will.
My mother Shin Young Ae, who's a woman of obsession,
repeated that she'll marry...
my father Cha Soo Il 10,000 times to marry him.
Joong Won, what time is it in the US?
I'm sorry to call you so early.
I looked it up,
and ice hockey is the best sport to play, okay?
For her son...
to play ice hockey well,
she said "ice hockey" repeatedly 10,000 times.
Let me tell you what Bok Sil did.
In other words,
she took in Mr Louis who lost his memory and became a pauper.
She fed, dressed and took care of him.
She took very good care of him.
- Excuse me? - Yes?
Why was Mr Louis wearing...
the clothes of Bok Sil's brother?
That's a good question.
On his way back home from the airport,
on the street... What do you call those motorcycles?
- A motorcycle gang? - That's right.
There was a fight with a motorcycle gang...
during which his clothes and car were stolen.
- Excuse me? - The one in red.
Are you saying that the person who died in the car accident...
is Bok Sil's brother?
That's correct.
Goodness, what a tragic story.
Doesn't that mean that her brother is dead...
instead of Mr Louis who became her boyfriend?
That's right.
That's why they broke up.
It hurt too much...
for them to stay together.
I feel bad for both of them.
Come on, Mr Lee.
Why are you crying? You're so embarrassing.
Can't Mr Louis and Bok Sil...
get back together?
Please, I want to be with her again.
King of Shopping, Louis that I know...
didn't know the Native American proverb.
However, out of habit,
he repeated, "I want to be with her again"...
10,000 times.
Please.
I want to be with her again.
His wish that he repeated 10,000 times...
was about to come true.
(Episode 12: A Dream Becomes Reality)
Louis...
Louis!
Louis.
Louis, what happened to you?
I thought you went to France. What are you doing here?
Is my name Louis?
Louis.
Do you know me?
Who are you?
I'm Bok Sil.
Ko Bok Sil.
Bok Sil.
Gosh, it hurts so much.
Is it my head?
Louis, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Were we...
very close?
Mr Kim, this is Bok Sil.
What? What happened to him?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Bok Sil, wait for me at the dock in Dongbaek Island with Mr Louis.
- Keep him close to you, okay? - Okay.
From now on, you have to take me with you all the time, okay?
Louis.
Are you hungry? Do you want me to get you something?
I want some coffee, please.
Coffee again?
Okay.
Wait here for me. Don't go anywhere.
Is it good?
There was a type of coffee you used to like more.
Do you know me well?
Of course.
Mr Louis!
Mr Kim, we're over here.
Stay right there, Mr Louis!
Louis.
Excuse me, Sir.
Can we go back?
I didn't mean to get on the yacht, but you're leaving the dock.
I can't turn it back.
You must stay on the yacht until the end.
Mr Kim, did you find him?
Yes, he's with me now.
Thank goodness.
Could you wait...
- until the yacht returns? - Okay.
Okay, thank you.
- Hello, Detective. - Bok Sil, where are you right now?
What's wrong? Is it something urgent?
We found Bok Nam.
What?
But Bok Nam is...
He's dead, isn't he?
Well...
he didn't die.
Hello? Bok Sil, are you still there?
Then...
where is Bok Nam right now?
We've been informed that he's in Busan.
In Busan?
Detective. I'm in Busan right now.
Please tell me where Bok Nam is.
Where in Busan are you?
I'm...
I'm on the sea.
Right now,
I'm on a yacht in the middle of the sea.
I can see Marine City,
Gwangan Bridge...
and Dongbaek Island.
Do you see another yacht around you?
Another yacht?
Bok Nam is on that yacht right now.
Bok Nam.
Bok Nam!
Bok Sil!
Bok Nam.
Bok Sil. I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Bok Nam.
Is it...
really you?
Yes.
Bok Nam.
Seriously,
what happened to you?
If you have been alive, you should've come and found me.
I went to our house in Gangwon-do,
but nobody was there.
Bok Nam.
Gosh, Bok Nam. I'm sorry.
No, Bok Sil. I'm sorry.
Bok Nam.
You brat.
Don't you dare run away from home again.
I won't.
Bok Nam.
How did you...
get on this yacht?
Actually...
What? Why do you have this?
Bok Sil. Are you surprised?
I promised you I'd find Bok Nam, didn't I?
I kept my word.
(3 days ago)
Bok Nam!
I'm sorry about before.
No. You don't have to be. Bok Nam.
Bok Nam... That's not it.
Gosh, it hurts.
(Fire Hydrant)
What's wrong with them?
Hey! Stop the car.
It's not...
Stop the car!
I said stop the car. You punk.
Oh, my gosh.
He almost killed me!
Darn it!
Get out.
You punk. You just hit someone. Get out of the car.
What is he doing? Get out!
What is it?
You seem like a rich guy. Are you going to hit and run?
Mr Kim.
Mr Kim...
Hey.
I'll take care of this. I'll see you there.
He's sly and rude.
I hate guys like him.
Gosh, that's a relief.
I thought he was hurt.
Your wallet and shoes.
Give them to me.
Your mobile phone.
My phone, too?
The guys I was with are very scary.
If you don't want to get beaten up, just do as I say.
That watch, too.
I can't. My grandma gave it to me.
Dae Sik saw you wearing it earlier.
If I don't bring it, he'll kill me.
But my grandma gave me this.
Take off your clothes, too.
What?
Gosh, I need to go to see Grandma.
Why isn't he coming?
Are you really going to come back in an hour?
Yes.
- Really? - Gosh, I am.
I don't have the address and my mobile phone. It's driving me crazy.
Mr Kim!
(Fire Hydrant)
Hey. I'll take care of this.
Bok Nam saved me.
Of course.
He's Bok Sil's brother indeed.
Bok Nam.
Bok Nam...
Bok Nam!
Where did he go?
(168 Steps Monorail)
Gosh, 168 steps? Here I go.
Bok Nam.
I can do it.
Oh, my legs.
I'm doomed.
Bok Nam.
Come here.
I'm really sorry about stealing your car and your clothes,
so please don't report me to the police.
Of course not.
Thank you so much for being alive.
Now, I can meet Bok Sil.
Bok Sil. Bok Nam!
Bok Nam, I'm a good person.
You don't have to run away from me.
You know my sister?
I know Bok Sil very well.
- How do you know her? - I lived with her.
No way.
Did my sister get married?
Married?
We haven't gotten married yet.
Are you saying that she lived with you in Seoul?
Yes.
That's why no one was there in Gangwon-do.
That's not why.
She came to Seoul to find you.
Gosh, Ko Bok Sil.
What brought you to Busan?
I looked for you everywhere.
I cried so much...
because I thought you died instead of me.
Here's what happened.
Why did you give him your clothes?
I was very scared.
I went back home because I was scared,
but Grandma and Bok Sil weren't home.
I didn't know what to do.
That's why...
I decided to go as far away as possible from Seoul.
So I ended up here.
I see.
You must have been scared, too.
I know how that feels.
I felt that way, too.
However, I wasn't scared at all thanks to Bok Sil.
I'll protect you from now on.
Brother.
I almost forgot.
What do you call your wife's brother in Korean?
Well,
it's your sister-in-law.
- Sister-in-law? - Yes.
Okay, my sister-in-law.
I'll protect you from now on.
Why isn't it an international call when he's in France?
Hello?
- In Sung. It's me, Louis. - What's going on?
Are you in Korea?
Don't be shocked.
- I found Bok Nam. - What? You did?
(Do it until you make it.)
Get everyone together and come to Busan now.
Bok Nam is alive as you can see.
I'm Ko Bok Nam.
I found him in Busan.
It wasn't Bok Nam who died. Someone else died in the accident.
Come to Busan...
and help me with the reunion of Bok Nam and Bok Sil.
Oh, I need Mr Cha to do something for me.
Bok Sil.
We have to go to Busan on a business trip.
- Right now? - Yes.
Did you know that Louis went back to France?
Yes.
He said goodbye in a letter.
He'll do well. He'll do well anywhere.
Mr Cha, please tell Bok Sil something that reminds her of me.
If you take Donghae Nambu Line from Haeundae, you'll get to Pohang.
See you in Seoul.
And send Bok Sil to Haeundae Station.
Louis.
In Sung will lead the mission.
Louis met Bok Sil.
Bok Sil.
Bok Sil, wait me at the dock in Dongbaek Island with Mr Louis.
Keep him close to you, okay?
Mr Kim will lead Bok Sil to the dock.
- Mr Louis! - Mr Kim, we're over here.
Stay right there, Mr Louis!
When Mr Kim chases after me,
I'll run to the yacht.
Stay here, okay?
Ms Heo will be in charge of Bok Nam.
Sir, after the woman comes in,
start the yacht as soon as the man leaves.
Even if she asks you to stop, you must keep going.
Go out to the sea.
Give the order to the yacht captain.
Bok Sil, where are you now?
Do you see another yacht around you?
Detective will call Bok Sil and tell her about Bok Nam.
Bok Nam is there, too.
Make it as urgent as possible.
Bok Nam, over here!
Bok Nam.
Bok Nam will appear when Bok Sil calls your name.
Bok Sil.
- Is everyone okay? - Okay.
- Okay. - I don't agree with this plan.
- Why? - Bok Sil will be very surprised.
If you appear as a pauper when you should be in France,
Bok Sil will be in such a shock.
That's why this is a surprise.
It's to surprise her.
When she's surprised to see Louis,
we'll surprise her again with Bok Nam.
It's a great setup to surprise her with Bok Nam.
- I don't agree, either. - Why not?
Is it necessary...
for you to pretend to be penniless?
You're too precious to do that.
I was actually penniless when I first met Bok Sil.
Bok Sil saved me even though I was poor.
By reenacting the day we first met,
I want her to remember how we met.
I'll use Bok Nam to prove that...
it was a blessing that Bok Sil and I met.
Mr Louis is so romantic.
He wants to plan...
a surprising event for Bok Sil.
I'm so touched.
Anyway, please help me.
All of you. Please.
- Okay? - Okay!
Okay.
- Okay. - Okay?
Let's start. Ready, action!
Why did you take a picture?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll do it again. It's a video now.
Ready, action!
Bok Sil. Are you surprised?
I promised you I'll find Bok Nam, didn't I?
I kept my word.
Okay. Good.
Why did you stop? I wasn't done.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'll start over.
In Sung, get it right this time.
- Shall I start? - Yes.
Bok Sil. Are you surprised?
I promised you I'll find Bok Nam, didn't I?
I kept my word.
Do you know how much trouble I went through?
I had to run around for hours.
You said Bok Nam was Slow Toad,
but he was so quick. He kept jumping around.
I even climbed 168 stairs.
As many as 168 stairs.
Also, I had to wear this thin jacket for today's event.
I wore more clothes inside.
Bok Sil.
The day I first met you was...
the luckiest day of my life.
Thank you...
for meeting me again today.
(Congratulations! We have found Bok Nam.)
The day I first met you was...
the luckiest day of my life.
Thank you...
for meeting me again today.
I promised you I'd find Bok Nam.
I told you to trust me.
Thank you, Louis.
What are you doing? Give them a big hand.
It must be there. She lives on such high ground.
- Can we really visit her like this? - Do you think I'm that rude?
I already got Bok Sil's permission.
She told me the password as well.
You're so tenacious.
What? What's wrong with that?
I'm the one...
who made you a postmaster when you had no ambition.
Well... That's true.
I can easily turn Bok Sil into an oriental doctor.
She's an extraordinary girl.
If we support her well, she'll be very successful.
So this is where she lives.
- Put them in the fridge. - Oh, yes. I will.
Freeze.
Who are you?
Why did you...
come into an empty house and open up the fridge?
What about you? Who are you?
How do you know Bok Sil?
Do you know Bok Sil?
Well... I'm...
Bok Sil's mother.
Bok Sil said she doesn't have parents.
I'm her neighbour and her security manager.
I'm like her step-mother.
What about you?
I'm...
Bok Sil's future mother-in-law.
Mother-in-law?
But Louis said he only has a grandmother and no parents.
Who is Louis?
Aren't you Louis' mother?
I'm Cha Joong Won's mother.
Oh, my.
Gosh. What is happening?
By Louis, do you mean...
- the successor of Gold Group? - Yes.
Are you saying...
he and Bok Sil are going out or something?
It's more than that.
They used to live here together.
Excuse me?
Why isn't he coming?
Ma Ri.
Date someone who likes you.
Both Mr Cha and Louis aren't interested in you.
Don't waste your time on them.
Mum. Are you really my mum?
Why aren't you taking my side?
I'm just worried that you might get hurt later.
I can set you up on a blind date. Are you interested?
He's my friend's son.
He's a great guy.
You know how much I care about beauty, right?
Are you Ms Baek Ma Ri?
Yes, I am.
What did you just say?
I said I already have someone I like.
She moved from Yokji Island to Busan.
I can't live without her.
Why did you come here then?
If you had said it sooner, I wouldn't have come here.
I came all the way from Seoul.
How dare you make a fool of me?
He is my mum's friend's son.
I shouldn't.
I shouldn't throw it.
I'm Baek Ma Ri, the Mother Teresa of Goldline.
Bye.
Okay. Go back to Seoul with Bok Sil and her brother.
I haven't been in Busan for a long time.
This city is not letting me go.
Look at you. You're all worried about me.
You've grown up, Louis.
Okay. I'll talk to you later.
Oh, isn't that Ma Ri? It's her.
What brings her to Busan?
- Ma Ri. - My goodness!
Did something happen? Why are you crying?
It's none of your business.
- Ma Ri. - Gosh, go away!
Don't come near me.
Okay. That time, I...
- No! Don't say anything. - All right. Goodness.
Did I scare you?
You're disgusted with me, aren't you?
Wait up.
- Ma Ri. - Why do you keep following me?
Well...
If you're depressed,
you should eat ulmyeon.
And eat jjajangmyeon when you're annoyed.
Do you want to go watch a movie with me?
I know of a good place.
It's over there. You see that mountain, right?
It's very pretty.
Do you want to come? Follow me.
What's he saying?
Hey! Let Bok Nam sit beside Bok Sil.
Why should I? I haven't seen her for a long time, either.
- Bok Nam could have died. - Me, too.
Shut it. This is my car.
Fine.
Go in.
Am I your driver or what?
Gosh, this is so pathetic.
Everyone, put your seat belts on!
My driver, let's go.
Hey! How dare you call me that?
Go, go, go!
The shape of the lighthouse resembles that of a baby bottle.
Bingo.
People call it Baby Bottle Lighthouse.
My random guess was correct.
I heard that women conceive babies after visiting this lighthouse.
Baby?
Jung Ran, you should have a baby before you get older.
Ho Joon.
Let me remind you.
We're not married, and you haven't even proposed to me yet.
And what? A baby?
Go through the proper steps!
You see how well Mr Louis treats Bok Sil.
He planned that touching event for her.
You should learn from him!
Jung Ran.
Jung Ran. I was just worried about you giving birth at an old age.
Don't worry about me and mind your own business!
Don't follow me.
- Jung Ran... - I said, don't follow me!
Jung Ran, let me explain. Jung Ran.
Are we there yet?
I must have been crazy.
I shouldn't have followed him.
Gosh, my feet hurt.
- Here. - What are you doing?
Wear them. You said your feet are hurting.
I cannot wear them.
Do you actually think these shoes go with my elegant outfit?
I know that they don't,
but you're in pain. I'll make it work. Just a second.
My gosh. Oh, no. What are you doing right now?
Gosh, wait for a second.
Oh, gosh. My goodness.
My gosh, look. Hey, stop it. Goodness.
Oh, my goodness. Hey!
Why are you running away with my shoes?
You told me to stay far away from you. We're almost there. Follow me.
His feet will be cold.
Is he pretending to be kind or what?
Gosh, just the sight of him annoys me so much.
Goodness, what is this?
This is ridiculous.
In 1, 2, 3.
- The movie is starting now. - Let's go.
- Isn't it so nice here? - I told you not to come near me.
Right, I was about to walk away.
That day,
I know you had a tough day because of me.
What are we going to do now? I have to go!
What do you want me to do?
If we can't pull over,
I might end up doing something I'll regret so much later.
Hold it, okay? You have to hold it at all costs!
Gosh, my stomach! My goodness!
- Goodness gracious! - Oh, my goodness!
Oh, no.
- I was... - Shut it.
Don't you dare bring it up. I don't even want to think about it.
I heard you don't drive that car any more because of me.
- Shut your mouth! - Okay.
- But if you need... - Gosh, seriously!
- I can take the car and... - What do you want from me?
Let's go watch the movie.
Is she cold?
Go away.
Shall I just let it out?
Is she thirsty?
- Ma Ri, I got this for you. - I said, go away.
Okay, I won't come near you.
I'm sorry.
I should just leave.
- Gosh, what is this smell? - It stinks.
It was me.
Judging from the sound,
I'm convinced that it was my fart!
(I'm convinced that it was my fart!)
It smells like he ate a ton of kimchi.
You got it wrong! I ate meat.
- We want to focus on the movie. - Yes, I'm sorry.
- Please sit down. - Okay.
I also did number two in a car a month ago.
My goodness. I apologise.
- I'm sorry. - We want to watch the movie.
Okay.
Didn't it sound like a blast of a ship horn?
Gosh, it's so hilarious.
Here. Eat slowly. There's a lot of food.
- He's not a ghost, right? - No.
He's not a ghost, indeed.
We thought you were dead. You better be good to your sister.
She went through so much because of you.
- Do you understand? - Yes.
I went through a lot, too. Do you get what I'm saying?
Yes.
Two guys in your life were thought to be dead.
Goodness. I must say, your life is so dynamic.
I know, right?
Eat slowly. Chew well.
Drink some water.
Gosh, I'm so full.
- Go home. - Why? I want to sleep here.
This room is way too small for the three of you.
The four of us slept in your room last time.
I only let you guys stay with us because you had nowhere to go.
You live in a fancy mansion now.
Why would you sleep in this tiny room?
Because Bok Sil is here.
- Yes, just sleep here. - I will.
Goodness. Let's go now.
They haven't seen each other for so long, so they should catch up.
You're so slow.
Oh, I see.
Bok Sil.
I'll let Bok Nam take my place today.
Thanks.
- Goodnight, my sister-in-law. - You, too.
Do you mean brother-in-law?
The two of you have a lot to learn.
You two are like two peas in a pod.
Sweet dreams.
- Goodnight. - You, too.
- You can sleep beside In Sung. - Gosh. No, thanks.
All right. Goodnight, guys.
- Goodnight. - Goodnight.
You must be tired. Let's go to bed.
I'll do it for you.
Bok Nam.
Do you know...
that Grandma passed away?
Yes.
I heard.
She was very worried about you.
Before I left for Seoul, I promised her...
that I'd be sure to find you...
and cook a warm meal for you.
Grandma.
Don't worry about Bok Nam and rest in peace.
I'll be sure to find him.
I'll fix a warm meal for him and take care of him.
Grandma, so...
don't worry about us...
and just rest in peace.
Grandma.
I kept my promise.
You don't need to worry about us any more.
The man I know,
King of Shopping, Louis, seemed naive,
gullible and inept.
However, he was a man with a non-judgmental heart.
His boundless sincerity...
transformed her sadness into happiness...
and made a miracle happen.
Yes, Nam Joon Hyuk speaking.
The suspect of the Eunsung-dong case woke up?
Okay. I'll be right there.
- Hey, let's go to the hospital. - Okay.
The suspect of the Eunsung-dong case regained his consciousness.
Oh, is that right?
We're on our way to the hospital now.
I'll call you as soon as we confirm his identity.
Okay. Thank you.
What if Mr Goo...
tells them about me?
What's going on?
It's me, Sir. The suspect is gone.
You two officers!
Were you two slacking off or what?
Search the area. Move!
Mr Baek. We're at the hospital now,
but the suspect is gone.
Seriously?
I wanted to know who he is.
Okay. Please let me know if you find him.
Hello?
Yes, it is.
May I ask who is calling?
I see. You work with my husband.
Mr Goo?
Please visit us sometime. I'd love to invite you over for a meal...
What is wrong with you?
Get out now. Leave!
Honey, he'll hear you. Do you have to be that rude to me?
Get out, please!
Why do you get angry at me all the time?
Mr Goo?
Where are you now?
Let's meet now. Let's talk in person.
I haven't talked to you in so long, Mr Baek.
So Kang Ji Sung...
went back to Gold Group while I was unconscious.
Are you...
trying to threaten me now?
Gosh, what are you talking about?
It's not like I went to see Ms Choi.
If you're going to keep that defensive attitude of yours,
I don't know how I'll change.
All right.
How much do you want?
What do you want me to do?
Hello? Hello?
What if...
Hello?
(Shopaholic Louis)
Mr Goo?
Mr Baek's voice is recorded here.
Why did you lie to me?
What do you want from me?
I like Bok Sil. It's too bad.
Don't look at me like that. You're making me feel vulnerable.
Why is that?
Is Bok Sil the only thing on Louis' mind?
I thought you looked familiar when I first met you.
Have we met before?
- What happened to his treasure box? - It's gone.
Disappear, so that no one can find you.
I'm mapping out a big plan at the moment.