Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Mr Cha.
- Mr Cha.
- What? What is it?
- I want to go to the bathroom.
- Then go! Just go!
- But I'm scared.
- Goodness.
Please.
I was having a nice dream.
Please?
Are you okay?
Of course, I am not.
What am I doing in the middle of the night? I'm not your secretary.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Can we go a little faster, please?
We're here.
- Please wait for me here.
- Okay.
It looks so shabby and grubby.
I bet there are ghosts.
Ghosts?
- Can you come inside with me?
- Are you out of your mind?
- Then can you sing for me?
- What?
Sing loudly until I come out.
- Who do you think...
- Loudly, okay?
I'll be right back.
Gosh, I'll be right out.
In this moment.
At this place.
The moment I desperately wanted and hoped for.
My dreams.
My wishes.
They may come true.
Right here today.
Can you sing more loudly?
In this moment.
Like magic
I throw away the chains that held me down.
The only thing
I have now is certainty.
The only thing.
That remains is victory.
There was a moment...
when someone was happy to sing for me.
Bok Sil, what is your most memorable moment?
Right this moment.
There was an emotional moment when someone cared for me...
even though I had nothing.
Honey, I found Louis.
- Someone was...
- I found Louis.
I found Louis!
She was most proud of herself...
when she found me.
Such a moment...
awaits my grandmother,
Choi Il Soon.
(EPISODE 13: THIS IS THE MOMENT)
Hello?
Mr Baek.
Who's calling?
Oh, hello? Who's there?
This is Mr Goo.
Mr Goo?
Hello? Hello?
Was it a wrong number? He hung up.
- It must be a prank call.
- I think so.
What brings you here at this hour?
Well...
I stopped by to see Ms Choi.
- Grandma is sleeping right now.
- Is that so?
I guess I came here too late.
Where's Mr Kim and Ms Heo?
- They're taking the day off.
- I see.
Then I'll come back later.
Mr Baek.
Do you want some ramyeon?
You're good at making ramyeon.
I learned it from Bok Sil.
Is everything over between you and her?
You were so determined to go to France.
I was surprised to see you after a few days later.
- Didn't you hear the news?
- What news?
All of my memory came back.
- What?
- I found Bok Sil's brother, too.
Isn't that great?
Right.
Why did you lie to me?
Lie about what?
You said that I was best friends with Ma Ri,
but that was a lie.
I remember Ma Ri bullying me when we were young.
Well...
I thought you two were close.
Why are you sweating so much?
What? Sometimes,
you sweat while eating when you get old.
Let's finish it.
That's interesting.
You sweat a lot when you get old.
Mr Baek.
Are you out of your mind? Why did you come here?
Get in the car.
Now!
Get me some fund so I can flee.
My identity has been exposed to the police.
I'll stay out of the country until things settle down.
How can you leave when you entered the country illegally?
I'll take care of it, so get me the money.
- How much do you need?
- One million dollars.
In cash.
Your voice...
is recorded here.
How dare you record my voice?
Do you think I worked for you without a good backup?
You probably have realised what might happen...
if you do anything wrong.
Gosh, look at these chestnuts.
My goodness.
They look big and delicious.
Gosh.
What kind of dream was that?
Could it possibly be a conception dream?
Bok Nam.
Your lunch is ready. Just serve yourself some rice.
Don't worry about it. I'm not a kid.
You are a kid. Do you think you're a grown-up?
Good morning, Bok Sil and Bok Nam.
- Hello, In Sung and Ms Hwang.
- Hi.
Hey, Slow Toad.
Did you sleep well?
Yes. I had a good sleep.
Gosh. You shouldn't have run away from home.
- Did you bring me food again?
- Louis told us...
It's just leftover. I told you my nickname was Ms Kindhearted.
You're not kindhearted.
- Not at all.
- Just put these in the fridge.
All right.
- Eat. You should go to work.
- Yes.
Let me give you a ride.
Louis told me to drive you every morning.
Gosh, how devoted.
Is Bok Sil the only thing on Louis' mind?
Let's go.
Thank you for the food.
(IN SUNG)
Hi, In Sung.
Mr Louis. Bok Sil went to work.
Okay.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Congratulations on finding Bok Nam.
I still can't believe that Bok Nam is alive.
I'm so good to see you happy.
Maybe it's because I'm Daddy Long Legs.
Is Bok Nam going back to school?
Well... He's not a very good student,
so he'll have to take some lessons first.
Is he not ready to go back to school?
Yes, he's not.
I guess he's different from you.
You should also study, pass the qualification examination...
and go to a university.
If you get proper education, you'll be much more successful.
I can see that.
Don't look at me like that.
You're making me feel vulnerable.
Why is that?
- Louis.
- Why aren't you at work?
Why would you feel that?
Gosh. It's none of your business!
My goodness.
(DADDY LONG LEGS, CHA JOONG WON)
What's that?
What is this? It says Daddy Long Legs.
Why is he Daddy Long Legs?
He's a director. Change it.
No.
- He asked for it.
- What?
Change mine to Dear Long Legs, then.
It's nothing to be jealous of.
Goodness.
Don't you have to go to work?
I'll start working from next week.
I am...
mapping out a big plan at the moment.
- Mapping out?
- You startled me.
I won't tell you.
You should eat lunch. I'm hungry. Let's eat lunch.
You got your memory back, but you still eat a lot.
What do you want to eat?
By the way,
why isn't In Sung eating with us?
He said he wants to eat alone.
He's actually more reserved than he looks.
He doesn't look that way.
Please order me one more.
You're a rich guy. It's not like you can't afford food.
My grandma and Mr Kim won't let me have delivery food.
I should eat it when I can.
I'll have one more as well.
I have a good appetite today.
You can eat more, Bok Sil.
You haven't been eating well because of your brother.
I haven't been eating well, either.
Hello? Could you bring two more jjajangmyeon...
to Singsingline, please?
We're ordering extra.
You should ask for some free dumplings. You're so inflexible.
Please give us some free dumplings.
Bok Sil.
Finish work early today.
- Why? Are we doing something?
- Let's eat dinner together.
Stop talking about meals. Bok Sil has a lot of work to do.
She has to work late.
No, my grandma is expecting her.
Ms Choi? Why?
She invited Bok Sil to dinner.
Did she?
Yes.
Give me the USB.
You didn't make a copy, did you?
Of course not.
It's all the cash...
I can spare.
Thank you, Sir.
How will you get out of the country?
I'll stow away in a week.
What? You'll stay for another week?
Leave here as soon as possible.
Go away, so no one can find you.
Don't worry.
Now that I have money,
I'll go into hiding for a week and then disappear.
We are...
total strangers now. Do you understand me?
Of course.
Ms Ko. Let's go.
I will...
buy you dessert outside.
It's fine. I don't need dessert. Give me that.
Why not? I already got 100 bowls of red-bean sherbet.
Hey. Do you want to hurt Bok Sil's teeth?
She can't eat 100 bowls at once.
I promised I'd buy her 100 bowls.
You can buy her one for 100 times.
I see. That's true.
- All right. Let's go, Bok Sil.
- What?
I'll be back tomorrow.
Mr Cha. I'll see you tomorrow.
He'll be back tomorrow?
Goodness. He makes everything so noisy and crowded.
It was a lot nicer when I was alone with Bok Sil.
Bok Sil.
- Is it delicious?
- Yes.
I'll buy you this forever. Eat it slowly.
Forever?
Of course.
Trust me.
I've always trusted you.
Let's finish this and go see Detective.
Okay.
(INVESTIGATION REPORT)
Are you saying you got the car key from Mr Baek, drove the car...
and met a motorcycle gang on the way?
Yes.
And Bok Nam, you took Louis' clothes to protect him from Kim Dae Sik,
- and gave your clothes to Louis.
- Yes.
You waited for Bok Nam believing that he would be back in an hour,
but he didn't. That's why you were wandering around.
Then I tripped,
hit my head against a fire hydrant and lost my memory.
Bok Nam, you gave Louis' car to Dae Sik.
Are you saying you witnessed the car accident?
No. I heard a sound of explosion, so I ran to the accident scene.
The car was already burning then.
You didn't actually see the accident.
I was too scared,
so I just ran away.
I'm so sorry.
I understand.
But it took a long time for Louis to go back to his family.
Apologise to him.
Louis. I'm sorry.
No, no. It's okay.
Don't worry.
Ms Baek.
Hello.
Have you eaten?
If you haven't, would you like to eat with me?
I know a nice restaurant.
Gosh. What's wrong with you?
My goodness.
Oh my gosh.
- Oh, my.
- Don't touch me!
I'm sorry. It wasn't intentional.
- My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
Stop right there!
Mum... Mum.
Mum?
How dare you lay a hand on my son?
Look who it is.
You're the rude girl who gave Louis three dollars.
I knew it.
You hit someone's precious son with your car,
and now you slapped my precious son in the face.
- No.
- It's not that.
Oh my gosh. What are you doing to my daughter?
- Gosh, Mum.
- Yes.
Mum?
Hello, Mother.
- Who are you?
- Why are you calling her "mother"?
Are you her mother?
Yes, I am.
She slapped my precious son's face,
so she must apologise.
- Mum, I'm okay.
- It's not okay!
It's because...
- he touched my buttocks.
- What?
- No, I didn't.
I didn't mean to.
I couldn't help it when I was catching Ma Ri from falling...
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Did you touch my daughter's buttocks?
- Yes.
- He didn't mean to touch her.
- Let him finish his sentence.
- My goodness.
Either way, he touched her!
- Ma Ri, are you okay?
- No.
Just look at you two.
You don't know how to be thankful.
He was only trying to help you,
but you blame him instead.
He saved you from cracking your head open,
but you slapped him instead of thanking him.
How dare you...
accuse my son of sexual harassment?
Shall we start a fight here?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry. You must be very surprised.
She's harsh with her words,
but she doesn't hit people.
What? She hits people?
No, I didn't mean that she does. Goodness.
- I'm so sorry.
- Why are you apologising?
Why?
Who told you to apologise?
- Shall I start with you first?
- What else can I do?
Do you want to see me get destroyed?
What's wrong with you?
Where are you? Please come now.
I'm so scared.
- Audrey!
- We're over here.
Who's giving a hard time to my dear Jae Sook?
You're Bok Sil's mother.
Bok Sil's mother-in-law...
- You're Mr Cha's mother. Hello.
- Hello.
Is this scarf...
from Fancy Styling Talk?
- That's right.
- Fancy what?
They both have the same one.
Did Louis give you that scarf as a present?
Of course he did.
Does that mean...
the coordinator of Fancy Styling Talk is Louis?
My goodness.
No wonder his sense of style was impressive.
Why do you call each other by strange names...
like Audrey and Vivian?
Those are our nicknames.
You should also get a nickname,
so we can hang out.
How about...
Cleopatra?
My son calls me Cleopatra...
because I always lie down like this at home.
That sounds good. What do you think of Cleopatra, Audrey?
It sounds good, Vivian.
- Welcome, Cleopatra.
- Cheers.
- Grandma, we're home.
- Come in.
- Come on in.
- Hello.
Welcome, Bok Sil.
Thank you for inviting me.
Ms Heo, please prepare our meal.
- Mr Kim, bring us welcome drinks.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Let's have a seat.
Have a seat.
Grandma, this is a present from Bok Sil.
Gosh, thank you.
(MR PREGNANT'S PEARS FROM NAJU)
Singsingline signed a contract with a company recently, and these are...
their top-quality pears.
These were grown...
at Mr Pregnant's organic farm in Naju.
- They're excellent in taste.
- I see.
Each pear is so big and strong.
You have such a good taste.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Here you go.
Please excuse me for a moment.
Where's the bathroom?
It's over there.
Mr Kim.
What if they have good news?
I don't think so.
- Bok Sil, are you okay?
- Yes.
I think two bowls of jjajangmyeon and red-bean sherbet were too much.
We shouldn't have had red-bean sherbet.
It's okay. I really enjoyed it.
- Let's go back.
- Okay.
(PREGNANT)
- Grandma.
- Yes?
Can Bok Sil eat next time? She has an upset stomach.
- What?
- What's wrong?
Of course. Let's eat next time.
It's certainly all right.
Let's have a big meal...
with In Sung and his mother next time.
You're the best, Grandma.
Did you know that...
your mum and I visited Bok Sil's house?
What?
Why did you do that without telling me?
You know how your mum is.
She likes to get ahead of herself.
No one can stop her.
We heard about Gold Group's grandson...
at her house.
I heard that the grandson and Bok Sil are very close.
I like Bok Sil a lot.
It's too bad that she's taken.
Shall I tell you something that you don't know?
What is it?
In fact,
I met Bok Sil first.
Before our second meeting,
a stronger candidate appeared and tore us apart.
- Goodness!
- Hello.
- Louis.
- I'll do it, Ms Hwang.
It's okay. I'm almost done. You get some rest.
Ms Hwang.
- Do you have any soda?
- Why do you ask?
Bok Sil has an upset stomach.
What?
How does your stomach feel?
It's because I ate too much all day.
Really?
In Sung, bring us some soda if you have any at home.
Okay.
- Louis, soda isn't a good idea.
- Why not?
It's nothing.
Why, you two...
What?
Bok Nam.
Gosh.
You didn't write a thing. You didn't work at all today, did you?
I'll help you. Look.
To find the maximum value of a cubic function, you need to differentiate.
Do you know what that means?
You don't know how to find a derivative?
You don't know how to find a squared function's maximum value, too?
Bok Nam, you're too ignorant.
How can you say that when you don't know how to spell?
That's not true. My spelling is perfect.
I studied when Bok Sil was gone.
Learning how to spell when you're 25 isn't something to be proud of.
I have an idea. I'll get you the best tutor.
He's been a tutor since I was young. He's amazing.
- It's okay.
- It's not okay.
I told you to trust me.
Even though you got your memory back,
you still tell people to trust you.
Did you get back Bok Sil's money that was stolen?
- You told her to trust you.
- I'll get it back for her, okay?
Why are you nagging me?
How dare you talk to me like that?
How dare you?
- Come here.
- Wait a minute.
Are you getting ready to propose?
Of course.
I'm collecting and analysing information from movies and dramas.
Stop analysing.
You won't get anywhere by analysing dating and marriage.
You're too busy analysing instead of acting on it.
I'm not acting on it?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Come on, it's okay.
You should also date, Mr Kim.
You're his first love.
Mr Louis, please.
Ask me if you have any questions.
I know more than you.
Come on, Mr Louis.
Ms Heo.
I have a favour to ask of you.
Are you saying...
the girls who swear a lot...
took Bok Sil's money twice,
looked down on you...
and ignored your calls?
They're no ordinary girls.
I can't believe this crazy girl.
If you bother us one more time, we will kill you, Punk.
You may not be able to handle them.
Jung Ran. Are you going to be okay?
I'm Heo Jung Ran, Busan Double Axe.
You have their phone number, right?
Hey, do me a favour.
It's nothing big. Can you track a phone number?
Boss. It's that way.
What are you...
Get your drinks up.
Now put your hands up.
Put, put, put put your hands up.
- What is this?
- Who are you?
Who are you?
Shall we have a little talk?
You brats.
Who are you anyway?
Me?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Gosh, darn it.
My eyes are burning.
You cannot use slang or swear words in this house.
Don't be ridiculous. What are you saying?
Whenever they swear, give them another 10kg of garlic.
It's me. The penniless guy who lost his memory.
I lost my memory.
Guys, I don't even have a penny.
I won't get beaten up, then.
He's really penniless.
- Give me money.
- Who is this punk?
Give me money. Give me money.
You took Bok Sil's money. Keep doing it until you can pay her back.
It's 30 dollars per 20kg.
If each of you peel 20kg, you'll get 90 dollars per day.
You took 1,000 dollars, then another 180. It's 1,180 dollars in total.
Peel it for 13 days. I'll knock down 10 dollars.
Did your memory return?
I can't believe this.
Is he really rich?
What a sick coincidence.
She swore.
- Give her another 10kg.
- Okay.
Another 10kg for Hyun So Ri.
Keep it up. I became mature after peeling it.
- Give them nice meals.
- Yes, Mr Louis.
Good luck.
He's so wickedly cool.
Another 10kg for Song Yeon Ah.
30 dollars for Song Yeon Ah.
30 dollars for Choi Hyun Jung.
30 dollars for Hyun So Ri.
So Ri.
Good job.
Hyun Jung. Good job.
Yeon Ah. Good job.
Big news, big news.
I have big news.
Bok Sil became a president of a company.
- What?
- Search for Singsingline.
Singsingline.
Bok Sil is the president.
Oh, my. It's a website for direct dealing of farm products.
They distribute farm products named after the grower.
When did she found this company?
Do you know what the bigger news is?
- What is it?
- The director of her company...
is Mr Cha.
- What?
That can't be true.
Why did he quit our company and start working there?
Mr Lee. What do you think?
Why else?
He must've followed Bok Sil.
- Gosh.
- Please stop talking nonsense...
and go back to work.
Looking at the question won't give you an answer.
Okay.
I think you should start from factorisation.
You know what factorisation is, right?
I've heard of it.
That's good to hear.
You've heard of it at least.
I'll get a new textbook tomorrow.
That's all for today.
Okay.
I thought Bok Sil looked familiar when I first met her.
But your face looks even more familiar.
Have we met before?
No.
Goodbye.
I'm sure I saw him somewhere.
These products look good.
Is it the right amount?
Yes.
Bok Sil.
You're here.
Hey. Stop coming here.
Why do you keep showing up?
I'm here for business today.
What business?
Please have a seat, Ms Ko.
You too, Mr Daddy Long Legs.
Why don't you...
make a contract with Goldline?
What?
It's not because of you.
It's not.
I'm suggesting this because Goldline is having a renewal,
and we need a company that directly delivers vegetables from the farm.
We'll have branch lines, and each line will be managed separately.
Also, the merchandiser's notes will be opened to the public.
You can keep your company's concept as usual.
Why aren't you saying anything?
We'll think about it.
Gosh. Bok Sil.
Are you turning down my offer?
Singsingline is invested by Mr Cha,
and managed by me.
We're now settling down and getting popular.
It's hard to decide whether working with Goldline is a good idea or not.
As an investor, let me ask you a few questions.
What are the terms of the contract?
You'll have to use Goldline's delivery service.
As for the profit, we'll get 20 percent.
It's not bad.
If we work under Goldline,
there will be additional distribution process.
That means we'll have to raise the price of the goods.
But if your products are promoted on Goldline's website,
the suppliers may earn bigger profits.
Bok Sil.
I think...
Louis' offer sounds good.
Why don't we work with Goldline?
Only if...
the price of the goods stays the same,
so the consumers won't bear the cost.
Then...
we have a deal.
Yes.
Bok Sil.
Stop. That's enough.
You should work with us, too.
Forget it.
I'm on sabbatical this year.
If you're going to support Bok Sil,
I'll rest at home.
Why? You can rest at Goldline.
How can I rest at a company?
Do you think I can do that?
I'll give you my room.
It's the biggest room in Goldline.
It has blinds, so you can sleep whenever you want.
Everything in the office pantry is free, of course.
My place is 190m and it has 3 rooms.
I'll give you the room...
that also has a bathroom in it.
Everything in the fridge is free, of course.
Are you making fun of me?
What are you doing? Let go of me.
I'm hugging you because I like you.
If I say your presence makes me relaxed,
would you believe me?
Gosh, go away.
I'm just saying.
Look at it.
Hello, everyone.
- Mr Louis!
- Hello.
- Hello, Mr Louis.
Hello, Mr Louis.
I thought you were going to stay in Paris for a while.
You must be surprised to see me again so soon.
No, I'm so happy to see you.
Don't do that.
Thank you so much for the warm welcome.
Let's work hard together and have fun.
- Okay!
- It's so exciting!
- Go, team!
I shall introduce new team members to you.
There they are.
Cha Joong Won and...
These two will manage our branch, Singsingline.
Please meet the CEO, Ms Ko, and the director, Mr Cha.
I look forward to working with you all.
You fools. How have you been?
- Good!
This meeting room will be Singsingline's office.
Mr Cha, you can use your old office.
- What?
- What about you, Mr Louis?
Well, I will be... Okay. It's here.
Hello. You can put it down here.
I'll just sit here.
- Is he a security guard or what?
- I see.
- Does he think he's a secretary?
- He's a romanticist.
Shall we have a quick meeting now?
Sure.
Goodness. He's certainly not all there.
Bok Nam.
Are you not familiar with the multiplication table?
I am, of course.
Bok Nam is studying and sitting in that comfortable chair.
- What are we doing right now?
- Shut it.
- I much prefer peeling garlic.
- I agree.
- Peel all of mine, then.
- No, I don't want to.
- You peel all of these.
- No.
- Take everything.
- You peel them all.
Work hard! You little...
- Oh, my. This house is beautiful.
- Bok Sil!
- It's decorated so tastefully.
- Don't embarrass me, Mum.
- Thanks for coming, Ms Hwang.
- Hello, Ms Choi.
Thank you for inviting us.
I should've invited you sooner.
I apologise.
Is the job hard?
Do you girls need a hand?
- Yes.
I'll sing for you so that you can work harder.
- What did he just say?
- Is he teasing us?
Is he the grasshopper in the fable?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
In this moment.
At this place.
The moment I desperately wanted.
And hoped for.
My dreams.
My wishes.
They may come true.
Right here today.
In this moment.
At this place.
Words can't describe how I'm feeling.
Right in this moment.
The moments I've endured.
And the difficult times I've been through.
Are dissipating in front of my eyes.
They're disappearing like a cloud of smoke.
In this moment.
Like magic
I throw away the chains.
That held me down.
The only thing
I have now is certainty.
The only thing.
That remains is victory.
In this moment
I'm on my own path.
Even if you abandon me.
And curse me
I won't give up.
The dream deep within my heart.
It's my earnest prayer.
My ardent prayer.
This house has gotten noisy since Louis came back.
I won't let anyone in if it bothers you.
No, I like it because it feels lively.
My whole life, I've lived in this huge mansion alone.
I don't know why I lived like that.
I even sent...
my treasure, Ji Sung, to that faraway land.
I don't think my Louis...
will make the mistakes that I've made.
Losing his memory...
taught him how to live well with people.
I agree.
By the way, did you look into what I asked you to find out?
Yes.
I don't think we can expect Mr Louis Junior.
Really?
That's so odd. It was certainly a conception dream.
I guess I was wrong.
By the way,
what's going on with Louis' treasure box?
Mr Louis finally remembered where it is.
Really? Where is it?
He said it's at the house in Busan.
I'll go to Busan right away.
- Yes, hurry up. Go now.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Jung Ran.
What is it? What's the matter?
Are you pregnant by any chance?
Be quiet! My goodness.
We just got back from Busan. How can you say such a thing?
Well, Ms Choi told me about her dream.
Her dreams usually come true, you know.
Be quiet. Shut it already.
Get out!
By the way, can Bok Nam really stay at your grandmother's place?
- I don't want to inconvenience her.
- Don't worry.
I told you numerous times that I'll take care of him.
Also, Mr Kim told me...
that Bok Nam's grades will barely improve...
even if they lock him up there...
and make him study all the time.
What? Is he that bad?
- Yes.
- Gosh, what should I do?
- You must be cold.
- No, I'm all right.
- No, I'm sure you're cold.
- What?
Who made food for us?
I asked In Sung. I told him that I want a night snack.
Are you going to eat again?
As you know, I'm always hungry.
Open it.
What kind of dish is it?
It doesn't look real on that little table, right?
But it's real.
The white gold double band model with diamond from Bulgari.
It's obviously fake.
- Can you afford this?
- How much is it?
It's 30 dollars.
I can't give you a fake ring.
This is how I really feel about you.
To be honest,
I would have bought that ring if I had 30 dollars.
Thanks, Louis.
Just a second, Louis.
Isn't it hot in here?
I know that it'll be summer soon, but it's already so hot.
Shall we step out for coffee?
Shall we?
Let's stay in. I'll make coffee.
What has gotten into you?
I don't want you to get water on your hand as you have the ring on.
Just a moment.
Louis.
How did you know that it was there?
I moved it there when you were gone.
I actually...
came here every day.
I cleaned the room...
and had coffee every day.
I put pennies into your piggy bank, too.
Why does it feel like it's getting heavier day by day?
Oh, my. Bok Sil will be here soon.
And I left...
before you got home.
From when you get on the bus to go to work...
to the moment your light goes off...
Sweet dreams, Bok Sil.
I've been watching you every single day.
I'm sorry that I've been watching you secretly.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Thanks, Louis.
Let's never be apart again.
I remembered. I remembered where I left my treasure box.
Where is it?
In the attic at the house in Busan.
I looked through that attic so many times.
It's under the floor.
Ms Choi, the treasure box is gone.
I think Mr Louis was mistaken.
Really? Okay.
Where on earth did you hide it, Ji Sung?
Louis.
Do you remember this?
Of course, I do.
- May I eat one?
- Of course!
Ji Sung!
- Ta-da.
- Ms Hong...
My little prince. Who made you cry?
Here. Try this.
Your grandma and Mr Kim will scold me if they see this. Hurry up.
Oh, my. It's chocolate.
It's delicious.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- Eat slowly, okay?
- Okay.
Ms Hong.
Did you give sweets to Mr Louis again?
No, I didn't.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
It tastes just like how I remember it from my childhood.
You don't have to hide it any more.
Your grandma and Mr Kim were too protective of you, don't you think?
Yes.
Ever since you came back,
Mother has been looking happier than ever before,
and things feel so much more lively at home. It's awesome.
I'm really happy, too.
Visit my bookstore often from now on.
Okay, I will.
Hello!
Are you looking for anything specific, Sir?
We spoke on the phone the other day. I'm Mr Goo.
I see. You work with my husband.
Mr Goo?
Hello? Who's there?
This is Mr Goo.
Mr Goo?
(SHOPAHOLIC LOUIS)
In this moment.
Like magic
I made a mistake.
I won't give up.
The dream deep within my heart.
It's my earnest prayer.
My ardent prayer.
May my prayer be answered