Goodness.
There's a separate office for the director, and the office is so big.
Does he really have to sit here of all places?
The new director is Bok Sil's boyfriend.
Mr Cha works for Singsingline. Maybe that's why.
I told you. Mr Cha likes Bok Sil, too.
- Gosh.
- No way.
Should I like Bok Sil, too?
Are you going to start to like Bok Sil...
just because Mr Cha likes her?
I think he will.
If what Mr Lee said is true, Bok Sil must be so happy.
She's loved by these two gorgeous men.
Who should she pick?
- Mr Cha is more manly and reliable.
- That's not true.
She has to choose Mr Louis.
He's the successor of Gold Group, handsome and kind. He's perfect.
Isn't he, Ms Baek?
Stop talking nonsense,
and go back to work. Now!
- Hello, Mr Cha.
Hello, Sir.
(Director Kang Ji Sung)
It's annoying.
The winner takes it all.
(Episode 14: The Winner Takes It All)
- You didn't make a copy, did you?
- Of course not.
It's all the cash...
I can spare.
Thank you, Sir.
How will you get out of the country?
I'll stow away in a week.
Do we need to leave now? That's not what we agreed.
All right. I'll see you there in two hours.
Help me.
Ma'am. Are you okay?
Please get me a bottle of water. Hurry up.
I wonder what is in his bag.
Here you go.
Gosh.
Thank you.
Goodness. If it wasn't for you,
I would be dead by now.
Oh my gosh.
You have gum stuck in your hair.
- Gum?
- Yes, it's gum.
What is this? Gosh.
Ma'am!
Ma'am! No.
I can't believe her.
This darn gum.
Goodness.
Oh, my.
Is this all money?
Hello!
Are you looking for anything specific, Sir?
We spoke on the phone the other day. I'm Mr Goo.
Mr Goo?
I see. You work with my husband.
You said you work with my husband, right?
Well, yes.
Please come in.
Please have a seat. I'll go and get some tea.
Mr Kim.
What is it, Mr Louis?
- Slow down. You might get hurt.
- I remembered.
- Remembered what?
- My treasure box.
- I remembered where I left it.
- Really?
Treasure box?
- Where is it?
- The attic of the house in Busan.
I looked through that attic so many times.
It's under the floor.
I wonder what is in that box.
What are these?
(Koboshi)
"Koboshi"?
(March 15, 1996 Mum, Dad and Ji Sung)
They're nothing important.
Why would he...
Hello?
Honey, Mr Goo came to my bookstore.
What?
Okay. I'll be right there.
He will be here soon. Please wait.
By the way,
why did you come here instead of...
calling him yourself?
Someone stole my bag.
My phone was in there.
I came to your bookstore once with Mr Baek.
Goodness.
Who stole your bag?
The same thing happened to Bok Sil when she first came to Seoul.
Really?
Goodness. There're so many bad guys in the world.
Excuse me, Mr Goo.
Have you called Ms Choi's house before?
No. Of course not.
That's right, Louis. Take a look at this.
I bought this at a boutique that I often go. What do you think?
Would this look good on Ma Ri?
It has a pretty pattern.
What kind of pants will she wear?
What do you recommend, Mr Fancy Styling Talk?
You're embarrassing me.
- A pair of slim fit jeans would do.
- Okay.
She's been so busy picking out clothes...
for the company retreat.
She's making a big fuss about it.
Sometimes I think Ma Ri takes after you,
but you two are very different.
She's my daughter, but also Seon Goo's daughter.
- It would look great on Ma Ri.
- Wouldn't it?
- Hey, you...
- Honey, you're here.
Hello.
Hello. You are here too, Ji Sung.
- Let's talk outside.
- Seon Goo.
Why are you being so rude to your friend's brother?
My friend's brother?
Thank you for the tea.
Sure.
Mr Goo. Please come again any time.
Did he tell you anything?
Tell me what?
Nothing. See you next time, then.
Mr Baek.
I think that friend of yours...
called my house before.
What?
No way. That's absurd.
That can't be true.
Excuse me.
Seon Goo.
Are you insane?
You should be gone by now. Why are you still here?
What are you plotting?
Someone stole my money.
What?
Dad.
When did he leave?
(March 15, 1996 Mum, Dad and Ji Sung)
What are these? Are these Ji Sung's?
What's on this tape?
What happened?
Is it broken?
What's wrong with this?
Give you more money?
You lost the money by mistake. Why should I give you more?
What else can I do? I can't flee Korea without money.
You moron!
If you get me the money again, I'll disappear without a trace.
Just get me the money.
Do you think one million dollars is easy to get?
Where did Seon Goo go?
I'm sorry for leaving without seeing him again.
You see each other often anyway. Take care of yourself.
You, too.
Goodbye, Audrey.
Bye.
- May I take a look at this?
- Certainly.
- Are you looking for a men's ring?
- Yes.
Bok Sil.
Hello. I'm ready to go.
Where shall we go?
Let's go to the warmest and the best place in the world.
Where's that?
Bok Sil's world.
- Are we going to stay here?
- Yes.
I missed our time we spent here together.
I'll hang out with you here all day today.
What shall we do?
They should arrive any minute now.
- Here's your delivery.
- There it is.
Hello.
- Thank you.
- Here's your delivery.
- Please come in.
- Hello.
Thank you.
- Here's your delivery.
- Please come in.
Thank you.
Perfect. Perfect.
Perfect? Perfect.
Something seems quite familiar right now.
This isn't all.
- Ta-da.
- Isn't this...
Perfect.
This bag was made just for you. It's furry like you.
- It's too expensive.
- Come on.
I bought it with the money I worked hard for.
You can't say no.
Don't make me return it. Just accept it, please?
Okay, thank you.
However, you must return expensive things like this from now on,
- so don't ever buy it again, okay?
- Okay.
Go clean, you brat. Hurry up.
Are you hungry? Do you want some ramyeon?
No, don't do a thing. I'll make you something delicious.
- Really?
- Trust me.
Bok Sil.
Yes? Wipe off your hands.
Gosh, that's hot.
Did you get hurt?
Goodness, Bok Sil.
Why am I so tired when you were the one who cooked?
Maybe it's because you're hungry.
Let's eat. Then you'll get your energy back.
Here you go.
- How does it taste?
- It's the best.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I should cook more for you.
- It's okay.
Come on. Have some more.
- Okay.
- Have some more.
Okay.
Now I understand why my grandma said...
she feels satisfied just by watching me eat.
I don't need to eat any.
Why aren't you swallowing?
Bok Nam.
Didn't you say you're familiar with the multiplication?
What's 9 times 9?
An ice cream cone.
Mr Kim, what's wrong with your face?
Did something happen?
I feel like I'm aging too fast.
Every hour I teach Bok Nam,
I feel like I'm aging one year.
What did you say?
Gosh, I can't let this continue.
Give me your hands.
- Thank you for cooking.
- You're welcome.
Ta-da. I don't want your hands...
to get dry.
Pay me 50 cents, too.
Okay.
Hold on.
It smells good.
Hello, Ms Heo.
Really?
I'm sorry. I'll be right there.
Okay.
- What happened?
- It's about my silly brother.
- My brother-in-law?
- Yes, let's go.
Stay here.
I'll give you the money tomorrow, so stay here until then, okay?
But your wife will be here.
I'll tell her not to come tomorrow.
Don't you dare call my house or do anything else suspicious.
- You'll be doomed.
- Don't worry.
Honey? Ma Ri?
Isn't anyone home yet?
It's the weekend.
It'd be nice if the family gets together...
and have dinner.
Why is that here?
Oh, my.
She did this again.
She always makes a mess, and covers it up with something.
I don't know why she does this.
Is this broken?
Bok Sil. Studying is so hard.
Do I have to do it?
You're a student. What else are you going to do?
- Should I quit being a student?
- Hey.
How can you be so immature after all that?
What's wrong with it? You didn't go to a university, but you're fine.
You little...
Look at you, Slow Toad.
Are you running away again?
Bok Nam.
Don't you know how much trouble your sister had to go through?
Please give him a good scolding.
I heard everything from outside.
Listen to me, Bok Nam. You have two choices.
You can either live like my son, or live like Louis.
Which one do you want?
- I want to live like Louis.
- That's right.
It's not his family that made Louis a director.
Do you know how hard he studied in France?
He went to one of the greatest universities in Europe,
and he speaks 10 languages.
I'll just live like In Sung, then.
- I'll be Louis' chauffeur, too.
- Hey!
I've been trying to be nice, but you don't seem to get it.
I'm saying you should study!
Bok Sil. He's nothing like you.
I'm sorry, Ms Hwang.
I'm going to the company retreat tomorrow. Please take care of him.
Don't worry. I'll turn him into a decent person by then.
- Bok Sil.
- What?
You'd better brace yourself.
- Give me the backscratcher.
- Okay.
You're dead.
Now, open your book.
Are you sure that's where you left your treasure box?
Yes. I put it under the floor.
Why isn't it there, then?
Don't think about it too hard. You'll get wrinkles.
Who do you think got me these wrinkles?
You're blaming me again. Gosh.
After the company retreat, I'll go to Busan and look for it with you.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, Mr Louis.
It's late. You should go to sleep.
Good night.
Good night, Bok Sil.
I want to be with the real Bok Sil.
Do I have to marry her for that?
Bok Sil.
Why are you still up?
Should we...
get married?
If we get married, we can be together every day.
- Do you like me that much?
- Of course.
He didn't hesitate at all.
You like me too, right?
I'll answer that if you win the singing contest tomorrow.
Gosh.
I'll give you a present, too.
Really?
What is the present?
It's a secret.
Don't be surprised.
I can't wait.
Go to sleep or you'll be late tomorrow.
Bok Sil. Give me a kiss.
Hurry.
Why isn't she answering?
(Louis)
What now? I just gave you a kiss.
You didn't.
Bok Sil. Did you give your phone a kiss?
Just go to sleep. Bye.
Gosh. She just hangs up on me now.
She shouldn't treat me like this.
This is how you give me a kiss.
Oh, my. It's nice.
Gosh, this is good. I wish Jung Ran was here.
We will now begin the company retreat...
to celebrate the merger between Goldline and Singsingline.
Mr Cha. I told you I would be someone who wears number one.
I feel like I used to wear number one.
That's right. King of Shopping, Louis bought number one.
You're so cool, Mr Louis.
Mr Cha. When did you buy this?
You were in the office with us then.
That's right. I never miss anything.
I have my ways.
Mr Kim. You're hovering again.
- Ms Choi told me to.
- Who is that man?
He's close to Louis.
I think he got invited because he recently helped Louis a lot.
I see.
How do you know all the important information?
Are you a daughter of one of the executives?
Well, please think as you like.
First of all, we should split into two teams.
- Take one.
- Yes!
Who's in the First Place Team?
- Me!
- Me, too. I'm with Ma Ri.
Who's in the Perfect Score Team?
- Yes!
- Me!
If you lose, you'll wash the dishes.
The first game is...
- One, two.
- Get in there.
- Ma Ri. One, two.
- Gosh.
- Go, Ma Ri.
- What is this?
- Bok Sil.
- Gosh.
Now!
- Now!
- Get in.
One, two.
Bok Sil, get in.
- No.
- She's good.
Go, Bok Sil!
- Let's go!
- Trip!
- Oh, my.
- One, two.
- Stop.
- Hurry up and get in.
No.
Louis' team won.
This is crazy. What's wrong with this rope?
- Let's go, Bok Sil!
- You can do it, Ma Ri!
Ready, go.
Go, Ma Ri...
- Bok Sil won.
- She won!
Ready, go.
- Go, Mi Young!
- Go, Hae Joo!
- Go, Ms Big News!
- Big news!
- Ouch.
- Ready and go!
Jung Ran!
- Let's go.
- Ready, go.
- Go, Louis!
- Go, Joong Won!
You can do it!
The third game is...
Let's go, Bok Sil.
I'll win this time.
- Gosh.
- That's right.
- We won!
- Yes!
- He will do great.
- Really?
Yes. He can do anything.
Have you even played jegichagi before?
You'll find out.
- Good luck. You have to win.
- We believe in you!
Go, Joong Won! You got this!
- Yes!
- He has the legs for this.
You can do it!
Great. That's it.
- Oh, my!
- That's it.
Louis takes a win.
- Oh, my! That's awesome.
- You guys will wash the dishes.
Well...
He's all talk.
Mr Cha.
- Gosh.
- Let's celebrate.
- Our team is the best.
- Good job.
It's okay.
Are you kidding?
- I don't want to wash dishes!
- Hey.
You lied about living in France, didn't you?
If my business fails, I should do something related to jegichagi.
- Bok Sil, aren't I so good?
- Yes.
Louis, how can you be so good when you haven't done it before?
- You are born to play it.
- I guess I do.
- I'm amazed.
- Me, too.
I'll be right back.
What is this now? Did she call the police?
Is she off today?
(Gift Certificate)
I wanted to buy a book, but I picked the wrong day.
Mr Goo, Mr Goo.
Mr Goo.
Where did he go?
This punk. He told me to bring money.
Is he scheming something or what?
- I love your personality.
- Thank you.
- You look like a good driver, too.
- I'm amazing.
- Everyone.
- Yes.
Here's to Goldline and Singsingline.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- I'm so happy to meet you all.
- Thank you.
- This is so delicious.
- Really?
- Ma Ri, do you need anything?
- No, I'm okay.
- You'll need this.
- Can you pass me...
- No, it's okay.
- All right.
- Bok Sil, spare me a second.
- What's up? I'm busy.
Come on.
Do you need me by any chance?
- You sound so excited.
- Yes, I am.
Have a seat.
Bok Sil.
What is this?
What do you think?
I grilled them for you. Eat up.
Only you can eat the meat grilled by me.
Only I can eat the food Bok Sil makes.
I'm honoured.
Eat up. Here.
How is it? Is it good?
Yes.
You should try one, too.
It's delicious.
This is the first team retreat I've ever been to.
Me, too.
- Isn't it so fun?
- Yes.
Do I find it fun because I'm with you?
It's fun because everyone is here.
Right. Yes, you're right.
- Shall we eat quickly and go back?
- Yes.
Here.
- It's delicious.
- I know.
- Wasn't it so good?
- Yes.
- I don't think we have enough meat.
- My gosh.
- We already finished all the meat?
- Yes.
- Give it to me.
- I'll go buy more meat.
There's no need. Someone will show up with meat.
He should be here by now. What's taking him so long?
I'll give you a hand.
He must be a model. Look at that model!
Is he an athlete?
Model? Whatever. He's a detective.
Just a police detective.
He played a key role in Mr Louis's return to Gold Group.
Hello, everyone. I'm really late, aren't I?
- Detective!
- Detective.
- Hey, Louis and Bok Sil.
- He invited everyone he knows.
- He's certainly not all there.
- You didn't have to bring anything.
- Hey, help him.
- Okay.
Let me introduce him to you. This is Nam Joon Hyuk.
- Hello.
Hello, everyone. It's nice to meet you.
Detective, please have a seat here.
May I? Thank you.
Let's have a seat, everyone.
- Okay.
- Please help yourself.
- Thank you.
No, I should be thanking you.
Since you're already here, you should join us for the event.
If I may, I'd love to.
What's the next event?
The highlight of our team retreat!
Ladies and gentlemen. The mysterious music show,
"King of Mask Singer" begins now.
We're about to watch five masked singers'...
fierce battle for the throne.
Let me introduce the first contestant.
Just his name is enough to scare his opponents.
CBR Gas Weapon!
I'm sorry, Ma Ri.
- Bruce Lee will sing...
- "Good Person"!
- You, too.
- No, not me.
He looks like the cartoon character.
I'm not sure who that is, but it could be Do Jin.
I know for a fact that it's not Mr Cha.
Oh, my! He almost got a perfect score.
Let's meet the second contestant now.
He has conquered the world with his voice.
The Man Who Knows How to Have Fun will sing...
"Nest".
The next contestant's sweet voice will melt all the ladies' hearts.
Please give it up for Romantic Knight.
"The Way to Me".
Let's meet the fourth contestant.
He's here to make the throne his.
Give it up for Singing Mickey.
"Honey"!
The last contestant...
is Music Commander in Your Town!
- Gosh, how lovely.
- Indeed.
It's the perfect love confession song.
I'd do anything to hear a love confession like that.
I think it's Louis.
Gosh, that startled me.
- He got the perfect score!
- Oh, my!
Music Commander in Your Town beat...
Bruce Lee in CBR Room by one point.
It makes him the King of Mask Singer!
First, let's reveal the identity of the singer who sang "Nest".
The Man Who Knows How to Have Fun...
is Mr Louis' forever soul mate.
It's Mr Kim!
- My gosh.
- He came to drop off the meat...
but ended up on this stage.
Please give it up for Detective Nam Joon Hyuk!
- You're so handsome!
- The copycat,
- our cute Do Jin!
- My goodness.
The charismatic boss,
Mr Cha Joong Won!
The new mascot of Goldline.
My dream, my hope and my money source.
Mr Louis!
Yes!
- You were awesome!
- Please say a few words.
Thank you, everyone. What a beautiful night!
- Yes!
- Congratulations!
You were so good.
I had no idea that it was you.
Bok Sil, did you know that it was me?
Of course. I can definitely recognise you even with the mask.
Congratulations on becoming the King of Mask Singer. You were so cool.
Really?
Then can I expect your answer and the gift?
Be patient, please.
Mr Cha!
You were cool, too.
(Goldline's King of Mask Singer)
What's the matter with him?
Is he upset because I beat him?
Hey! Let me see.
- It's red.
- It hurts.
- Show me the coin.
- No!
- Come on.
- I'm embarrassed.
Gosh, I'm so embarrassed.
- One, two.
- No, no!
Yes. Good. That's it.
- That's it.
- Louis' team won.
- No!
The winner takes it all
Goodness.
Mr Cha.
I'll help you.
It's fine. I said I'll take responsibility as the team leader.
Go and get some rest.
We're on the same team, and we work together.
- I can't let you do it alone.
- Gosh, I said it's fine!
(Incoming Call: Mother)
Hello?
I stopped by your place, but you're not here.
Are you working late today?
I'm at a team retreat. I'll be home tomorrow.
Really?
I need you to see this and pick one now.
Pick what?
Three young ladies want to meet you.
All of them look elegant and pretty.
I told you that I don't want to go on blind dates.
I'll move if you're going to keep doing this!
I was going to stop, too.
But you said Jang Geum is seeing the chairwoman's grandson, Louis.
How can I not set you up with girls?
Let's talk another time. I have to go.
Wait, Joong Won!
He didn't even listen to me and hung up on me.
Well, he'll see this if I leave it here.
What are you doing? You said you're going to help me.
Oh, right. Yes.
She didn't really mean anything,
so don't take it seriously.
Okay.
Well,
that's a pretty ring.
Thank you.
It looks expensive.
I guess Louis proposed to you?
No, that's not it.
He got it because he promised to buy it for me a while ago.
Louis, that fellow.
He fulfills his promises better than I expected.
Wear these.
It's too pretty to get soaked like that.
I can take it off briefly. You wear them.
Just wear them. That's why I gave them to you.
I've been taught to always respect my elders. You wear them.
I'll rinse these.
Are you saying I'm old?
You wear them!
You should've just listened to me.
Don't come. Don't come.
Welcome.
So the three of us will use the same room, right?
Yes.
- Mr Kim, do you snore?
- I grind my teeth.
Ma Ri, you're next!
Ma Ri, be careful and walk gently.
Is this a minefield? Why are you telling me to walk gently?
I'm obviously choosing Number One.
What? Will I be sharing the room with Bok Sil?
I can't sleep when there's someone else in the room.
Don't worry. Bok Sil sleeps quietly.
- Oh my goodness.
- It's your turn.
Mr Louis' hands and feet get cold,
so he can't sleep in a tent. I'm worried.
No, don't worry. I'm a lucky guy, you know.
I've never been unlucky with games like this.
I'll choose Number Four.
You're a lucky guy, so you won't catch a cold.
I'm next.
There's one tent left.
I'll choose Number Nine.
Good luck!
- Ms Kwon, let's chat all night.
- That sounds great.
Mr Cha, please come to Room Number Four. Best of luck!
Then I will...
choose Number Two.
Here I go.
Mr Cha, nothing is going your way today.
That means Do Jin and I will be using the same room, right?
This is not right.
Let's do it again!
- Oh, boy.
- Do you actually grind your teeth?
Gosh, stop it. You're just going to end up looking pathetic.
Who drew this? This ladder isn't drawn properly.
Let's do it again. We must do it again!
Enough.
That's enough.
We have to do it again.
We must do it again.
Darn it.
What's with us? Why are we stuck together from the start to the end?
This is what we are.
Gosh. You irk me, you leech.
Don't cling to me so that I can hate you all I want.
Let's go.
Dear me.
This feels nice.
I've never slept in a tent before.
If things were like before, Mr Kim wouldn't have let me sleep here.
I'm not surprised.
It's cold. I'm cold.
I feel colder!
I have to sleep in an unfamiliar environment...
with someone glued to my back.
I won't be able to get any sleep tonight. Darn it.
I'm not surprised.
Mr Cha?
Gosh.
(Louis)
Are you sleeping?
Of course not.
Bok Sil, can't you fall asleep because you miss me?
Goodness.
(Bok Sil, can't you fall asleep because you miss me?)
- Of course not.
- Gosh.
(Of course not.)
(Gosh)
Shall we meet?
(Shall we meet?)
Why? To give me a present?
Where shall we meet?
(Why? To give me a present? Where shall we meet?)
- How about the bench by the tree?
- I'll come pick you up.
It's okay. I can get there alone.
See you in 10 minutes.
Where are you going?
Weren't you asleep?
I can't sleep unless it's my bed.
I'm sensitive.
I see.
I'm going outside for a minute.
Hang on.
Are you going to see Louis?
I have something to give him.
Is it necessary when you see him every day?
Gosh, that's right.
Don't put on a wet jacket. It's too cold outside.
I think it's better than not putting anything on.
- Why don't you wear mine then?
- What?
- Is it okay...
- Just wear it.
It's annoying to imagine Louis taking off his jacket...
for you.
Thank you.
Why isn't she here yet?
I can't wait any longer.
(Turn Off)
Bok Sil.
Is this my present?
Are you hiding to surprise me?
Is this a surprise?
Bok Sil.
Bok Sil!
(Ko Bok Sil)
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message...
- Hello?
- It's me.
Where are you? I told you to stay put at the bookstore.
Is that why you called the police?
What do you mean by that?
I'm not a fool.
I won't go down alone.
Mr Goo, where are you?
Let's talk in person.
I have your daughter.
What?
Bring the money to the clock tower in Gold Square by noon tomorrow.
I'll tell you where your daughter is when I get the money.
If you call the police, I can't guarantee...
your daughter's life.
Hello? Hello?
Bok Sil!
Bok Sil.
(Shopaholic Louis)
Have you seen Bok Sil? I was supposed to meet her,
- but I can't get a hold of her.
- What's going on?
Bok Sil is missing.
Bok Sil!
- Why was Bok Sil kidnapped?
- You're the heir of Goldline.
She got kidnapped because of me?
Stay alert. You're the only guardian of Bok Sil, do you understand?
The reason why I shouldn't come back to life.
The reason why I shouldn't get my memory back.
You must express how you truly feel.
If you lose the chance, you may lose it forever.
I'll find Bok Sil no matter what.