Come and sit down.
You'll be my assistant from today.
How can I serve the chairwoman of Gold Group?
Forget it.
Do you have any places to go?
Jung Ran.
I pick out good things, and I pick out good people.
However your life has been so far...
and how much educated you are, it doesn't matter.
You risk your own life to help out...
a total stranger.
That makes you...
a valuable person.
- Jung Ran.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Thank you for taking care of me so diligently...
up until today.
I've always relied on you.
Isn't it too early a day to embarrass me like that?
If you have something...
you want to say, you should say it while you can.
You may lose your chance to say it forever.
You sound like someone going away.
I'll go prepare your breakfast.
Okay.
Grandma has her own way of living her life.
And I love her...
and her way of life.
(EPISODE 15, MY GLORIOUS LIFE)
I'm her precious grandson.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Bok Sil!
Bok Sil.
(BOK SIL)
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message...
Bok Sil.
Where did he go?
Did he go in the room alone to sleep?
That brat.
Hey.
Where have you been?
- Have you seen Bok Sil?
- No.
That's strange.
I was supposed to meet her, but I can't get a hold of her.
There was only a ring on the ground.
Calm down. Let's check the room first.
She might be back in the room.
Okay.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
My goodness.
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
- Is Bok Sil inside?
- What?
Oh, my.
Did she say anything?
She went out to meet Louis.
Weren't you with her?
Please wake everyone up and let them know what's going on.
We'll look for her outside.
What's going on?
Bok Sil is missing.
What?
Gosh.
Oh my goodness.
- Bok Sil.
- Bok Sil!
Bok Sil.
- Did you find her?
- No.
Her phone is turned off,
and she dropped the ring on the ground.
I don't think she's simply missing.
What do you mean?
We must check first.
I'll go to the security office.
Please keep on searching.
Let me go with you.
Please continue searching for her.
Please call me as soon as you find anything.
- Call us if you find anything.
- Okay.
Let me go with you.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let me go with you, too.
- In Sung.
- Yes?
- Let's search this area together.
- But I...
I have your daughter.
- What?
- Bring the money...
to the clock tower in Gold Square by noon tomorrow.
I'll tell you where your daughter is when I get the money.
If you call the police,
I can't guarantee your daughter's life.
Hello? Hello?
What?
Dad.
Ma Ri!
Are you okay?
- Where are you?
- I'm at the company retreat.
Oh, that's right.
Are you really okay?
Unless you have something to say,
I have to go because Bok Sil is suddenly missing.
Is this the place?
What? Bok Sil is missing?
No way.
Did he kidnap Bok Sil instead of Ma Ri?
He doesn't do anything right.
Why did he kidnap Bok Sil? My goodness.
Wait.
He said if I give him the money, he'll tell me where she is.
All I need to do is give money and get Bok Sil back.
That's right.
Stop.
Can you zoom in?
Is this it?
Nothing is certain yet. The face isn't clear.
Can you make it clearer?
No, this is the clearest.
That's Bok Sil.
I lent her that coat.
I'm sure of it.
Bok Sil.
He seems quite familiar.
Has anyone seen that man before?
I can't recognise him because of the mask.
I've never seen him.
Why did he kidnap Bok Sil?
No one is against her and she has no money, either.
You have a lot of money.
You're the heir of Goldline.
What?
Are you saying that she's kidnapped because of me?
- Well...
- Because of me?
Is it because of me?
Stay alert, Louis.
You should stay calm at a time like this.
You're the only guardian of Bok Sil. Do you understand?
I'll find Bok Sil no matter what.
What should I do?
If he's after your money, he'll call you soon.
Keep checking your phone.
Let's stop the search and go back to Seoul.
I'll look up the license plate as soon as I get to Seoul.
Bok Sil.
Isn't she...
This woman is related to Louis, so do a background search...
and keep an eye on her.
It's Ko Bok Sil.
I bought it at a boutique that I go. Would it look good on Ma Ri?
What on earth happened?
I thought it was Ma Ri's jacket.
Gosh.
Have you lost your mind? What are you doing?
There's been a mistake.
I told you that I'll give you the money.
Why are you making things worse?
You made me think that you weren't trustworthy.
What are you talking about?
Either way,
all you need is the money, right?
I'll give you the money right now,
so let Bok Sil go.
Bring me the money to where we met last time.
I'm sorry for being late.
I checked the license plate, and it's a stolen car.
It'll be hard to figure out the suspect.
What about the surveillance cameras?
We haven't found out anything.
We're looking at the recordings of all cameras in the vicinity,
so they'll call us soon.
We're searching for the stolen car, so let's wait a little more.
Has the kidnapper called you?
No.
I'd give him money if that's what he wants,
but he isn't calling me. My goodness.
Stay strong. He'll call you soon.
Why isn't he here yet?
I can't wait any longer. I'm going to look for her.
Where do you think you're going?
I don't know, but I must look for her.
I'm worried that something happened to her.
You may get exhausted. You must stay strong.
I wish he would call.
(BOK SIL)
Bok Sil.
"Bok Sil"?
Do you know the owner of this phone?
- Isn't this Bok Sil? Who is this?
- I'm calling from a hospital.
The owner of this phone is in our hospital now because of an accident.
What?
What's the name of the hospital?
That punk.
Why isn't he coming?
He let someone steal his money,
kidnapped a wrong person and made a whole mess.
Now, I'm here with the money again. Why isn't he here yet?
My goodness.
Bok Sil.
- This isn't Bok Sil.
- What on earth is going on?
Wait. He is...
Why is he...
What? This is Mr Goo.
Do you know him?
Yes. He's the brother of Mr Baek's friend.
I met him at his wife's bookstore.
What did you say?
He's the person who got hurt in your rooftop room before.
What?
Has this patient injured his head before?
Yes. He was unconscious for a long time,
and he left the hospital without proper treatment.
There's a possibility that he won't wake up.
What about Bok Sil?
He knows where Bok Sil is. What happens to her?
Calm down. We'll find a way.
Bok Sil... Are you talking about...
the woman who was taken here with this patient?
Where is she?
(DETECTIVE TEAM 1-3)
Hey. Joon Hyuk found the victim of...
the rooftop room robbery who ran away from the hospital.
- Where?
- He's in another hospital.
- Go and join him.
- Yes, Sir.
Detective Lee. What is it?
The victim is in the hospital now.
What... What did you just say?
He injured his head in a car accident.
He's unconscious again.
We will take care of him now. Please don't concern yourself.
Why? Did something happen?
He tried to kidnap someone.
There will be an extensive investigation.
Bok Sil.
- Louis.
- Bok Sil.
Are you hurt? Where? How bad is it?
I'm fine.
I just pulled a ligament.
- Louis...
- Bok Sil. You must've been scared.
I promised I'd protect you. I'm sorry I didn't keep my word.
But I'm fine.
I'm so sorry, Bok Sil.
Aren't you hungry? You've been through much overnight.
- A little.
- Wait here.
I'll go and get some food.
That detective is like the best servant you can have.
By the way,
why do you think he kidnapped me?
I thought he was after money, but I don't think he was.
He is the same person who got beaten with a hammer in our rooftop room.
What?
Are you sure that man knows Mr Baek?
Yes.
He said he was the brother of Mr Baek's friend.
Isn't it strange?
Why would Mr Baek's friend break into our place?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Honey.
Where have you been?
You look awful.
Jae Sook.
Are you...
Are you sick?
There's a box on my desk.
Please take it to Mother's house in Busan.
There is...
a secret place under the floor of Louis' attic.
You can put it there.
Why do I have to put it there?
Don't ask why.
Please do as I say.
You should go now.
Okay.
Attorney Hwang, it's me.
Can we meet?
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Eat up.
Hold on.
What are you doing?
I'm going to tie it for you.
- Make it pretty.
- Of course.
I should...
You look so pretty.
Really?
Sure. Let's eat.
Okay.
- I spilled it.
- I'll wipe it for you.
Please wipe my mouth, too.
- Water, please.
- Okay.
Here you go.
I thought I lost it.
It went to its owner.
I knew it was mine right away. Is this your present?
Yes.
- There is one more.
- Another present?
- Come closer.
- What?
I like you very much.
Is the profession your present?
What should I do?
We can't. What if someone comes in?
Is it okay now?
Ms Ko Bok Sil.
Gosh. Don't. Go away.
- Don't touch me. No.
- I'm just...
No. Go away. Don't touch me.
What are you...
Ms Ko Bok Sil. You may go home today.
Okay.
We'll clean it up.
Okay. Make sure you do that.
I'm sorry.
- She startled me.
- I'll do it.
You got it on your face.
- You still have some food here.
- No, I'll do it.
- Why?
- I'll do it.
- But you injured your hand.
- I still can do it.
- It will hurt.
- It won't.
Bok Nam.
- Bok Nam.
- They're here.
- In Sung. Get the blankets.
- Okay.
Move it.
- Gosh, Bok Sil. Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Oh my goodness. Lie down.
- Lie down.
(BOK SIL'S MAIDS)
My dear Bok Sil. You must've been so scared.
You're hurt. Gosh.
(BOK SIL'S MAIDS)
I'm fine.
It must've been hard.
I said I'm fine. Don't treat me like a patient.
No. You should take a rest. Get some sleep.
Why did he kidnap Bok Sil and put her through all this?
That jerk. He better watch out because I'm going to break his legs.
Did the police catch the suspect?
He's injured and unconscious.
The guy at the hospital.
There's a big chance that he's a hitman who is in Korea illegally.
That's why we've been keeping a watchful eye on him.
- Pardon me?
- How can he be Mr Baek's friend?
Isn't it fishy?
This is just my speculation,
but I think Mr Baek could have hired him.
If Mr Baek actually hired a hitman...
- Gosh.
- That guy is so weird.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
Where is the guy who was just here?
He just left.
Do you know him?
No.
Why do you ask?
Never mind. It's nothing.
Mr Baek could have known...
about Louis being alive.
But why did he keep it to himself?
(LOUIS)
I wanted a minor accident.
I didn't want him to get into such a big accident.
What will you do now? How will you take responsibility for it?
He died!
It's not like we wanted it to happen.
We just followed the plan,
but the driver sped up suddenly. That's why it became a big deal.
That time,
if the situation had not gotten out of hand like that,
I wouldn't have had to scheme...
in order to cover up what happened.
There's no point in regretting now.
Detective, is Mr Goo still unconscious?
If he wakes up, you have to ask him why he kidnapped Bok Sil.
I'll take care of everything here. You should get some sleep.
You've been running around so much since yesterday.
The same goes to you.
Okay. Thank you for everything.
Bye.
I brought a glass of warm milk.
Please drink it and get some sleep.
- Mr Kim.
- Yes, Master.
Am I...
allowed to drive?
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
I want to drive for Bok Sil.
You used to go on about wanting to drive even when we lived in France.
That's right.
But when you arrived in Korea,
you drove off in Mr Baek's car and caused a huge mess.
Hence, Ms Choi might not allow you to drive.
Sorry?
I drove off in his car?
I heard you ran away in Mr Baek's car while he was in the washroom.
Get going.
Something came up, so I have to stop by the office.
You can drive, right?
Okay.
I never did such a thing.
Pardon me?
To be honest,
I have been suspicious of Mr Baek.
He took your baby tooth as well as your watch from the house in Busan.
I also ran into him when I went to look for you.
But he's the one who brought you back,
so I had no choice but to trust him.
Hello.
He did seem very surprised to see me that day.
My memory came back.
- He looked surprised then, too.
- What?
The reason I shouldn't come back alive.
The reason my memory shouldn't come back.
What could it be?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Who is it at this hour?
I'm sorry to visit you so late.
It's all right.
I was going to go see you tomorrow.
Does that mean...
you know why I'm here?
Ji Sung,
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Mr Baek.
I didn't...
plan such a big accident from the beginning.
I want Louis...
to inherit Gold Group.
Ms Choi didn't discuss it with me at all.
She suddenly announced that she wants you to have Gold Group.
I was livid when I heard that.
I mean,
I have devoted my life to growing Gold Group.
Ever since your father passed away,
I've been treating Ms Choi like my own mother.
However, it was so easy for her to nudge me away.
You were in a faraway land,
but she decided to give you everything.
Her decision hurt me so badly.
I thought...
that getting you injured a little through a car accident...
would terrify her...
and make her send you back to France.
But...
it got out of my hand.
It turned into a huge accident, and I couldn't control it any more.
Believe me, Ji Sung.
I thought you were dead. Since the day you came back,
I've been living every single day in anxiety.
I've been so nervous...
about people finding out what I did.
I've been feeling as if I'm a fugitive on the run.
Mr Baek.
I know that you've been looking after my grandma by her side...
instead of me and my deceased parents,
and I really appreciate it.
Louis...
That alone should be enough for me to forgive you,
but...
someone died because of the accident.
I will accept punishment...
for what I did.
I have actually been...
sorting things out in order to turn myself in.
The company shares Ms Choi gave me.
I told Attorney Hwang...
that I want to transfer them all to you.
Mr Baek.
I guess it's human nature.
Once I started becoming greedy,
I couldn't stop myself from becoming shameless.
One thing concerns me, though.
Ms Choi could faint if she finds out about this.
I'm worried.
Please don't worry.
I'll keep it from Grandma.
I don't want to make her sad.
Thanks, Louis.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(DETECTIVE TEAM 1-3)
While I'm gone,
take good care of Ma Ri and her mother, please.
Okay. Please don't worry.
I'm here to turn myself in.
Thank you for admitting everything...
that you've done wrong.
There's something that isn't consistent with Mr Goo's testimony,
so I'd like to cross-examine.
Pardon me?
Everything from the car accident to kidnapping Ko Bok Sil...
was ordered by Mr Baek.
What are you talking about?
He threatened me to give him money.
I threatened you?
I never asked him for money.
He's lying.
He's trying to put the blame on me.
He was trying to kidnap my daughter,
but kidnapped Bok Sil by mistake.
I just work for an errand service.
All I did was what he told me to do.
It's not true. I didn't order him to do that.
I know that...
it's not easy to believe me right now,
but I really didn't do it, Louis.
Detective Nam explained it to me.
Is there any way you can prove yourself?
I went to the bookstore with the money,
but it was after Mr Goo disappeared.
There are no surveillance cameras near the bookstore.
I don't have anything to prove myself.
The bookstore?
Mr Cha, there's something we have to do.
- Are you sure that's the car?
- Gosh, you startled me.
Don't whisper to me.
Yes, it's been there for a few days.
In the same spot.
Shall we go?
He's so excited.
Goodness.
This is the police. I'd like a quick search.
Gosh.
I caught him.
Stay still.
Where did you get these photos?
Ms Hong had a stalker.
- A stalker?
- Yes.
We confiscated all the photos he took...
in front of the bookstore.
Detective, please solve this issue.
Of course I will.
The two are having a conversation in this photo.
The next day, Mr Baek is at the bookstore with the money.
Isn't this enough for evidence?
You should become a detective. You're so observant.
By the way,
why were you at the bookstore?
You seem quite close to her.
It's difficult for a woman to run a bookstore alone.
Besides, she helped us a lot in finding Louis.
To express my gratitude, I often helped her with...
- carrying heavy books.
- You like to pry, don't you?
You should mind your own business.
Why did you take...
the risk of kidnapping Ma Ri?
What about the money you received at first?
I didn't have a choice because the money got stolen.
That old lady had amazing pickpocketing skills.
She's a professional pickpocket?
Detective Nam, what are you doing?
- Did you get the camera recordings?
- And her identity as well.
She's Cho Ha Ni with nine prior pickpocketing convictions.
I caught her in the past.
Can you find out where she is now?
This is my area of expertise.
I sent some people already.
Thank you.
Please stop denying it. You were caught on the surveillance camera.
That wasn't me.
It was someone who looks like me.
Gosh.
I'm glad that you got better.
- You should still be careful, okay?
- Okay.
Let's stop by the police station.
I told Mr Baek to apologise to you in person.
But he didn't kidnap me.
- Let's pay him a visit anyway.
- Okay.
Ms Cho, let's get it over with.
Where is the money?
You really don't believe me, do you?
Gosh, what time is it?
Detective,
how can you keep me here without any evidence?
My goodness.
- Detective.
- Hello, Bok Sil.
Ma'am!
My grandma had cold hands, too.
Ma'am.
I won't ask you about your lies...
about your grandson.
I hope that...
you'll return the money because it belongs to someone I know.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Detective must be waiting.
Your leg got better.
I'm glad.
What kind of clothes are these?
They look so cheap.
I don't want this.
Then why don't you go only with your underwear on?
I've never met anyone so obsessed...
with her clothes!
It belonged to my late mother.
I'm sorry.
Don't pay attention...
to an old lady like me.
I wish you luck.
Living in Seoul can be very difficult.
- Gosh.
- Okay, Ma'am.
I hope you find your grandson.
Ma'am.
This...
Get some food.
Take care.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Why do I even remember that?
It's so annoying.
Call the detective for me.
I'll tell you where the money is.
Really? I'll bring him now.
Who knew...
I would exchange 10 million dollars with 10 dollars?
To prove your innocence, Mr Kang Ji Sung found evidence.
You should be honest now.
Someone died in the accident.
Who would believe that you didn't intend to kill someone?
I'm telling you the truth.
Didn't you ask me for a favour...
because you feel guilty?
Please call me if the patient regains consciousness.
You don't need to give me this.
That was because...
I was worried about Mr Goo not waking up.
It didn't mean anything else.
We got the money back.
Also,
we found this.
It's a voice recording.
All you need to do is to cause a fender bender.
- Why don't you get rid of him?
- No.
If Ji Sung gets injured a little,
Ms Choi will send him to France right away.
There's no need to make a big mess.
- You didn't make a copy, did you?
- Of course not.
Mr Goo lied to me.
Thank goodness.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Bok Sil helped me find it, so you should thank her.
Your sentence will be greatly reduced because of this.
This way, please.
Thanks a lot.
I owe so much...
to the two of you.
Thanks.
Louis...
I heard that the president of Goldline...
got arrested for disgraceful conduct.
Things must be chaotic at the company.
Things are bad for the company, but I'm more worried about Jae Sook.
She must be so distressed about her husband being behind bars.
Jae Sook.
I'm sorry that I was always irritable with you.
I haven't been myself for a long time...
because I've been preoccupied with covering up what I did.
Just know that I've been very distressed as well.
I have to be punished for what I did,
but I want you and Ma Ri to stay healthy and well.
I also want to let you know that I thank you...
for always being good to Louis.
Will I ever be able...
to pay you back for everything you've done for me?
Why did he...
Why...
Dad.
Why did he do that?
I already looked everywhere.
- Are you sure you left it here?
- Absolutely. I'm sure.
See?
This wasn't here the last time I came here.
You're getting old. You should get reading glasses.
I still have good vision.
Stop telling me that I'm getting old. It hurts my feelings.
Mr Baek told me that aging makes you sweat when you eat.
Does aging also make you cry more easily?
Mr Louis, please.
All right.
This is the music box made for the 30th anniversary.
(KOBOSHI)
Hi, Koboshi.
You used to love Koboshi so much. You even wrote it there.
I've been wanting to ask you. What does Koboshi mean?
Does it refer to a seed of something?
It's a name of a kid with a pretty smile.
That kid must be doing well, right?
Yes, probably.
Anyway, I'm so glad that your memory came back.
After the news about your death,
Ms Choi looked everywhere for this box.
Grandma did? Why?
It's because her precious memories are in this box.
Ms Choi, I finally found it.
- Really?
- You can watch it now.
(MARCH 15, 1996, MUM, DAD AND JI SUNG)
- I'll give you some privacy.
- Okay.
Come here.
Did you have fun?
That voice.
That voice...
I've wanted to hear it so much.
- Shall we jump? In 1, 2 and 3.
- In 1, 2 and 3!
Isn't it so much fun?
My son, Geum Seok.
My daughter-in-law.
I miss you guys.
My gosh...
Ms Choi.
Where is my sister-in-law?
It's "brother-in-law".
Right, brother-in-law.
That word is just stuck in my head.
He went out.
It must be torturous for him to be sitting in his room.
He can go out and play.
I used to want to run around and play when I was at his age.
I'm sad that I never got to do it.
All right.
Oh, Louis.
This.
Are you giving this to me?
It's your hard-earned money. You should have it.
Get whatever you wanted to buy.
Shall I get a gift for Grandma?
Yes, you should.
People usually buy long johns for their parents with their first pay.
Get red long johns for her.
No.
I want to buy something else.
What?
It's a secret.
Grandma.
I got this for you with my hard-earned money.
I'm not talking about my pay from Gold Group. It's my real first pay.
Louis.
Bok Sil told me to get red long johns, but I got this instead.
I thought this pair of high heels would look awesome on you.
My goodness. You picked out...
the perfect gift for me. I love it.
- Try them on.
- Okay.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
My gosh, they fit me perfectly.
How does it look? Does it look good on me?
Perfect.
This pair of high heels was brought to this world for you.
The one who came to this world for me...
is you, Louis.
Thank you so much...
for coming to me.
Grandma.
Why isn't Grandma here yet?
- I'll go let her know.
- It's okay. I'll go.
Grandma!
My grandma!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Grandma, wake up.
Breakfast is ready.
Grandma.
Grandma...
I'm so sorry. I came too late.
Grandma.
My dear grandma...
Grandma...
Ms Choi...
I can't believe this.
Grandma...
Grandma.
(CHOI IL SOON)
Goodbye, Grandma.
People buy things based on different values.
Observing one's shopping pattern...
can teach a lot about that person.
Grandma.
Why do you wear high heels when you have a bad back?
I wear high heels...
because I want to stay young forever.
It's like my attitude towards life.
When you wear high heels,
it straightens your stooped back...
and makes your steps livelier.
I wanted to walk like that forever.
In a young and confident way.
The one who came to this world for me...
is you, Louis.
Thank you so much...
for coming to me.
Time passed,
but I could still feel the void left by Grandma's death.
Then one day...
Jung Ran. Jung Ran.
A new life came to our house.
It felt like Grandma's gift to us.
Jung Ran.
- Oh, my.
- I love you.
You're making me dizzy.
My beloved friend, Mr Kim,
hasn't proposed to her because he hasn't fully analysed her yet.
Bok Sil, who is so stubborn,
rejected my offer to live together in my house.
She's still living in our rooftop room.
- Bok Sil, I'm here.
- Hi.
Hi, Louis.
- Bok Nam, you're here, too.
- I'm staying home today.
- It's too crowded outside.
- I see.
I cooked ramyeon because Bok Nam asked for it. Let's eat it together.
- I did good, right?
- Yes.
I wanted to eat out with Bok Sil.
- Louis and Bok Nam, set the table.
- Okay.
Will it work now?
Yes. It's all fixed. We also got the tape inside.
Thank you.
What is this?
My gosh.
Where did this come from?
- It's delicious.
- Yes.
Hello, Ms Hong. What is it?
Louis. I have a present to give you.
What present?
(THE LAST EPISODE OF SHOPAHOLIC LOUIS WILL AIR SHORTLY.)