Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
The world is connected as one.
- Hello?
- Ji Sung.
Hang up.
You can call anywhere whenever.
- It'll be expensive.
- With who?
We didn't see it last time.
You can send and receive messages anywhere.
I miss you.
Why did you run away from home?
People from Seoul came to our house to film a documentary.
I was curious about the life in a city.
A documentary?
Do you remember the title?
"Hinterlands of Korea".
You see the title of the show, "Hinterlands of Korea", right?
"Hinterlands of Korea"?
Are you all right?
Bok Sil.
This is why she looked so familiar.
You already fell in love with her when you saw her.
That's not true.
Isn't she cute?
Was this really our first encounter?
(FINAL EPISODE: WHEN YOU WISH UPON A STAR)
The president is here.
It's the president.
Oh, my.
- I love you, Mr Cha.
I thought Mr Louis would become the president.
Someday he will.
Don't you think Mr Cha became more handsome?
Indeed. Even his moustache looks cool.
What is this? Why is he so handsome?
What?
Do I still have feelings for him? Really? Why?
It feels strange. Oh, gosh.
It's delicious.
Coffee tastes the best here except on our rooftop.
I agree.
This reminds me of the time when we first came here.
It's as sweet as honey.
This is coffee. Isn't it delicious?
Where did you get that dress?
It's my mum's.
I cried so much when I lost this.
Bok Sil, you don't have a mum?
I don't even remember her face.
Do you have amnesia too?
She passed away when I was very young and so did my dad.
Oh... I see.
I wonder if I have any family.
Of course you do.
Don't worry too much.
Your memory will return.
Like you said, my memory returned.
I got to see the family photo and I remember Mum and Dad's faces.
I feel bad that it's not the same for you.
It's fine. I'm happy enough that I found Bok Nam.
Thank you for finding Bok Nam, Louis.
Bok Sil.
Hey. People are coming in.
Please have some coffee.
Thank you.
Sir.
Mr Louis, you look handsome as always.
I love you, Mr Louis.
- Thank you.
- You're the best, Mr Louis.
Here, Do Jin.
- I'll leave the tray with you.
- Yes, Sir.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
(PRESIDENT CHA JOONG WON)
Gosh, there's so much paperwork.
I should've continued my sabbatical year. Why did I take this job?
I wonder if everyone is doing a good job.
I'm so curious.
I'm not bored. I'm not bored at all.
Gosh, this is so dull.
How can we induce purchase aside from providing coupons?
- That's...
- It's clear on your proposal.
Good job.
I can't believe this.
Did you copy from another company?
There are no distinguishing points.
- It's my own...
- I'm saying it's that good.
There're many distinguishing points.
Main page advertisement is costly.
Main page post is costly. This isn't good enough for the special sale.
This is perfect for the special sale.
The prices are competitive enough.
The prices aren't competitive. Negotiate the charge fees.
You don't need to negotiate the charge fees.
Okay. Yes, Sir.
- He's so kind.
- Yes.
Peter Drucker said this.
"Knowing trends won't"...
"guarantee a success by 100 percent"...
- "But not knowing trends will"...
- "Guarantee a failure."
Mr Lee.
What grades are your children in?
They're in 4th and 2nd grade. The other 2 are 5 and 1 year old.
At this rate,
do you think you'll be able to work until your youngest starts school?
the company should support your children's education.
You're a trend leader. You're ahead of your time.
- Oh, my.
- Good for you, Mr Lee.
Gosh, all right.
As for Bok Sil,
your reputation is great among all of our new clients.
Thanks to Singsingline,
Goldline's image has improved as well. Thank you.
Thank you.
You're all...
so good at your job!
- Yes!
- Gosh.
What's going on? Why is everyone not working?
Get to work.
I am working ahead of my time.
What are you saying?
Why do you keep coming here? You have your own office.
I don't come here for no reason.
As the president,
I'm here to see if you're working of slacking off.
Welcome.
Bok Sil.
- Is our Singsingline going okay?
- Yes. Thanks to you.
Why does he call it "our Singsingline"?
Why do you call it "our Singsingline"?
That's right.
I'm still Singsingline's investor.
It is our Singsingline.
They always bicker around.
I'm not sure if they're friends or enemies.
That's right. Mr Cha.
How many stars did you get from Mr Louis back then?
Why won't you tell us?
Why do you think Louis gave me stars?
Don't you know how he is?
Here. Take a look.
This shows what kind of person Louis is.
Thanks. From King Louis.
Gosh.
He knows how to destroy formality. It's a creative destruction.
You should learn from him.
I knew it.
Why do you keep it in your wallet?
It's not your business.
Bok Sil. Let's go and talk about Singsingline.
Yes, Sir.
How did it go with...
Why does Mr Cha...
keep it in his wallet like that?
It can't be.
Does Mr Cha like Mr Louis?
Gosh. No way.
We reduced our profit margin because of the distribution process,
but we were able to earn this much of profit. This is amazing.
Bok Sil. Great job.
It's because you taught me well.
Are you...
free tomorrow?
Do you need me for something?
Would you go on a date with me?
Pardon me?
They're beautiful.
The walk...
and the weather are beautiful.
Walking outside makes me feel refreshed.
I really enjoyed today's lunch.
You always treat me. I'll buy you lunch next time.
Today's lunch was our last lunch together.
Sorry?
We'll have to take Louis with us from now on.
Louis won't let us eat alone together.
He wanted to join us today, but I stopped him.
Sometimes, Louis reminds me of a giant puppy.
He always follows me around.
He doesn't like me being with other people.
Sometimes, he gets jealous when I'm with Bok Nam.
Louis lived apart from his family for a long time,
so he needs love and care more than average people.
Treat him well.
I will.
I'm very glad that...
you're Louis' girlfriend.
- Where are we going?
- Right.
Wait here for me.
Here you go, Bok Sil.
(SAMPLE QUESTIONS FOR THE EXAM)
Bok Nam already bought his books.
These are for you.
- For me?
- As I told you before,
you can become successful.
After getting a high school diploma, take the college entrance exam.
You should enter the university.
You're smart and hard-working, so you'll do well.
Mr Cha.
I don't know your plans with Louis,
but I hope you won't give up your studies...
no matter what.
Mr Cha.
You're such a good person.
A good person?
Okay.
I'll always be a good person to you.
Let's keep it that way.
Okay.
- Pay me 55 dollars.
- What?
I was just kidding!
- Isn't it cold?
- Yes.
Oh, my goodness.
I think I'll throw up...
if I smell food at all.
You should still eat.
Try some of this.
I put a lot of effort in it.
I said I can't eat right now.
Open it.
How amazing can it be?
Does it look like a fake because it's on a table?
However, it's real.
As real as my love for you.
Thank you so much.
Jung Ran.
Please marry me.
I'm sorry my propose is late.
How did you come up with this idea?
My senior colleague taught me.
I did my research, but this was the best.
I completely agree.
- What are you doing?
- We're moving in.
We'll stay here until you get married.
- Are you being serious?
- I also...
want to see you get married.
This won't make me get married.
I know you can't live with us,
so you'll try to get married as soon as possible.
What kind of logic is that?
We'll find out, won't we?
Are you okay with ramyeon?
Honey, I'll make it. You get some rest.
I'll make it since you did a lot of packing.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Stop!
Are you adding plum syrup to ramyeon?
I won't put up with it any more.
Honey.
Dad. What's wrong?
The kitchen is mine starting today.
Don't come in any more.
Why are you acting like this?
Also,
there won't be any plum syrup in my kitchen...
any more.
Gosh, are you okay?
Stop it, Dad.
Why are you fighting in my kitchen?
Fine.
You can have this kitchen to yourself.
I won't live here anyway.
Mum, Mum.
Is this why you came here?
Now, I really want to get married.
I'm starting to romanticise about marriage so much more.
Where would she go in the middle of the night?
I'll stay out of it, so you must take all responsibilities,
okay?
- Gosh.
- Hey.
Ms Baek will treat us to drinks today.
- Cheers.
- Why are you buying us drinks?
I'll pay.
I don't think Ms Baek can go home alone.
Mr Cha should take her home.
Oh, my goodness.
Why did she drink so much?
Goodnight.
Mum, what do you think of Mr Cha?
Isn't he great and manly?
Is that Mr Cha's mother?
Goodness.
Gosh, please come in, Vivian.
I'm sorry for coming late at night.
Hello, Ms Shin.
I haven't seen you in a while.
I hope I'm not disturbing your rest.
Not at all.
I was just reading some poems.
I'll do some cross-stitching before going to bed.
Do what?
Goodness, you're so ladylike.
I hope you enjoy your time here.
Thank you.
Now that you're already here,
why don't we have a sleepover and invite Cleopatra, too?
I'm in.
Cleopatra.
Didn't you say you bought a building in Singapore?
No, I bought a hotel.
Didn't you say you were buying something in Paris, Audrey?
I'll build a hotel, too.
What's the point of saving money? I should invest it.
Audrey got into my land.
Pay your taxes before you build a hotel.
Why do I always stop in Vivian's land?
Let's see.
Okay, here I go.
I'm on the deserted island again. I'm going bankrupt.
I lose my turn in this round.
Let me throw again.
- No way.
- Come on, Cleopatra.
- Let me have another turn.
- No way. It's my turn.
Vivian,
why did you fight with your husband?
Is it something serious?
Yes.
Come on, that's nothing.
Is that what you fought about?
Isn't it nice if your husband cooks for you?
The kitchen is necessary for women to feel important,
but he treated my plum syrup as if it's some virus.
How could he?
You should be grateful to have a husband at all.
My husband died...
a long time ago.
I poked my thighs so many times to stay faithful to my late husband.
My husband is in jail.
Gosh. I'm sorry, Audrey.
We didn't mean to make you sad.
Marriage is hard for everyone.
That's right.
Tomorrow is the wedding. Shall we get ready?
How?
We should do some skin care to look good. What do you say?
- Yes!
I'm so nervous.
I am, too.
It looks delicious.
Bok Sil.
You'll be wearing a tight dress tomorrow. Don't eat too much.
Okay.
- I'll just have one more bite.
- Okay.
- Is it delicious?
- Yes.
You can have one more bite.
- Just one bite?
- What?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Ms Choi Il Soon, my grandma,
told me that observing what one buys can teach you...
a lot about that person.
I hope Joong Won marries someone soon.
In Sung hasn't turned 30 yet,
so he still has time.
He hasn't turned 30 yet?
Goodness. I thought he was older than my son.
It's because he took bad herbal tonic when he was young.
His father looked very young.
Really?
I want Ma Ri...
to stay single and live with me forever.
I can't give her to anyone.
How can you be so immature?
After you die, Ma Ri would be in her 60s.
Would you want her to live alone at that age?
- I got them some herbal tonic...
- Ms Shin, a health food lover,
- that helps them have a baby.
- got them herbal tonic...
and plum preserve, the cure-all food.
Everything is possible...
- with money. Money is the best.
- Ms Hwang thinks money is the best.
She prepared cash in an envelope.
I wish they would have a beautiful life together.
- I hope they enjoy...
- Ms Hong loves beautiful things.
She got them a graceful tea set.
- You're here, Mr Cha.
- Thank you for inviting me.
Who invited him?
I did.
This is a happy occasion. You should make up with him.
Young Ae.
I'm sorry.
I missed you.
Is everything ready for the bride?
- In Sung.
- Yes.
- Come here.
- What is it?
What do you think about working at Goldline's merchandising department?
Really? Are you just going to hire me?
Try our open recruitment next year.
You've already taken the easy way to work as Louis' secretary.
- Come on. Just hire me.
- I said I can't.
Mr Cha, a fashionable man who loves sunglasses,
gave them two stylish pairs of matching sunglasses.
In Sung, the life of every party,
got them a nice lamp.
- I'm sorry I'm late.
- Hello.
Gosh, this house is amazing.
- Where should I put this?
- Over here, please.
Over there? Okay.
You're showing off your strength with the present again.
Detective Nam Joon Hyuk, who is like a strong tree...
showed up with a heavy plant as a present.
You know strength is all I've got.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
- What did you say?
- He said no.
Anyway, where is Louis?
I don't know if it's out of love for their company,
but people at Goldline prepared dozens of Goldline gift certificate.
We will now begin the wedding ceremony.
Let's welcome the bride and the groom.
Gosh, she looks beautiful.
You look so beautiful!
Ma Ri, who has exquisite taste and sense of smell,
gave them the finest home diffuser that...
only the best hotels use.
Bok Sil, an angel without wings,
got them a lifelong free coupon for Singsingline's products.
And...
I, a shopaholic and the king of shopping,
offered them a sturdy car...
that Mr Kim can drive Ms Heo and their baby with.
Of course, what's more important than presents is...
the earnest heart that one can give to the other.
Now,
the bride will throw the bouquet.
If you want to catch it, please come out.
Yes. Come on out.
Please throw the bouquet.
Ma Ri.
Do you like Mr Cha?
How did you know that?
I saw you. You couldn't stop looking at him.
- Have you told him how you feel?
- He rejected me.
- What?
- Ma Ri.
If you like someone, you should show them who you really are.
Don't exhaust yourself pretending to be someone fancier.
Ms Baek.
If you want to come across as sincere, don't fake your feelings.
Being yourself is a powerful thing.
(MA RI)
What is this?
Ms Baek.
Did you intend to send it to me?
What does this mean?
Gosh.
What should I say?
It's my feeling towards you.
I'll send you one every day.
Why would you send me your feelings?
Because I want to.
Fine. Go to sleep, Ms Baek.
It worked.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
- In Sung.
- Yes?
Do you like Ma Ri?
- Is it obvious?
- Yes.
- Do you like her?
- Of course.
There's something you should know.
What is it?
- Ma Ri likes Mr Cha.
- Yes?
What?
Well, I thought you should know the truth.
It's up to you to have a crush on her or not.
Keep it up if you can handle it,
but stop now if that's not the case.
Do you know...
what kind of unforgettable memories...
Ma Ri and I share?
I even pretended that I farted to save her face.
That can't be.
Well, I just don't want you to be heartbroken.
That's why I'm telling you this now.
It's your choice.
To keep going or not.
It's up to you.
Ma Ri, what should I do?
Our encounter was
You only live once.
I'm just going to give you my all, Ma Ri.
I love you.
I love you, Ma Ri.
I love you! Ma Ri.
I should get married soon, too.
Bok Sil, marry me.
Not this one.
Bok Sil, let's live together.
No.
Bok Sil.
Let's eat together for the rest of our lives.
Not that one.
Bok Sil.
Stay by my side forever.
That's no good, either.
What should I say?
Bok Sil.
As of today, you're my woman...
Gosh, what should I do...
I told you. I don't care whether she's a doctor or not.
I won't go on blind dates.
I'm going to find someone I like and date her freely.
You can't control these things. Give up already, Mum.
What's this now? She looks like a North Korean spy.
Is she here for me?
What are you doing now?
Please spare me a few minutes.
What?
Let go! Let go of me!
Are you crazy?
You're a psycho.
Buy ginseng.
Are you crazy?
Buy wild ginseng.
It may not look like anything special,
but it's real 15-year-old ginseng.
Here. Please have a look.
It doesn't look that special, but it's real 50-year-old ginseng.
I came to Seoul today, but I got my bag stolen in the train.
Did you also get your bag stolen...
upon arriving in Seoul?
What are you talking about?
Why are you telling me to buy your ginseng all of a sudden?
Come and have a look.
Look at this. Examining the head...
tells you whether it's real or not.
Look at this. The head tells you...
whether it's real wild ginseng or not.
This is 100 percent real wild ginseng.
I harvested it myself. If you don't buy it, you'll regret it.
You don't even need to examine this. It's cultivated ginseng.
I know.
How do you know?
I know because I have a lot of experience with wild ginseng.
So just tell me why you're telling me to buy this.
This is one-of-a-kind wild ginseng.
You won't be able to find ginseng like this even if you travel...
the entire country or all over the world!
What's the reason?
Is this also one-of-a-kind ginseng?
I have no idea...
what you're talking about now.
Then what is it?
To be honest, my parents...
became ill all of a sudden.
Hence, I'm in urgent need of money.
How much do you want to sell it for?
I don't want to sell it to you.
What?
I want a contract with Singsingline.
How daring.
I see. So you're not here to sell this box of ginseng.
You want a contract.
My family has a ginseng field.
You probably know that Geumsan...
is famous for ginseng grown in the region.
Goodness. You're a seasoned salesperson.
I have to look after my parents,
so I don't have time to be explaining all the details.
There's the saying, "Make haste slowly."
Since I'm already here, I'd like to secure a good client.
It looks like you have a good eye,
so I won't say more.
She certainly has a knack for sales.
But why do you want to work with Singsingline?
Singsingline is the best.
Am I wrong?
I should've introduced myself first.
My name is Wang Mong Sil. Wang Mong Sil.
Farewell to you, Ko Bok Sil.
Goodbye.
I look forward to working with you.
- Bok Sil, I'm here.
- Hi.
Louis!
- You're here, too.
- I want to rest at home today.
The streets get too crowded on weekends.
I see.
I made ramyeon. Come join us. Bok Nam said he was craving it.
- I did a good job, right?
- Yes.
I wanted to take Bok Sil out for food.
Louis and Bok Nam, get the table ready.
Okay!
Move.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
It's so good.
What is this?
My gosh.
Where did this come from?
It's delicious.
Yes, Ms Hong. What's going on?
Louis, I have a gift for you.
What is it?
My gosh.
I can't believe it.
Bok Sil.
You can't sleep again?
I'm so excited. My heart is pumping so hard.
About what?
About watching a film.
What film?
We said we'd watch a film together but haven't done it yet.
It's too scary.
That was the first film I've ever watched.
Hey, what was that about?
Well, I brought you because it was free.
Let's watch a non-scary one next time.
Yes, something that's not scary.
I'm going to say no to a horror film.
It's a touching one.
Why is it empty?
We're the only ones here.
I know.
I rented the entire cinema.
What?
I wanted to watch it with just you.
What is the film about?
It's starting.
(GOLD DEPARTMENT STORE'S 30TH ANNIVERSARY)
Now, let's start the ceremony...
marking the 30th anniversary of Gold Department Store.
Everyone got the free gifts we gave out, right?
Now, get ready for the highlight of the event.
We'll select recipients of the limited-edition music boxes...
made for Gold Group's 30th anniversary through a random draw.
Isn't it pretty?
To celebrate our 30th anniversary,
we only made 30 of these...
- music boxes.
- What is this?
- Are you sure this is a film?
- Yes.
Keep watching.
There are only two music boxes left!
The 29th music box goes to...
- Number 81!
- Great.
Thanks.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
The last one, the 30th...
music box, goes to...
The last lucky number is...
77.
- Oh, my.
- I'm so jealous.
- Who got it?
- Who is it?
Here! We're here!
That dress.
That dress is...
She's your mum.
And that's your dad.
Mum...
and Dad?
Here you go.
I hope you don't lose it and keep it for a long time.
Okay.
- How adorable.
- Great.
Yes, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Oh, you're expecting another little one.
Have you decided on the baby's name?
We want to name him Bok Nam, Ko Bok Nam.
Bok Nam.
May luck be with you.
All right. I'll take a photo of everyone.
Just a second.
- Okay.
- All right.
My mum and dad...
are smiling.
They're smiling at me.
Bok Sil.
You look a lot like your mum.
Bok Sil, you have to keep watching.
Something very important is waiting.
Ma Ri!
Ji Sung, what's the matter?
Did something happen?
Where is mine? Where is mine?
What are you talking about? Did you lose something?
No, my music box. I want a music box, too!
Only those who were selected through a random draw got them.
I want one, too! I want a music box, too!
The music box is mine!
Ma Ri, why are you being like this now?
Stop crying. Or I'll scold you.
Ma Ri!
Keep an eye on Ji Sung for me.
Ji Sung, I'll be right back. Stop! Come with me, Ma Ri.
I want a music box, too. Give me a music box.
Don't cry.
Are you giving this to me?
Yes.
What's your name?
Ko Bok Sil.
Koboshi?
My daughter, you're such a sweetie.
Shall we go now?
Koboshi!
You must be surprised.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(KOBOSHI)
Don't cry,
Koboshi.
(GOLD DEPARTMENT STORE)
My Koboshi whom I've been enshrining in my treasure box...
is right in front of my eyes now.
Louis didn't forget about me and has cherished me all along.
Thanks to his heart,
we were able to meet again after travelling...
a great distance in circles for a long time.
That's what I believe.
It's cold. Let's go inside.
Okay.
Gosh, I feel as if I'm back in my hometown.
Welcome back.
- Bok Sil.
- Yes?
I'm curious about something.
What is it?
When no one else believed me,
you trusted me.
Did I look that trustworthy to you?
When I was growing up,
I had no one telling me that I can lean on them.
I had to...
support Bok Nam and my grandma as the pillar of my family.
You were the very first person who said those words to me.
What you said...
gave me solace.
It made me feel safe.
Bok Sil.
I will...
say those words...
to you...
for the rest of our lives.
Just trust me.
Thanks.
Bok Sil.
I love you.
I love you, too.
(THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR WATCHING LOUIS AND BOK SIL'S STORY.)
(MEMORY JOTTER)
Let's roll.
Since yesterday, the aeroplane...
It has been... Yesterday, it was a helicopter.
He's probably in his room.
- What was that about?
- Will this look good on Ma Ri?
Gosh, I can't unfold this.
Right now
Goodness.
- Why didn't you come in?
- Are you going to keep hesitating?
Why aren't you swallowing it?
Cut!
- Come on.
- Cut!
Go away, you fool.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU