Subtitles by VIU
In my new beginning,
she was there.
Sir, is Goldline Tower coming up soon?
You must have taken the opposite route.
Cross the street and take the other bus.
Hey, you.
Here. You should wipe the floor better.
Gosh.
In my new beginning, she was there.
I'm sorry. I'll clean it up now.
Ko Bok Sil.
(Episode 3)
Hello, stranger.
Where are you going?
I'll be your umbrella.
Come on.
What's your name?
I don't know.
- How old are you?
- I don't know that, either.
You thief. You swindler.
Give me back my ginseng. Give me back my money.
What's going on? Are they fighting?
What are you doing?
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- She passed out.
- He hit her.
Oh, my.
Bok Sil.
- Bok Sil.
- Goodness.
- Call 911 and the ambulance.
- Big news.
Big news.
Mr Cha got in trouble.
- What do you mean?
- An ambulance came...
for the cleaner who was cleaning the lobby. It's a big mess.
What happened to the cleaner?
Mr Cha hit her and she passed out.
- What?
He didn't hit her. He pushed her hard.
They're the same thing.
Anyway, at first,
Mr Cha screamed and started the fight.
Suddenly, that woman said,
"You swindler. Give me back my money."
As she said that, she attacked him.
No way. Mr Cha isn't someone who would deceive others.
Goodness.
You never know.
During the day,
a hysterical director and a mysterious swindler at night.
Like Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde.
He could be someone like that.
I'd like to ask you a favour.
Can I check the footage on elevator three...
around 10am yesterday?
There. Stop.
Can you zoom in to that man?
That's Louis.
But he's dead.
Who is that beggar?
Hot fish cake soup on a rainy day.
Isn't this great? What do you think?
I love it.
Now, let me get your story straight.
When you woke up that day,
you were wearing this fake jacket which belongs to Bok Nam,
and sleeping next to a scary homeless man.
You didn't remember anything before that, right?
That's anaplastic amnesia.
Didn't you have any wounds on your head?
Yes. I think this part was swollen.
Oh, my gosh.
A part of your brain was probably injured by physical damage.
- Are you a doctor?
- No.
Hey. Do you really have three dollars only?
Are you sure that the girl you live with is a cleaner at Goldline?
She will get money soon.
Now, let me see.
Gosh. You look like a rich boy.
You also have great skin.
I'm 100 percent sure that you're from a rich family.
Are you a fortune-teller?
A fortune-teller? No. I'm not.
What do you do then?
- I'm a job seeker.
- What?
I said I'm a job seeker.
What's that?
Don't you know what a job seeker is?
I'm looking for a job. I spend my day studying.
That's why I know many things.
Ma'am. Can I have some more fish cake soup, please?
- You can get as much as you want.
- Wow.
Malnutrition?
Goodness.
(VIP PATIENT'S ROOM)
Ko Bok Sil...
Here it is. What?
She has no money. How can she be a VIP patient?
Who are you?
Are you Bok Sil's mother?
No.
I just came to give her this. She left her clothes at the company.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I am not related...
to Bok Sil in any way.
Don't you ask me to take care of her or pay the hospital bills.
I will pay the hospital bills.
Don't worry, and please talk freely.
I heard Bok Sil has been working at our company for a month.
Tomorrow is her payday, so it's been a month.
Bok Sil is hard-working and good at her job,
but she looks a bit shabby maybe because she's poor.
She asks me to let her use my phone, and to find her a place.
Today, she even borrowed money from me.
She also said a swindler took her ginseng that is worth 5,000 dollars.
Gosh, she's a brave girl, but she was crying her eyes out.
I felt bad for her.
What kind of a person deceives a young girl...
who has just moved to Seoul and takes her ginseng?
Someone like that should get thrown at the river,
or get shoved into a fire pit. He must be punished.
No one deceived...
her.
You're being a little strange.
Why are you taking the swindler's side?
I'm just saying everyone has their side of the story.
That jerk should have called her at least.
She called him a million times.
That jerk. I will kill him if I ever see him.
You... You swindler!
- Give me my ginseng back.
- I'm not a swindler.
Calm down, all right?
Why am I here?
You suddenly passed out.
What are you doing?
Right. I remember you flinging me to the ground.
What are you talking about?
I never flung you to the ground...
or took your ginseng without paying.
Here. Open it. You said you'd sell it at 1,000 dollars,
but I'm paying you the proper price.
- Mr Cha.
- It's 4,000 after the commission.
There's transaction fee to every product in this world.
That's the rule. Don't cry over it.
Mr Cha. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
From now on, I'm not a swindler, but the saviour of your ginseng.
- Who am I again?
- The saviour of my ginseng.
That's right. The saviour of your ginseng.
Start working at the merchandising department from next week.
Okay. What? Hold on.
- What did you just say?
- The merchandising department.
Don't you understand me?
What is that place?
- Look, I...
- Stop complaining.
Who am I?
The saviour of my ginseng.
Just do what your saviour says. I'll be going now.
Rest up during the weekend. Eat a lot of meat.
Bok Sil!
Why are you so late? I've been waiting forever.
Hey. I found the swindler... No. I found the saviour of my ginseng.
- What?
- Surprise!
What's this?
Oh, my gosh.
Where did you find him?
At the company. Isn't that amazing?
I was going to find him for you, but you already did.
Just try to bring your memory back and find Bok Nam for me.
Okay. I'll find Bok Nam for you no matter what.
- You can trust me.
- You're so reliable.
- What is this?
- It's hotteok.
Doesn't it smell nice?
Let's eat. I'm hungry.
Why are you eating outside? It's night-time.
There is a bug inside.
A bug? Where is it?
Where?
- Where is it?
- Why isn't it there?
- There is no bug.
- Goodness.
- What?
- There...
It has so many legs.
Hey.
This is a house centipede. It's a good bug.
Don't touch it!
Are you okay now?
Bok Sil.
Have we met before?
What are you talking about? Did that hotteok make you go crazy?
It's late.
Let's go to sleep. We have a lot to do tomorrow.
I don't have an appetite.
Ms Choi, you must eat.
You might pass out at this rate.
Ms Choi.
Would you like the breakfast that Mr Louis used to have?
- What Louis used to have?
- Bring it over.
As rice is important to Koreans,
you told me to always serve him rice in the morning.
Is this the breakfast...
- Louis used to have?
- Yes, Ma'am.
We always served him organic and natural food without preservatives.
What are you doing?
Do you want me...
to hit you and get bruised?
Or do you want to get a nosebleed...
and feel the bone break in your nose?
Did I do something wrong?
Stay out of Ms Choi's food.
If you ever show off again,
you'll find out what it feels like...
to lose all of your teeth.
All right?
Ms Heo.
Yes, Ma'am.
Hey.
You are a handful.
Do you like it that much?
Let's get some household goods after eating.
Do you mean shopping?
Goodness.
Bok Sil.
(FRYING PAN)
Bok Sil, that one.
Sir?
Sir, please give us this one.
Gosh, Bok Sil.
I love it here.
Me, too.
Hey, how come...
you're so good at shopping?
You have a good eye.
They talk to me. They ask me to buy them.
You're definitely crazy.
Let's go shopping for clothes. I have a reputation to keep.
I can't keep wearing this imitation.
Where did your brother find such a jacket?
I bought it for him for 20 dollars.
No, no.
It was part of Louis Ssaton's SS collection.
As a limited edition,
additional 100 jackets were launched.
These jackets were numbered...
from 1 to 100.
The jacket with number 1 is over 10,000 dollars.
I have no idea what you're saying.
What I mean is...
You don't know too many things.
Look who's talking.
I have to go shopping now.
Ta-da.
Do I look okay?
It looks cute on you.
Wow, you look pretty.
We haven't even bought rice, but we already bought so much.
Oh, let's buy mobile phones.
With a mobile phone,
we can buy anything we need while lying down at home.
They even deliver goods to your home.
There's no such thing.
Are you stupid?
Who are you calling stupid?
Look, everyone is using a mobile phone.
You can do anything with that.
Look, you can shop, watch TV,
take photos and make phone calls.
Buy me a mobile phone.
I'm the only one who doesn't have it in my class.
You can use the internet, chat with friends,
watch TV and play all kinds of mobile games.
Please, Bok Sil.
You're saying the same thing Bok Nam said.
That's right. Bok Nam.
If he has a mobile phone, you can track down his location.
Really?
These two phones are under your name, Ma'am.
Thank you.
What did you do?
Stop it. Stop!
Gosh, stop it.
Goodbye.
Bok Sil.
What now?
Please help me. It's so exhausting.
- Gosh.
- You eat so much.
Where does all the energy go? Give it to me.
- I've never felt like this before.
- Feel like what?
It's heavy, my arms hurt, I'm sweating and short on breath.
Gosh, it's exhausting.
Hello.
- You startled me. In Sung.
- Hello.
You must be Bok Sil.
He's our neighbour. He lives downstairs.
Yes, hello.
I'm In Sung. Jo In Sung.
- Hello.
You're prettier than I thought.
You look tough, too.
Are you in your early 20s?
You don't wear make-up?
- No.
- I see.
Isn't he amazing?
He's not a fortune-teller, but he knows a lot.
What was it? He's a job...
A job... What was it again?
Gosh.
- I'm a job seeker.
- What?
I'm a job seeker.
A job seeker?
Oh, you're looking for jobs.
Isn't that awesome?
- Did you go shopping?
- Yes.
- We couldn't carry any more.
- I see.
Do you want me to help you?
(MAXIM GOLD)
- Please deliver them to here.
- Okay.
Detective.
I'll give you my number.
You finally bought one.
This is great. Did you get your salary?
Yes, I got paid and got money for ginseng too.
Bok Sil, you'll finally live properly.
Detective.
I heard if you have a mobile phone, you can find Bok Nam.
Please find him.
Bok Sil.
It's the other way around.
Bok Nam has to have a mobile phone for us to track him.
Is that so?
Well, how is the homeless guy? Is he okay to handle?
Guys, you have a delivery.
Wow, this is a great partition.
We have a plastic one. Yours is much prettier.
Why did she put up a curtain?
- Have you never used this before?
- No.
I used to make a fire in the furnace.
Furnace?
- The one you burn firewood?
- Yes.
Bok Sil does everything so well.
Look how quick her hands are.
She's very mature for her age.
I know, right? She will make a great maid.
- A maid?
- Yes.
Goodness.
What does it say?
- What are you doing?
- Take a look at them.
They have an English writing on the back.
"Louis"? Give me.
This is a designer label.
- It has gems on it. Gosh.
- Really?
What? This brand doesn't make underwear.
How do you know that?
"Louis"... Louis.
Louis.
Maybe that's your name.
Bok Sil. He's not in the army.
No one has their name on their underwear.
But the name Louis suits you. You should name yourself that.
- Should I?
- Yes.
Louis.
Mum. Did Louis have a twin brother?
What are you talking about? He was an only child.
Were there any secrets about his birth?
Maybe he had a twin brother or just a brother.
Ma Ri. What's going on?
I saw a beggar at the company who looked just like Louis.
Unless he reincarnated as a beggar, it's not him.
It must be just someone who looks similar.
Go ahead. I need to go to my office to take care of...
some urgent business.
You can drive, right?
Okay.
He just left.
Louis is dead.
Louis.
Gosh, it's so good.
- It's undercooked.
- I don't mind.
- That's mine.
- Finding's keeping.
It will burn. Flip it.
Look.
I will be...
working at Merchandising Department from tomorrow.
What do people do there?
- I thought you were a cleaner.
- Well...
Someone with a high rank told me to start working there.
Is that the saviour of your ginseng?
That's just a trick before he fires you.
- What?
- Many companies use that trick.
He wants to fire you, but it will make him look bad.
He also needs to pay compensation.
If you insist that you won't leave,
that will be so much trouble for the company.
That's when they move you to a whole different department.
What would happen?
You'll be bad at your job, become passive and won't be able to fit in.
You'll feel like you're useless,
and your self-esteem will hit rock bottom.
You will end up quitting even if they ask you not to.
Are you saying he moved Bok Sil to another department to fire her?
That's right. That's more convenient for the company.
- Bok Sil. Cut the meat.
- Okay.
Come on. He could've just fired her. Why would he go through all that?
I think he recruited her because she's good at her job.
What a beautiful young man. Did you have a sheltered life?
But he paid for my ginseng.
He may be an honest and kind-hearted man.
Maybe because you lived in the backwoods,
you have no idea how things work.
You accused him as a swindler. He just paid you to keep you silent.
I guess you wouldn't know how the big companies work.
Goodness. I thought it was strange that you didn't ask for food.
- Hi, Mum.
- You were eating here.
It's pork belly.
I like pork neck better.
- Please eat up.
- All right.
You should cook it a bit longer.
Hey. Don't you have any sauce?
I'll go and get it.
Eat up, Mum.
- This is delicious.
- It is.
Bok Sil should eat it.
How petty. It's just a few pieces of meat.
Fine. I won't eat it.
You're so cheap. Gosh.
Are you leaving already?
Your burden won't let me eat. I'll just go home.
Burden? Me?
You are, aren't you?
Thanks for the meal.
- Goodbye.
- See you.
It's fine.
There are still four pieces left.
- Mum.
- Yes?
Don't you think they're a little slow?
Look who's talking.
You've been jobless for 10 years saying you'll study...
and become a public official. You're just a big idler.
You're not so quick-witted yourself.
Go out and make even just a dollar.
It's my wish that you buy me a meal with the money you make.
Bok Sil. Are you asleep?
No.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking about Bok Nam.
Bok Nam loves meat.
I wonder if he's eating well. I'm worried.
If my memory comes back,
I will find your brother for you. Trust me.
Okay.
We don't have a closet,
or a refrigerator.
We still have a lot to buy.
I'll order them all,
so don't worry and go to sleep.
You have to go to work tomorrow.
Good night,
Louis.
"Louis".
She called my name.
Why are you following me?
Don't you say you want to come with me.
I like the flower pattern,
but the fabric and the design are so old-fashioned.
Yes. Indeed.
- Wear the one you bought yesterday.
- No.
Wow. She is actually quite stubborn.
Hey. Are you here to get on the bus with me?
Wear this at least.
Details like this are what completes a look.
This makes your old-fashioned style look better.
It looks great on you.
Have a good day!
Don't come home late!
Hello!
Oh, you're that cleaning lady who was taken to the emergency room.
Yes.
- Are you here to clean our office?
- Well...
Good morning, Mr Cha.
Ms Ko Bok Sil here will be working with us starting today.
Say hello to everyone.
Oh, right. I'm Ko Bok Sil.
I look forward to working with you.
Mr Lee. You said we're short-staffed, right?
- Yes, but...
- Ms Ko will...
take care of our administrative tasks,
- so use her help wisely.
- Okay.
- Do Jin.
- Yes.
Go to the support team's office and get a laptop for Ms Ko.
Sure.
Go fill out your forms and get your employee card.
Follow him.
Okay.
We'll have her intern with us for a month...
and decide whether to hire her on a full-time basis or not,
so consider yourselves informed.
- Prepare for the meeting at 10am.
- Okay.
Sure thing.
What is this preposterous situation?
Goodness gracious.
Does Mr Cha have a crush on her or something?
- No way!
- Mr Lee, that is nonsense.
I heard that you're working on promotions for the fall.
Yes.
We're launching a mobile UI with a more curated product selection,
so we want them to coincide with the launch.
That sounds great.
- Will Sunny Land open in October?
- Yes.
We're doing our best to create a one-stop destination...
- for shopping and entertainment.
- All right.
I'll get back to work, then.
Oh, right.
I heard something strange from the human resources team.
They told me that you hired one of our cleaning staff as an intern.
What if people gossip and complain?
She's hired for a month on a trial basis as we were short-staffed.
I think we can try grooming her into a merchandiser.
You don't know how to use computers?
No.
Then do you know how to use the internet?
I used it a little bit in middle school.
How can we hire someone like her?
She doesn't even know how to use computers or the internet.
It's like hiring an illiterate for a position at a publishing company.
She must've used mobile shopping applications at least. Right?
Do you own a mobile phone?
Yes! I bought it yesterday. I've tried making calls.
- Oh, my.
- Here.
Bok Sil, I need you to do an errand for me.
Get an iced dark mocha with no caffeine.
Just one.
- I want an iced Americano.
- Then I'll get matcha latte.
I'll get an iced Americano, too. I want a large one.
I'd like strawberry cream frapp.
I want caramel macchiato. The standard size, please.
(ICED AMERICANO? DARK MOCHA? STRAWBERRY... MACCHIATO?)
(WHAT SIZE?)
(WHAT?)
- Well, I can go with...
- I'll go with you.
Bok Sil, I'll help you.
If you have any questions,
please feel free to ask me.
Let's go.
My goodness.
Ms Baek is just too amazing.
She's so kind-hearted, too.
She has everything. She's just flawless!
It's so hard to be pretty, competent and kind at the same time.
She's too perfect.
All women at this company want to be like her.
- I'd like whipped cream on it.
- Sure, that's no problem.
- Would you like everything to go?
- Yes.
Just a moment, please.
Hello. I'd like one strawberry cream frapp...
and one iced dark mocha.
I also need 1 matcha latte and 2 iced Americanos.
One of them has to be large.
I need a standard size of caramel macchiato, as well.
Louis Ssaton... Louis Carlos.
Louis XIV.
- Gosh, there's nothing about me.
- Louis!
Louis, you should eat.
It's lunchtime.
Oh, look at this!
Fried eggs and doenjang stew.
- It's mine.
- There are two bowls of rice.
Let's just eat it. Dinner is on me.
How did you know that I'd have lunch ready?
I can tell from Bok Sil's face.
She's certainly the type to prepare food for her room-mate...
before going to work.
Impressive.
Hey, you need a rice cooker.
Then you'll be able to eat warm rice at every meal.
Gosh, I must say...
that Bok Sil is...
such a great cook. Everything is so delicious.
You're such a lucky guy.
Doesn't your mum cook for you?
She does.
Only once in a while, though.
Oh my goodness.
Gosh, I'm so full. I feel like throwing up.
Do you have coffee here?
I do, but I don't have any hot water.
You just have to boil water.
How do I do it?
My goodness. Who are you, really?
Buy a stove and an electric kettle.
With a proper stove, Bok Sil will be able...
to make side dishes and soup at the same time.
And an electric kettle is so handy for boiling water.
You're so knowledgeable.
How can you know nothing about kitchen equipment?
It must mean that you've never had to do these things.
Louis.
By any chance,
were you locked up somewhere and only ate what someone gave you?
No.
He exudes too much luxurious vibe.
He looks too healthy for that.
Yes.
He could be a spoiled kid from a super wealthy family.
Here, this is for you.
I'm so amazed every time I drink this.
It's honestly so delicious.
A super wealthy family? Forget it.
The chairwoman's grandson.
You know that he died from an accident, right?
I guess you really never know what life can throw at you.
I heard that he was very young, too.
Yes. He was only 25 years old.
- I used the plum preserves. Try it.
- Sure.
I got a wedding invitation from Sang Yeob for next month.
When is Joong Won...
going to meet someone he likes and get married?
Here.
Just a second, please! Gosh!
Gosh, I'm sorry.
You could've taken the next one. Why did you run in like that?
Is someone waiting for you at home or what?
How did he know?
- Don't run inside the building.
- Okay, I won't.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Take care.
(BOOK THE MOST ROMANTIC GETAWAY IN EUROPE.)
Bok Sil. Bok Sil, come over here.
Did I live here? It looks so familiar.
What?
If you turn at the end of that alley,
you'll find a caf called Petit Queue.
Their coffee and croissants are so delicious.
- Really?
- It's amazing.
Louis! Bok Sil!
Have a look at this. You have to work,
so you don't have time to look for your brother. Aren't I right?
Hence, Louis and I founded a company to find Bok Nam.
We'll go around all the heavily populated areas in Seoul...
and distribute flyers.
Louis will also sing from time to time.
"Please help us find Bok Nam." Like this.
It'll be like an event. Isn't it a good idea?
You can join us on weekends or after work.
Really?
We'll need 30 dollars a day...
to pay for our lunch and travel expenses.
- You'll have to pay us for that.
- Of course.
We won't charge you for the work we do.
We'll just think of it as doing some volunteer work.
Thank you so much.
- You're so thoughtful.
- Gosh, don't mention it.
That's what neighbours are for.
I'm doing it because I don't think his memory will come back soon.
Oh, right. You just need to sign here.
- Sure.
- Write "Ko Bok Sil".
(KO BOK SIL)
Perfect. That's great.
Louis. You remember the song I taught you earlier, right?
Do you want to sing it for Bok Sil?
- All right. In 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I'm too shy.
She won't pay us, then. Just do it.
In 1, 2, 3, 4.
"Please help us find Bok Nam". In 1, 2, 3, 4!
- I don't know...
- Goodness.
Mum. Eat slowly, okay?
- Where will you be working?
- What?
It's a start-up company dedicated to promoting creative economy.
I can work flexible hours and get a lot of benefits, too.
Above all, they trust me immensely.
I even got paid in advance.
- It sounds like a great company.
- Yes.
You're finally going to work after being out of job for 10 years.
- I'm proud of you. Come here.
- Okay.
Great job. I'm so proud of you.
Hello, please help us find this person.
- Thank you.
Hello.
(LOOKING FOR A MISSING PERSON!)
Goodness. Hello, please help us. Thank you.
All right. We're done for the day.
- Let's go home, Louis.
- Already?
- Yes, why not?
- Help us find him.
If you don't want to go home right away,
we could stop by the market over there.
- Market?
- Are you in? Great, let's go.
How much is this?
- It's three dollars.
- Take a look.
Sir, what about that one?
- This is cool.
- In Sung, try this on.
Ta-da.
How do I look?
Oh, my.
Wow.
- There you go.
- Wow!
This is totally my style.
- In Sung.
- Yes?
- What do you think?
- The colour is fantabulous.
What does that mean?
I'd like to get that one, please.
- Look at this.
- In Sung, this is crazy.
You can get dressed from head to toe with 10 dollars.
I'm more amazed by you, Mr Shopping Expert.
That's some special skill you got there.
You have such a great eye.
- I want to know who I used to be.
- I'm curious, too.
Who are you, seriously?
Starting today, I'm going to call you the King of Shopping.
King of Shopping? It sounds familiar for some reason.
He's overreacting again.
- Louis!
- People like him take flattery...
- way too seriously.
- Louis.
(GOLD DEPARTMENT STORE)
Louis, what's the matter?
Are you feeling sick?
I have a splitting headache.
- My chest hurts, too.
- Gosh, does it hurt a lot?
Louis. What can I do?
He doesn't have a fever.
I don't know what it is, but he wouldn't let it go,
so I bought it with my personal emergency stash.
They wanted 50 dollars for it because it's limited-edition.
I'd like to be compensated for it.
"Gold Department Store"?
It's beautiful.
Louis used to love this beach.
Koboshi, here. It's here.
Here. Come here. This way.
Koboshi? What does that mean?
He wouldn't tell me. He keeps saying that it's a secret.
Thanks to Koboshi,
Ji Sung laughs a lot these days. It makes me so happy.
Did you say that Koboshi lived for 14 years?
We buried him in a sunny spot.
It was stressful because Mr Louis didn't eat for a month after that.
I should thank Koboshi.
He stayed by Louis' side in my place.
Shall I grill some ham for you?
Bok Sil. This is 1 of the 30 limited-edition music boxes...
Gold Department Store made 18 years ago...
to celebrate their 30th anniversary.
- It tells you all that?
- Yes.
How's your headache?
You should just stay home today if you're still feeling unwell.
Don't go out.
No, I should do my best to find Bok Nam.
Why do you keep following me around?
It's because I like you.
What are you talking about? You're making me blush.
I knew it.
(HANUL SEARCH)
(GOLD DEPARTMENT STORE)
(GOLD GROUP'S HEIR DIES FROM AN ACCIDENT.)
So Gold Department Store and this company belong to the same group.
The chairwoman's grandson...
died.
I see, that was from a car accident.
Bok Sil.
You're slacking off already?
- I'm sorry.
- Every second and minute matters,
yet you're just browsing on the internet.
Do you want to be let go after your probationary month...
and clean for the rest of your life?
No.
Bring the list of companies we'll be meeting with today...
- as well as the schedule.
- Okay.
In Sung, let's go to work.
Just a moment.
Hello?
I'm calling from Financial Supervisory Service.
Did you lose anything that contains your personal information...
such as your wallet, identification card or passport recently?
Yes, I did. Do you have my identification card?
Yes! I do!
What is my name?
What should I say?
Goodness!
Your name is Song Joong Ki.
Song Joong Ki?
I see. My name is Song Joong Ki.
Where are you? I'll meet you there.
Wait, Sir! Please listen to me first.
Well, a fraud ring tried to scam people using your name,
and there are a few victims who fell for their tricks.
If we fail to have them settle right away,
Mr Song yourself could get arrested.
Arrested?
You'll need to send all the cash you currently have...
to a designated bank account.
Please stay on the phone with me...
and go to a bank nearby with your debit card right away.
This investigation is confidential,
so you must not tell anyone about it.
Please go alone.
Will I be able to get...
my identification card back after the case is settled?
Of course.
What's my address written on it?
You live in Cheongdam-dong.
Are you at the bank yet?
Yes, I just arrived.
Louis! Let's go, Louis.
Louis!
Louis! Did he step out?
The number you're calling is busy at the moment.
Please leave a message after the tone...
(2,000 DOLLARS, WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRANSFER THE AMOUNT ABOVE?)
I just sent it.
Nice!
That is awesome.
Mr Song, you're free now!
Then where should I go now?
Go home! Where else would you go?
What? Hello?
Hello?
"High-quality Brand Day".
It's so wrong that the discount is exclusive to Nara cardholders only.
What should people like me with no credit cards do?
King of Shopping, Louis.
"King of Shopping, Louis"?
I guess he's not home yet.
Oh, he didn't eat anything.
Don't look for me.
What? "Don't look for me"?
What is he up to? He really is a man of mystery.
Does he not want to be found?
Sorry? Are you saying...
that he left? He doesn't even have anywhere to go.
He probably just wants some alone time. Leave him be.
Why, though?
Did something happen?
You said that your phone is under Bok Sil's name.
How can Bok Sil be Song Joong Ki?
I didn't know. I really had no idea.
I just wanted to know who I was. That's all.
Go catch it!
Koboshi?
Koboshi.
Koboshi!
(FIRE HYDRANT)
Koboshi.
Koboshi, come over here. Koboshi.
- Koboshi!
- What?
Subtitles by VIU
(SHOPAHOLIC LOUIS)
Where did you even find him?
Shall I kick him out for you?
You're uselessly handsome.
He acts like he's from a rich family sometimes.
Honey, I saw Louis.
Kang Ji Sung died from a car accident that day.
- Stop the car. Now!
- What are we doing?
- Is he seeing someone?
- Who is he dating?
- Did Bok Sil leave?
- What's wrong, Bok Sil?
I'm just so happy.
Bok Sil.