I'm sorry for breaking our agreement.
I'll return the refrigerator and washer to you if you'd like,
but that will make...
Bok Sil's life much more difficult.
Do whatever you want, Mr Cha Joong Won.
What a sneaky brat.
Just wait until I catch you.
Bok Sil.
Why am I unbearably uncomfortable?
My name is Ko Bok Sil. Ko Bok Sil.
I want to know...
what it is that I'm feeling.
(EPISODE 7)
(ROYAL POOL HALL)
Go to Royal Pool Hall after 10pm.
He plays billiards and sleeps there 3 to 4 times a week.
Excuse me.
Bok Nam.
What? Goodness.
Excuse me.
What's going on? Are you looking for someone?
Do you know Ko Bok Nam?
I'm his older sister.
I haven't seen him for over a month.
Do you know where he is now?
How would I know that?
Bok Nam stopped coming here. Stop bothering me and get out.
Is it Bok Sil?
- Gosh, she's so persistent.
- Block her calls.
Where is Bok Nam?
His sister is looking for him.
Please clear the way for us.
Please move out of the way.
Please clear the way.
Oh, that's where I live.
My goodness. Another person died in that rooftop room.
My gosh, is it that handsome guy?
That's what I heard. I can't believe this.
Please wait.
- Wait a second.
- Are you his family?
- I'm his guardian.
- Please get in.
Louis. Wake up.
What's going on?
Why do these things keep happening in our neighbourhood?
Gosh, tell me about it.
Did something happen?
Gosh. In that rooftop room,
- a burglar killed someone.
- What?
- Bok Sil.
- You're not allowed to go in.
I live here.
Louis. Where have you been?
- What happened?
- I don't know.
A stranger was found dead in your place.
- It's not Bok Sil, is it?
- Goodness.
- My phone is ringing.
- You can't go in.
- Could you bring me my phone?
- I can't touch the incident scene.
Why isn't he answering?
Hello, Bok Sil? Louis? He's here with me.
Where are you?
That's my question. Where on earth have you been?
I went out to pick you up.
- You're okay, right?
- Of course. Where are you?
- I'm on an ambulance.
- What?
Are you hurt? Where? How bad is it?
I'm not hurt, so please stop yelling.
Don't go anywhere else.
- Just say in In Sung's place.
- Okay.
What did she say?
- She told me to stay in your place.
- Okay.
Excuse me. Do you live here?
Yes.
Where have you been?
I went to the bus stop.
What's your name?
- It's Louis.
- What's your family name?
I don't know.
How can you not know your name?
Sir. He recently had a memory loss.
He doesn't know who he is, where he is from or what he used to do.
The police said his fingerprints aren't registered.
What is it?
Just say you're sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'll take your fingerprints for now.
How did it go?
Go on and take a look.
(93-5, EUNSUNG-RO)
(KO BOK SIL, 93-5 EUNSUNG-RO)
Is this the place Bok Sil has been living?
- Are you okay?
- I don't feel very well.
I understand.
Louis.
- Detective.
- Are you okay?
Where is Bok Sil? Where is she?
- She's on her way here.
- Gosh. If I had known,
I would've done something.
Why didn't you tell me about this place?
- We didn't know.
- I didn't know, either.
By the way, who is this?
I'm Jo In Sung, his downstairs neighbour.
- He's a job seeker.
- Hey. Goodness.
I think job seekers are cool.
I found out who died instead of Louis.
It was Ko Bok Sil's brother.
You know her, right? Mr Cha hired her in our department.
Apparently, Louis was wearing her brother's jacket.
Don't be surprised.
Louis is staying with Bok Sil right now.
She's taking care of him so she can find her brother.
Isn't Joong Won involved in that matter?
Why would he be?
Then why did Joong Won go in and out of their place?
Hello?
Do you know the owner of this phone?
He is having an emergency surgery.
He didn't have his ID card, so we don't know his name or address.
Hello? Are you listening?
Where did he get hurt? How bad is it?
He had a severe head injury.
What on earth is going on now?
(SEOUL MAPO POLICE STATION)
I see. Thank you.
Sir.
I can't identify the victim who is currently having a surgery.
He may be an illegal immigrant.
- Check his mobile phone.
- It's probably a burner phone.
Check the call history and find out whose phone it is.
I'll go to the hospital and see if his phone is there.
Maybe it's inside his clothes. I'll be back soon.
- Hey.
- Yes, Sir.
- What about the weapon we found?
- They're verifying fingerprints.
Come in.
Ms Hwang. You can't do this to us.
I heard you kept it a secret from us.
If I were home, I would be in the hospital now.
I'm sorry.
It's so scary to think that I almost died today.
I said I'm sorry.
That's why I'm letting you two stay here.
- In Sung. Get the blankets.
- Okay.
I should've told you.
I thought the same thing wouldn't happen again.
I just thought it'd be better. You would've been terrified if you knew.
That's right, Louis.
You must've left this place if she told you.
- Ouch.
- I wouldn't do that.
Gosh, you brat. You're more loyal than I thought.
You worry about Bok Sil.
It's fine as long as everyone is okay.
By the way, where have you been, Bok Sil?
We've been looking all over for you.
I went out because...
some girls said they would tell me where Bok Nam is if I pay them.
So? Did you meet Bok Nam?
He wasn't there.
- How much did you pay them?
- 1,000 dollars.
- What?
Is it your job to get conned?
Why are you all so dumb?
Bok Sil. You should've told me about this first.
- I'm the smart one, you know.
- Are you kidding right now?
- You're no better.
- I know.
Thinking that I have to take care of all of you...
makes me feel so hopeless.
Oh, dear me. What a fate.
Goodness.
Bok Sil. I'll get that money back for you.
- Just trust me.
- Okay.
Gosh, this is so frustrating.
Do you really trust him?
Why would you trust the things someone so dumb like him says?
Leave them be.
They have some kind of...
a belief system that you'd never understand. Just go to sleep.
Gosh. I'll get sick just by looking at you.
By the way,
was the man on the ambulance the burglar?
Why would someone burgle someone so poor like you?
Who is the person who attacked the burglar?
Hold on.
It can't be the same criminal who hasn't been caught yet, can it?
Maybe a serial killer does live in our neighbourhood.
This is the third incident.
Gosh, it gives me the chills.
Oh, right. Why did the policeman...
ask me so many questions?
I know. That didn't feel good.
Hey. What if...
- they're suspecting you?
- What?
What?
- Go to sleep!
- Yes, Ma'am.
I'm at the crime scene in Eunsung-dong.
Gosh, I've never seen such a mess.
It's full of reporters and cameras outside.
This alley is already so small.
It'll be full of people now.
The fact that I'm at the heart of the scene...
which everyone is talking about excites me so much.
It's so overwhelming.
What's so exciting about that?
Bok Sil, I want some ham.
Ms Hwang.
Do you have any ham?
I want some Maxim Gold coffee before that.
Where's the coffee?
Gosh, will you look at him?
- Look how picky he is.
- Pardon me?
You aren't the only one eating.
It's so delicious.
Bok Sil, I want some water.
I want some more ham.
- Do you have cold water?
- Cold water?
I want to have some fish for dinner.
Hey!
You do all kinds of things, don't you?
(MAID 1, 2, 3)
Goodness, bring the rag. I have to clean up now.
- I want fish.
- Gosh, why you...
Regarding the Eunsung-dong attack,
the police think it could be a serial murder...
since two similar incidents happened in the area 3 and 6 months ago...
and are carrying out the investigation.
However, it was found that the victim who was injured...
and underwent a surgery yesterday...
was not the resident at the scene of the crime.
It's expected to cause confusion in the police investigation.
As soon as we receive updates...
- The police said...
- That place...
seems familiar for some reason.
Don't say that. You're scaring me.
What a scary world.
- Always be careful, Ma Ri.
- Sure.
The police assume that the culprit...
- could be a serial killer.
- Our neighbourhood should be okay.
- It should be.
- Right.
- It's so scary.
- Currently, the police are...
Dad, are you okay?
You don't look well.
Honey, go to Busan for a while.
To Mother's?
Make sure Mother doesn't watch the news.
If she's about to watch the news, switch the channel.
Why? Why shouldn't she watch the news?
Just do as I say.
- Don't ask why.
- What's the problem now?
On the way to Busan. It's a lonely journey.
She travels by herself.
What does she do?
- Honey, look at this photo.
- What?
- Is it a selfie taken in the car?
- Yes.
Is a chauffeur driving? The seat looks high-quality, too.
- Look at it.
- It's a nice car.
She's a VVIP at a department store.
She must be very rich. What might her husband do?
I'll dig into it next time we meet.
Is it going well? Do you want some help?
No, I'm fine. I'll do all the cooking.
You just focus on your phone.
Sir.
All the numbers on the call history are registered under someone else.
What if the person in the hospital is a hitman?
- Is he awake yet?
- No, he's still unconscious.
Sir.
We received the fingerprint results from National Forensic Service.
- The fingerprints belong to one.
- Whose?
Louis, the tenant of the rooftop. He's had a memory loss.
A memory loss?
He was at the scene of the crime yesterday.
I got his fingerprints because I couldn't check his identification.
- These are the results.
- Since when did he live there?
- He...
- It hasn't been long.
Just a little over a month.
- How do you know that?
- I know him.
He's not the culprit.
He's not daring enough to do such thing.
I don't care. Bring Louis here.
Let's get this over with.
You don't know your name. You don't know your age.
You have no occupation.
Your address is the scene of the crime.
At the time of the crime,
you went to the bus stop,
but you have no alibi.
You left your cell phone at home, right?
I absolutely didn't do it.
The hammer was covered with your fingerprints.
How will you explain that?
I used it to peel garlic.
How do you peel garlic with a hammer?
I thought it'd work. It was my first time peeling a garlic.
I'm not a bad person.
Detective.
He can't even kill an insect.
It's true.
You should rest at home on your day off.
Why would you go and exercise?
Go ahead and eat. I added some ice.
Okay, thank you.
- You must have made it.
- It's delicious, isn't it?
- Yes.
- You didn't add plum extract?
- I forgot.
- How could you forget that?
- I'm done.
- I'm done, too.
You're done already?
Joong Won.
Between you and the naked boy at yours...
There is nothing going on, right?
I told you many times. I just took him in out of pity.
He moved out, so I don't live with him any more.
Young Ae, let's stop bothering him...
and watch television instead.
- That sounds good.
- Okay.
I wonder if the suspect is caught.
- It's the talk of the town.
- As you can see, the crime scene...
is crowded with investigators and reporters.
The crime that took place in this rooftop room...
- is the same place...
- That's Bok Sil's place.
Where murder cases happened 3 and 6 months ago.
The police assume the culprit...
- could commit another crime soon, - Bok Sil, where are you right now?
And are carrying out an investigation.
What?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Are you back again?
How old am I?
I'm 21 years old,
so maybe 20?
Am I younger than you?
You behave like a little kid,
but because of your face, I think you could be 20.
Bok Sil.
Not knowing myself...
is a really scary thing.
Perhaps,
I'm a bad criminal.
You could've been a monk who doesn't know about this world.
What if I was being chased by loan sharks?
I bet you were someone rich who spent a lot of money.
- I might be an orphan.
- I think...
a good family took care of you.
I could be married and have a wife.
I hope that isn't the case.
Someone with all possibilities and impossibilities.
That's me.
Louis.
You're kind, beautiful and lovely.
I can just tell.
Everyone shows...
his past self in the present.
Bok Sil.
Hey, what are you doing?
Thank you.
Look, everyone. Isn't it good to be young?
You're right.
Wow, that's great.
- Be quiet.
- Look at them.
Stay away from her!
Oh, my. Mr Cha.
His fingerprints were found on the weapon,
and he can't prove his alibi.
Can't you check the location of his mobile phone then?
He left his phone at home that night.
We thought maybe it was an excessive self-defence,
but the means of the crime is the same as for the last two incidents.
More importantly, we can't be sure of his past.
- Do you know he had a memory loss?
- Of course.
I'll be his personal reference.
I said I'll be his personal reference as well.
- I told you. It's not them.
- Detective.
Bok Sil. You'll be fine. Don't worry. You, too, Louis.
We can't find the criminal's footprints on our database.
What kind of shoes was he wearing?
Bont Riot's custom thermoformed shoes.
They're cycling shoes.
They thermoform the shoes with carbon fibre according to...
the rider's foot. You won't find the same pattern anywhere.
It's customised.
These.
Those shoes look like these.
Not a lot of place sells those kind of shoes. You can start from there.
Maybe the criminal is someone who is good at cycling.
How did you know all that?
Maybe you were a cyclist.
- Can he try riding your bicycle?
- Can I?
Sure. Go ahead.
Gosh, I can't do this.
You can't even ride a bicycle. How did you know about the shoes?
- Were you into shoes then?
- Was I?
You two will stay in my place for a while.
It's annoying and troublesome, but I'm being generous.
Come with me.
There is something wrong with his personality.
- What are you talking about?
- He's looking at us.
Let's go with him for now.
I should be carrying them.
My body still aches. I'm sorry, Bok Sil.
You still have pain relief patches all over you. I'm fine.
That punk.
I'm not so sure about this.
His place is very nice.
He has a huge fridge and plenty of space.
- He also has a lot of furniture.
- I must be out of my mind.
What am I doing here?
He and I must've been enemies in our past lives.
Darn it.
It's all fixed. You'll like it.
Gosh. Thank you.
Surprise! This is a pink hat. It's your favourite colour.
I love it.
- Do I look good?
- You look great.
Excuse me for interrupting, Ms Hong.
- Can I ask you something privately?
- Me?
- What is it?
- It won't take long.
Why did you touch the box I keep Mr Louis' teeth in?
How did you know that?
It was pretty obvious.
Oh, my.
You said you'll have his watch fixed. Why did you take his tooth?
One of his upper teeth is missing.
That's... Well...
It's something...
my husband asked me to do.
I asked him why,
but he didn't tell me.
Maybe he wanted to keep it as some kind of a charm.
He said it's nothing important.
Why would he do that?
Excuse me?
I heard you asked your wife to bring you Mr Louis' watch and tooth.
She told Mr Kim all about it.
- Hello? Mr Baek?
- Dad. Is everything okay?
Call your mum now.
- Are you listening, Sir?
- Okay.
It's nothing important. Thank you, Ms Heo.
She's not answering.
You have such a great sense of humour.
You laugh at everything, don't you?
Goodness.
Mr Kim. Turn on the TV.
- I should watch the news.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Gosh. It's been a while.
Are you tired? Man up.
Bok Sil. Can you draw me a bath? That's the bathroom.
You should do it. I'll take a bath.
Do it.
Of course.
Would you like a cold bath?
- Make it 36.5℃ hot.
- Yes, Sir.
I'm sorry.
You must know this already. He's a bit slow-witted.
Why are you sorry?
- Stop saying you're sorry.
- Yes, Sir.
- Here.
- Mr Cha.
Thank you so much...
for taking us in.
Stop saying thank you.
If you really want to thank me, let Louis say it.
You can use that room.
Louis can use the room he used before.
I hate it when people get in my way,
so try not to. Do you understand me?
Yes, Sir.
- Tidy these up.
- Okay.
Please get some rest.
Wow.
- Bok Sil. Don't touch my things.
- Yes, Sir.
You can eat anything in the fridge.
Hang out the wash over there.
Separate the recyclables and neatly put them in there.
Pardon?
Hang out the wash over there, and separate the recyclables there.
Yes, Sir.
He told me not to get in his way. Why is he following me around?
Bok Sil. Make the bed with these.
- Okay. Give them to me.
- No. I'll do it.
- Let me do it.
- No, I'll do it.
- Just...
- I said I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- No, I will...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What are you two doing?
Nothing. I was about to make the bed.
Stop. You don't need to explain.
You did nothing wrong.
- For dinner, I'll order some food.
- I'll cook.
Bok Sil.
Don't stay close to Mr Cha.
What are you talking about?
He generously took us in. Be kind to him.
What are you doing?
Give me a massage.
It still hurts here.
Get up now.
The injured victim of this incident hasn't...
recovered his consciousness despite the surgery...
Due to this incident in Eunsung-dong...
The news is just filled with cruel stuff these days.
It's not good for mental health.
Mother, let's watch something else.
Jae Sook, don't change the channel. Just leave it.
Oh, that show you like must be on now.
Shall we watch "Real Story Eye"?
The police think that the suspect...
What made Ms Kim Soon Ja this lonely...
could have been our lack of apathy.
We should give it some deep thought.
- We're waiting to hear from you.
- It's over.
We're looking for this man who was running...
covered in pain relief patches in the afternoon of October 12.
The man was spotted running a distance of about 10km...
from Hyunwoon-dong to Eunsung-dong...
with pain relief patches all over his body.
- What you're seeing now is...
- That guy...
(PLEASE CALL THIS NUMBER IF YOU KNOW HIM.)
Isn't that Louis?
No way. He's dead.
It's probably someone who looks like him.
That line from his neck to his shoulders.
That angle and his body proportions.
My analysis is convincing me that he is Mr Louis.
- What?
- That's impossible.
You think he's Louis?
- Look into it immediately!
- Yes, Ma'am.
Gosh, what is going on?
Louis... Ji Sung...
- Mother.
- Ms Choi.
Mother, please calm down.
- You'll faint again.
- I'll check her blood pressure.
Mother.
Have you two been starving all day?
Order one more bowl for me.
Just eat this, okay?
The meat is too tough.
It tastes like it's been deep-fried three times in oxidised oil.
Stop complaining and just eat it!
Well...
May I also get another bowl of this?
Hello, I'd like to get two more bowls of jjajangmyeon delivered.
Thank you.
- Bok Sil, I want water.
- Okay.
Stop.
Keep eating.
- Oh, no. I'll get a cloth.
- Sit down.
Hey, you go get it!
Okay.
- Move it.
- That hurt.
(BUTLER CHA)
Shall I wash the dishes after?
- No, I'll do it.
- Forget it!
I'll clean the dishes.
Stop bugging me and just go watch television.
Today's episode will be so much fun.
(BUTLER CHA)
What is it about?
That guy has amnesia,
- and she left him.
- Why?
Because he has nothing.
But he turns out to be a rich heir.
Today, she'll find out about it and regret everything terribly.
Doesn't it sound so interesting?
Please make me a cup of Maxim Gold.
Stop it. I'll make it for you.
Bok Sil, just watch television.
- She's furious.
- What?
She's about to pass out.
Why on earth am I doing all this?
Mr Baek, it's me.
Pardon? What did you just say?
We saw...
someone who looks just like Mr Louis on television,
and everyone has been going crazy.
Mr Kim went to Seoul,
- saying that he'll find Mr Louis.
- Mr Kim?
And Ms Choi is finally asleep now.
She had to take a tranquilizer because she was so surprised.
You should try to watch that show online...
or call the broadcasting station.
That guy does look a lot like Mr Louis.
Hello?
Mr Baek, can you hear me?
Mr Baek.
For now,
please focus on looking after Mother.
I have to go.
Honey? I found Louis.
I switched to Channel 11 when we were watching television together,
and some guy who looks like Louis popped up on the screen.
Everyone was at a loss for words because they were so surprised,
but I screamed aloud, "Isn't that Louis?"
Honey, aren't I so awesome?
We were able to watch that show because I changed the channel.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why in the world are you doing this to your husband?
I don't even want to see you, so don't show up before me.
Hello?
Why is he mad at me?
Mr Goo is bedridden,
and the entire country is talking about that incident.
What is this bomb now?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What are you doing here at this hour?
I wanted to soak some rice.
Soaking makes rice taste better.
I'll make breakfast, so you don't need to do anything.
I don't want you touching my stuff.
- I'll do it.
- I said I'll do it.
- I'll just do it.
- I'm going to do it.
- Please let me do it.
- I said I'm going to do it.
- I want to...
- Gosh!
What a waste.
I'll clean it up. You should go to bed.
It's fine. You go to bed.
Mr Cha, may I give you a nickname?
Sweet Churl.
What?
You sound so mean and harsh,
but your actions are actually the opposite.
Where did you learn to be like that?
When was I ever sweet to you? Clean up this mess and make sure...
you don't leave a grain of rice on the floor. Got it?
Okay, I got it. Please don't worry and get a good sleep.
Oh, I'll make breakfast for you tomorrow.
I'm freeloading here, so I should do that at least.
I feel weird.
What is this feeling?
I can't sleep.
Gosh, you startled me.
Why are you already awake?
- I couldn't sleep a wink.
- What?
- Why? Was the bed uncomfortable?
- I felt uneasy in my heart.
What are you talking about?
Shall I give you a hand?
Don't cause trouble if you want to help me. Don't do anything.
I'll just watch you, then.
Hey, go and watch television or something. You're bothering me.
No, I should at least do this.
(EXCLUSIVELY AVAILABLE ON GOLDLINE, LOUIS SSATON 2016 FW COLLECTION)
(YOUR ORDER HAS BEEN COMPLETED. THANK YOU FOR YOUR ORDER.)
Yes! I had to get my hands on it.
Is breakfast ready?
Seriously?
Do all men own that jacket?
I know you see this everywhere, but mine is different.
This is that authentic limited-edition jacket,
and his is obviously a counterfeit.
Take a closer look. Mine is...
a work of art where every stitch was hand-sewn by a craftsman,
whereas this was cheaply made by digital printing.
Now that I'm looking at them...
You're right. They look very different.
My gut is telling me that I probably used to wear Number One.
Whatever.
Thanks for making breakfast, Bok Sil.
All right. Let's eat, guys.
What are you doing right now?
Only I can eat what Bok Sil makes.
- Hey, what is wrong with you?
- What?
Goodness.
Only I am allowed to eat the food you make.
I'm sorry.
- Buy whatever you want to eat.
- I don't want it.
Are you feeling sick? You didn't eat much at breakfast,
and you don't even want your allowance.
- Bok Sil, let's go.
- Okay.
- Where are you going?
- I'll take you to work.
- I'm taking my car.
- That's good.
I have to stop by somewhere anyway.
Isn't his car so cool?
Whatever. Something is telling me that I used to own a cooler car.
Also, I think I used to have about 100 pairs of shoes...
and used to live in a castle-like mansion.
- I see that you like to bluff.
- What did you just say?
Keep it up if you think it's helpful for your mental health. I get it.
Dad.
You look more stressed out than yesterday. What is bothering you?
Is it because of the inaugural ceremony?
Ma Ri, that's not important right now.
- I'm Kim Ho Joon.
- Yes, hello.
I'm sorry to visit you this early, but it's about an urgent matter.
I heard from Mr Kim.
He already met up with the director of the show.
They'll share comments on all social media channels...
and look for that young man together.
The show's production team hasn't received any information yet.
Jung Ran, you should also go to Seoul...
- and help Mr Kim find him.
- Pardon me?
You want me to accompany him?
I don't want to. I'm going to have to say no.
- Do you hate Mr Kim that much?
- Yes, I do.
It's probably because you don't know him well yet. He's a good guy.
He's so smart, too.
He's also very responsible and reliable.
Why is he still single, then?
I guess he hasn't met the right person yet.
Judging from his looks, I think I know the reason.
If you really don't want to go, I can try to persuade Mother...
not to make you go to Seoul.
I must follow Ms Choi's order.
I'll see you soon.
Ms Hwang, I'll do it.
What are you doing?
You do important work now. Don't dirty your hands.
You get backaches, though.
You're so clueless.
If you office workers clean too, I'll lose my job.
Don't creep on my turf...
and just focus on your work.
Okay.
Is living at the director's place going all right?
Does he pick on the two of you by any chance?
Not at all.
I'm not worried about you, but Louis worries me a lot.
He's absolutely clueless, you know.
He's like a little kid. He's such a handful.
- He annoys you, right?
- Yes.
- Give us our money back.
- What is this?
- Who's this prankster?
- What's going on?
What? What does he mean by that?
Don't you know? It's the name of the King from Joseon Dynasty.
Yeongjo, Jeongjo and Donjo. You girls don't know?
Oh, my. You're certainly the smartest one out of us.
I'm so impressed.
Give us our money back. Give us our money back.
- It keeps coming.
- Give us our money back.
- Block the number.
What's wrong?
Hey, did you really have to bombard them with text messages?
That's why they blocked your number.
You didn't even spell correctly.
You frustrate me so much.
You obviously need help from this smart guy here.
Watch this, okay?
Call them again and say this.
"This is Officer Jo In Sung from Financial Supervisory Service."
Don't you remember the phone scam?
This is Officer Jo In Sung from Financial Supervisory Service.
We received a report about a phone scam you recently experienced.
Get lost, you stupid jerk!
Hey, it won't be easy to deal with those girls.
I know, right? I told you. They're scary.
For this upcoming Black Friday,
we'd like to run a big sales event.
Then we should negotiate...
- with the brands we carry.
- That's right.
We need an event to encourage customers to join Goldpay.
Also, think about how we're going to promote the event online.
How about we create a separate tab for the event on the main page?
We'll consider it if many brands confirm their participation.
I sense a serious increase in our workload.
I'll do everything.
One person won't be enough.
Mr Lee.
Once again, you're the first one to detect an increase in our workload.
Seriously, that's such a special talent.
It never ceases to amaze me.
Look into hiring temporary part-timers.
Okay.
You said Louis lives with Ko Bok Sil, right?
That house...
in Eunsung-dong where the murder attempt took place two days ago.
That's where they live.
What? Does that mean Louis is injured?
No, he's fine.
The injured victim is someone else, so don't worry.
First and foremost,
we need to find out where Louis is now.
Asking Ko Bok Sil would be the easiest, right?
Bring it up as naturally as possible.
Bok Sil.
I saw the news. It must've terrified you.
I heard that the suspect hasn't been caught. It must've been so scary.
Thank you for your concern.
Where are you staying now?
You probably had nowhere to go.
Well...
I'm staying with my neighbour downstairs.
- Your neighbour downstairs?
- Yes.
This is so narrow.
Is this where they're staying now?
Does someone actually live here?
Hello, stranger.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
The suspect hasn't been caught. Is there anything you'd like to know?
- Are you a reporter?
- No.
You know that the police think it could be a serial crime, right?
- Are you a police officer?
- No.
I'm...
My name is Jo In Sung. It's very nice to meet you.
I live here.
Who are you by the way?
How is the patient in Room 607 doing?
I'm from the police.
His vitals have been stabilised, but he's still unconscious.
Someone else came by earlier and asked the same thing.
Oh, I guess Detective Kim was here.
Have a great day.
Please take a look at this photo.
Someone wrote that this guy was spotted at this hospital.
He came to the hospital I work at as a patient...
a little while ago and caused a ruckus.
It looks like the nurse, Ms Moon, wrote it.
Where is she now?
She's off today. Please come back tomorrow.
Mr Baek? Mr Baek Seon Goo.
Mr Kim, what brings you here?
What about you, Mr Baek?
Well...
My friend is hospitalised here,
so I came to see him briefly.
I see.
Hey, we have to eat together.
I love this so much.
Is this different from the meat we had the last time?
Yes, it's Korean pork.
I see, Korean pork.
It's so delicious.
Can we eat this again for breakfast tomorrow?
Mr Cha, please come join us. The meat is ready.
- Wait for me.
- Whatever.
Hey.
Hurry up.
There he is.
Whose is this?
- Mine. Give it to me.
- I don't want to.
- Please give it to me.
- No.
I said no.
I said I don't want to.
Hey! Let me see.
You got a burn.
What is this?
What do you think it is?
It's the very first coin you gave me.
Give me your hand.
50 cents for washing dishes.
It's covered in oil now.
Why are you looking at me like that, Bok Sil?
You're a fool.
What? A fool?
You're more like a fool.
- You fool.
- What?
What's your problem, you fool?
And you're smiling now. What a fool.
Let me see. Show me your finger.
- It's red.
- It hurts.
- Show me the coin.
- No!
- Come on.
- I'm embarrassed.
Ouch, my fingers...
(HANGUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL)
It's me.
I just ran into Mr Baek Seon Goo at the hospital.
I'm not sure where he went, though.
Who's here at this late hour?
It's past 11pm.
Mr Baek?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(SHOPAHOLIC LOUIS)
I think Mr Cha has a crush on Bok Sil.
Mr Cha, do you have feelings for Bok Sil?
- Louis showed up at work.
- You must be Bok Sil's boyfriend.
I'm more than that.
I'll never let you go.
I'm flattered, but I can't reciprocate.
You said her brother is dead.
Ma Ri, you should tell her the truth.
I'm going to give you everything you want.
They say that giving shoes is like a parting gift.
Bok Sil. Don't be surprised and listen, okay?
Bok Sil, you're the only one for me.