Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Why are you shopping in the morning? It's tiring.
I feel a little depressed.
Why? Is Mr Cha bothering you?
Is he giving you a hard time?
No, he wouldn't.
I bet he was surprised...
to see himself doing the work that he assigned to others.
You have a talent for making people surprised.
I wonder when I'll get my memory back.
I wonder what my job was.
All of a sudden, I wanted to go to work today.
Don't you feel out of the loop...
in this busy world?
Among so many offices in those tall buildings,
don't you wonder why you aren't working in one of them?
You want to participate no matter what.
Don't you feel a strong desire to join the workforce?
Have you read my mind?
- Who am I again?
- A job seeker.
- What did you say?
This is what job seekers do.
Not only do they study, but they also contemplate.
The more you study,
the deeper your thoughts get.
You're starting to mature.
You still have a long way to go to be as mature as I am.
Let's finish shopping.
Then look for Bok Nam.
- All right.
- Good.
Awesome.
I want to become a better person.
After that, I'll tell her.
(EPISODE 8)
Wait for me.
Bok Sil moved in with Mr Cha.
Pardon me?
I see.
I'm sure Mr Cha has a crush on Bok Sil.
Otherwise, why would he take her to his place...
when she's burdened by someone?
There's a boy named Louis that Bok Sil is taking care of.
He's very friendly,
but he is...
He's very strange like an alien. He's a burden on her.
- I see.
- Yes.
It's a pity that you didn't get to see Bok Sil.
It's okay.
I only came by as her boss because I was worried about her.
I know I shouldn't say this when we've just met.
Your face, your body... I mean, you have...
such a kind heart.
I'm flattered.
Stop it.
On top of that, you're modest.
Gosh, it's hot.
Dad, Louis is living with Mr Cha.
- What did you say?
- It's so annoying!
Bok Sil is also living with him.
I'm going to make her move out.
Ma Ri, calm down.
Leave it up to me.
Okay?
Who's here at this late hour?
It's past 11pm.
Mr Baek?
What? Mr Baek?
Why is Mr Baek here?
Hide in the study for now. Hurry.
My shoes.
Hurry up.
- Hold these.
- Mr Baek.
Why brings you here?
I'm sorry for coming so late.
I have something urgent to tell you, so I stopped by.
- Let's talk inside.
- Wait.
Is Mr Cha at a high position in the company for Mr Baek to...
Be quiet!
Is someone there inside?
No way. You know I live alone.
I think there's someone in the room.
Mr Baek.
Mr Baek!
I know you're the president,
but I don't think it's appropriate for you to act like this.
I'm sorry.
I guess I became sensitive after hearing some rumours.
Do you sleep in the study?
Yes, I work and sleep here sometimes.
I see. Let's talk here.
Have a seat.
Okay.
I heard something strange about you today.
About me?
I heard you're living with a female employee from your department.
Is that true?
On top of that,
I heard she's the cleaner whom you hired...
a month ago.
I couldn't believe what they were saying, so I threw a fit.
You wouldn't do something like that.
You wouldn't do that because of a girl.
You wouldn't hire people for ulterior motives.
Would you, Mr Cha?
I've mentioned this before.
Bok Sil will make a great merchandiser.
That's why I gave her a chance.
She took the chance and was hired as a temporary worker.
She earned it with her effort.
Don't criticise me and say that I had ulterior motives.
Of course not.
You're the most trustworthy person in the world.
However,
such rumours won't benefit you at all.
It will be bad for your upright and proud image.
I don't want that.
Thank you for your concern.
What do you think about...
sending Bok Sil to our branch in Shanghai?
Excuse me?
Give it some thought.
It can be a good opportunity for her.
Forgive me for intruding at this hour.
- Stay here. I'll go.
- Goodbye, Sir.
Mr Cha. I'm sorry.
I was selfish to only look out for ourselves.
I didn't know it would cause you trouble.
If Bok Sil is sorry, I'm sorry as well.
- Go and pack your things.
- Okay.
Stop right there.
I don't know who spread a ridiculous rumour,
but I'm fine.
I'm okay with living with you two.
I'm the owner and I say it's fine.
Don't be dramatic and go to sleep.
Mr Cha. I still think...
- we should...
- Thank you for letting us stay.
What are you doing?
You should gladly accept someone's kindness.
That's the courtesy.
Am I right, Mr Cha?
It's not like you to say something right.
Mr Cha.
You don't like Bok Sil as a woman, do you?
That's ridiculous.
It's what the president said.
It's not true, is it?
- Of course not.
- Thank goodness.
Are you...
really going to send Bok Sil to the Shanghai branch?
No.
Don't worry yourselves needlessly and just go to sleep.
Go upstairs.
Should I spread the word that I live here as well?
Just go upstairs.
If Bok Sil is sent to the Shanghai branch, Louis will go with her.
All we have to do is make sure Louis doesn't show up...
until the company shares are settled.
Louis doesn't even have an ID. How will you send him to China?
I will take care of that matter.
Bok Sil wouldn't want to go, either.
She's pulling out all the stops to find her brother.
You said he already died.
You should tell Bok Sil that her brother is dead.
When she hears it, she'd want to go somewhere far.
That will be the perfect motive for her to leave.
You should hurry.
Are you sure he bought a flower here?
Yes. He was so picky about choosing the flower.
- So, which one did he pick?
- An orange-coloured rose.
Mr Kim. Do you know well about the flower language?
Red means passion, yellow means jealousy and pink means happiness.
- Do you know what orange means?
- I don't know.
It means first love.
Have you ever been in love?
Mr Louis. You shouldn't ask that kind of a question so bluntly.
That can be rude.
We're close enough to talk about it.
Would I be in love someday?
You'll have to see.
If I fall in love with someone,
I'll give her this orange rose. Just a single rose.
- What's wrong with you?
- It must be Mr Louis.
Did he say anything else?
He said he will give that flower to the woman he lives with.
Excuse me?
I don't think they were married, but just living together.
- That's how he sounded like.
- He can't be living with someone.
I remember him distinctly because he paid with coins only.
That doesn't sound like Mr Louis, either. It can't be him.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I'm sure it's him.
Here, 1 for a dollar, 2 for 2 dollars.
Grab anything you want.
Louis.
In Sung. What do you think?
You have such a good taste.
I'm just so curious.
- Did it talk to you again?
- Yes.
- What did it say?
- "Louis". It calls my name.
Louis.
I think you're mentally ill.
You're a long way off becoming as good as me.
- I'll take this.
- Okay.
Gosh. Please come again.
- Could you put this in a bag?
- Sure.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Please come again.
- Is the criminal caught yet?
- No.
That's strange. I gave them a big hint. He should be caught by now.
I wrote a letter to the United Nation.
Korea will be reunified soon. You'll see.
- What are you talking about?
- It sounds absurd, right?
You sound absurd, too.
Okay. I got it.
Sir. We have the address of Jung Gil Do, the suspect.
Good. Let's go then.
He might run away,
- so guard his house well.
- Yes, Sir.
Let's go. Hurry up.
You punks! Move it fast. Let's go.
Bok Sil.
Yes, Ms Baek.
- Can I talk to you after work?
- Okay.
Have you got the list of the stores for Korea Black Friday?
Is it going well for each category?
Of course. A lot of enterprises are willing to sell their products.
See? There is an enormous amount of sample products.
I don't want to see that.
- Tidy them up now.
- Yes, Sir.
Mr Lee. Did you hire a temporary part-time worker?
He will start working from today.
- Bok Sil went to pick him up.
- I see.
- Why are you alone?
- The part-timer had an emergency.
- He's sorry, but he can't come.
- What?
Mr Lee, you're so great at recruitment.
How can you be so great at everything?
- I'll find another...
- Forget it.
Yes, Sir.
I'll get someone.
Goodness. Let's move them.
Gosh, I said I'm sure.
He's a regular customer here.
He pays with 50 cent coins only. It's hard not to remember him.
Wouldn't he be some kind of a beggar?
He must beg for coins and spend them.
He came here a while ago and bought a t-shirt.
That's why I left a comment on your post.
A while ago? When?
It was about 20 minutes ago.
- 20 minutes?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- Please call me if he comes again.
- Please.
- Look at that.
- Hurry up.
- Gosh.
- Oh, dear.
- Let's take a look at that.
- Sure.
- Are you okay?
- Gosh.
- Oh, my. Are you okay?
- Sorry.
Excuse me, Mister!
You should watch where you're going.
He could've gotten hurt.
Give me your phone number.
- Mister!
- Ms Heo.
- I'm fine, so stop.
- But I'm not fine.
You shouldn't hurt your back.
Her pupils are shaking and her lips are sticking out.
She's truly worried about me.
- Are you really okay?
- Why?
Why would she be?
It's really delicious.
Hello? Gosh, really?
I'll be right there.
- What is it?
- I got a job.
- I'll get 50 dollars per day.
- Great!
- Where?
- At Goldline.
50 dollars?
Hey.
Goldline is that way.
I need to get something. See you later.
What is he going to buy again?
Why can't he start work without his things?
Wow, 50 dollars is a lot.
Perfect.
Hello.
- Hello.
Where is Mr Cha?
He's out for lunch.
How about Bok Sil?
- Do you know her?
- Yes, I'm close to her.
Did they go out for lunch together?
I'm not sure about that.
Gosh, that's annoying.
I'd like a cup of Maxim Gold.
Okay.
Who is he?
He seems so familiar.
All of his clothes, shoes and scarf belong to Mr Cha.
What?
Mr Cha, someone is here for you.
That rascal.
Have you lost your mind? Who told you to wear my clothes?
How dare you?
He'll be working part-time today to help out with the chores.
- Say hello.
- Hello.
- His name is...
- Louis.
Do you mean Louis from Louis XIV?
You don't have a last name?
Well, it's...
King.
- King Louis.
- King?
- Bok Sil.
- Ms Park.
- Who is this?
- I'm her guardian.
Right, he's Bok Sil's boyfriend.
Isn't that right, Louis?
No, he's not.
I'm more than her boyfriend.
We live...
We're looking for someone.
He's helping me find my brother.
Why are you wearing Mr Cha's clothes?
We live...
We met while being on a diet.
You lost a lot of weight.
Get to work now.
There's so much piled up in front of the storeroom!
Okay.
- What's going on?
- Goodness.
Here you go.
Thank you. What's your name?
Lee Kyung Kook.
I'll remember that name.
Okay.
He's a part-timer.
(A PART-TIMER)
He made coffee for a part-timer. Good job, Mr Lee.
How did you meet Bok Sil?
How did you find this job?
What do you do?
Which gym does Mr Cha go to?
Don't worry about the part-timer. Get to work.
What are you doing, Mr Lee?
Gosh.
Open the boxes and check the items.
Separate the items...
per category and bring them to each person in charge.
That's not so hard.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Shall I put them here?
Yes.
Dad!
Dad, we're in trouble.
Ma Ri.
What's going on?
Hello.
Let's discuss it later.
Okay.
Dad, Dad.
Louis came to the office.
He's at merchandising department right now.
What?
Why did he come to merchandising department?
Did you find out why he came?
I didn't have a chance to find out. I ran here as soon as I saw him.
Wait.
Is he here for the part-time job?
Part-time job?
We have so much work because of the Black Friday event.
We hired a part-timer.
Since Bok Sil is working here,
Louis keeps getting involved.
We need to get rid of her now.
Goodness.
- This is missing, right?
- Yes.
What happened here?
Louis.
Are you okay?
Goodness.
Gosh.
Of course I'm not okay.
Some woman attacked me.
She's not here.
That woman...
pushed all these boxes on me as soon as she saw me.
Mi Young?
If it's not Hae Joo either...
Is it Ms Baek?
Come on, that's nonsense.
Who do you think she is?
I know, I've seen her somewhere.
Gosh.
That's right.
I was run over by her car.
After running me over,
she gave me money and called me.
Are you saying the woman who pushed the boxes on you...
is the same woman who hit you with her car?
That's so strange.
He looks normal, but he's a bit strange.
- He's delusional.
- Right.
I was jealous of Bok Sil for having a handsome boyfriend.
It turns out he's a little iffy.
But he's so familiar.
King Louis. Have I seen him somewhere?
- Have you seen me before?
- Goodness.
When? Where?
When?
- Hurry.
- Hurry what?
- What's that smell?
- Something smells bad.
- That homeless man?
- That pervert?
- That hurt.
- Is he a homeless?
Oh, my goodness.
Did Bok Sil meet him in the lobby when she used to be a cleaner?
It's a meeting of a cleaner and a homeless man...
by fate.
What a tragic story.
Poor Bok Sil.
What?
What's all this?
What happened here?
Bok Sil, I got hit in the face.
Who hit you?
This.
Gosh, you should have been more careful.
That must hurt.
Bok Sil. Isn't it strange?
You're the only one who believes what I say.
Mr Cha also says I'm a big liar.
You only need one person who will believe...
what you say.
- Is that person you?
- Of course.
Ms Baek. Did you...
hit Louis with your car?
What are you talking about?
Did you say Louis?
Haven't you seen the new part-timer?
No, I haven't.
I knew it. He's just crazy.
Hae Joo said he is Bok Sil's boyfriend.
- Is Bok Sil into appearances?
- She's more like a philanthropist.
- We'll go into a meeting now.
- Okay.
Put it over there. Good.
What are you doing here?
Are you trying to avoid someone?
No, Sir.
The suspect got caught. Let's go to the police office.
- Really?
- Let's go.
- How did it happen?
- Let's hurry.
- Did they catch the suspect?
- They did.
That's strange. I gave them a big hint. He should be caught by now.
Gosh. He's good at taking guesses.
It gives me the chills.
Jung Gil Do, the suspect of the serial murder case...
- in Eunsung-dong got caught.
- What was your...
- motive for your murder?
- He had never left any evidence,
but he failed to see the unidentified powder...
on the floor of the house he committed the third murder.
Why was there powder on the floor? Bok Sil keeps it very neat.
His footprints became...
- a big clue.
- I wonder who he is.
(ON THE DAY OF THE INCIDENT)
Why isn't Bok Sil home yet?
I wonder if she's okay.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I can't get to it.
My goodness.
It's so hard to have a cup of coffee.
I should wait for Bok Sil.
(5 MINUTES BEFORE THE INCIDENT)
What is all this?
Sir. Shouldn't we give Louis a reward?
It wasn't a report on the suspect.
Still.
We caught the suspect faster because he told us about the footprints.
He's right. If we hadn't looked into on the cycling shoes stores,
- we wouldn't have caught him.
- You little...
He will smack you.
We can't give him 100 percent of the reward.
Check if we can give him a part of it.
When the inspection is over,
- take off the police line.
- Yes, Sir.
Is the victim at the hospital still unconscious?
Yes. He's probably a burglar.
- Should I continue investigating?
- You should.
I told you I left that comment by mistake.
I just took him for someone else.
That's why I deleted the comment.
Wait. Please take a look at this again.
Excuse me. I'm busy.
- But...
- Wait.
You won't receive any more reports? Why?
- I got a call from his guardian.
- His guardian?
She said her son has a mental deficiency,
and she doesn't want him to go on TV shows.
I understand his parents feel that way.
We took down the pictures and the video.
I'm sure I know that man.
Stop it. He just said that man has parents.
I'm sure he's just someone who looks a lot like Mr Louis.
Besides, how can a dead person come back to life?
Can I get his contact number?
- We don't know that. Excuse me.
- Wait.
Mr Baek. It's me.
We went to the hospital and the broadcasting station.
That man is not Mr Louis.
Okay, Sir.
Who were you talking to?
You said you didn't want to see me. What changed your mind?
- How is Mother?
- Mother?
She's asleep now. Why?
Bring her to Seoul.
Is it... Is it because you found Louis?
No. It's not that.
Don't say anything silly to Mother.
Just bring her here.
I won't forgive you if you say something silly again.
Who is the person you keep talking to?
It's just my friend.
You're lying.
I'll ask you again. Is there anyone you have to make reports to?
Why do you care whom I talk to?
Why are you ordering me around? I can't believe this.
Why is she lying to me?
Was she talking to her boyfriend?
Gosh, what am I thinking? Wait for me.
Gosh, that restaurant makes the best pasta.
I was so happy when I was eating their pasta,
but now I'm sad to work overtime.
Is Ms Baek working outside the office today? I haven't seen her.
She is not avoiding Louis, is she?
You're driving me crazy, Mr Lee.
Why do you always say crazy things?
You do it all the time. It's annoying.
- Did Bok Sil and Louis leave?
- What?
Two stars for Park Hae Joo.
You talk too much. You're so noisy. From Louis.
What a jerk.
Gosh, he's making me laugh.
How many stars did you get?
One star for Kwon Mi Young.
You look down on me. From Louis.
Just 1? I got 3 stars.
Three stars for Byun Do Jin.
I only like your style. From Louis.
I got five.
Five stars for Lee Kyung Kook. You're kind.
Thank you for the coffee. From Louis.
Why are you making a fuss about this? He's only a part-timer.
I know, but isn't this annoying?
His spelling is all wrong. How dare he judge us?
He's a good judge of character.
He wants us to put up the products he stuck post-its on.
He says they have a competitive quality.
Who does he think he is to evaluate the products?
What a joke.
He may actually be an expert in this field.
There's something special about him.
Where is Louis?
Did he finish all of his tasks?
Yes, he completed everything.
Get back to your work!
Bok Sil, why did you lie to me?
- Pardon me?
- Is Mr Cha your neighbour?
How can you fool me like that?
You're acting suspiciously.
I'm sorry that I lied.
I didn't want to put Mr Cha in an awkward position.
Right, so why did you start it to begin with?
I heard that you moved into his place with a guy.
You don't need to hide it from me. I already know everything.
Could you please not tell other people?
I was actually going to move out today anyway.
You have to move out.
Stop inconveniencing other people.
Got it?
Okay.
I actually asked you to meet me today to talk about something else.
What is it? Is it something important?
Bok Sil. I'm going to tell you something, but don't be surprised.
Actually...
Bok Sil!
Louis?
Go. Yes, just go.
Bok Sil, let's talk some other time.
Sorry?
You startled me.
Ms Baek.
Hello, Ms Baek.
- Do you need a hand?
- No! Don't come near me.
You two should just leave.
What?
Your voice sounds familiar.
My gosh!
She's taking the tray with her.
Miss! You can't take the tray!
It's not really a covetable item, don't you think?
Miss! Stop, you thief!
How dare you accuse me of stealing this tray!
You'll be so surprised if you find out who I am,
so just take this and go.
Why do I keep seeing Louis everywhere I go?
Gosh, what should I do?
Ms Choi, I am so sorry.
I was convinced that he was Mr Louis.
Ms Choi, I apologise.
I'm okay.
Mr Kim and Ms Heo, thank you very much for trying.
I'm sorry, Mother.
I caused a fuss and turned it into a big deal.
No, don't worry.
Thanks for looking after me.
Where is Seon Goo? Why isn't he here yet?
And what's taking Ma Ri so long?
They're coming together now.
Why do we have to go to Grandma's house?
Grandma is in Seoul now. Let's go say hello.
- Is something going on?
- The shares need to be finalised.
We're meeting the attorney, Mr Hwang, tomorrow.
Dad, can we really leave Louis like that?
How many times have I told you? I'll take care of everything.
Pretend not to know anything in front of Grandma.
- Got it?
- Okay.
Are you that happy to get the reward?
Of course! I have money rolling in from various sources today.
Buy Bok Sil delicious food with this money.
I'm going to spend it all for her.
Where are you going?
Detective Nam called me and told me that the suspect has been caught.
I see.
That's good.
I'll move back home. Thank you for letting me stay here.
You can stay here if you find that rooftop room uncomfortable.
I have extra rooms anyway.
Thank you very much, but it's all right.
Also, I won't go to the branch in Shanghai.
I have to find my brother and help Louis get his memory back,
so I must stay in Seoul.
I don't want to...
send you there, either.
You still have a lot to learn.
You cannot escape my training programme.
Never, never, never.
Okay.
Don't get distracted and focus on work. Understood?
Okay!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Did you come here by yourself?
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm always unwell.
Help me put pain relief patches.
Let's go.
Come on!
It's clean.
Is someone here?
- Ms Hwang!
- Hey, Bok Sil.
- Oh my gosh!
- You're here, too.
I'll do it. You must be exhausted.
You didn't have to clean my place for me.
I'm an expert in this, you know. You two should wait outside.
I just have to wipe this spot here.
Nothing feels nicer...
than coming back to a clean home.
Don't you agree?
Ms Hwang.
- Goodness.
- Ms Hwang...
What is the matter with him? My goodness.
- Get up now.
- Hey! What are you doing now?
She's my mum!
What is wrong with you guys? My gosh.
- Stop acting like kids.
- You come here.
- Have you two lost your minds?
- Ouch!
Get up! You two are adults. Stop being so childish.
(LOUIS)
I hope you enjoy the food.
What food?
I hope you enjoy it, Sir.
See you again, Mr Cha Joong On.
It's Cha Joong Won, you fool.
He just doesn't get it.
My gosh. Louis.
Are you really paying for all of this?
It's not much.
- Please help yourself.
- You really are a big spender.
Seeing how you splurge convinces me that you're from a rich family.
Mum, come join us. Sit here.
All right. Let's eat.
Bok Sil, tell me if there's anything else you crave. I'll buy it for you.
This is more than enough. Stop ordering food.
My goodness.
That clueless guy is slowly starting to grow up.
I really can't believe this.
Of course. I'm a competent person.
I can't be called the clueless guy forever.
I'm King of Shopping, Louis.
Only those who are incompetent brag about themselves like that.
Hey, eat before it gets cold.
I hope you all enjoy the food!
- We will!
- Thanks!
Jo In Sung, don't eat too much.
Really, Song Joong Ki?
Don't do that!
It's okay.
Louis, you shouldn't splurge like this. You have to save money.
Do you actually think that I'd eat...
something this greasy in the middle of the night?
I'm speechless.
I shouldn't eat all of this. How many calories does this have?
Yes, it's fine. I'll just go for a run after.
So we're back here now.
Yes. Our place is the best, don't you think?
Whatever. You enjoyed staying at Mr Cha's place.
What I'm saying is, I'm happy to be just with you.
I'm happy that you'll cook only for me now.
Bok Sil.
I've been thinking hard since last night.
Seeing how even the president of the company picks on you...
made me so upset.
Quit your job. We can start an online shopping mall together.
For some reason, I get the feeling that I'll be great at it.
What?
You don't trust me? I'm King of Shopping, Louis.
I trust you, of course. I'm the only person who believes in you.
I should learn more, though. Mr Cha told me to do so.
Whatever. You're choosing Mr Cha over me.
You're sulking over nothing again.
What do you want to do the most right now?
I'm going to make everything you want happen.
- I want to see the ocean.
- The ocean?
Let's go!
- I see the ocean!
Bok Sil!
- Oh, my.
- It looks like you.
This song sounds so familiar.
- Do you know this song?
- No.
What are you doing?
Nice!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Hey, be careful!
Come on!
Louis!
Oh, my shoe!
What?
Wait here. I'll find it.
- Hey, I see it over there.
- I'll get it.
- Mr Cha gave it to me as a gift.
- What?
Hey, what are you doing?
What do you think?
- I'm letting it go its way.
- Gosh, you little...
It's so cold!
My gosh!
There it is.
Here, it should be okay now. I'm cold.
- Why are you standing there?
- I don't have the other shoe.
Don't worry. I'll give you a piggyback ride.
What? My gosh. Hey...
It's pretty.
Of course it's pretty. I picked it out, you know?
My grandma said that giving shoes is like a parting gift.
What?
- You pay for it.
- I don't have any money on me.
I didn't bring my wallet.
Why did you have to make such an ominous remark?
How much is this?
Hello.
I'm from the police.
I'm glad I caught you today. I came by a few times to meet you.
Well...
Did I do something wrong?
No, I just have a few questions for you.
Do you have...
the music box made for Gold Department Store's 30th anniversary?
Yes. It's over there.
(GOLD DEPARTMENT STORE)
Yes, this is the music box.
Then have you ever heard of the name, Louis?
Louis?
I love the smell of books.
I'm hungry.
Do books look like food to you? Goodness.
It's carrying all the traces of time.
(AS SOON AS I GOT OUT OF THE LONG TUNNEL...)
(AT THE BORDER, I ARRIVED AT A TOWN OF SNOW.)
(EVERYTHING UNDER MY FEET TURNED WHITE IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.)
- What...
- Hey.
(I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.)
(MY MOUTH COULDN'T EVEN UTTER ANY NAMES.)
(AND I BECAME BLIND.)
- What's going on?
- Gosh.
- Try reading something else.
- Okay.
(I PACKED UP AND LEFT, )
(AND I CAN'T BE HAPPIER ABOUT IT!)
Louis, you must've been extremely smart.
- I'm so impressed with myself.
- My gosh.
I'm seriously so cool.
Mr Cha and Ms Hwang should've been here to witness this.
- Bok Sil, record a video of me.
- What?
- Hurry up.
- Oh, okay.
Just a second.
Ready, go!
I'm this smart. Don't be disrespectful to me, got it?
Is there anything else I can read?
(23 DOLLARS)
What does that mean?
It says...
"In Search of Lost Time".
It's like my current situation.
Bok Sil.
I want to get my memory back,
but my new life now...
also makes me very happy.
My heart is filled with warmth...
and joy.
King Louis. If that's the case,
when was the most memorable moment...
of your new life so far?
Bok Sil!
The moments I spent...
waiting for you all day long.
What about you, Bok Sil? When was the most memorable moment for you?
Right now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What should I do?
What's wrong?
Are you feeling sick?
(SHOPAHOLIC LOUIS)
Mother, Louis is alive.
- What is this about?
- Did he disappear without a word?
His grandmother is the chairwoman of Gold Group?
- Mr Louis!
- Gosh, Louis!
I'm glad that Louis found his family.
- Bok Sil must be waiting for me.
- No.
- I'll be quick.
- You cannot leave, Mr Louis.
- Have you heard from Louis?
- Not yet.
Bok Sil.
Louis and Bok Nam were switched.
You promised me that you'd find Bok Nam for me, right?
I'll be sure to find him.
Just trust me.