Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[EPISODE 10]
Don't ever do that again, Yoon Seo Jung.
Don't disappear
without a word ever again.
Look at you,
messing with your senior again.
Huh?
Oh no!
Stop it already!
What's the matter?
What's going on...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Excuse me!
Wake up, sir!
- Can you walk?
- Yes.
Here, watch your step.
Is this 911?
We're on Interstate 39,
and there's been an accident here!
Yes, about six cars!
Just a moment, sir.
- Are you all right, sir?
- I didn't do it.
I really wasn't speeding!
I was going really slowly!
- This isn't my fault!
- Calm down, sir!
I got it, so calm down, all right?
Oh... oh no!
Just a moment.
Excuse me.
Are you injured anywhere?
Do you feel any pain near
your hip, neck, or other spots?
I'm just a hired designated driver.
I didn't do anything wrong!
Can you get up, sir?
I'm telling you, I really
didn't do anything wrong!
Excuse me, sir.
Can you help this man up?
Staying on the road is dangerous.
Please go to the side of the road.
- All right.
- Please, get up.
Let's get you up.
Let's check the other cars, too.
- I'll look over there.
- I'll inspect the ones in the front.
Oh... you hit me?
Did you just hit me?
Hey, call the police.
Call the police!
How dare you hit me? Huh?
Do you know who I am?
Can't you see that this is an
emergency patient who needs surgery?
You people always use patients as an
excuse when you're in a tight spot.
Hey. I've been a hospital
inspector for 12 years now.
I know how you people think better
than I know the palm of my hand!
How dare you... Hey, what are
you doing? Call the cops, now!
Yes, sir.
This is the police, correct?
This is Doldam Hospital's ER.
You have to hurry over here.
There's been an assault.
Hey, punk.
You're really in for it today.
I won't let you off easy with
just an out-of-court settlement.
Doctor! Big trouble, sir!
It's Doctor Kang Dong Joo.
He says that there's been an
accident with six cars on the highway.
Oh my god.
What's going on there?
There's one patient with a damaged
carotid artery that has already expired
and the four patients who are still
conscious are outside of their cars now.
Including those who are unconscious,
we have about 10 injured patients.
What about Yoon Seo Jung?
Is she there now?
Yes. She's looking for other
injured people, just in case.
Nurse Oh. What's the
temperature outside right now?
Negative one degree Celsius
and it's due to drop two or
three more degrees in an hour.
Hey, Kang Dong Joo.
Children, pregnant women, and those with
excessive bleeding are your priorities.
Send the highest-priority people
over on the ambulances first.
Yes, sir.
And make sure to keep
the injured patients warm.
Make sure that the unconscious
patients are kept warm, no matter what.
You got that?
Yes, sir!
Do you have anything we can
cover people with in your cars?
Just a moment!
Allow me to inspect
you for injuries, sir.
- Oh my.
- Do you feel any pain anywhere?
Are you all right?
What about you, ma'am?
Excuse me for a bit.
Oh, it's cold.
It's so cold.
You punks have been
drinking and driving?
Hey, Sis.
Why is it so cold?
It doesn't look like you
have any bleeding.
Excuse me. Don't move,
and just stay in the car for now.
Please close the door.
It's so cold.
Blood.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Oh, Eun Seol.
Eun Seol. Eun Seol!
Eun Seol!
Eun Seol. Eun Seol,
open your eyes!
Eun Seol!
Somebody, please help!
Help us, please!
Please help us!
Over here! Use these.
Here you are, ma'am.
Please stay here for a moment.
Help us!
I don't think we'll be
able to handle this ourselves.
Call and ask for backup.
- Hurry and get the supplies out.
- Yes, sir.
Please, please!
Save my daughter!
Are you all right, ma'am?
- Please, save my Eun Seol!
- Who? Eun Seol?
Please save my Eun Seol!
Oh, Eun Seol!
Excuse me!
Oh no, my Eun Seol!
My poor baby!
- Eun Seol!
- How old is your child?
How old is your child?
Four years old!
She's four years old!
Where's your car seat?
You put a toddler in your
car without a car seat?
- Eun Seol.
- Oh, my baby!
Huh?
Excuse me.
Can you hear me, sir?
Mister! Mister!
You've hurt your leg quite badly, sir.
It needs to be realigned, so I'll get
someone to help you right away.
So please wait here just a bit.
Wait just a moment, please.
Just a moment.
There's... one...
more person. One more.
Honey, are you all right? Honey!
Can one of you go
and get the doctor?
My husband has chronic
obstructive pulmonary disease!
Please go and tell the doctor!
Pul... pulmonary obstructive what?
Honey! Oh... oh no!
She seems to have internal
hemorrhaging in the abdomen.
Please hurry and get her
to Doldam Hospital.
Yes. Please come with us too, ma'am.
You have to live, Eun Seol!
Are you all right?
Yes!
Can you move your neck?
Do you have any pain in your hip,
legs, or anywhere else?
No, I don't!
But... over there.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
There's a patient up there!
He has an open fracture
on his right leg.
Please hurry over to him
with something to realign it.
Go over there, with a
stretcher and a bandage! Hurry!
- Yes, sir!
- Senior!
What does that look like to you?
It's a person, right?
All right, please inhale this
when I count to three.
One, two, three!
Okay.
I'll give you some oxygen now,
so just inhale slowly through your nose.
Okay.
Excuse me. Back up.
Got it.
One, two, three!
One more time!
There we go.
He has a lower leg crush
injury on both legs.
There's a lot of bleeding, too.
We'll have to put a
tourniquet on him first.
A tourniquet?
- Will this work?
- Yeah, one more.
One more?
Here's one more.
Hydration, please. And get something
to realign this, as well as some fluid.
Yes.
Large bags of warm saline,
c-lines, Foleys, and intubators.
Five of each, please.
- Empty out this hybrid room...
- Where should I go?
and empty all of
these beds here, too.
And move all of the patients
in the D-zone inside.
- Teacher Kim!
- Yes?
The first patient will
be here in three minutes.
It's a four-year-old female child.
According to Doctor Kang, she has some
muscle guarding around her abdomen
so she may have a seat belt injury.
Leave the scene of the
accident in Yoon Seo Jung's care
and call Kang Dong Joo
to the hospital.
Right away, sir.
- Nurse Park.
- Yes?
What about the female patient
with Boerhaave syndrome?
Doctor Nam Do Il is preparing
her for surgery right now.
Call Doctor Yang from Jungil Hospital
and entrust the surgery to him
and entrust the four-year-old girl
coming in now to Doctor Nam.
Yes, sir.
Are you going to continue
being difficult, Doctor Bu Yong Joo?
- Why, you...
- Hey.
Didn't you hear?
It's a six-car accident.
What are you trying to do here,
when people's lives are at stake?
I'm just doing my duty.
That's what I get paid to do, after all.
No, you're just on a power trip
and ignoring the situation at hand!
Are you going to take responsibility
if someone ends up dying, at this rate?
Well...
none of this would've happened if you'd
just followed orders from the beginning.
This is your own fault,
so you can't blame us for it.
Why, you idiotic little bastard.
We have a patient!
It's a four-year-old girl,
and she's unconscious.
Her capillary refill time is falling!
We'll have to get her
into the hybrid room!
Doctor, please save my Eun Seol!
Honey.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
This person needs an orthopedic surgeon,
so please take them to a big hospital.
Yes, we will.
You two surgeons head
back to the hospital now.
I'll take a look at the remaining
injured patients before I go.
Wait.
See you at the hospital.
Yeah. See you at the hospital.
- Oh man.
- What's the matter?
Is his condition bad?
He drank so damn much
that he's throwing up now.
Oh... water.
Give me some water.
Water, okay?
Do you have any water, Sis?
What's his blood alcohol level?
He refuses to comply. He says that he'll
get a blood test at the police station.
I said let's go.
Let's go, man!
I'll let you take my blood
at the police station.
Oh, really?
Well, sure. We'll do that,
if that's what you want.
What are you doing?
You're pretty.
Wow, that was fast.
All done.
I'm guessing his BAC
will be around .451.
Oh, yes.
Also...
Don't go driving after you've
had so much damn alcohol.
That's essentially the same as
committing murder, you son of a bitch.
Hey, Sis!
Who are you?
Who do you think you are,
speaking to me so harshly?
You talking to me?
I'm the Crazy Whale of Doldam Hospital.
Doctor Yoon Seo Jung.
They want you to step in for a bit.
Her spleen is damaged, and the
capsule surrounding it is torn.
- Doctor.
- Yeah?
We have the results of the
CT scan. Come over here.
This is the spleen.
You see the dark bits?
It means that there's bleeding there.
Is her condition really bad, sir?
Well, she is a toddler, so...
it's risky to even put her
under general anesthesia.
But if we don't operate on her, she'll
be in danger due to heavy blood loss.
Oh... oh no!
Operating on children is different
than operating on adults.
The only person at this hospital
who can operate on her is me.
Well?
Are you still planning
to get in my way?
Rules... are rules, after all.
She may be my daughter, but...
I can't just change the rules
all of the sudden because of this.
Honey!
Geez, you pathetic bastard.
Okay, then.
I'll do my job, so you do yours.
Because I have to operate on this child,
no matter what you choose to do to me.
It seems that you don't quite get it yet
but doctors have only one job.
And that job is to save the patient,
no matter what it takes.
All right, bring this child to the OR.
Yes, Doctor.
We need the guardian to come
and sign the consent form, please.
Okay.
We have a patient!
- This way, please.
- This way.
Yes, this way.
This way.
She's a woman in her 20s. She was
upside down in car, held by a seatbelt.
Please give her a
cervical spine x-ray.
Yes, I will.
- Hey, Kang Dong Joo.
- Yes?
You told me there was a patient with an
open fracture. What happened with him?
We had two patients with
lower leg open fractures
but one of them had a light fracture
while the other had a severe one.
They're on their way to a hospital
with an orthopedic surgeon.
Senior Seo Jung will come back after
the other patients are taken care of.
We have two patients in need of surgery.
One has Boerhaave syndrome and
one is a child who needs spleen surgery.
I'll take care of the child, but which
one of you has experience with Boerhaave?
I've done it once before.
- With a laparoscope?
- Yes.
Okay. Then you be the
main surgeon, Do In Bum.
And you assist, Kang Dong Joo.
Yes, sir.
I'll go and get ready.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What? What do you mean,
you still haven't found a hospital?
We've called every single big hospital
nearby, but all of their ORs are full.
They have no beds in their ERs, either.
What should we do?
The patient's BP isn't too good,
and he's still bleeding out.
Oh man...
I thought you said
you've done this surgery before.
I'm just doing one more simulation.
Is there something wrong with that?
No. I'll go and get ready then,
Doctor Do In Bum.
Are you ready, Doctor Nam?
Doctor Nam.
Yeah. Let's start.
Knife.
Trocar.
Scope.
Scalpel.
I'm opening up the peritoneum now.
Please monitor her vitals.
Okay.
Eul Seol said that she
wanted to see her dad...
and you said that you'd be staying here
longer than you'd originally thought
so I packed some clothes
and other things for you
and we were on our way
to come see you.
Why did you take the car seat out?
Because she kept telling me
that she didn't want to sit in it.
It's not like we knew that
we'd get into an accident!
Please move out of the way!
We have patients coming in!
Hey, how could you bring
orthopedic patients here?
What else were we supposed to do?
Was I supposed to leave them to die
while going from hospital to hospital?
Look at you,
saying unpleasant things again!
There were no supplies in the ambulance
and they're bleeding quite a lot.
We'll find a hospital to transfer them
to while giving them transfusions.
Hey, we're overflowing with
emergency patients as it is!
Light or heavy.
Which one do you want to do?
Light.
Okay.
Can you hear me, sir?
BP is 90/60, with 120 bpm.
Change the drip from the
ambulance to a warm saline
and put one more line in him
for two total liters of hydration.
- Yes, Doctor.
- Scissor!
Please bear it for a bit, Patient!
I'll be cutting the bandages off.
Please prepare a bandage
and a splint, please.
Yes, Doctor.
I think it's this side,
but I can't see the perforation.
Pull the scope out a bit.
I told you to pull it out a bit!
What do you want me to do?
Should we call Teacher Kim?
Hey, Doctor Do In Bum!
No. I'll do it.
I found it.
Here's the tear site.
Suture number 3.
All done.
We'll be doing the fundoplication now.
One more suture number 3, please.
Hey, how's your patient?
I think we'll have to amputate
both of his legs below the knee.
He has a severe fracture
near the back of his skull, too.
- Is it wide?
- About 10 palms.
Same with this patient.
He has no pulse near his foot.
How did it go with finding a
hospital to transfer them to?
I'm looking into it now,
but it hasn't been easy.
Ask Chief Jang to help us, too.
He has some personal connections.
Will do, Doctor.
All right. Shall we tend to the
other guests waiting for us, then?
The left side...
and the right side.
The left side.
I'll take care of the
right side first, then.
What do you mean by that?
Why did they bring
orthopedic patients here?
No hospitals would accept them
and their condition isn't
too good, I'm afraid.
Oh geez. Looks like Doctor
Yoon Seo Jung caused trouble again.
Are you still having
trouble breathing, sir?
I'm a lot better now.
To be honest, tomorrow is our
54th wedding anniversary.
Wow, really? You two have been
together for 54 years now?
My missus married me
when she was 19, so...
- Oh, stop it!
- she's suffered a lot.
The doctor is in the
middle of examining you.
Please take a deep breath.
We'll give you some more oxygen and
get your breathing back to normal.
And what about you, ma'am?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Did you hit yourself against
something hard, or...
Nothing like that, but...
I don't know if it's because I was so
shocked, but my heart is beating so fast.
My missus's heart hasn't
ever been too good, you see.
Could you give me your hand, please?
Your heart rate is a bit fast.
Does your heart feel stiff?
Or do you feel pain anywhere else?
Oh, I'm sure it's just the shock.
I'm fine, so please get
my husband feeling better first.
Please be sure to tell me if you
feel any pain anywhere. All right?
Speaking of which, Doctor.
- How old are you right now?
- Oh, there you go again.
What?
I'm just asking because she looks like
she's about the same age as our youngest.
- Please get some more rest.
- Okay.
Did you call the kids?
I told them to take their time
since the roads are slippery.
Oh.
Get some shut-eye until they get here.
Sure.
Oh my, oh my.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Tell me the truth. This was your
first time doing that, wasn't it?
You were lying about having
done it once before. Right?
Well, it wasn't really
a difficult surgery.
And it was successful in the end.
Isn't that good enough?
You think that surgery is a joke?
Well, of course it's not.
But it's nothing to risk
your own life over, either.
Looks like he got you this time.
Right?
This is what you like, right?
Coffee with both cream and sugar.
Oh, yes.
Please, have this.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Have you ever thought that
you wanted to quit your job?
Why are you asking me that
all of the sudden?
When you felt like you wanted to quit...
how did you overcome that
feeling and get through it?
I was just curious.
Well, I don't know.
I feel like I couldn't quit
if only because all my suffering up
until now would've been for nothing.
And I don't have the confidence that
I'd be better at anything else if I quit.
Is that... all?
Don't you have a personal
conviction as a doctor
or feel like you had a personal
calling to this profession?
I think you'd have to work for at least
10 years to have either of those things.
Because talking the talk is
different than walking the walk.
I got a call from the ER.
I have to go.
Thank you for the coffee!
What's going on?
His BP is rising and the
bleeding is getting worse.
Decrease the amount of fluids
and get me a c-line and a Foley.
Yes, Doctor.
I'll take care of inserting the c-line.
Can I get the Foley, please?
Doctor! The patient at bed five
is going into cardiac arrest!
Take care of the c-line here for me!
Yes, Senior!
Doctor! My wife isn't breathing!
Can you hear me, ma'am? Ma'am!
- Get me a monitor here, please.
- Yes, Doctor.
No response, and she's not breathing.
I'll move her to a bed!
Honey! Honey!
Excuse me.
One, two, three!
Connect her to the monitor and get
the supplies for intubation ready!
It seems that his central venous
pressure is quite low.
He's not excreting any urine, either.
If his BP keeps rising despite him having
no blood, his bleeding will get worse.
Okay, let's hook him up to a tube.
Our target is getting
his systolic to 100.
- Let me know when you've put it in.
- Yes, Doctor.
Get the defibrillator, hurry!
That's enough.
I told you to stop it!
We agreed that we
wouldn't do this, Doctor.
We already did the paperwork to say that
she wouldn't get this kind of treatment.
I think he's talking about a
Do Not Resuscitate order, Doctor.
Sir!
That's enough.
You can stop now, Doctor.
You sure did suffer
a lot up until now, Honey.
You must have suffered quite
a bit while living with me.
[WOO YEON HWA]
Please monitor her input
and output rates carefully.
And make sure you check
on her hemovac drain, too.
- Yes, Doctor.
- All right.
Her spleen is a bit damaged,
so we've moved her here
but thankfully,
her condition isn't too bad.
We'll watch over her for a day and move
her to a regular hospital room tomorrow.
Oh, thank you!
Thank you so much!
You can step in for a bit, if you'd like.
Yes, Doctor.
What...
am I supposed to do?
I don't know what you expected
as a reward for treating my child...
but tell me, sir.
What is it that you want from me?
Go see your child.
I mean, it's good to try and
live a productive life and all
but let's not live bad lives
because of that, all right?
People need to know what they're even
living for, first and foremost. Right?
What do you mean by that?
They called one of our orthopedic
surgeons to go to Doldam?
Why?
I'm not sure about the reason, sir.
I only heard that it was the
decision of the inspector.
- Get me Inspector Choi on the line.
- Yes, sir.
There are two severely injured patients
here due to a six-car traffic accident.
The situation is quite dire, so I called
an orthopedic surgeon from Geosan.
Hey, Inspector Choi.
What are you trying to do, here?
I'll report the details to you
once I get back to Seoul.
I'll be hanging up, then.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Yes, Director Do?
Where are you right now,
and what are you doing?
Do you even know what's going on
at Doldam Hospital right now?
Um... did something happen there, sir?
How ridiculous of you to say!
Are you seriously
asking me that right now?
Where are you right now?
Are you out drinking again?
No, sir! What do you mean, drinking?
Of course I'm not, Director!
Director?
Bu Yong Joo.
What about Yoon Seo Jung?
Did she come back?
Yes, but...
A patient expired not too
long ago due to cardiac arrest.
Are you a bit better now?
Yeah... it's not like this is my first
or second time to have this happen.
But I just can't seem to get used to it.
You did your best, though, Senior.
Isn't that enough?
Did I really do my best?
I'm not so sure about that.
Am I really doing this right?
Is my very best
the best for the patient, too?
Doctors are human, too.
And you're human, too.
I'm not sure that's a good enough
excuse for someone who's died, though.
Doctor.
Come with me.
Do you want me to come with you?
No, it's fine.
I'm sorry to have been
a burden to you.
Go in.
Here, sir?
Hey.
Do you want me to embarrass you
in front of everyone, then?
No, sir. I'll go inside.
Doctor!
Honey, it's the doctor.
She saved you.
There's only one way to know
if a doctor is doing a good job.
Through his or her patients.
That's the only way to know.
Don't try to take responsibility for
matters regarding life and death, too.
All you can do is give it your all
while utilizing what you've learned.
Just focus on that.
As of today, you're no longer
non-clinical personnel.
I'm going to make things super tough
on you from now on, so prepare yourself.
Yes, I'll prepare myself.
Don't cry. It'll make you grow on me.
Why are you just
standing here? Go in.
Oh, thank you so much, Doctor!
Thank you so much, Doctor!
Thank you so much!
Thank you.
Yes.
Thank you. Thank you.
[LETTER OF RESIGNATION]
[LETTER OF RESIGNATION
FROM KANG DONG JOO]
[STUDENT ID CARD
JANG HYUN JOO]
So you've been working on
something interesting, I see.
Since when have you
been sitting there?
It's been a while since I got here.
And I was doing some reading,
since I saw something interesting.
Is this the "painting" you're working on?
[PROFILE: KANG DONG JOO]
You broke into someone else's office
and rummaged through my things?
That's quite a rude habit
you've got there, Manager Joo.
The chairman was curious.
Can't you go ahead and start now
if you have a plan this detailed?
This is merely a sketch.
And have you chosen the people
to be involved in this "sketch," as well?
May I ask who they may be?
Teacher Kim...
Oh, I'm sorry to have
interrupted you two.
What is it, Nurse Oh?
I received word that an orthopedic
surgeon from Geosan is on the way.
It seems that Inspector Choi
helped us out. What should I do?
Call our anesthesiologist,
Doctor Nam, first.
Have Kang Dong Joo
and Do In Bum assist.
And please make preparations
for the surgery with Nurse Park.
And call Yoon Seo Jung, too.
She's not a surgeon, but it'll be a good
learning experience for her to assist.
Yes, Doctor. I'll do that.
I'll be going, then.
You're coming too, Senior?
Yep, I got a call.
The patient's vitals aren't
too stable right now
so we really have to be
ready for anything.
Please prepare 10 packs of RBC
and and 10 packs of FFP.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay, then.
Let's get the patient with two
injured legs to the OR first.
- Yes, Doctor.
[DIRECTOR DO YOON WAN]
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
Go ahead, Senior.
All right. We'll get started now.
BP is 100/60.
I can maintain that.
Tourniquet on to 280.
Set it for 90 minutes, please.
Will all of these people
be working with you, too?
I don't know.
I'll have to look into it starting now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Hello.
- Yes.
Oh, would you like me to
wake up Nurse Oh for you?
No, it's okay. Looks like
she was up all last night, huh?
Yes. It hasn't even been an hour
since the surgery ended.
Oh, I see.
Everyone must have worked so hard.
That... was the most spectacular night.
I finally thought of new
characters for my webtoon!
I'll give you this as a
commemorative gift and go.
Wow!
Wow, it's quite cool.
That's nice.
What brings you here
so early in the morning?
You even came to see me yourself.
I wanted to apologize to you
for what happened before
and I wanted to report to you that the
issue regarding Doctor Yoon ended well.
It ended well?
How, exactly?
The psychiatrist's report
about her was good
and the patient who received the
expensive treatment is conscious now.
So you didn't come here to
apologize to me, per se.
You came to rub all of this in my face.
To say that you were right,
and I was wrong.
That's what you came to say, right?
Even if this incident ended like this...
Director Do won't give up.
He has quite a stubborn streak
about him, you see.
I'm sure that you're well
aware of this too, though.
[DIRECTOR DO YOON WAN]
He'll start with what you consider
important and take them, one by one.
Come on... I need to sleep.
And he'll try and touch whatever
you may consider a weakness.
Are you still confident?
Take it.
What did you want
to discuss with me?
And so early in the morning, at that?
How's the tea?
Do you like it?
I heard that your car got towed.
So I told them to get you a new one.
I guess you hadn't heard yet.
Oh man, it's cold.
What time is it now?
Chief Jang.
What are you doing?
I was just sorting the trash.
You were doing that, Chief?
What about Ms. Yeon Hwa?
I believe she quit.
I guess the work was too difficult.
She just left without a word.
Oh, I see.
That's too bad.
You have to do even
this kind of work now.
There's nothing that I cannot do
for the sake of Doldam Hospital.
Well, I'm pretty much
finished cleaning up here.
So I'll get going now.
Ah, that's nice.
[STUDENT ID:
JANG HYUN JOO]
Geosan University.
Surgical Department.
Jang Hyun Joo?
What are you doing?
Teacher Kim.
I'm sorry. The door was open,
so I came in for a bit...
What do you think about Bu Yong Joo?
Do you think that he's a good person?
Or... maybe a genius doctor?
Is that what you think of him?
I want to know why you're
asking me such things, sir.
I thought I'd have to know that
before trying to win you over.
Get out.
Doctor.
Well?
What do you think about
teaming up with me?
Get out!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever