Subtitles by VIU/SA143
(Episode 11) Subtitles by VIU/SA143
(Jang Hyeon Joo)
Geosan University,
College of Medicine. Jang Hyeon Joo?
What are you doing here?
Master Kim.
I'm sorry.
The door was open so I came in for a second...
What do you think of Dr. Boo?
Do you think he is a good person?
Get out.
Master Kim.
I want to know...
why you are asking this question.
I will need your answer...
before getting you on my side.
What do you think?
Do you want to take my hand?
Get out.
Master Kim.
(Medical Office)
I don't know what to say.
You neglected me once. I still remember it like yesterday.
Consider it a progress...
of me testing your worth.
When you become my age,
you'll be able to see things.
Whether the other person is the real deal or not.
Whether that person will make it or not.
So...
Do you think that...
I'm the real deal?
You'll receive 15-percent increase in salary...
and the research fund of 100,000 dollars every year.
I think that's a good start.
It is an exceptionally good offer.
In fact, I don't feel comfortable about that.
Let me show you how it'd be like to be...
on my side.
No matter what you want,
you will get more than that.
I don't think you will do that for me with no strings attached.
What do you want from me in return?
Boo Yong Joo.
I want him.
He wants to operate on the chairman of the foundation.
And it bothers me a lot.
Are you afraid of...
all the spotlights that Master Kim will get...
after the operation?
Even if he gets to perform the operation,
I don't want it to be successful.
What do you mean?
Come on, you know what I mean.
Why did you do that?
What were you doing in Master Kim's office?
I saw Manager Jang rummaging through the garbage can in there.
I just got curious.
Manager Jang did that?
I was just glad that my orderly job was over,
but I'm back on his blacklist again.
What should I do?
You have no choice.
You will just have to face the fact that you will be...
on his blacklist forever.
I think this is all about the student ID
What are you talking about?
I found a student ID with the name Jang Hyeon Joo.
I guess he is mad because of that.
Do you know anything about that?
It says she was a medical student of Geosan University in 1998.
I don't know anything about what happened in Geodae Hospital.
I first met Master Kim...
in the winter of 2002 when the World Cup was held.
I see.
- There's one. - There's what?
There is someone who might know about Jang Hyeon Joo.
- Jang Hyeon Joo? - You started college in 1999...
and started your internship two years late.
Hey, you didn't have to say that I started my internship late.
So do you know Jang Hyeon Joo or not?
I do know.
- But... - But what?
She died in her 2nd or 3rd year...
of medical school.
I heard she died during liver abscess surgery.
(Student ID, Jang Hyeon Joo)
Excuse me.
Do you happen to know who is Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
(Student ID, Jang Hyeon Joo)
Times of concealment of truth.
If you choose,
I will make you the next Dr. Boo.
Times of distorted truth and full of lies.
A success rate of 97 percent in all operations.
I'm the one...
who made the legend of Boo Yong Joo.
How is that even possible?
It is a matter of life and death.
Let's say that I had the marketing point in tune with the times.
The miracle hands.
I got him with the nickname.
I can do the same thing to you.
With all the groundless rumors and vicious gossip,
the essence of a man has to take a back seat.
All you need to do is make up your mind.
What's real?
I will take care...
of the rest.
And what's not real?
We can't even tell what is real in this world.
Do you know...
who performed the liver abscess surgery?
I don't know. We were not that close.
It can't be...
Master Kim, right?
No way!
I know.
Wait. It's not impossible at all.
Dr. Song told me Dr. Boo was kicked out of the hospital...
because he killed a patient.
Dr. Song also mentioned that he killed his student.
- He killed his student? - Wait.
It was 1998, so...
Dr. Boo was kicked out...
in the year of Jang Hyeon Joo's death.
Is it true that she was his student?
This is scary.
I just got goose bumps.
Where is the patient with effusion?
The patient with effusion.
He's in the hybrid room.
(Chapter 11, Psychological Entropy)
Did you go to somewhere?
Yes.
Did you meet with President Do?
Yes, I did.
What did you...
talk about with him?
Do I have to tell you that?
I was just wondering if he said anything about me.
In fact, I got a great offer.
A great offer?
What is that?
A 15-percent increase in salary...
and the research fund of 100,000 dollars every year.
So did you take it?
Did you take it?
Did you take that offer?
Dr. Kang Dong Joo.
I told him I'd think about it.
It was an exceptionally good offer,
so I couldn't take it immediately.
Are you saying...
that you will take it eventually?
Why would I not take it?
It is a great offer.
I should get going.
I'm tired.
- We are ready for thoracentesis. - Okay.
Let's begin.
It's done.
Bring this to the lab.
Yes, Master Kim.
Tell me if it exceeds 1L.
I will need to check his condition.
Okay.
It's done. Thank you.
Why? Do you want to tell me something?
Well, it's...
Do it later if it is not about a patient.
- Master Kim. - Yes?
There you are.
This is an emergency.
What's wrong?
President Do suggested a great offer to Dr. Kang.
A 15-percent increase in salary...
and the research fund of 100,000 dollars every year.
He tried to kick Dr. Yoon out with her pay cut down,
and now he tries to appease Dr. Kang with a pay raise.
The whole scenario is a part of his plan...
to collapse Doldam Hospital.
Don't you think?
What?
To collapse Doldam Hospital?
What's that noise? It's loud.
Hey, can't you hear me?
Don't you see I'm trying to sleep?
I didn't see that. Were you sleeping?
I heard you met President Do.
Did you hear that already?
A 15-percent increase in salary...
and the research fund of 100,000 dollars every year?
So, will you take it?
I'm thinking about it.
Are you saying that you actually want to take it?
If you were me, wouldn't you even consider it?
No, I wouldn't.
Why would he offer such a big money...
to a fellow surgeon like you?
It means he wants something from you.
And you will have to do anything to meet his expectation.
You will be used and manipulated by him.
Eventually, it will destroy your life and conscience.
Don't be so dramatic about it.
I just got a good offer,
and you are destroying my life and conscience already.
There is no such thing as a free lunch.
Based on my own experiences,
that's how life is.
Why are you so worried?
If he wants to go, he'll go. If he doesn't, he won't.
His life may get ruined once he does that because of money.
Do you like him that much?
What are you talking about?
Why do you say that?
Aren't you two dating?
Dating? Who?
Me? With him?
My gosh.
Who said that? Did Dong Joo say that?
No, it looked like that.
Then I guess what you saw is wrong.
No, never.
My gosh. Why would I date him?
Yes, President Yeo.
Right now?
- Who is that? - Hey, Dr. Kang.
I was about to call you.
We have a patient with abdominal pain.
Is Dr. Jung gone?
It's his lunchtime. Should I call him?
No, I got this.
How may I help you?
It's not me. It's my friend.
I see.
Wait.
Can we talk to a different doctor?
I would prefer to see the doctor who stitched up my knee before.
It's lunch time. I'm the only one available.
- Let me take a look. - Okay.
- Ms. Eom. - Yes.
Sir, where do you have pain?
His stomach.
He kept on saying his stomach hurt since yesterday.
Sir, can you lie down?
Turn over slowly.
Let me take a look.
How are his vitals?
It's 100 over 70, 130 beats per minute.
- Check for his temperature. - Yes.
Sir, I will feel your stomach now.
His tenderness is very severe.
His temperature is 39.6°C.
- Bring FAST. - Okay.
Does this hurt?
Sir.
How did you get hurt?
When did you get hurt?
Doctor, can you give him some painkillers first?
Did you hit him?
- No. - Dr. Kang.
Move.
I see some fluid in there.
Could it be trauma hemoperitoneum?
Set up IV lines and hydrate him with two liters.
Mix 50ml of Demerol and 2 ampoules of denogan...
with 100ml of normal saline.
We'll keep him hydrated and start with CT scans.
- Also, check his OP Lab. - Okay.
Sir, we'll give you some painkillers...
and proceed with the CT scan.
Stay here, okay?
Are you okay?
- Ms. Oh. - Yes?
Somethings is odd about them. What should I do?
What do you mean, odd?
That patient with abdominal pain...
looks like he's been beaten badly.
The patient is very conscious about the other guy.
I don't think I should leave them together.
Young Gyun.
- What do we do? - Don't worry.
We'll leave after you get that painkiller.
What?
A lawsuit?
Against who? Me?
Are you the one who collected the blood sample...
of the drunk driver yesterday?
Yes, I am.
Did you know you have offended the law...
by injuring him...
with an unconsented...
blood collection?
What are you saying? I was consented.
- Were you? - Yes.
She got his consent.
Do you have a consent form?
It wasn't a situation where I could fill out a form,
but he gave me the consent with his own words.
He kept insisting on a blood test instead of breathing into a machine.
He has no recollection of giving such a consent.
My gosh.
- Excuse me, we need to talk. - Hey.
I'm about to die.
- Help me. - Just hang in there.
Darn it.
You said it yourself.
You wanted a blood test for your blood alcohol level.
That's why I took your blood sample. What are you trying to do?
Who are you?
Mom.
She's the girl who drew my blood.
I see. It's you.
You are the one who drew out blood from my precious son.
I heard you made a claim for damages.
You can talk to my lawyer about that.
He's our representative.
Son, I brought some soup.
- You can have one, too. - Thank you.
- My goodness. - Did you ask for a lot of meat?
Of course. It's me, your mom.
Eat up.
It's good.
Look at you two.
People have died.
A man died on the site and another died in the emergency room.
There are eight people seriously and lightly injured.
And two road workers even lost their legs!
So what?
How can you eat in such a situation?
How can you play games?
You are unbelievable.
It's not like you paid...
for these soups.
Who are you to say anything about my son having a meal?
His blood-alcohol level was at 0.18 percent.
That's like committing a suicide, driving in that condition.
We'll take care of the law.
We will make compensations with the people affected.
My goodness.
How dare a mere doctor like you come up to me...
and try to teach me?
Are you a judge or something?
Don't you feel...
any guilt or blame as a human being?
A young guy like him can have a drink from time to time,
and he might want to drive!
Didn't you hear that people have died?
This hospital is awful.
- We should get discharged. - Mom.
No.
Police will come after me the moment I walk out.
Our lawyer told us...
to stay here for a while.
This isn't the only hospital around.
You can eat.
- I'll take care of this. - Okay.
Lawyer Hong, it's me.
Some weird doctor came and began to tell us what to do.
She's giving me a headache.
Have you eaten?
It's not hemoperitoneum. It's pan-peritonitis.
It's bowel perforation.
I can see diverticulum,
but I don't think it's diverticulitis perforation.
I think...
it's bowel perforation caused by a trauma.
I saw a bruise on his stomach which looked like a result of a beating.
I think that's more likely.
He has sepsis, so he needs an operation now.
I will do it.
I'll tell Dr. Do...
to assist you.
Ms. Oh.
- Will you call Dr. Do? - Yes.
Aren't you going to ask me anything?
Like what?
I met President Do today.
I thought you'd know already.
Does my knowing change anything?
But still.
I thought you'd say something.
It's your life.
The decision is yours, too.
Our hospital...
can't give you what he offered.
You can choose to go if you'd like.
I thought you wanted me to become a doctor that's needed.
Isn't that what you said?
How can you...
ask me to follow terms and conditions?
I meant that I can't stop you if you wanted those.
Even if I persuade you to stay here with this and that,
you will...
always wonder what lied in the road you haven't taken.
Why did you talk to him like that?
- What do you mean? - I know you don't want to...
let Dr. Kang go.
You could have told him that he's the kind of doctor we need.
That's probably what he wanted to hear.
He's the one who has to make the decisions in his life.
I can't make him to do anything...
against his own will.
Let's just say that he decided to stay here.
Do you think he'll be happy?
Unless he finds the reason...
for him to stay here,
he won't be happy here no matter what.
Dr. Kang respects you.
That's not true at all.
He just wants to learn how to operate like me.
That's about it for him now.
Gosh.
- You know what? - What?
That you're a very twisted man.
- Am I twisted? - Yes, Master Kim.
I don't understand her. Am I in the wrong one here?
Every time he opens his mouth, he tries to lecture someone.
I'm so tired of...
How can someone be so stubborn?
I don't understand how anyone can be so shameless.
There isn't a person in the world who will like him...
if he never speaks from his heart.
Does speaking the truth mean the end of the world to him?
She's not even slightly remorseful for hurting other people.
She even brought her son hangover soup.
I will never understand such irrational people.
I've been working by his side long enough to understand,
but how will a fresh face like Dr. Kang...
be able to understand Master Kim's true intentions?
- Don't you think so? - That's exactly my point.
Did something happen?
He told Dr. Kang that he could leave here any time...
for places with better conditions and that he will not stop him.
What? Are you serious? No way.
That's exactly my point.
What's going on with you, Dr. Yoon?
I just got sued by a DUI assailant.
What?
Is he crazy?
What is this world coming to?
That's exactly my point, Ms. Oh.
Excuse me.
May I help you?
A soldier went AWOL from his base.
We're on a search for him at the moment.
He ran away from his base?
Can I look around the hospital?
Please be quick and don't disturb the patients.
Excuse me.
Slowly.
I'll take you to the operating room now.
Ms. Eom, have you seen the patient on that bed?
Why? Is he not there?
No. His friend is missing, too.
What? That's strange.
What's going on?
It's the young male patient with pan-peritonitis.
I was going to move him to the operating room, but he went missing.
He's missing?
Can you describe what that patient looks like?
How old did he look? What was he wearing?
He looked in his early 20s.
Is this him?
Yes, it is.
- Let's go. - Yes, Sir.
What's going on, Ms. Oh?
He's a run-away soldier.
- What? - What?
- A run-away soldier? - Yes.
The military police in plain clothes are searching the hospital.
The two men are nowhere to be found.
It's not safe for him to move around.
He could die if we don't open him up right now.
Wake up.
Joo Hyuk. Hang in there, Joo Hyuk.
Young Gyun. I...
I'm not going to make it.
I'm...
in pain.
Wake up. Wake up, Joo Hyuk.
No.
Are you coming out of Doldam Hospital?
He shouldn't be going anywhere with the condition he's in.
- Get him on my back. - No.
We can't go back to that hospital.
If my friend goes back there, they'll take him away.
Your friend could die if you don't go back right now.
Dr. Kang. I just got a call from Dr. Nam.
He's on his way to the ER with that run-away soldier.
Aren't you coming?
Can you hear me, Sir?
Sir.
- What happened? - He lost consciousness out there.
- How are his vitals? - It's 80 over 40. This isn't good.
His body temperature is 39.8°C.
How could you take him with you with the condition he's in?
Did you get his consent?
I got it from himself when he still had consciousness.
Okay. Dr. Nam.
I'll be right back after I get changed.
Let's move this patient to the operating room.
Stop.
Hold on.
It's him, Private Park Joo Hyuk. Call it in.
Private Park Joo Hyuk.
Park Joo Hyuk.
You have the right to remain silent,
and anything you say may be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to consult an attorney. Got it?
What are you doing?
Can't you see he's unconscious?
By principle, we have to read AWOL soldiers their Miranda rights.
As of this moment, Private Park is under our control.
You can't do that.
He's a sepsis patient. He could lose his life any minute.
I'll contact the army hospital to transfer him from here.
Can't you see his condition?
He can't afford to lose more time.
If that's the case, you should move him to the operating room right now.
- What's the hold up? - Master Kim.
Are you the person in charge of this hospital?
I wouldn't say I'm in charge of the entire hospital,
but I am responsible for this operation.
He's a run-away soldier.
I'd like to make a request for extradition.
You can do that after we operate on him.
If you keep this up,
you'll be charged with obstruction of justice.
Once the doctor decides that it can't be done,
you're not allowed to transfer the patient.
I'm sure you're aware of interference with medical treatment.
- Doctor. - Yes?
What are you still doing there?
Move him to the operating room.
Okay. Let's move him.
Officer.
Don't worry about it.
He's almost as good as dead.
He's not going to run out of the operating room now.
Do you have the contacts of your friend's parents?
- I do. - Notify them right away.
Tell them that they should come to the hospital as soon as possible.
Okay.
Set up central lines with ODW...
mixed with 32ml of norepinephrine.
- Execute a drop of 10cc per hour. - Yes, Doctor.
What condition is he in?
It's 70 over 40. He's barely holding on.
- Shall we start? - Okay.
What are you doing?
Master Kim told me to record this operation.
Let's begin, Dr. Kang.
Scalpel.
I'll report back to you right away.
The situation is complicated.
No, Sir.
They seem pretty busy.
- I'll take care of it discreetly. - It's a run-away solider...
being operated in a general hospital.
No wonder they're busy.
Whenever some internal violence happens in the military,
at least one of the high personnel ends up getting fired.
Have you served in the military? Army? Navy? Or the air force?
What?
Why do you ask?
I'm just curious.
Which unit were you in?
Well, it's a...
- A... - The army?
- I see. - Yes.
Dr. Yoon, you're here.
May I see you?
What could Dr. Song want with me?
I don't know.
Did you want...
me?
Dr. Yoon.
Did you threaten a patient today?
Pardon?
Threaten?
Why did you run into their room...
and say unnecessary things like...
that they should feel sorry,
and that many people died because of him?
You shouldn't display...
your feeble heart of justice in public, Dr. Yoon.
A doctor...
should only do what a doctor should.
Apologize to them. Immediately.
What did you say?
Didn't you hear?
Apologize to them.
I can't.
What?
Right.
I was overemotional.
I did run to them...
and tell them about the people he hurt.
I know that I shouldn't have gone that far.
However, I won't apologize.
Dr. Yoon!
This is unbelievable.
They can...
walk out of here with a few pain relief patches right now,
and they'll be totally fine.
Their car was such an expensive car,
and six airbags went off.
They are not hurt at all.
They are sitting here because they don't want to get arrested.
Hey, Miss. Are you finished?
I'm not a Miss.
I'm Dr. Yoon Seo Jung.
Unbelievable.
Your hospital is a mess, Dr. Song.
My gosh.
I haven't been here for long.
Where are your manners?
Apologize immediately.
Apologize on everything including what you just said.
Like I said, I won't.
Are you going against the words of the head surgeon?
Please only give me orders which I can comply with, Sir.
If you are finished,
I'll be leaving.
Look at her.
Hey, Dr. Yoon!
Stop right there!
Dr. Yoon.
What will you make of me if you leave like this?
She is...
the wife of the provincial assembly, Han Gi Jun,
who's also a close friend of the governor.
So what?
What does he have to do with me...
let alone his wife?
You don't know the real world.
What I mean is she is someone...
you should calm by apologizing...
regardless of your opinion about her.
Why would I do that?
I'm not a politician or a public worker.
Like you said, I'm a doctor.
You said I just need to do what a doctor does.
Then why would I need to apologize to someone like her?
That's the order of this world.
Dr. Yoon!
Let's go and apologize. It'll make things so much easier.
I will talk to her...
into dropping the charges against you.
Forget about it and tell her to sue me.
My goodness!
Darn it.
Hey! Dr. Yoon!
Turn in a written apology and explanation by tomorrow!
Do you understand?
I'll get him.
- Please come with me. - To where?
Wait.
Get up and sit here.
Hey.
I already got checked up.
Where are we going?
(Intensive Care Unit)
- What are you doing? - Look at them.
Look at what you've done.
Did you say you'll compensate with money?
Do you think their lives are compensable with money?
Look at them!
You'll only realize what you've done only after you see this.
Money is your talent.
Your rich mother is your supporter.
That's great.
That's great, but...
shouldn't you at least learn...
what conscience is?
What are you doing over there?
Mom.
My...
Hey!
- Did you just hit me? - Yes, I did.
What will you do? Press charges against me?
Go ahead.
How dare you make my son cry?
Who do you think you are?
Why are you so shameless?
- Don't you know what you've done? - What did you say?
You feel no guilt and you have no shame.
Since when did the world...
let people like you get powerful?
- How dare you say... - Forget about it.
I will file a counter-charge of your assault.
There will be...
no settlement or compromise whatsoever.
Who does she think she is?
My goodness. She's unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
My goodness.
Who on earth is she?
The inflammation is only within the perforation site.
It's not in the diverticulum, is it?
Definitely not.
It's definitely caused by a trauma.
They must have beat him to death.
Do you think he was bullied by the entire infantry?
I understand why he would want to run away after this.
We'll conduct bowel resection...
and functional end-to-end anastomosis.
Dr. Kang, his blood pressure is dropping.
- Increase norepinephrine to 20cc. - Okay.
- Is he okay? - I think he's in a septic shock.
- We must hurry. - Okay.
GIA, please.
Specimen.
Saline, please.
Keep it coming.
Master Kim.
- Master Kim. - Yes?
- I've been looking for you. - Why?
You have to come to the president's room.
Dr. Yoon got herself into a trouble again.
The discipline of this hospital is unacceptable.
She ignores the order of a head surgeon.
And she crossed the line with her words to a patient...
and his guardian.
Look at this.
This is unacceptable, isn't it?
I thought about letting this go,
but I get angrier the more I think about this.
I won't let this pass.
Kneel down and apologize immediately.
I must receive her apology.
What are you doing?
She said you should apologize.
- Pardon? - Apologize to her.
Bowing to her at a 45-degree angle would be enough.
What do you mean by that?
You see...
I heard what she said,
but I don't think Dr. Yoon did something to deserve to kneel down.
However, she kept requesting for an apology.
We can't just ignore her request.
Ma'am, why don't we...
settle this with a 45-degree bow?
Wait a second. Master Kim.
I forgot. We need you to apologize first.
- What are you talking about? - You hit her.
Then, you should apologize to her first.
even if you won't compensate her.
Are you kidding?
Do I look like I'm kidding?
So is that how you're going to deal with this?
All right, then. It seems you don't want to apologize to me.
Let's let the law decide.
I'll make sure to humiliate...
both you and that lady doctor.
Go ahead, then.
I'm an expert at dirty fights.
What's wrong with you? You should resolve the situation.
Dr. Yoon's apology will resolve all. Why are you making it complicated?
Gosh.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Rich people have so much...
to lose through a dirty fight.
What did you say?
President Yeo and Manager Jang are...
such gentlemen that they can't fight dirty.
But I'm different.
I'm such an ignorant person. When I get angry,
I wouldn't mind doing anything to get what I want.
I feel sorry for you.
You might lose everything.
Are you threatening me?
You're the one who threatened first.
You mistreat others using your money and your husband's power.
How dare you say such a thing?
Your son caused a six-car rear-end collision while drunk driving.
Then, you came to the hospital,
and pushed a doctor around.
You even slapped her in the face.
It would be so funny if this story is on the newspaper.
- Are you sure about this? - You...
Darn it.
Gosh.
Please apologize to her first.
If you don't, she won't apologize to you, either.
Why do you keep smirking like that?
It's the first time you have taken my side.
I'm on cloud nine.
It means I've been recognized as your student, right?
Am I right?
Who says you're my student?
- Am I not? - I don't keep students.
Is it true that she was his student?
(Student ID, Jang Hyeon Joo)
I'll still be your student even if you don't think of me as one.
My dream is to become like you.
Remain impartial with your patients from now on.
Even if he did something wrong, he's just a patient to you.
Do you hear me?
Yes, Master Kim.
I'll bear that in mind, Master Kim.
Excuse me.
I am sorry.
I am really...
My goodness.
(Intensive Care Unit)
Hello? This is ICU.
One patient will go there soon. Please prepare a bed.
That's impossible.
Everyone in the ICU needs to be monitored until today.
No bed is available in the ICU. What should we do?
Let's take the patient to the hybrid room for now.
Can we take care of him in there?
I'll stay with him.
Let's keep him there until there's a bed available in the ICU.
Yes, Dr. Nam.
- Please keep that for Pathology. - Yes, Dr. Kang.
Let's move the patient.
Run the arterial blood gas analysis.
Yes, Dr. Nam.
He doesn't look so good.
- What are his vital signs? - The BP is 80 over 40, and 130.
What was the highest dosage of norepinephrine?
- It was 20cc per minute. - Double the dosage, please.
Is urine coming out?
- No. - Check his OP Lab again.
- Do we have the ABGA result? - Yes, it's here.
The acidosis is severe, too.
Give him three ampules of sodium bicarbonate not through CVC.
Yes, Dr. Kang.
- Is his guardian here? - Not yet.
The patient is in a critical condition.
Did the surgery go wrong?
The surgery was successful.
We completed his abdominal operation successfully.
However,
he has severe intra-abdominal infection.
He developed septic shock due to peritonitis.
What will happen to him, then?
We're giving him vasopressor drugs for now,
but If his blood pressure keeps dropping despite that,
his organs would be damaged,
and in the end,
he may die.
I see.
If you think of the probability...
what's the probability that he'll die?
We can't be sure about it now.
In fact, it seems that the cause...
of his injury is external shocks.
What do you mean by external shock?
To put it simply, he's been beaten up.
He has bruises on different parts to think only one person beat him.
It is highly likely...
that he was gang-beaten by two or more people.
Are you...
saying...
that he was bullied by other soldiers?
I'm telling you about the cause of his injury.
I see.
- Good shot. - Good shot.
Hello. It's been a long time.
I have been quite busy. I couldn't call you often.
What is the matter?
I see.
I understand what you mean.
I'll take care of it as quietly as possible.
Bye.
Yes, President Do.
I was worried because you have been avoiding my calls.
A run-away soldier was taken to that hospital today, right?
Is that so?
Why do you not know what happens in that hospital?
I'm sorry. I'll go look into it right away.
Find out who operated on him,
and check the patient's condition.
See if he'll make it through tonight, too.
Yes, I will.
(Information Desk)
Dr. Kang.
- Yes? - I heard we have a deserter here.
He moved to the hybrid room after the operation.
- The intensive care unit is full. - I see.
Did you perform the operation?
Yes. Why?
I see.
Doctor, he's in cardiac arrest.
Inject 1ml of epinephrine every 3 minutes.
- What's going on? - His vital signs dropped rapidly.
Now he is in PEA arrest.
I will check his pulse.
- PEA compression. - I will do that.
President Do, it's me.
Things are not going well here.
The patient is in arrest.
It seems Dr. Kang performed the operation.
It says Dr. Kang is his doctor in the chart.
(General Surgery, Kang Dong Joo)
Okay. I will be there soon.
Okay.
Do we need the death certificate...
with death from disease?
Okay. I will do that.
Did someone die?
What do you mean?
I heard you...
talking about a death certificate.
I'm just wondering who is it for.
I don't understand what you mean.
Are you saying...
that I'm hearing things or what?
Excuse me.
Why does he keep rolling his eyes at me?
I will check his pulse.
It's back.
His vital signs are still unstable.
The BP is 70 over 60, and 100 beats.
He has no light reflex...
and no stem sign.
At this rate, he will soon have brain death.
Master Kim.
Is he your friend?
Can you please go check my friend?
Don't worry. His doctor is treating him now.
He is young, but he is an experienced doctor.
Dr. Kang.
Can I see you for a moment?
Go see him. Dr. Nam and I will take care of the patient.
I will be right back. Call me if something happens.
By the way,
why did your friend run away from the army?
Can you tell me...
how he got hurt?
Have a seat.
- What's the matter? - I need to ask you something.
Open it.
(Medical Certificate of Death)
(Park Joo Hyuk, Born on October 31, 1995)
(Death from Disease)
(Dr. Kang Dong Joo)
They are having an important meeting.
I see. I will join the meeting.
What is going on?
What are you doing here?
President Do won't stand for you any longer.
He will...
take away things...
that matter to you...
one by one.
So,
what are you going to do?
Let's say...
I will help you keep Doldam Hospital with my money.
But...
I can't change a person's mind with money.
What's your plan?
What's your plan to protect your people?
(Dr. Romantic)
Let me ask you a question.
Why did you become a doctor?
The choices you make show...
that you are no different from them.
We can't do that with the death certificate.
You can't disregard the truth.
It's not that the truth is always right.
I will never forgive you.
I will never forgive doctors like you.
Stop making a fool of young people...
to satisfy your selfish interests and desires.
I swear I will stick my neck out...
to disqualify you.
Don't ever come back to Doldam Hospital again.
I will make you regret it from now on.