(Medical Certificate of Death)
(Park Joo Hyuk, Born on October 31, 1995)
(Death from Disease)
(Dr. Kang Dong Joo)
What...
- is this? - Just sign the paper...
and submit it.
This patient is still alive.
He's alive.
- I don't understand. - His vital signs are dropping,
and no urine.
He's in arrest with no stem sign.
It means he is about to have brain death.
Patients may have no stem sign right after the ROSC.
We have to wait at least for 1 to 2 days before making any decision.
And death from disease?
This is the medical record of the patient from the military hospital.
It says he has been treated...
for diverticulum for some time.
- Just for your information. - It was not about diverticulum.
It was definitely trauma hemoperitoneum.
I cut his abdomen open and saw it with my eyes.
He is a deserter.
Do you want to say...
violent death for a man like him?
Don't you think...
it can be a sensitive issue?
What if...
the fact becomes public?
Much noise will be...
raised all about it on the internet and everything.
And they will end up...
firing some middle managers for no reason.
It'd be so irresponsible of us to do that, don't you think?
So...
do you want me...
to lie about the patient?
I want you to make a rational decision.
So...
you are telling me to lie...
about a patient who is clearly still alive...
by signing the death certificate?
There are times...
when silence can be better than the truth.
And I think this is the time.
I'm sorry,
but I'll pretend I wasn't here.
Kang Dong Joo.
Don't be childish...
by demonstrating your bravado.
You are a grown-up.
As a doctor,
and as a member of the society,
I want you to act more responsibly, okay?
Let's stay quiet...
and make it simple, Dong Joo.
What is going on?
What are you doing here?
What are you all doing together?
What are you conspiring about?
President Do.
(Episode 12)
Young Gyun.
What happened to my boy?
Where is Joo Hyuk?
My boy.
Joo Hyuk.
Gosh.
My goodness.
He is in arrest, Dr. Yoon.
Page Dr. Kang, Ms. Oh.
Can you give us some space, please?
- Please, Ma'am. - Ma'am.
Excuse me.
Joo Hyuk.
Doctor.
(Emergency Room)
Yes, Ms. Oh. I'm on my way.
- What is it? - He is in second arrest.
Bring the defibrillator. Quickly.
(Medical Certificate of Death)
200J.
Move.
Shock.
Commencing compression.
Let me.
Checking his pulse.
Let's try again. Charge 200J.
Ready, Dr. Kang.
Shock.
Come back.
You're still young.
You have to come back.
(Death from Disease)
Come back.
Dr. Kang.
Time of death.
It's 8:48pm.
(Dr. Kang Dong Joo)
(Chapter 12, The Boiling Point)
(Seoul to Jeongseon)
- Is this the one? - It's the one behind it.
Okay.
By the way,
how do I get to Doldam Hospital from here?
(Doldam Hospital)
Our deepest condolences...
for the outcome of the circumstances.
The funeral procedure...
will be arranged by the military forces.
Thank you.
I'm sorry that he ran away from his base.
I appreciate you doing this.
Let us know if you need any help.
Goodbye.
Joo Hyuk was murdered.
What?
What are you talking about, Young Gyun?
Three of his superiors...
beat him and punished him every day for no reason.
That's why he didn't go back to his base.
That's why he died.
Shut it.
You can't say those things without any proof.
The parents of Private Park Joo Hyuk...
must be very confused right now.
Even the doctor who operated on him said that.
He said Joo Hyuk's injuries were result of an assault.
I heard him saying that to you.
I heard him say it, Mr. Park.
Go ask the doctor.
He'll tell you what really happened.
The doctor.
Where can I find him?
I'll take you to him.
Would you come with me?
(Medical Certificate of Death)
You've got to do it.
Do you think...
that I like doing this for President Do?
I just don't want to get on the wrong side of him.
I'm not intending on living my life as a minority.
I want to be part of a mainstream.
You're too young to realize how important this is.
Once you get to my age, you'll see.
The way you see in life changes once you get in your 40s.
The world becomes a completely different place...
depending on whether you join the mainstream or not.
President Do is the only person you have to kneel down.
If you do that,
your whole life will be changed.
Do you understand?
Dr. Kang.
Park Joo Hyuk's parents want to ask you something.
Are you free right now?
Please come in.
Hello.
I'm Joo Hyuk's father.
Did you say that...
Joo Hyuk was beaten?
Is it true?
Please, Doctor.
He was healthy and well just until two months ago.
How did he end up like that?
We have to know.
Please tell us...
what you know.
Please, Doctor.
Doctor.
What are you doing, Dr. Kang?
Answer them.
I...
need to look over the records.
I have to check...
his medical records from the military hospital.
It may take a little while...
until I can write a medical certificate of death.
Goodbye, then.
Where are you going?
I just need some air.
Why did you do that?
- Why? - You knew about his bruises...
and you saw the enterobrosia during the surgery.
Why didn't you tell them anything?
Are you listening?
Hello?
Are you listening to me, Dr. Kang?
I'm just tired.
I'll talk to you later.
What's with him?
(Doldam Hospital)
Welcome.
Dong Joo.
I'm sorry if I am interrupting something.
You're not interrupting anything.
Come in, come in.
Are you here to grab a drink...
or to have dinner?
I need a bottle of soju.
Sure.
(Medical Certificate of Death)
(Mother)
Taxi.
Here.
It's on me.
Drink.
If you can't drink it,
you don't have to.
No.
I can.
Do you want another round?
Sure.
Are they chugging drinks?
Master Kim and Dr. Kang?
Chugging drinks?
He says so.
How much did they drink?
They are on their eighth bottle of soju.
Eight bottles?
When did you find out?
- What? - About me.
That I am the boy who turned the ER upside down.
Since when did you know?
Let me ask you a question, too.
Why did you become a doctor?
Do you remember what you said?
If you want revenge,
revenge with your skills.
That's why.
I wanted to show everyone that I am not a sissy.
I no longer wanted...
anyone to disregard me.
I wanted to show them...
that I am different from them.
But...
look at the choices you make.
You are no different from them.
Because I can't end up here.
I have to go up the ladder.
That way, I can...
at least stand up against President Do or someone else.
Is that why...
you were keen to take 15-percent increase in salary...
with 100,000 dollars of research fund annually?
If you accept that,
does that make you go up that ladder?
You are hiding under President Do...
and giving him your loyalty.
Then you'll become the head surgeon.
Your name will be all over the academic journals.
Is that...
the success you've been running after?
That's how the world is.
This world calls that a success.
If I don't make it...
into the mainstream, I become a nobody.
Is that why you want to abandon your pride...
and your conscience?
No shame...
and no pride?
If you live as a nobody,
does that keep your pride?
If you have no power,
how can you keep your conscience?
Do you know how much it hurts to be humiliated...
because you have no power and no money?
Do you know?
That's right.
Greed is often...
self-justified.
"I couldn't help it."
"That was the only choice I could make."
Hey, Dong Joo.
It looks like...
you are sick with greed,
not your conscience.
It's not like you can read my thoughts.
- Got that? - I do know a little bit about...
the dilemma your kinds feel...
between your reality and ideals.
But...
a surgeon who has someone's life in their hands...
should also live with the responsibility...
as heavy as a person's life.
Do remember that.
This is the video footage of Private Park's operation.
You can do whatever you'd like.
You can keep it, throw it...
or do whatever else you wish.
But it's on you.
Do Il, keep the bill on my tab.
Okay.
- Excuse me. - I'm sorry, we're closed.
I'm not here to get treated.
Are you here to pay your bills?
Then please proceed to counter number three.
I'm looking for Dong Joo.
Dr. Yoon, where are you going?
It's about that jerk, Dong Joo.
He's at On Your Way and completely drunk.
My goodness. He's so annoying.
If he was going to drink, he should be responsible.
Excuse me, Dr. Yoon.
Or he could have gone home and had a couple of drinks.
- Dr. Yoon. - I'm too old for this.
Do I have to go out at this hour, in this weather...
to take care of my drunk junior...
instead of working?
Isn't that right, In Beom?
Isn't that right, Manager Jang?
What's wrong?
This is Dr. Kang's mother.
Hello. I'm glad to meet you.
She is Dr. Yoon Seo Jung of Emergency Medicine.
I see.
It's nice to meet you.
I guess Dong Joo lives here, right?
Yes. We have a company house around here,
but Dong Joo...
Dr. Kang feels...
more comfortable in this staff room.
As you know, Dong Joo is... Gosh.
Dr. Kang...
gets very stubborn once he decides to be.
Tell me about it.
He is just like his father.
But at the same time, I think...
he could study so hard because of his stubborn streak.
You are right. I think so.
Would you like to have something to drink?
You don't need to feel so nervous and uncomfortable around me.
Okay.
Let's just have one more round.
Let's go to a karaoke room. It's on me.
What's wrong with him?
- Dong Joo. - It's on me.
Why did you drink so much?
Dr. Kang Dong Joo.
What?
It's Seo Jung.
You are here, my precious Seo Jung.
What are you doing? Get off me.
Get off.
Stop it. Why are you doing this to me?
Your mother is here. Get off me.
Hey.
Do you know...
how much I like you?
Hey. Pull yourself together.
I told you to let go of me.
Didn't you hear me?
I said...
I like you a lot.
Gosh.
Get off of me!
Dong Joo.
Dong Joo, are you okay?
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Hey, Dong Joo. Are you all right?
Hey, Dong Joo.
It's hot.
Well... Where is Dr. Kang?
What's wrong, Dr. Yoon?
Did something happen?
I just want to sink deep under my feet.
Dong Joo.
Dong Joo?
The doctor named Seo Jung.
Do you like her?
I do.
I do like her.
I like her.
Gosh.
(Doldam Hospital)
(Kang Dong Joo is not a doctor. He is a murderer.)
Kang...
Who did this?
Oh, my goodness.
Who did this stupid thing? Gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
(Kang Dong Joo is not a doctor. He is a murderer.)
I searched through the whole building...
and collected all the flyers in sight.
Oh, gosh.
There you are.
Well...
Who is doing this to Dong Joo?
I'm wondering the same thing. The staffs are working on it.
Is Dr. Kang here yet?
What should we do? His mother came here to see him yesterday.
(Kang Dong Joo is not a doctor. He is a murderer.)
Mom?
Dong Joo.
You are up.
What are you doing here?
I came here to see you.
- When? - Last night.
Why did you drink so much? Don't drink too much.
Do you want some water?
Do you have some honey here?
- I guess you don't. - No.
Okay.
I will send you some honey...
as soon as I go back to Seoul.
Drink it.
Drink.
Wait.
Is there anything you can have?
Let me see.
Gosh.
(Kang Dong Joo is not a doctor. He is a murderer.)
Who are you?
What are you doing there?
What do you think you are doing?
(Kang Dong Joo is not a doctor. He is a murderer.)
What on earth are you doing?
I'm demonstrating against him.
Stop it, or I will call the police.
Call the police.
You should protect him. You are a doctor like him.
Just do it.
- What? - I will do this again and again...
even if I get arrested.
I will keep giving out the flyers no matter what...
until he gets kicked out from the hospital.
Just bring it on.
Who are you?
Why are you...
posting up the flyers here?
Did you forget it already?
You killed my father.
You postponed my father's operation for some former senator...
called Go Man Suk or something.
Don't you remember?
What do you mean the operation has been postponed?
Is there something wrong with my dad?
We'll have to wait and see for a few more days...
and decide on the date of the operation again.
Doctor.
Are you...
Mr. Seo Myung Hoon's daughter?
You remember the name.
Did he pass away?
Yes. He died.
After you postponed his operation,
they kept changing his doctor and the operation kept being postponed.
After that, he passed away from acute sepsis.
Why did you postpone the operation?
His operation was scheduled first.
Is it because the other man was a VIP...
and my dad was a nobody?
How can you...
You can't be discriminate with people's lives at stake.
Do you call yourself a doctor?
You're not supposed to be like that.
How can you play with people's lives?
Doctors aren't supposed to be like that.
My dad was there first.
My dad was here first.
My dad was...
here before that person.
You have to treat my dad first.
I will never forgive you.
I will never forgive doctors like you.
I will bring shame to your name.
I swear I will stick my neck out...
to disqualify you.
(Kang Dong Joo is not a doctor. He is a murderer.)
Kang Dong Joo.
Don't let it get you down.
I'll contact the police and sort this mess out.
You don't need to worry at all.
No. Don't help him with that.
Let's just see how things pan out.
But Master Kim...
If we don't do anything, Dr. Kang and Doldam Hospital's
reputation will be tarnished.
There's nothing to worry about.
People forget after some time.
For now,
you just have to go through with it.
The hospital will clear your name later.
He has to go through with it.
If someone solves this problem for him,
he'll never learn from it.
But his mother is here to see him.
Don't worry about your mother.
I'll make sure that she doesn't get the wrong idea.
Being a doctor is harder than people can ever imagine.
Your mother has to know that.
Did you hand in the medical certificate of death?
You just...
get that done and over with.
I'll take care of the rest.
Got it?
This man killed my father.
His name is Kang Dong Joo and he's a doctor here.
(Medical Certificate of Death)
(Death from Disease)
(Death from Violence)
Kang Dong Joo.
Did you not hand in that medical certificate of death?
Private Park Joo Hyuk's parents...
were up all night waiting.
Hey, Dr. Kang.
I have to think things through.
About what?
It's a medical certificate of death. There's no need to think.
You just need to put down the facts.
It's not that the truth is always right.
Where is this coming from?
He's a deserter.
Can you imagine how messy it'll get...
if we declare him death from violence?
I can't not stop thinking about...
the consequences that will bring.
And why in the world do you have to think about that?
You're just the doctor who operated on the patient.
The doctor's job is to convey the facts.
Is it included...
under that incredible offer...
with 15-percent increase in salary...
and 100,000 dollars' worth of research funding?
I told you this might happen.
I told you that you might end up betraying your conscience.
It's not like that. Don't jump to conclusions.
Are you sure?
Just...
Just leave me alone for a moment.
Disregarding the truth isn't right on its own,
but when it comes to death certificates,
you should never disregard the truth because of the external pressure,
okay?
In any case...
you are tempted by those things,
I'll be...
immensely disappointed in you.
Dr. Kang. The police have arrived.
This man killed my father.
This is illegal what you're doing here, Miss.
- Let go! - This is privately owned land.
If you're going to protest, you'll need permission by the police first.
This man killed my father.
His name is Kang Dong Joo and he's a doctor here.
- Please take a look at it. - That's enough, Miss.
This man killed my father.
- His name is Kang Dong Joo and... - You have to come with us.
I'm not going anywhere. Let go!
I apologize.
What are you doing?
Why are you apologizing?
This man, Kang Dong Joo...
is my son.
My son has committed a grave sin.
This is all my fault.
It's all my fault.
I apologize.
Please forgive him.
I'm really sorry.
- Mom. - Save it.
You've done wrong.
Apologize to her.
Don't you remember how your father died?
How could you do this?
You shouldn't have.
Apologize to her until she can forgive you.
Do it.
(Kang Dong Joo is not a doctor. He's a murderer.)
Please...
- leave her alone. - What?
But we received a report. We have to deal with this.
It's all right.
Let her be...
and leave her alone.
No words...
can justify my actions.
I wish I could go back in time...
and make things...
right again.
I'm filled with regrets...
and ashamed.
You are a horrible man.
My deepest...
apologies.
You horrible man.
Bring my dad back.
Bring him back.
Dad.
Isn't that Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
Is he Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
That's him. He's Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
What is he doing here?
President Do, it's me.
What did you say?
Who showed up in this hospital?
You can't do this. I said, you can't do this.
I'll call you back.
What a surprise.
What brings you all the way here?
I have something to tell you.
You could have just called me. Why did you...
How dare you!
Never come to Doldam Hospital again.
Also, stop taking advantage of young people...
to satisfy your selfish interests and desires.
Let Dong Joo and Seo Jung go.
Stop confusing them.
From now on,
I won't let you do it to them. Is that clear?
(Medical Certificate of Death)
Do you not even feel ashamed?
How could you...
try to make the young people do such a thing at your age?
You pathetic jerk.
(Medical Certificate of Death)
This is your son's...
medical certificate of death.
(Death from External Causes)
And this is...
the video of your son's surgery...
performed by me.
This will be enough evidence.
If...
you need me to testify...
in order to prove the truth,
please contact me any time.
My wife says,
"Thank you."
I am sorry...
that it's too late, ma'am.
Please don't say that.
You let us know what truly caused our son's death.
We can't ask for more.
Thank you.
What's this?
(Death from External Causes)
Dong Joo must be out of his mind.
Dong Joo, stop there.
Are you completely out of your mind?
Why are you trying to do?
I just did what I learned.
A medical certificate of death is...
the last thing that a doctor can do...
for the patient and the family.
Why don't you get it?
President Do ordered not to leave anything that can cause controversy.
Don't you know what will happen if you go against him?
I do know.
Also,
I know how shameful it is to follow that order.
Is it that hard to ignore the feeling of shame just once?
I just...
didn't want to get caught.
What?
Also,
I came to think...
that this might be a place where I can pretend to be a nice person.
The thought came across my mind.
I think Doldam Hospital is that kind of place.
Are you saying...
that you wouldn't mind if you can't return to Geodae Hospital...
forever?
Are you sure you won't regret it?
Maybe.
I'm sorry that you had to see me like that.
Did you expect...
it would be easy to save people's lives?
Unexpected things happen while you work.
I don't think...
I can return to Geodae Hospital for a while.
That's okay.
The hospital you're working at now doesn't seem so bad.
I also like the lady who is your senior doctor.
My senior doctor?
You know.
The lady you call Seo Jung.
The doctor in the emergency room.
How do you know Seo Jung?
Do you really not remember anything?
Did you completely black out?
What happened?
If you want to know, go ask her.
Even though you're my son,
it's embarrassing to say it myself.
Why are you laughing? Why?
(Doldam Hospital)
Did you see your mother off?
Of course.
Did you give the death certificate to the parents?
Yes, I surely gave it to them.
About last night...
You shouldn't talk about what you did while you were drunk.
That's the manner you should keep if you know how to enjoy drinking.
Anyway, you lost the 15-percent increase of salary,
and the research fund of 100,000 dollars every year.
Since you got on the wrong side of President Do,
you won't be able to return to Geodae Hospital for a while.
Poor you.
You will have to stay at this awful hospital a little longer.
I guess so.
I lost the chance to get a good raise...
and a chance to return to Geodae Hospital.
I have to spend a long winter in this awful hospital.
It's already so frustrating.
That's why I'll ask you this.
Go out with me, Seo Jung.
Are you joking with me?
Is that a no?
Can't I...
date you?
No.
You can't.
What's the reason?
I want to know why you're avoiding me.
Can't you tell me?
Yes. I can't.
You like me, too.
Don't you?
Did you say you'll ask me out three times?
One more to go.
What are you doing here?
What?
Well, I was...
on my way to the emergency room.
Hello, Father.
You have to do something.
What did you say?
Do you have a date for me to get hospitalized?
Yes.
We finally have the date.
You can come in...
tomorrow afternoon whenever you want to.
Then...
are we doing the operation right away?
I'll check your condition...
for 2 to 3 days...
after you're hospitalized.
Will you do that with the machines I got you?
Yes. I'll do with those machines.
If nothing is out of the usual,
your operation will be held early next week.
It's a simple operation.
You won't have to be in the hospital for long.
Make sure you are...
a part of that operation.
I'm just a general surgeon. How could I...
You have to come up with a way to get into that operation.
You can use your head for once.
Tell me everything which happens...
in that operation.
I need...
to know everything.
Really? Did Seo Jung do that?
After that day,
she's been reading all of the related articles.
I thought you should know.
Do you have an operation team in your mind?
I do have a vague picture.
I will sleep on it for a couple more days...
until I am completely decided.
I see.
I hope Dr. Yoon gets a chance this time.
It's just...
my wish, though.
Goodbye, Ms. Oh.
What brings you here?
Why? What is it? Tell me.
It's about...
Chairman Shin's operation.
It's not much of an operation.
We're just changing the batteries of his artificial heart.
May I be...
the first assistant?
Why? You're a general surgeon.
When I was an intern,
I have participated in heart transplant operation once.
I've also been...
in aortic dissection once,
four times at cardiovascular bypass operation,
ECMO operation once,
and VAD operation twice.
If you take the first assistant,
that will push back Dr. Yoon.
Do you understand that?
Is there...
any way I can participate?
Don't you look forward to this?
Who will become...
a part of Master Kim's operation?
I'm not sure.
Whoever that may be,
he or she is very lucky.
(We thank Hwang Chan Sung for his special appearance.)