- What brings you here?
- It's about...
Chairman Shin's operation.
May I be the first assistant?
Times of needs.
Make sure you are...
a part of that operation.
Tell me everything which happens...
in that operation.
The others' needs are prioritized...
over one's own decisions.
Do you have experience in cardiothoracic surgery?
Before you even realize what you really want,
the world forces you...
adapt to its standards.
When I was an intern,
I have participated in heart transplant operation once.
It makes you say things.
I've also been in aortic dissection once,
four times at cardiovascular bypass operation,
Things get exaggerated.
ECMO operation once,
and VAD operation twice.
Sometimes, you lie about what you say.
It sure is...
good to have a powerful dad.
You're more experienced than I thought.
Back then, I was in a dilemma...
where I couldn't decide whether I should be a GS or a CS.
If you take the first assistant,
that will push back Dr. Yoon.
Do you understand that?
Is there...
any way I can participate?
In the end,
it requires you to make others fall in despair.
This is the world we live in.
When do you plan to operate on Chairman Shin?
I made a request...
to the manufacturer for the parts I need.
They told me that it'll be...
either this weekend or early next week.
Do you have an operation team in your mind?
I'm not sure.
Our only cardiothoracic surgery doctor is not in a good condition.
You said it won't be a difficult operation...
because you only need to change the batteries.
There might be something wrong with the artificial heart itself.
I see.
Recently,
there had been many reports made...
on the defects of Chairman Shin's artificial heart.
Have you come up with a specific operation schedule?
I have to take many variables into account.
It'll probably be 10 days from now.
What? 10 days?
Do you think she understood?
I think so.
(9 DAYS LEFT)
(8 DAYS LEFT)
- Dr. Yoon.
- Yes?
You got a parcel.
I see.
It got here faster than I thought.
What's in there?
(FROM JK MEDICAL TO YOON SEO JUNG OF DOLDAM HOSPITAL)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(6 DAYS LEFT)
Purse string suture?
Have you done it before?
We use it to finish off an acute appendicitis operation.
Is it difficult?
The suture method itself isn't too hard,
but you need to be careful because serosa is very thin.
The serosa is about 2 to 3mm thick and you need to suture that.
- That's very thin.
- You need experiences.
Well, I guess being experienced is a part of your ability.
What about veins? Have you ever done it on veins before?
Veins?
No, you need to relax.
When you suture organs, you have to use the right amount of pressure.
If you use too much pressure, it rips, but if not, it won't work.
I know that much.
Do you want to do this alone?
No, Dr. Kang. Please continue.
See.
Now, the essence of purse string suture is...
to stitch up as thin as you can.
You must stick a needle into the blood vessel,
and pull it out right before you reach intima.
What if I cut through the endoderm?
General surgeons like me can wash out the excrements...
from the bowel.
But for cardiac surgeons...
The pressure in the aorta...
will cause blood to shoot out into the ceiling.
My gosh.
Why? Does your hand still hurt?
It's been fine.
But it does get a bit stiff when I get too focused or stressed out.
Let me see that.
You go from here...
to here.
Use your wrist to snap out.
- Let me try.
- Okay.
Like this.
- And this.
- No, it has to be thinner here.
- Like this.
- And snap.
Go in as thinly as you can and turn out right before the intima.
Like this.
That's it.
- Like this?
- Okay.
- Good.
You're good.
One more time.
Go in a little harder.
- Okay.
- That's it.
- You're great.
- It was okay, right?
Manager Jang.
What's going on?
Master Kim is finally...
about to announce the staff members of his operation on Chairman Shin.
As you all know,
Chairman Shin will be hospitalized here as of tomorrow.
We'll get prepared for the operation to change the batteries,
but things may change anytime after we conduct some examinations.
So remember that.
I'll hold a conference about the operation...
tomorrow at 8pm after the patient comes in.
Make sure all of you are prepared.
Then...
who will be the first assistant of this operation?
The first assistant of...
Chairman Shin's operation is...
Seo Jung.
You'll take the position.
That's all.
(CHAPTER 13, THE ART OF TURMOIL)
Everyone, It's finally the day.
The chairman of the foundation,
the secretive supporter of Doldam Hospital,
Chairman Shin will be...
hospitalized here at our hospital.
It's such a historical day.
Congratulations.
Make sure you clean this place as if you clean your own home.
Put all of your efforts in.
- Yes.
- The chairman will be here.
What on earth is going on? Just keep everything as it is.
But it's him who's coming.
What do you think about...
laying out a red carpet from the porch to lobby?
I think it's overdoing it.
Is that so?
Be careful.
Make sure it looks artistic. Turn the lights on.
Yes, Sir.
That's great.
Make sure you do this as if you're making your own tree.
Is it Christmas already?
So...
I became in charge of Chairman Shin as a cardiac surgeon...
and not as an emergency medical personnel.
Congratulations, Dr. Yoon.
I guess reading those books on artificial hearts paid off.
- Did you notice?
- Of course, I did.
- It's so awesome.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
You will still visit the emergency room, right?
What do you mean, still? I will be around.
This calls for a celebration.
- Buy us food!
- All right!
Yes, this is Kang Dong Joo.
Come to my room.
Yes, Sir.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
We tried to put everything together for you, Chairman Shin.
If you need anything else, please do let me know.
I am Jang Gi Tae, the manager of Doldam Hospital.
This is enough. Thank you for your kindness.
Yes.
Who's this?
- Are you my doctor?
- I'm...
Song Hyun Cheol, the chief surgeon of Geodae Hospital. We met before.
And this is Dr. Do In Beom.
He's President Do's son.
- Hello, Chairman Shin.
- Is this young man...
- my doctor?
- No, that's not the case.
We just came by to say hello to you, Chairman Shin.
So what?
Where is my doctor?
What happened, Manager Jang?
Why isn't his doctor here?
I'm here.
Hello, Chairman Shin. I am Yoon Seo Jung.
I am your doctor.
Are you a woman?
Don't you have...
any male doctors?
- Chairman Shin.
- Where's Master Kim?
Tell him to come immediately. How dare he do this?
He must know that I'm here. How can he not show himself?
- Call him immediately!
- Okay.
Put some time aside tonight.
What is it?
I have to hold a video conference...
with some doctors in Cleveland...
regarding artificial hearts.
I have a lot of materials to cover.
Okay.
Master Kim. You have to see Chairman Shin immediately.
There is a problem.
Hey. Why are you here?
He's the chairman of board. Of course I have to be here.
I'll give him my regards...
and introduce myself to him.
I'm worried Dr. Yoon might not handle the operation very well.
Perhaps you should consider replacing her.
What are you standing there for?
I said get out.
I'll give you an explanation of the tests you'll undergo.
Dr. Yoon...
You will go under a blood test and an X-Ray scan today.
Didn't you hear what I said?
You will have to go on a fast starting this evening...
and we'll do a CT scan on you tomorrow morning.
I said I only talk to Master Kim.
Bring him here.
Master Kim...
has many things to do for preparing the operation.
Simple tests like these can be done under my supervision.
Like I said,
I don't feel comfortable...
with a female doctor.
So am I, Chairman Shin.
- What did you say?
- Put yourself in my shoes.
If I told you I felt uncomfortable treating you because you're a male,
would you feel pleased?
Then let's call this off.
Get me a new doctor.
That can't be done.
I'm a doctor and you're a patient.
If you have any complaints in the future regarding the treatments,
I'd be happy to oblige,
but if you make complaints regarding any other issues,
I'll just ignore them.
What did you say?
What are you talking about?
Are you joking around with me?
I'm trying not to be intimidated by you.
If I don't, I won't be able to proceed with the treatments.
When did you start coughing?
When people get old,
it comes naturally.
You don't need to know that information.
I understand.
Please change into a hospital gown.
Please check his temperature...
- and his blood sample.
- Yes, Doctor.
Until later, then.
- Master Kim.
- Hello.
Have you gone out of your mind, Dr. Yoon?
Ignore him?
He's not the one to be ignored.
What was I supposed to do, then?
Should I sue a patient for sexual discrimination?
Seriously...
Do you think...
you can run the tests on him without running into a problem?
I'll finish running the tests in two hours...
and get him to rest.
Is there anything I should take care of?
There isn't.
- Off you go, then.
- Okay.
Are you going to let her be like that?
Didn't you see how rude she was to Chairman Shin?
Look.
The moment a doctor gets intimidated by the patient,
the whole medical treatment goes down the drain.
She's doing everything by the books.
- Master Kim.
- Yes?
Shouldn't you pay him a visit?
He's looking for you.
I'm very busy right now. Tell him I'll come by later.
Gosh.
We shouldn't neglect a VIP patient.
Oh, my goodness.
This is Dr. Kang.
We have an emergency patient, Dr. Kang.
It's a 7-year-old boy with a 10cm-long lacerated wound.
I'm on my way.
What?
He's refusing to be tested?
Yes. He keeps asking for Master Kim.
- Did you take his blood?
- He won't let me.
His body temperature is 38.3°C.
Give me that.
I'm going to take your blood, Chairman Shin.
When did the coughing get more severe?
It became more frequent since last week.
Does he have phlegm?
I think so.
Have you checked the color of it?
What do you think you're doing?
I was watching that.
What are you doing right now?
I'm treating a patient right now.
You can keep watching after I'm done.
I told you I don't want to be treated by you.
Bring me Master Kim right now.
Do you know how much money he took from me?
I'm not going to let someone like you treat me.
Someone like me is more than capable of doing this.
So let me listen to your chest.
Get Master Kim to do it!
You might have pneumonia, Chairman Shin.
- What?
- If that's the case,
you need to take antibiotics right away.
If not, we won't be able to put you under general anesthesia.
That means no operation for you.
But...
Not only that,
but Master Kim will be furious with me.
He'll call me an idiot who couldn't even diagnosis pneumonia...
and a quack who doesn't belong here.
Well, that's...
You've never heard of...
Master Kim ranting, have you?
The worst thing in the world is to be scolded by Master Kim.
That being said,
please cooperate with me.
I'm begging you.
My gosh.
I'll start with the auscultation.
Take a deep breath.
Exhale.
One more time.
Inhale.
Once more.
Let me take a look at your scar.
No.
It won't hurt if I...
He fell from the slide at a playground.
Did you fall on your head?
He must have.
I don't know for sure.
I didn't see him fall.
Are your parents not here?
They're both working right now.
My mom said she can be here after 7pm.
Please let me take a look.
- No.
- Good boy.
Do you...
want this candy?
What's wrong? Don't you like sweets?
I want two.
If you let us treat you...
Surprise.
I'll give you two more.
Can we take a look at it now?
Here you go.
You're good at this.
This is nothing.
Can I take a look at you now?
Good boy.
It'll sting a little.
I'll have to stitch up the open wound.
After that, let's run him through a brain CT.
Yes, Doctor.
Let's see.
Good boy.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm just a bit tired.
Should I page a different doctor?
It's okay. I'll do it.
He's been overdoing himself all this time.
He has.
It's an emergency patient!
Soo Jeong!
Don't die. Don't die on me.
This way.
- Move away.
- Don't die.
- What happened?
- She became unconscious from pills.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
Hello?
What's wrong with him?
My son is running a high fever.
Please come this way.
Ms. Eom.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
- He has pneumonia?
- Yes.
His chest sounds are not good and his temperature is 38.7°C.
We're running tests on sputum smear and blood culture.
According as Community-Acquired Pneumonia,
give him injections of triaxone.
Yes, Doctor.
There's something else.
Here.
This is a different model of artificial heart...
than the one in Chairman Shin.
Chairman Shin's artificial heart is Model A.
That model is reported to be defected.
I heard it could get discontinued soon.
Are you considering...
the replacement of his artificial heart?
Go over the data thoroughly.
We'll talk about the details at the conference meeting.
Okay.
This is going to be tough.
In Soo, are you leaving already?
Is it 6pm?
Not yet.
In fact, my wife and mother-in-law are here already.
So I'm leaving a bit early today.
But still, you should stay here until 6pm.
Chairman Shin shows signs of pneumonia, so I'll be busy by then.
Actually, I asked Dong Joo to take care of the emergency room.
I'm sorry. My mother-in-law is so fussy.
See?
That's her.
I will come back as soon as possible after dinner. I'm sorry.
Hello? Are you here?
Okay. I'll be there.
Gosh. Dong Joo and I are such pushovers.
Don't even ask me. I won't carry on the duty instead of him.
Dong Joo has been on duty for three days in a row.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Not at all.
I will be right back after checking Chairman Shin's condition.
Can't you do that for me?
I said no. I have a lot to do.
Okay. You are so cheap and nasty.
Hello?
I will be there in a second.
Don't ever ask me to carry on duty for you.
I will never do that.
What?
He's not just changing the batteries...
but replacing the artificial heart?
I guess that's the plan.
I can't believe this. He always gets his own way.
It seems difficult to go ahead with the surgery, though.
Apparently, Chairman Shin is showing signs of pneumonia.
I think they'll have to postpone it a few days because of inflammation.
Okay. Keep me updated on what's going on.
Replacing the artificial heart?
Soo Jeong, are you all right?
Wake up, Soo Jeong. I'm sorry.
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
What medicines did she take? Do you have them with you?
Yes.
There you are.
She took a handful of them.
What's your relationship with her?
I'm her boyfriend.
In fact, we had a little fight.
So...
Okay.
Can you please wait outside while I check her condition?
This way, please.
Soo Jeong, please don't die. Hang in there.
Miss, please get up now.
Open your eyes.
Your boyfriend is not here.
You should be honest with me now...
so that I can treat you properly.
How many pills did you take?
Are you going to tell my boyfriend about that?
No, I won't.
Two.
I took the medicines because I had a stomach pain.
Then why did you lie to him?
We just had a little fight,
and I messed with him in a fit of temper.
I didn't lie to him, though.
It is true that I had a stomach pain.
Even so, you are not supposed to do this.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
I will give you some fluid. Get some rest before you go home.
Okay.
Is she okay? Is she dying?
She is safe in life and limb.
I will give her some fluid so that she can get some rest.
Thank goodness.
I'm so relieved. Soo Jeong.
Soo Jeong, I'm really sorry. I won't do that again.
Soo Jeong, I'm sorry.
- Get her some fluid.
- Yes, Doctor.
There's a patient with high fever. The whole family doesn't look good.
Okay.
- Ms. Oh.
- I'm coming.
What's the matter?
The coughing started to get worse since last night.
Excuse me.
He's showing no improvement after taking the medication.
All the family members are coughing. How long has it been?
I started to feel chilly and cough about 3 or 4 days ago.
I thought I'd get better.
But my wife and son picked up a cold from me instead.
Let me listen to his chest first.
Okay.
Take a deep breath.
The lung doesn't sound so good. We should X-ray his lungs.
Isn't it just a cold?
I need to check your condition, too.
Please sit on the bed behind you.
Breathe in deeply.
Have your family traveled to overseas countries recently?
No, I just went...
on an overseas business trip for about two months.
- Which country?
- Saudi Arabia.
Saudi Arabia?
When did you come back?
About...
four days ago.
No way.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Ms. Oh. Can I see you for a moment?
Just listen.
We will close...
the emergency room now.
Dr. Kang, what are you talking about?
We have suspected MERS cases.
Isolate the suspicious patients in the hybrid room...
and close down the emergency room according to the manual.
Prepare protective films to block the entrance of the hybrid room.
And make sure to have enough N95 masks, disposable gloves, and gowns.
Pull yourselves together.
The faster we move, the less serious it gets. Okay?
Put on the protective gears, first.
(EMERGENCY ROOM)
Hello? Master Kim speaking.
What?
(EMERGENCY ROOM)
(HYBRID ROOM)
Please stay in the hybrid room until further notice.
What is going on?
The whole family of a patient who went to Saudi Arabia...
is having a high fever and cough.
They are suspected MERS cases.
Dr. Kang Dong Joo just ordered to shut down the emergency room.
How many people are there in the emergency room?
The number of patients are unclear,
but the number of medical staff are five...
including Dr. Kang, Ms. Oh, Mr. Park, and Ms. Eom.
We prepared two boxes of bottled water, and N95 masks.
Hurry.
Go report to the Korea Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
Ask the public health center for protection suits.
Okay.
Also, discharge the patients who may leave the hospital,
and contact the hospitals designated for MERS, too.
I will do that.
Hurry.
Master Kim.
I'm sorry.
What happened? Is something going on?
It's a turmoil.
There is a suspected patient of MERS in the emergency room.
His temperature is dropping. It's at 37.8°C.
We have to see the results to discern what caused this,
but I started administering experiential antibiotics.
If this works, you'll feel better very soon.
If it doesn't, we'll check the test results...
and switch the antibiotics.
Why is...
Master Kim nowhere to be seen?
He called me here,
but he's so busy minding his own business.
Why would a doctor be busy?
It's because of his patient.
Master Kim is...
really busy right now to prepare for your operation.
You surely do talk a lot.
You should have been a newscaster...
instead of a doctor.
You would have been good at that.
My gosh.
Actually, I really don't talk that much.
I am very introverted, Grandfather.
What did you say?
I meant Chairman Shin.
We just installed a brand new air purifier.
It also emits hot air. You can make a use of that.
It's not that hard to operate.
(DOLDAM HOSPITAL EMERGENCY ROOM, CODE GREEN)
I have to go.
You can rest, Grandfather.
I mean Chairman Shin.
She's a bit of a dork.
Yes, I understand.
What's going on?
Why is the emergency room in code green?
There is a suspected patient of MERS...
in the emergency room.
The orders are to remain in your post...
until further instructions.
And you are to be extra careful...
as Chairman Shin's doctor.
Dong Joo was in the emergency room, so I asked him to cover for me.
Dr. Yoon, are you listening?
Dr. Yoon.
Dong Joo.
Get away from the door.
Do not come anywhere near the emergency room, Seo Jung.
Are you...
okay?
Why do you look so sick?
I'm fine.
So stay away from here.
Dong Joo.
Dr. Kang.
Go.
Dong Joo!
Did you call the public health center?
When will the protection suits arrive?
You know what, Master Kim?
They won't pick up.
(JEONGSEON PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER)
It looks like...
everyone has gone home.
What about Centers for Disease Control and Prevention?
I did, but they only told me...
to move the patients to a designated hospital.
Call them again.
- Hurry!
- Okay.
Yes.
I heard it.
But...
are you sure the patient has MERS?
You people are the ones...
who have to make the diagnosis!
Exactly.
So send the patients to a designated hospital.
We have given those hospitals everything they need,
so if you send them over...
We have three patients here.
How are we to send all of them?
If the public health center can't contain all of them,
you can just call the 911.
There is only one ambulance which is designated...
for this entire area.
How are we supposed to go back and forth three times...
to Gangneung, which is two hours away?
Do you want us to do that all night long?
If one ambulance is not enough,
you can call a private ambulance.
Stop talking with such nonsense!
All of the emergency crew members must wear protection suits...
to transfer the suspected patients of MERS.
We don't even have...
any protection helmets,
let alone a protection suit.
How can you tell us to call a private ambulance?
Yes, Doctor.
Like I said...
we have given everything you need to the designated hospital.
You just have to transfer them there.
Transferring them itself is the big problem here!
Just the transfer!
Why can't you understand?
You are the central control center!
Understanding is...
Did you just talk down to me?
Hey.
We need to find a way to work around this.
Screaming at me won't solve any of these problems.
Forget about it. I'm hanging up, you idiot!
You are unbelievable. Hello?
Doldam Hospital?
Who does he think he is?
Master Kim.
I just dicharged...
everyone on the second floor who can leave.
You can take charge of the emergency room.
I'll take care of the second floor.
- Please.
- Sure.
Master Kim.
Hey, why are you down here?
Didn't you hear what I said about keeping your post?
What will happen to those people...
in the emergency room?
What's your plan?
We're trying to reach the public health center.
You should keep your post upstairs.
Emergency room.
How are things going in there, Ms. Oh?
Master Kim.
The possible MERS patients are...
moved to the hybrid room.
We have separated them from us with quarantine plastic curtain.
What about other patients?
We have not informed them about the situation yet.
I thought it would cause a big turmoil if they find out.
I think you should still tell them about it.
Get blood samples of the possible MERS patients,
and take the samples of their sputum as well.
Leave it out the back door,
and we'll take it from there.
After that,
the emergency room will be...
completely quarantined.
And it will remain sealed...
until we have a definite diagnosis.
I understand.
Don't worry too much...
about this place, Master Kim.
I'll do my best.
Well...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(KANG DONG JOO)
(SEO JUNG)
Aren't you going to answer it? It's from Dr. Yoon.
Mr. Park and I will...
take charge of hybrid room for now.
No. I'll go with you.
I'll go with Mr. Park.
- Would that be okay with you?
- Of course.
I have a very strong immune system, Ms. Oh.
Let's go in.
What's going on?
Are we in danger?
Sir.
You have heard of MERS, right?
Doctor.
Are you saying that we have MERS?
The symptoms of MERS are similar to those of a cold.
It's hard to tell them apart.
Since your husband traveled to the affected country,
we have every reason to doubt it.
My goodness.
Are we going to die?
Not all MERS patients die.
Besides, we don't even have a definite diagnosis.
Please don't worry too much.
We'll run some basic tests.
You will get a blood and sputum test and a chest X-ray.
Please give them bottles for sputum samples.
Let's run CBC, blood chemistry test, ABGA,
and take a chest X-ray for each of them.
Yes, Dr. Kang.
Please take this. It's for your sputum sample.
(SEO JUNG)
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
Ms. Oh, Dr. Kang isn't looking so well.
I think he needs to take some rest.
What's going on? What's going on in the emergency room?
Excuse me, ma'am. We are closed for today.
Please go home...
I heard that my children are in this hospital.
He's a seven-year-old boy.
I heard he hurt his head and transferred to emergency room here.
In our emergency room?
What are you talking about? We can't go home now?
- Why can't we go outside?
- Sir.
There are possible MERS patients in there.
What?
MERS?
Are you saying that those people have MERS?
All of them?
We're not sure yet. They might not have it.
So please go back to your bed and follow our instructions.
This is completely ridiculous.
You should have let us go first.
How could you lock us all in here?
Do you want us all die together?
People from the public health center will come...
and take each of you home.
Until then, you are not allowed to leave this hospital.
Gosh. I can't believe this.
Honey.
Seriously!
Sir.
Sir!
Sir, please stop it.
That's enough already! Please go back to your bed.
Let go of me.
I said, let go!
Why should I stay with MERS patients?
Move away. Open the door!
There are also children in here.
Please don't arouse anxiety by raising your voice.
Follow our instructions for now.
Open the door right now!
I'm sorry, sir. Please stop making a scene and go back to your bed.
- You might cause a bigger turmoil.
- Gosh.
- Do you understand?
- You jerks.
Honey!
- Honey.
- Soo Jeong.
Soo Jeong, what's wrong? What is the matter?
Ma'am, what's wrong? Where does it hurt?
My stomach... My gosh.
It hurts so much.
Please lie on your back for me.
With your knees bent.
I'll press your abdomen for a second.
- Does it hurt here?
- A little bit.
When you press there, the right side hurts even more.
Rovsing's Sign?
How about here?
This time, I'll press your abdomen a little longer.
Please hang in there.
What? Acute appendicitis?
Yes, she has severe rebound tenderness,
and shows Rovsing's sign and Dunphy's sign.
First, check her OP lab.
- Please check her OP lab.
- Yes, Dr. Kang.
Can she wait for the anti-contamination clothing?
I'm not sure yet.
I think I'll have to see.
Let me know if she's about to fall into a critical condition.
Yes, Master Kim.
Ms. Oh, please administer one ampoule of tramadol via IV.
Yes, Dr. Kang.
Dr. Kang.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
You startled me.
We have an acute appendicitis patient in the emergency room.
Get ready for a surgery.
My shift is over.
It can worsen the situation if she doesn't get a surgery.
Let's prevent it while we can.
You know the situation we're in right now.
Why would I cut open the possible MERS patient's abdomen?
It's not contagious because the incubation period hasn't passed.
There is a zero percent chance you'll get MERS.
Still, I don't want to do that. I refuse to perform that surgery.
- Hey!
- Gosh.
Doctors are humans, too.
Doctors get sick, and we can get MERS, too.
If we're unlucky, we can die from it. You know?
I have my rights to protect my own life. You should know that.
Right.
You are absolutely right about everything you said.
That's why you should get ready, you jerk!
Darn it!
Give me protection suit first.
Master Kim. Master Kim.
What now? What is it?
Dr. Kang Dong Joo is...
Dr. Kang, are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm all right.
You can't go on like this. Please go take a rest, Dr. Kang.
It's not that bad, Ms. Oh.
- Dr. Kang!
Dr. Kang, wake up.
Dr. Kang.
Dong Joo.
Dong Joo!
No, Master Kim. You can't go in there.
Dr. Kang, wake up.
Dr. Kang.
Hello?
Master Kim, Dr. Kang is unconscious.
His pulse is weak, and he has fever.
What should we do, Master Kim?
Please give us an order.
Put him on a bed, and check his vital signs.
I will call you right back.
- Let's move him to a bed.
- Yes, Ms. Oh.
I knew it.
I knew one of us would end up dying because of him.
Mr. Goo.
Bring me N95 masks and gowns.
I will get in.
What did you just say?
Did Dong Joo faint?
Yes.
He seems to be in a critical condition.
So who is in the emergency room now?
No one.
No one?
Are you saying there is no doctor in the emergency room?
What about Dong Joo?
Who is taking care of him?
Hold yourself together, Dr. Kang.
Dr. Kang.
His vital signs are not good, Ms. Oh.
You can't do that, Master Kim.
President Yeo.
I don't even have time for this.
You are the control tower of this hospital.
You can't just get carried away by your feelings...
and get into the emergency room now.
What about the public health center?
Our staff are on the way.
Dr. Song.
Perform the operation as soon as we get the protection suits.
What are you talking about? I'm not performing the operation.
You only think about yourself in a situation like this.
Do you still call yourself a doctor?
You can see your junior doctor is lying in the bed right there.
How dare you say such a thing?
Gosh.
Please think it all through once again.
You can't do this with Chairman Shin's operation ahead.
Do you know what they say about this situation?
For patients,
it's not the order of arrival. It's the order of emergency.
The emergency patient here is not Chairman Shin.
That's the patients in the emergency room.
I will get in there.
I will get in the emergency room.
Please let me.
Dr. Yoon.
I told you...
to keep your position.
Just go.
I've completed the change-over already.
I'm Do In Beom, sir.
I will be taking care of you...
instead of Dr. Yoon Seo Jung.
What?
Who told you to do so?
Are you my senior?
An emergency medicine specialist should be in the emergency room.
Not a surgeon.
I know you are a surgeon with triple board,
but the doctor who has to be in there...
is me.
If the patients are...
confirmed to contract MERS,
you will be excluded from the CS operation.
Are you sure you've thought about that?
Yes, I am.
I will...
get in.
Please let me.
(EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(DR. ROMANTIC)
We have a problem in the hospital, Chairman.
When are you going to tell Master Kim?
I will tell him after the operation.
Don't say a word until then.
- Who is his doctor?
- It's Master Kim.
Are you talking about that jerk?
If you knew it so well,
why would you do that?
I'm okay.
I have always wanted only one thing from you.
And I just heard the answer I wanted to hear.
Everything else is fine.