Subtitles by VIU/SA143
Dr. Kang, are you all right?
Doctors are humans, too.
We can get MERS, too.
If we're unlucky, we can die from it. You know?
Dr. Kang.
Mr. Goo.
Bring me N95 masks and gowns.
- I will get in. - You can't do that, Master Kim.
You are the control tower of this hospital.
Please think it all through once again.
I will get in.
I will get in there.
I will get in the emergency room.
Please let me.
What?
An emergency medicine specialist should be...
in the emergency room.
I will...
get in there.
Please let me.
Dr. Kang.
Hold yourself together, Dr. Kang.
His vitals are 100 over 70, and 120 beats per minute.
But his temperature is 39.8°C.
Gosh.
How could he treat patients when he was so sick?
What should we do, Ms. Oh?
What is his temperature?
Dr. Yoon.
Tell me about his vital signs and temperature again.
They are 100 over 70, 120 beats per minute, and 39.8°C.
Dr. Yoon.
Inject normal saline 200cc per hour...
and give him fever reducers.
Would that be enough?
It's just syncope.
He's just showing symptoms of serious dehydration.
Let's just hydrate him for now.
He will feel better after a good sleep.
Where is the patient with appendicitis?
She's over there.
By the way, Dr. Yoon is not supposed to be here, is she?
If the patients are confirmed to contract MERS,
she will be excluded from Chairman Shin's operation.
Really?
That's too bad. She's been working so hard for that.
Please lie on your back for me.
I will press your abdomen.
If something goes wrong,
you will regret your decision.
And are you okay with that?
I thought I'd be okay.
I felt that way at the moment.
I will get in.
I wanted to be with him.
I wanted to stay with him.
At that moment.
(Chapter 14, Paragonimiasis Effect)
- Please hurry. - Okay.
Manager Jang.
(Doldam Hospital)
Do we have suspected MERS cases?
They are just suspected MERS cases,
but the emergency room is shut down for now.
Then why aren't you wearing a protection suit yet?
Well...
It's not here yet.
Excuse me.
Is anyone in there?
Hello, sir.
Who are you?
How are things in the emergency room?
The patient with appendicitis is not looking good.
Her fever and physical condition are getting worse.
It seems she's advanced peritonitis, too.
When can we operate on her?
I'm not doing it without protection suits.
Where are protection suits?
Don't you have them yet?
Master Kim.
I just heard from the public health center.
They will bring protection suits within 30 minutes.
Dr. Song, did you hear that? It will be here in 30 minutes.
Go prepare for the surgery now.
Am I finally going to see Dr. Song performing a surgery?
You will finally perform a surgery for the first time in our hospital.
- Congratulations. - Stop it.
What is Dr. Kang doing in the emergency room?
I will go prepare for the surgery, then.
Dr. Yoon.
Take care of the patient for the next half hour.
As soon as we get protection suits, Dr. Song will perform a surgery.
Okay.
Get the patient propacetamol via IV...
- and administer antibiotics. - Yes, Doctor.
Dr. Yoon, here.
Excuse me.
(Patient Rooms)
Chairman Shin's condition has improved.
His fever came down to normal...
and his lungs sound good.
What's wrong?
Did you come up here by your own will...
or did Dr. Yoon call you up here?
What do you mean by that?
I'm curious how...
Dr. Yoon found out that Dr. Kang fainted.
They didn't call it in to the second floor station.
Dr. Kang fainted in the emergency room.
I don't really know.
I'm only here because Dr. Yoon paged me.
Are you saying that she called you first?
Yes. That's right.
I see.
Oh, my.
The busy man has finally showed up.
How are you feeling right now?
That cheerful female doctor...
put me under this and that...
and I feel much better now.
She's good at what she does.
She'll be my first assistant...
when I operate on you.
Is that so?
Then why did someone replace her?
Did I make her upset?
The truth is that we have a problem in the hospital, Chairman Shin.
What?
Excuse me.
May I...
go in there as well?
That can't be done. Please sit tight and wait.
My children are still young.
The oldest one is only in her middle school.
The people from the health center will come and take measures.
Please be seated and wait.
Mr. Goo.
Please take a seat and wait.
Do you want this? You must be hungry.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Soo Jeong.
What are her vital signs?
It's around 90.
The body temperature is 35.8°C.
It's gotten much better since the admission, but it's still low.
- Give the patient another blanket. - Yes, Doctor.
Have the protection suits still not arrived?
Excuse me.
You can't be doing this.
Let me go in there.
My children are in there.
Please move aside.
Calm down, Sir.
Let go of me!
Please move aside.
Please. Please let me be with my children.
You can't be doing this, Ma'am.
There are rules to follow.
Please. Please let me be with them.
Let go of me!
I don't want to die here.
Let go!
Sir.
Nobody's dying here.
Nothing has happened yet.
It hasn't even been confirmed that the patients have MERS.
Please contain yourself.
And what if it really is MERS?
What are you going to do, then?
Then you must not leave here even more.
If you run out of this room without any clear solutions,
you'll put everyone else in danger.
Is that what you want to do?
If you make a scene one more time,
I'll tell your girlfriend about what you did...
the moment she wakes up.
You will be ashamed.
Dr. Yoon.
This patient's blood pressure is dropping.
Soo Jeong. Soo Jeong.
I see.
How long does it take to make a definite diagnosis?
It'll take about 24 hours...
before we can make a preliminary diagnosis.
Tell me when that happens.
Then, I'll leave the hospital...
or find a new hospital to be treated in.
Aren't you afraid, Chairman Shin?
Why would I be when I have you?
MERS is...
not the kind of disease a GS like me can handle.
It's got a very high fatality rate.
If I was meant to die,
it would have already happened 20 years ago.
The fact that I'm still alive and well...
must mean that I'm not meant to die that easily.
(Manager Jang)
Go on.
- They must be looking for you. - Okay.
20 years ago?
When are you going to tell Master Kim?
I will tell him after the operation.
Don't say a word until then.
- Do you understand? - Yes, I understand.
I'm sorry. We got informed too late.
It's okay.
How many protection suits did you bring?
There were 20 of them at our health center.
We brought them all.
Okay.
Dr. Song. Dr. Song.
I don't even have an assistant. How am I supposed to work alone?
With In Beom treating Chairman Shin,
- I can't operate by myself. - Don't worry about that.
I'll be the assistant.
- You will? - That's right.
(Emergency Room)
Open the door, Mr. Park.
Dr. Nam.
How did the anesthesia go?
Okay. You can start.
Hey.
- Stop shaking. - What are you talking about?
Scalpel.
Aren't you going to start?
There you go.
His fever went down a lot.
Yes.
Dr. Kang has been working too hard lately.
I guess so.
May I have your attention?
People from the public health center just arrived.
Each one of you will be...
sent back home soon.
Even after you're home,
you may not go outside until we have...
a definite diagnosis of the symptom.
You will be monitored...
by the public health center until you are off quarantine.
We only have one vehicle from the public health center,
so we will...
first take home...
the diabetic patient.
What about the kids?
We'll take care of this. Will you stay out of it?
You always have to put kids first...
in any emergency situation.
What on earth is this?
A diabetic patient is...
the most vulnerable to MERS.
We will send the diabetic patient home first,
then move on with the children.
I see.
In that case,
when will I go?
I think you will be...
the last person to go home.
You sleep like a baby.
Dong Joo.
- Here. - Why?
- Are you disinfecting me? - Put the mask on.
Don't take it off.
Mr. Goo, what's this?
(Doldam Hospital)
Master Kim.
Master Kim. Master Kim!
Master Kim!
Yes?
We finally have the diagnosis.
- What? - It's...
It's...
It wasn't MERS!
We are clean, Master Kim!
Dr. Song, Dr. Song!
Dr. Song!
It wasn't MERS!
We are clean!
Go, Doldam Hospital!
(MERS corona virus not found. Negative.)
If it wasn't MERS,
what did that patient have?
Give me the blood test result.
The blood test result.
Oh, yes. Yes.
My gosh. Master Kim.
- Is the result out? - Yes.
Their first diagnosis is negative.
Really?
We're alive.
That's a relief.
What is it if it's not MERS?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
Why is his eosinophil level so high?
Pardon?
Eosinophil level
Wait, that means...
Have you had any raw freshwater food 2 to 3 months ago?
- Freshwater food? - Yes.
No, we had no raw food.
We don't even eat sashimi.
Mom.
What about marinated crabs?
Is that cooked?
Marinated crabs?
Were they made with freshwater crabs?
Oh, right.
Mother brought some because you like those.
It was before you went on your business trip.
She said those crabs were in season.
When was this?
It was right before my business trip.
It's been about two months.
Why?
Mr. Park, let's examine their sputum.
- Their sputum? - I think they have paragonimiasis.
That's why the eosinophil level was so high.
I'm an idiot.
Why didn't I catch that?
My gosh.
I can't believe...
you made the decision to send her in.
If she was unlucky, she could have missed the operation.
I couldn't stop her.
I see.
That's how...
the MERS turmoil came to an end.
It was just a case of paragonimiasis...
caused by unfermented marinated crabs.
(Doldam Hospital)
And...
When did you wake up?
Just now.
Really?
Your fever is gone.
You look better, too.
Are you dizzy? Or do you have any ear pains?
You had three cases of overworking.
Lack of sleep, lack of water, and lack of nutrition.
Why were you so stubborn?
I can't believe you lived here for two months.
Was it you?
What was?
You were with me this whole time.
You held my hand.
You must be hungry. I'll get some food.
Right?
You must have dreamt it. No.
- No? - No.
I don't think so.
Are you sure?
I think so.
Really?
What are you doing?
I am checking to see...
if you are lying or not.
Look, you just avoided my eye contact.
I didn't.
Oh, right.
It was paragonimiasis, not MERS.
I see.
Yes. It was because of the pre-fermented marinated crab.
So it was paragonimiasis.
It's funny, right?
Yes, it is.
Fine. It was me. I was by your side.
Right?
You also held my hand.
I was checking if you had fever.
Do you know how much you were burning up?
It went up to 39.8°C.
It went as high up as...
What is this?
Hey.
I'm dizzy.
Let me stay like this for a while.
If you're dizzy, you should eat.
You should eat.
I...
lost all my power to resist him.
This paragonimiasis.
Ms. Woo?
Hello. I'm Woo Yeon Hwa and I'll be working as a pay doctor here.
I look forward to working with you.
What's going on, President Yeo?
She used to be a resident at Gangwon Hospital.
But I thought your nationality was Chinese.
I'm an international student.
An international student?
You must come from a wealthy background.
My mother is Korean.
I see.
Then why were you admitted here looking like a homeless?
I was a medical resident who fled.
You should have told us so.
Back then, I didn't want to be a doctor ever again.
It was too exhausting for me.
Why did you change your mind all of a sudden?
Because of you all.
When I saw the staff working at this hospital,
I thought to myself,
"I want to become a real doctor."
This is good news.
A familiar face will be joining us.
Isn't that right, Master Kim?
So, what's your specialty?
I'm a GS.
She even studied general surgery.
This is good.
Even foreigners apply for general surgery.
The domestic students should learn a thing or two.
They all want to be dermatologists or plastic surgeons for money.
They almost never apply for general surgery or cardiothoracic surgery
This isn't right. Korea is supposed to be a medical powerhouse.
My goodness.
Look.
You have a fair point, but it is not the appropriate time for that.
Is that right?
I'm sorry.
I'll consider myself an intern and try my absolute best.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
You were a resident?
I'm here as a pay doctor,
but think of me as an intern and shove me around as much as you want.
Is that so?
I like your mindset.
How's your stamina?
I'm pretty determined.
You're even determined?
Hello, Doctor.
Hello, Yeon Hwa.
She used to be a resident at Gangwon Hospital.
On top of that, she was a GS.
Is that right? General surgery?
- Yes. - This is good news.
Starting today,
I'll give you all kinds of valuable advice.
Yeon Hwa...
Can I call you by your name?
Of course. You can call me whatever you like.
Okay.
You can depend on me, Yeon Hwa.
- Okay. - Be careful, Yeon Hwa.
Seo Jung's also known as Crazy Whale.
- You little... - What? I'm right.
Dong Joo. Do you want some pizza?
Where did that come from?
I got it last night.
I just heated it up. It's hot.
Eat all you want.
From now on, snacks are on me.
I'm serious. 100 percent.
Thank you, In Soo.
Do you want some, Manager Jang?
I'll pass. I'm on a diet.
Come eat, Yeon Hwa.
We should eat while we can or...
We have TA patients. All three are seriously injured.
See that?
This is what happens.
They'll be arriving in three minutes.
Three minutes.
Take your time and unpack your things.
- Okay. - Until later.
It's good to see you again, Yeon Hwa.
Okay.
It's a TA patient.
She's a 35-year-old female driver.
It looks like she smashed her head into the steering wheel.
Her blood pressure is normal, but she's vomiting.
She's experiencing a severe headache and dizziness.
What about her vital signs?
It's 100 over 65 and 120 beats per minute.
It could be hemorrhage.
Execute drops of maxolon, then I'll do a brain CT on her.
- Yes, Doctor. - One, two, three.
The glass window broke and got embedded in her arm.
I'll take a look at your arm, Miss. Stop crying.
Are you experiencing pain in any other parts of your body?
No. Please get it out.
Pieces of glass could still be in there. You need to get X-rayed.
- Mr. Park. X-ray scan, please. - Yes, Doctor.
- What's the status? - He's experiencing shoulder pain.
- It hurts. - It's dislocated.
Sir, your shoulder seems to be dislocated. We have to X-ray you.
- Get on it, Ms. Eom. - Yes, Doctor.
Okay.
It's you again. Please go wait on that bed.
Master Kim...
My goodness.
Sir.
Mr. Goo.
Is it a cardiac arrest?
This patient has a pacemaker.
How are his vital signs?
Systolic 60 and 40 beats per minute with no spontaneous breathing.
What should we do?
Please page Master Kim. I'll start with intubation.
Let's move the patient.
What are you still doing with the Ambu bag?
Get him on the ventilator.
I was about to do that.
Ms. Oh.
Mix dopamine with dobutamine...
and execute drops of 10cc per hour.
Get Isoket ready...
and use it when the patient's blood pressure increases.
Insert a Foley catheter and check his urine.
Yes, Doctor.
This is the ABGA report.
I think you should go there, Dr. Yoon.
Okay.
This is the ABGA report.
It's a respiratory acidosis.
I'll do echocardiography.
It's DCMP and ejection fraction is very low.
It's 25 to 30 percent at best.
You said you have done an ECMO operation, right?
- Yes, I have. - Not you. Hey!
I'm asking you, In Beom.
Yes, I have.
Okay. You'll be the surgeon.
Seo Jung, you'll be the assistant and page Dr. Nam.
Do it fast before the machine gets here.
Yes, Doctor.
What are you doing?
Will you help me?
With what?
What is this?
I want to give a woman I can't tell you the name...
of a Christmas present.
Which one looks better?
Christmas gifts?
Isn't it romantic?
Exchanging Christmas gifts...
and warm hugs?
And...
I'm sorry.
If you have...
a secret crush on someone,
why don't you make a move with a Christmas gift?
No, I'm okay.
Do you think so?
Is this better?
This one looks nice.
- Proceed. - Needle.
Guide wire.
Scalpel.
Gauze.
Pass me the smallest dilator.
The next one.
I will put in the cannulas.
Are you sure?
- Sorry? - Are you sure about this?
It seems Dr. Do got confused for a moment.
Infusion line has a red label.
I see.
I was a little carried away.
Stop it.
Dr. Yoon, switch places with Dr. Do.
- Ms. Oh, assist the operation. - Yes, Doctor.
Dr. Do.
Follow me.
Answer me.
What's the difference between...
veno-venous and veno-arterial in ECMO?
Veno-venous is used for respiratory failure...
while veno-arterial is used for heart failure.
- What was the operation for? - It was for veno-arterial.
Why do you pull the drain line to right atrium?
That's because of...
a possibility of IVC collapse in case of increase in ECMO flow.
Why does it matter?
There might not be enough of returning blood to the drain.
Do you think you know that so well?
How could you make such a mistake with cannulas?
You'd thought...
it was something that anyone with good techniques could do.
But you clearly overlooked one thing.
ECMO is...
all about physiology which is more than...
inserting cannulas.
You may...
deceive me with your words,
but you can't do that with your hands.
A surgeon's hands never lie...
about his experiences and efforts.
You...
lied about something that you'd never actually done.
And you attempted to slip a trick over on me.
I won't ask you...
why you had to do all those things.
But,
Do not degrade yourself...
by acting as if you were expendable.
Are you coming from the airport?
Of course I am. Chairman Shin is in the hospital.
Where is he now?
How is he doing?
He's not in this hospital at the moment.
I heard he was hospitalized.
He's at Doldam Hospital in Jeongseon.
In fact, that's why I wanted to meet with you.
Why?
Is anything wrong?
This is what I was concerned about in the first place.
Don't try to scare me.
Just come to the point.
It seems your artificial heart has a mechanical problem.
For this situation,
we should replace your artificial heart instead of changing batteries.
And it is not an easy operation.
Are you kidding me?
How could you let him have such a risky operation in a small hospital?
I tried to persuade him,
but he didn't listen to me.
So I asked you to come all the way...
to persuade him.
I understand...
how stubborn he is.
No one can reason him out of his obstinacy.
So...
who is his doctor? Is he good?
He is Master Kim.
Master Kim?
I'm not sure if you remember him or not.
He used to work at Geodae Hospital...
with his name, Boo Yong Joo.
Boo Yong Joo?
Are you talking about that jerk?
What? Now do you feel...
scared?
We have to remove your artificial heart...
and replace it with a new one.
That's a very rare case.
We don't even have exact numbers for the success rate.
It means there are only few cases for the operation.
You should be honored, then.
I'm giving you...
a chance to perform such a rare operation.
Aren't you confident?
If it's not that, you should do this.
May I ask...
why do you have...
absolute confidence in me?
I already gave you my answer.
I'm a patient who struggles to survive,
and you are a doctor who tries to save a person's life.
We are two men of tenacity.
That makes the chance of me surviving go up.
Every doctor...
tries his best to save a patient's life all the time.
Do you think...
they will do the same...
when billions of dollars are at stake?
- Pardon? - Cut the chatter. You're doing it.
Even if I die during surgery,
I won't hold a grudge if you perform the surgery.
We will do a CT scan on you tomorrow morning.
And we will conduct the examination...
that's been delayed because of MERS.
Nine days later,
we will perform the operation on Chairman Shin.
We will remove his artificial heart...
and replace it with a new one.
- Dr. Kang. - Yes.
You will be removing the batteries in the abdominal region.
They were transplanted two years ago,
so they must be stuck tight to the fibrous tissues.
Once you remove them,
I will begin to remove...
- the main device immediately. Okay? - Okay.
- Dr. Yoon. - Yes.
You will be the first assistant as originally planned.
It is all about speed.
Make sure to be well prepared.
Yes, Doctor.
Dr. Do.
You will be Dr. Kang's assistant, okay?
Yes, Doctor.
Before the operation,
we will simulate the procedures three times.
I will let you know as soon as the schedule is fixed.
So keep everything in mind. That's all.
Are you all ready?
- Yes, Master Kim. - Yes, Master Kim.
Scalpel.
Cut open his chest and insert a cannula.
Set up the heart-lung machine. These must be done in three hours.
Make an incision into the abdominal subcutaneous tissue,
and remove the battery, the TET,
and the controller within 45 minutes.
Do we have 45 minutes for both incision and removal?
No, it includes the closing the incision.
Don't forget that the patient is 72 years old.
We need to reduce the surgery time as much as possible.
I understand.
Switch the positions.
Remove the existing artificial heart in two hours.
Install the new model in two hours.
Stop the bleeding in 1 hour, and close up the chest in 1 hour.
The total surgery time is 9 hours and 45 minutes.
That's not good.
We have to reduce it to seven hours...
to minimize the damage from the surgery.
First,
let's finish setting up the heart-lung machine in two hours.
Let's finish replacing the hearts 30 minutes faster...
for each process.
We still have 45 minutes left.
Then, I'll finish my work in 30 minutes.
I'll make an incision...
and remove the battery, the TET, and the controller...
in 30 minutes.
Seal it up, too.
I'll give it a try.
That's not good enough.
- I'll pull it off. - Okay.
We still need to reduce 30 minutes, Master Kim.
Do you have any idea?
The preparation of the surgery is going well.
It seems that everyone thinks it will be successful.
I think Chairman Shin believes so, too.
Unexpected changes can happen anytime.
By the way,
how much longer should I work here?
Until I say that's enough.
Until then, swallow the pill.
I'll get in touch soon.
Do not degrade yourself...
by acting as if you were expendable.
Thank you.
What?
The one is for me, but the other is...
not for me.
What am I doing?
Forget it.
Are you leaving now?
Yes. I'm a little tired.
I'm going home to rest.
I see.
I'll get going.
Dr. Yoon.
There's another package for you.
What is it?
I'm not sure, but it seems to be...
from someone who wants to spend Christmas with you.
What is this?
Dong Joo.
Can I talk to you for a second?
You said she would like it.
Women usually like it.
Maybe it's not her preference.
Does she like handbags?
What's this?
It's my Christmas gift for you.
I heard that kind of gift makes a woman happy.
Take it back.
Why?
Do you not like it?
I don't want to receive it.
Take it back.
What do you mean...
you don't want to receive it?
I didn't imply anything by saying that.
I just don't want it.
Do you hate me that much?
As a man,
am I not good enough for you?
- It's not like that. - Then, what?
How do you...
really feel about me?
I...
like you.
- Then, why? - However,
the deeper my feelings for you grow,
the more I think of the accident that happened five years ago.
That's not right.
I shouldn't put the accident...
before my feelings for you.
That's disrespectful to you,
and I feel bad for you.
So...
So, Dong Joo,
- we cannot... - I wouldn't mind that.
There has been...
only one thing that I wanted from you.
And I just heard...
the answer I wanted to hear.
That's enough for me.
As long as you have feelings for me,
everything else doesn't matter.
So please...
Seo Jung, please...
Can't we be together?
(Doldam Hospital)
(Medical Records for Shin Myung Ho)
(Dr. Romantic)
(Epilogue)