You should do this.
May I ask...
why do you have absolute confidence in me?
I'm a patient who struggles to survive,
and you are a doctor who tries to save a person's life.
Every doctor...
tries his best to save a patient's life all the time.
Do you think...
they will do the same...
when billions of dollars are at stake?
Pardon?
So who is his doctor?
Is he good?
I'm not sure if you remember him or not.
He used to work at Geodae Hospital...
with his name, Boo Yong Joo.
Boo Yong Joo?
Are you talking about that jerk?
Yes.
That's him.
Times of subordination.
Rather than respecting one's individuality and capability,
the world compares and standardizes people...
to put them into fitting roles.
Dr. Boo Yong Joo. Answer the following.
Have you ever had your junior doctors to perform surgery for you?
It's been reported that the two table deaths prior to the one of...
Jang Hyun Joo were caused by such incidents.
Is that true?
I told them to do it?
I told them to perform those operations?
Why aren't you saying anything?
When have I ever...
told you to perform operations for me?
Quiet down, Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
I ask the questions.
You only answer them.
The so-called elite organization...
and the efficient rulers of the organization own this world.
To know that...
the things you accomplished here at Geodae Hospital...
were based on such unlawful and contemptible methods...
As an administrator,
I have to say it's a disgrace.
I'm sorry,
but you have to let someone else perform the operation.
She's a candidate for the next presidency.
Clear your schedule so we can set a date for the operation.
There are patients...
who wait up to 3 or 4 months...
to be operated by me.
I'll operate on them first according to the order of...
who's been waiting the longest.
(Employee Report)
You're supercilious and free-wheeling.
Does being a well-known doctor making a lot of money...
make it okay to neglect the ethics...
and morals as a doctor?
You were the ones who put your hands together...
and gladly appointed me.
We didn't know that you were such an immoral and shameless being.
Were all these patients operated using my name behind my back?
You're too busy and famous of a doctor, Dr. Boo.
It couldn't be helped.
Every patient who come to our hospital wants to be treated by you.
Even so, how could you use my name...
to deceive the patients?
If you're worried about this getting leaked,
you shouldn't be.
The hospital will...
have your back.
You jerk.
Who told you to perform that operation?
Tell me!
We can no longer keep a lid on your past actions.
The doctor's union and the hospital association will be notified.
We will take measures...
so you will no longer be able to work as a doctor.
That is...
the final decision of the board.
Loyalty for a clique becomes the greatest virtue.
Capable men of principles...
get abolished once they lose their value.
That is how strange this world has become.
(Members of Council)
(Doldam Hospital)
It's okay.
Take me to the hotel today.
- What about Chairman Shin? - I'll see him tomorrow.
He's probably sleeping, anyway.
(Chapter 15, The Cornered Stone Syndrome)
Good morning.
Is it?
Good for you.
Are you not feeling well?
You seem to be in a very good mood, Dr. Kang.
- Why is that? - I'm just...
It's a good morning, that's all.
Hello, good morning.
You're here.
Hey.
It's so hot.
Why is it so hot in here. Aren't you?
The weather must have gotten warmer. It is hot in here.
I have to go to the staff room.
I need to do something in the emergency room.
- Okay. - Okay, then.
- I'm going this way. - Right.
It's hot in here?
It's 2°C below freezing point out there. What are they...
We have a patient experiencing abdominal pain.
Name of the patient is Hwang Gi Soo. He's a 45-year-old male.
He's not showing symptoms of vomiting or diarrhea.
He just said his stomach hurts and that he's cold.
His vitals are 100 over 80, and 120 beats per minute.
His temperature is 39.5°C.
Hold on.
You checked to see if he has a history of gallstones?
Yes, I asked him in case that's the case here,
but he said they didn't show up in the checkup of earlier this year.
You checked thoroughly.
Good work.
I hear your stomach is aching. When did that start?
A month ago.
The pain used to come and go.
Last morning, it started to hurt a lot...
and last night, my whole body was aching.
I was burning up.
Please raise your knees.
I'll feel your stomach.
- Does it hurt when I press here? - Yes, it does.
How about...
- here? - That hurts the most.
Do you drink often?
I drink once or twice a week.
Have you recently experienced a sour stomach?
I have.
I see. We'll have to run some tests first.
You might have an infection in your stomach. We'll have to do a CT scan.
Doctor.
Please make the pain go away first.
I will.
Please set up IV lines of tramadol.
I'll do an op lab of amylase and lipase,
- and then do an abdomen CT scan. - Yes, Doctor.
I'll go to the CT Room.
You scared me.
- Did it work? - What?
The necklace.
Well...
Congratulations, Dr. Kang.
I told you it'd work.
I don't want to flatter myself,
but I know these things very well.
I see.
Did you put the necklace on her yourself?
- Do I have to? - Dear me.
That's basic.
What do you mean?
Why do you think men spend all that money...
to buy presents for women?
There must be a reason behind the actions of men.
A ring is to hold a woman's hand.
A necklace?
It is for a hug.
Like this.
Is that so?
So did Seo Jung put on the necklace?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, no.
If she didn't wear the necklace on purpose,
it means something.
Maybe, she didn't like the necklace...
or the person who gave it to her.
That doesn't sound right.
You shouldn't let your guard down.
Dr. Kang.
Could you go check out the patient in the third bed?
Okay.
What do you think you are doing now?
You don't need to bother.
I was just a little jealous, so I messed around with him.
Were you jealous?
- Why? - My romance ended in failure...
unlike his.
I should go, then.
Hello? What's up?
Are you wearing the necklace I gave you?
Why are you asking me that?
Aren't you?
I'm busy now. I'm on my rounds.
Just tell me...
you are wearing it or not.
Excuse me, Dr. Kang.
We are working now.
You shouldn't mix business with pleasure.
- I'm hanging up. - Seo Jung.
What was that?
Isn't she wearing the necklace?
Good morning, Chairman...
Shin.
- His daughter? - Yes.
Chairman Shin's daughter has just arrived.
Maybe you know her, too.
She used to...
work at Geodae Hospital as the head of strategic management.
Stop being so bullheaded and leave the hospital.
You are being absurd.
I'm hospitalized here.
Why would I leave?
You should stay in more decent hospital.
A hospital with better doctors.
Why did you come here?
Just go back to Florida and take care of your children.
You are bothering me.
Who asked you to come here?
Is that President Do?
It is an artificial heart operation we are talking about.
How would I even let you have such an important operation...
in this lame hospital?
Also, you are the chairman of the foundation of Geodae Hospital.
What if the chairman has an operation...
in such a small hospital and it goes wrong?
Geodae Hospital will lose face.
People will soon think you have poor judgement.
Some will even say you are in your dotage.
What?
Dotage?
If you don't want any of it, you should come to Seoul with me.
I will take care of the discharge procedures.
Excuse me.
He can't leave the hospital without his doctor's permission.
What are you doing?
A patient is not supposed to leave the hospital...
without a doctor's permission.
I'm the director of this hospital.
I mean I'm the one...
of high rank.
Do you understand?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
What are you doing here?
What would a doctor do in a hospital?
I'm taking care of the patients.
You are already kicked out from the medical world.
How dare you pretend to be a doctor in the doctor's gown?
I didn't do anything wrong to be disqualified.
And you guys set me up...
to be kicked out.
So did you cajole Chairman Shin...
for your comeback?
I thought he was just an old man with a lot of money.
I had no idea that he was the chairman of the foundation.
Or that he was your father.
It's been a lot of surprises for me.
I will move him to Geodae Hospital immediately.
Is it what Chairman Shin asked?
It is my decision. I'm his guardian.
I can't leave my father to a doctor like you even for a moment.
A doctor like me?
What does that mean?
- What? - You'd better define the word.
You are being vague,
so I'm not getting your point.
Let's be clear about this.
What do you mean by "a doctor like me"?
Look, Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
Everyone calls me Master Kim here.
Master Kim?
Do you think you can hide your past with a new name?
I'm not hiding anything.
Let's just say it is for self-examination.
I once...
pursued a better life...
by taking a wrong way...
with seductive words of yours.
It is to show that I introspect about my mistake.
- Chairman Shin's daughter? - Yes.
She says...
she is the one...
of higher rank than us.
And she seems to have some ill-fated relationship with Master Kim.
Do you know anything about that?
I told you.
I met Master Kim after he left Geodae Hospital.
But you have worked with Master Kim for so long.
Didn't you hear anything about that?
No. Never.
What are you doing?
Are you dating Dr. Kang?
Who told you that?
Did Dr. Kang say that?
No, it's just Manager Jang's guess.
He says there is something going on between you two.
Is that right?
No, it's not.
It's not true.
- I'm serious. - I see.
I'm telling you.
Trust me. You have to trust me.
Okay.
Oh, my goodness.
- Dr. Woo. - Yes?
Where is Dong Joo?
He's in the hybrid room.
- What do you think? - I think...
it is pancrease tail.
I see. I thought so, too.
I don't think it is pancrease tail.
You don't?
It is abscess for sure,
but I think it is originated in bowel.
Bowel?
Is that what you think?
Do you want me to page Master Kim?
Dr. Kang.
Why would you call Master Kim? I'm right here.
The scan is unclear,
so I just wanted another's opinion.
You've been so disrespectful...
and disobedient to me.
Do you think you are really great as Master Kim favors you?
I don't think Master Kim favors me.
Look closely at the scan with your eyes.
It is obviously originated in bowel.
- But it is connected to... - Hey.
Are you trying to teach me or something?
I'm just giving my opinion.
It may look like that but...
So it is originated in bowel.
It can't be pancrease tail.
Don't you think, Dr. Do?
That's what I think.
- Dr. Song. - The patient's BP is dropping.
It is 80 over 40.
Set up central lines and execute a full drop.
Also, inject 10cc of norepinephrine.
And bring me a Foley catheter.
Stop it.
Stay back.
Set up central lines and execute a full drop of 500cc.
And...
Inject 10cc of norepinephrine, too.
And bring me a Foley catheter.
Dr. Do will operate on this patient.
He is my patient, Dr. Song.
You can't even read the CT scan right.
Set up central lines and move him to the operating room.
Yes, Doctor.
Let me inject antibiotic while you set up central lines.
Dr. Kang looks pretty upset.
I think so.
- Dr. Woo. - Yes.
Have you assisted an operation before?
- Yes, I have. - Okay.
You will be assisting me today.
I will see you in the operating room in 10 minutes.
No matter how I look at it, it's near the pancreas.
Seo Jung, can you knock?
What was that about with Dr. Song?
Why did you get into an argument?
We just had some disagreements.
By the way, Dong Joo,
did you say something weird to Manager Jang?
Like what?
Did you tell him that we're dating or something like that?
I...
I've never put it bluntly like that.
Then why did Ms. Oh ask me that?
What did she ask you?
She asked me if we're dating.
Are you sure you didn't lead her on?
No way. I'm very careful when it comes to things like that.
Why aren't you wearing the necklace?
Why do you keep asking me that?
I just want to know...
if we're dating now as of yesterday.
This is exactly why I can't start anything with you.
We didn't start anything?
What was yesterday, then?
Yesterday?
What happened?
Don't you remember?
I guess it can't be helped. I'll have to do it again.
- See? - What? What did I do?
How can I start things with you when you're so blatantly obvious?
I'm obvious?
I doubt it. I have an amazing poker face.
I'm Poker Face Kang. Haven't you heard of it?
Poker face, my foot. You make it look so obvious.
Tell everyone here at Doldam Hospital, why don't you?
Can I do that?
Gosh.
Promise me one thing.
What is it?
Promise me you'll only be professional at the hospital.
I will continue to be your senior doctor...
and you will continue to be Dr. Kang.
Like how we've been until now,
we can't bring our emotions to the workplace.
We'll be simple coworkers.
Let's do that, okay?
Okay.
I'll promise you...
if you say we'll be dating as of today.
- I'll have to see about that. - You'll have to see about that?
When is it going to be?
I'll have to see about that. Get back to work.
I love you.
Do you want to die?
I knew it. You need to work on your poker face.
At this rate, everyone here at this hospital will become aware.
Stop that.
What?
- Oh, "I love you"? - Gosh.
You want me to stop saying I love you?
- Stop it. - Okay.
- I love... - Stop it.
Fine. From now on, I'll never say that I love you.
I love...
I love you. I love you.
Stop it. Stop.
I love you.
- I love you. - No.
What is it that you're after?
Going back to Geodae Hospital?
Don't you have any questions regarding Chairman Shin?
I'm sorry, but President Do will run things around there for a while.
It's most likely that the board will reappoint him.
There's nothing for you to gain even if you do go back there.
Chairman Shin...
is in a worse condition than we expected.
You must be trying to make a dramatic turn-around...
by performing a successful operation on Chairman Shin, but...
You can read CT scans, right?
From what I know, you too are a graduate of a medical school.
Whose is that?
Chairman Shin.
As you can see,
he has late-stage lung cancer.
Lung cancer?
Yes.
That's what the CT scans say, at least.
What about treatment?
Can it not be treated?
There are many different kinds of lung cancer, Chairman Shin.
First, we'll have to do a biopsy...
to find out what kind of cancer it is.
Then, we can try to figure out how to treat it.
My gosh.
What if it doesn't get treated?
How much time do I have?
Three months...
at maximum, Chairman Shin.
Regardless of my heart?
Yes.
So...
what do you intend to do?
There isn't much a doctor can do at this point.
There aren't many proposals to make, either.
(Doctor's Office)
Dr. Woo.
- Are you going for an operation? - Yes.
Is it the abscess patient?
Yes. Dr. Do told me to...
be his assistant.
I see.
Do you...
What are you doing here?
What? I'm the assistant.
But I asked Dr. Woo.
She said something came up. I'm filling in for her.
You don't have a problem with that, right?
How are you going to approach this?
It's peritoneal abscess.
It looks like originated from bowel. I'm planning on bowel resection.
Okay.
Commencing operation. Scalpel.
- Master Kim. - Yes?
Dr. Kang told me to give this to you.
Please take a look at the CT scans of patient Hwang Gi Soo.
Where is Dr. Kang now?
He's in the operating room with patient Hwang Gi Soo.
It's an abscess patient.
Dr. Do is performing the operation. He said it's originated in bowel.
But Dr. Kang...
thinks the origin is from the tail of pancreas.
Hwang Gi Soo.
(Medical Records of Hwang Gi Soo)
The bowel looks...
The bowel seems to be fine.
I'll check on the pancreas.
I'll perform omentectomy. Pad.
Bovie.
Retractor.
It's the tail of pancreas.
Is that right?
I'll call you back, Madam Oh.
- What brings you here? - Patient Hwang Gi Soo...
He's under operation for bowel origin.
Dr. Do is...
Dong Joo had a different opinion. Why did you ignore him?
Did I?
I can't remember clearly.
You looked at the CT scans yourself.
Did you not suspect...
even by the tiniest bit that it could be pancreas tail?
I did think suspect that at first,
but Dr. Do was really certain that it was bowel origin.
If two fellows are in disagreement,
you should have looked into the matter more carefully.
You are the head of general surgery.
Instead,
all you did was taking sides.
What are you talking about?
I can read CT scans just fine.
Dr. Do and I came to the same conclusion.
What do you take me as?
(Do In Beom)
Yes, Dr. Do.
What is it?
I opened up the patient, but he bowel wasn't the origin.
Really?
What is it, then?
It's the pancreas tail.
I see. I get it.
It's understandable.
Things can be different than expected...
when we actually open the patients up.
Don't lose your composure. Managing such situations...
is part of a surgeon's capability.
So what should we do now?
Have you ever performed distal pancreatectomy?
I have once. I assisted it a few times as well.
That's great. You have experience.
Why don't you show us what you can do?
I'll come in if there's a problem, so don't you worry.
Okay.
It's the pancreas.
Gosh.
Is that the truth?
Have you really performed distal pancreatectomy before?
Why? Do you think I was lying?
You lied about the Boerhaave's syndrome.
Commencing distal pancreatectomy.
I'll start with dissection. Forceps.
Bovie.
Please call Dr. Song again.
Okay.
What are you doing? Aren't going to pick that up?
I don't recognize the number. I'll pick it up later.
(Do In Beom)
What's going on?
Tell me. What's going on?
Dr. Do is performing distal pancreatectomy right now.
And?
You tell him what the problem is.
I'm calling to ask...
whether you're supposed to dissect the spleen as well.
He's calling to ask you.
Tell him.
Of course. You have to dissect it as well.
Why? Is there a problem?
I'm having difficulties exfoliating the spleen artery.
I'm afraid I might cut the artery.
I see.
Oh, my. What should we do?
What do you think you should do?
You have to get in the operating room.
Who?
Me?
Should I be the one going in there?
Okay. Wait there, Dr. Do.
I'm coming in.
Thank you.
You're pathetic.
Spleen-preserving distal pancreatectomy.
- Have you heard of it? - I have.
I don't have experience of it.
If so, consider this an honor.
Watch carefully.
Forceps.
Bovie.
Because of the anatomical arrangement, the dissection of...
the pancreas tail requires the dissection of the spleen as well.
However, there's been a report...
saying that without the spleen, the patient's immune system weakens.
So nowadays,
we tend to dissect the pancreas without touching the spleen.
From what I heard, you've been off-field for some time.
But you're doing quite well.
Of course. I'm the head of general surgery of Geodae Hospital.
It's almost done.
You exfoliate like this...
and dissect the pancreas tail.
All done.
Do you see that?
It's clean, isn't it?
Yes.
What... What's going on?
I think the spleen artery has been damaged.
Pad.
Pass me more.
Can you spot the location of the bleeding?
There's no clear vision.
Try to spot the bleeding location.
Suction. One more.
Irrigation.
Suction.
I did it. I located the vessel.
This is not looking good.
I think we'll have to remove the spleen.
- Suture. - Wait a minute.
Wait for what?
What do you think you're doing? Get out of my way.
There's a tear in the splenic artery.
If we just suture this area,
we can save the spleen.
May I do it?
What are you doing?
This is my operation. Why are you taking it away from me?
If you're feeling confident, you can do it.
You said you have done it before.
If this goes wrong,
this is all on you, Dr. Kang.
Are you still going to do it?
You really are consistent.
The first thing you do is looking for someone to blame.
Stop your nonsense.
Are you going to do it or not?
Loupe.
Okay.
Number five.
Dr. Kang.
Give it to me.
Focus.
Cut.
Okay.
Releasing.
Irrigation.
There's no bleeding.
I think the spleen will be fine now.
Should I close him up?
Do In Beom.
How much longer are you going to lie at an operation table?
What are you talking about?
Take today for example.
You've never done distal pancreatectomy before.
Isn't right that we switch positions, then?
It was my operation.
I thought I could handle the operation.
I've done simulations by watching videos of it on the Internet.
Hey.
How can watching a video and the actual operation be the same?
That's how I always practice.
How else am I going to experience all the different cases?
You irresponsible scum.
Without such practice,
becoming a surgeon is impossible.
Once you cut a patient's abdomen open,
no one knows what will happen.
So...
you will keep lying to get more experiences?
You were just lucky with the spleen. Don't get smart with me.
I hope you will stop lying about your experiences.
If you do that again,
I will send the issue to the committee.
You coward.
Hey.
What a jerk.
Get off me.
- Get off. - Hey.
You jerk.
Why don't you bring your father?
- You idiot. - Mr. Goo.
Let go of me.
Get off me.
Hey.
Please stop that.
Gosh.
Hey.
What? Did they have a fight again?
Dr. Kang was so cool in the operating room.
It made Dr. Do a little frustrated.
Was Dong Joo cool?
- What happened? - He was doing angiorrhaphy.
It was like Master Kim was there.
He was just like Master Kim.
Stay focused.
Cut.
Did Dong Joo imitate Master Kim?
He was not just imitating. He was as good as Master Kim.
His skills were not as good as Master Kim's,
- but they were pretty close. - What was that?
He always backbites Master Kim for being so arrogant.
Maybe he learned something while backbiting Master Kim.
People get closer after a fight.
So where are they now?
What was that about?
What did you two fight about?
Say it.
He intercepted my surgery,
so I got upset.
I will make sure this never happens again.
What about you, Dong Joo? Do you have anything to tell me?
No, I don't.
Okay.
If you don't, get out of my office.
I heard you two had a fight again.
I heard you knocked against each other.
He hit me first. What was I supposed to do?
What's wrong with you two?
You are of the same age. You can be good friends.
You two are very difficult people,
so you don't have many friends.
What are you talking about? I have many friends.
Is that so? Maybe that's why no one has come to Jeongseon...
to see you since you came here.
That's just because they are busy with their work.
What about you? You don't have many friends.
I do.
Ms. Eom, Dr. Jung, Mr. Park...
And I often drink beer and talk with Ms. Oh...
and Dr. Nam.
They are my friends.
- I see. They are your friends. - Right.
Then the trees and birds in the backyard of the hospital...
are your friends, too.
I should get going.
You can't just leave like that.
Weren't you worried about me?
Make sure to put some medicine on the wound.
I should go.
I love you.
I told you not to do that.
This is so embarrassing.
That's enough.
I want you to leave now.
Hey.
You are grown-up. No more fighting.
I told you Dr. Do hit me first.
Maybe you made him upset.
I know what he's like.
He's not the kind of person who'd hit someone for no reason.
He grew up without knowing a day of hardship.
- Are you siding with him or what? - That's it.
Be more cautious in the future.
This is a hospital, not a boxing ring.
They are not that good at acting.
What was that about?
Why are you so upset?
Me?
I'm not upset.
I was never close to Dong Joo.
And he intercepted my surgery,
so I lost my temper.
You are not telling me the truth.
Or...
is it that...
you don't know how to tell the truth?
- Pardon? - That's it. Get out.
About Chairman Shin's operation.
I'm afraid...
we won't be doing the operation.
He has lung cancer terminal.
Go and tell your father about it.
What do you mean?
That's what you are here for.
And that's why you wanted to join my operation team.
You know what?
I prefer a cornered stone...
than a round one.
If you are a cornered stone,
it means you have your own style...
and your own thoughts.
I like to see a cornered stone being faced...
with the mason's chisel.
I don't like anything roundish and lukewarm.
Rubbing the corners off me,
I'd like to make myself better...
with my philosophy and belief.
I may thought that...
you were one of those people.
You did something...
you didn't have to do that day.
I don't think it was just your sheer bravado on your father's coat-tails.
I thought you did it only for the dangerous patient.
And you were not that bad.
So I tried to get you on my side.
And?
Maybe...
I was wrong about that.
Go tell your father about that.
Chairman Shin won't have an operation in our hospital.
So...
he doesn't need to be anxious about it anymore.
And I guess...
you should leave Doldam Hospital.
Lung cancer terminal?
Late-stage lung cancer?
Yes, that's what I heard.
What about the operation?
What will they do with the artificial heart operation?
Chairman Shin won't make it until then.
Did Boo Yong Joo say that?
Are you sure he said...
he'd give up on the operation?
Yes, he said that to me.
Okay.
I get it.
Father.
What? Tell me.
Can I...
go back to Geodae Hospital?
Wait a little longer...
until things are settled.
Stop whining.
Come in.
It's me.
I came here as soon as I heard about Chairman Shin.
You must be devastated.
Who told you about him?
At Doldam Hospital,
there are a few people who are my eyes and ears.
I see.
It's hard to say this to you,
but since it turned out this way,
I think Chairman Shin has to give up on the heart surgery.
What is your opinion?
Do you think...
I should go through the surgery?
Or do you think I am going to die soon anyway...
and I should not...
get the dangerous surgery?
To be honest,
in a situation like this,
following the patient's decision is...
the only thing a doctor can do, Chairman Shin.
If I decide...
not to get the surgery,
what would happen?
I meant to fix your heart,
and keep asking you for money saying that I saved you.
Anyway, my plan would fail.
My goodness.
How can you still make jokes like that in such a situation?
We cannot assure you or predict...
whether your heart or your lung...
will stop functioning first, Chairman Shin.
What if...
I decide to get the surgery anyway?
The artificial heart replacement surgery...
also have a high risk.
Neither of them would be a good choice.
Right. I see.
- Hello, President Yeo. - Hi.
Manager Jang, you were here, too.
Would you like to have a cup of coffee, too?
Yes, thank you.
About Dr. Kang...
He may appear to be picky, but once you get to know him,
you can see that he has such a good heart.
- Don't you think so, President Yeo? - Well, yes.
He seems so.
In fact, the shapes of his eyebrows...
and the area between the eyebrows...
indicate that he is a man who would love a woman forever...
once he falls in love with her.
Don't you agree, President Yeo?
I guess. I don't know much about physiognomy.
He has a face of a man...
who would be a good husband as well as a good boyfriend.
Thank you for this, Manager Jang.
I'll get back to work.
Okay. Go on now.
Just as I expected, she can't hide her feelings.
Dong Joo, we have an emergency.
What do you mean?
I think Manager Jang has noticed.
- What has he noticed? - You startled me.
I mean, he seems to suspect us.
He went on talking about weird things with President Yeo.
I think he might spread a weird rumor in this hospital.
So?
Let's have a fight.
- Fight? - Yes.
Let's fight more intensely.
Let's make it look like a real fight.
Dr. Yoon.
Why did you give the patient an analgesic first?
Dr. Kang, it's because I...
Can't you see that the patient is in pain?
- The patient was in so much pain... - I wasn't far from here.
I can come here from my office in only two minutes.
You should have called me first.
I could have checked if it was surgical abdomen.
Right. I thought of that, too, but...
Don't you know that analgesics...
except for NSAIDs don't affect physical examination?
- I do. That's why I gave an order. - In case of an acute abdomen,
call a surgeon first from now on.
The emergency room isn't a control room for the hospital.
The doctors in here are...
also good enough to make decision.
Do you want to start a fight between GS and ER doctor?
Hey!
Stop acting up. I'm your senior.
What's wrong with you two?
I told you, it was my fault.
- It's not your fault! - It's not your fault!
Dong Joo and Seo Jung...
squabble every time they see each other.
I know.
- That's fake. - You startled me.
Fake? What do you mean?
They're trying to hide the fact that they're a couple.
The fight is a cover-up.
No way.
Don't jump to a conclusion. That's not true.
What would you do if I'm right?
You can have a free drink at my bar for one month.
Free food, too.
All right. Food is free, too.
Why would you two make a bet...
on whether they are a couple or not?
- It's fun. - It's fun.
It's from Master Kim.
I can't seem to get along with you.
Everyone, please be seated.
What is going on, Master Kim?
As of today,
the meeting on Chairman Shin's surgery...
will be suspended.
What do you mean...
the meeting will be suspended?
The CT scan result came out.
He has terminal lung cancer.
Terminal lung cancer.
Considering his condition,
the artificial heart replacement surgery...
would be too much for the patient.
Therefore, everything we have...
May we come in?
It's okay. You don't have to get up.
Are these people the staff members who will participate...
in my surgery?
Yes, Chairman Shin.
I see.
They all look trustworthy.
- Don't you think so? - Yes, I agree with you.
I was discussing...
your surgery with them.
That's good.
In fact, I came down here...
to talk about it.
- Master Kim. - Yes?
Let us...
stick to our original plan.
Pardon?
Just as we planned,
let's proceed with the surgery.
Chairman Shin.
Since things turned out this way,
how about you become the chairman?
What do you say?
I think Geodae Hospital needs...
a young chairman at this juncture.
You call me a greedy old man...
or say that I'm senile.
Even if...
I have only one day left to live,
I want to breathe comfortably.
I'm going to die anyway.
It's not too much to ask of you, is it?
Right, Master Kim?
(Dr. Romantic)
Has Boo Yong Joo decided to perform the surgery?
Do you think President Do will just let Master Kim do that?
He could put everyone at Doldam Hospital in trouble.
I will offer him two propositions.
The staff members will be replaced?
With the staff from Geodae Hospital?
Boo Yong Joo...
Why don't you change the staff members?
He will never give up on his staff.
If you can't change the staff,
you have to accept another offer. Are you sure you'll be okay?
Now I just have to...
eliminate him from this industry for good.
(Epilogue)
Are you tired?
Thank you, Dr. Yoon.
That's pretty.
Did someone give it to you as a gift?
It's nothing.