Are these people...
the staff members who will participate in my surgery?
- Yes, Chairman Shin.
- I see.
They all look trustworthy.
Don't you think so?
Yes, I agree with you.
I was discussing...
your surgery with them.
That's good.
In fact, I came down here...
to talk about it.
- Master Kim.
- Yes?
Let us...
stick to our original plan.
Pardon?
Just as we planned,
let's proceed with the surgery.
Chairman Shin.
I think Geodae Hospital needs...
a young chairman at this juncture.
So I'd like to have you...
as the next chairman of the foundation.
Watch what you say about that.
My father...
is still in good condition.
I know...
you wouldn't feel comfortable talking about it.
But it wouldn't be amiss...
to have some ideas of what's ahead and do something.
He is...
He is going to have the operation.
- Is he going to have the operation?
- Yes.
Chairman Shin wants to proceed with it no matter what.
Did you...
make your decision after due consideration?
Of course I did.
It is a matter of life and death.
I know I am old...
and I've lived long enough.
But it doesn't mean that I don't cling to life.
On the contrary,
I don't have long to live,
so I desperately want to live longer.
It's...
just not right.
Should I wait until I die...
doing nothing?
That doesn't sound like me.
It's not a simple operation where we just replace batteries.
We are talking about replacing the artificial heart itself.
It won't be easy...
to go through the operation.
I know.
Do you still want to...
proceed with the operation?
Even if I have one day left to live,
I want to live a decent life.
I want to die like that.
Master Kim.
I want you...
to respect my choice.
Okay?
What did Boo Yong Joo say?
Did he say...
- he'd perform the operation?
- I'm not sure.
What if he says yes?
Who in the right state of mind would do such a thing?
He knows Chairman Shin's condition better than anyone.
You know he's Boo Yong Joo.
Making what appears to be impossible...
into possible is his favorite thing.
He's more likely to proceed with it than to refuse it, don't you think?
If so,
he will be digging his own grave.
What do you think he is doing?
Is he considering whether or not...
to proceed with the operation?
It seems like he is.
Is he going to do that?
Or is he giving up?
I don't think so.
I agree with you.
You think? I knew it.
Master Kim wouldn't give things up so easily.
If so, what is he trying to decide?
Maybe he is busy...
making plans for the operation.
What you say is very plausible.
Is he making plans for the operation?
What kind of plans...
is he thinking about...
to make the operation successful?
(CHAPTER 16, BURDEN OF RISK)
Give him hydration.
Once he gets better, send him to an outpatient department.
Dr. Woo, I need to talk to you.
Why did you call a surgeon for this?
- Pardon?
- He doesn't have severe symptoms...
and he passes gas.
You can handle it in the emergency room.
He has a history of operation,
and I found ileus on the x-ray. So I called a surgeon just in case.
I know there is no real boundary between ER and GS in this hospital,
but don't you think you can't call a surgeon just for everything?
Dr. Woo Yeon Hwa.
I heard you were a first year resident of General Surgery.
Then you are supposed to know when to call a surgeon.
- I'm sorry, Doctor.
- Don't even be sorry.
Just be good.
What's the matter?
I guess he is upset with me.
Why?
That's because I did something wrong.
You jerk.
Dr. Woo, did you just ignore my order?
I told you to assist the operation, not Dr. Kang.
Dr. Kang insisted to do that.
Are you saying Dr. Kang's order takes priority over mine?
I can't give you an order when you act like this.
I'm sorry, Doctor.
- I should've given it more thought.
- Don't even be sorry.
Just make sure to do your job right.
Are you saying we should reduce more time?
- Can't we do that?
- Will you...
proceed with the operation?
I'm just thinking it may be manageable.
Only if we can finish the whole process within six hours.
Within six hours?
That's ridiculous. Six hours?
This surgery usually takes at least 9 to 10 hours...
and we reduced it down to 7 hours and 30 minutes.
You're going to reduce it down by an hour and a half again?
That's why I'm asking you.
How much more time can you save from that?
10 minutes... No, even 5 minutes is good.
Do you think you can do that?
Are you...
seriously considering finishing the operation in six hours?
Can you do it or not?
- Six hours?
So that's what he's been trying to figure out.
In order to finish in six hours...
Hold on.
That means we can't afford to touch a single artery while...
excoriating the tissue through sternotomy and cannulation.
Even then, we'd barely be able to finish in time.
Even if we do that, we won't be able to finish in six hours.
Excoriating the tissue without touching the artery is impossible.
Don't you think it could be possible for Master Kim, Ms. Oh?
It's not like he's been specializing in heart surgeries.
This will be difficult even for Master Kim. It can't be done.
My thoughts exactly.
Besides, doing the surgery...
will not benefit Master Kim whatsoever.
He will be criticized regardless of his success or failure.
- Do you think so?
- That won't be all.
In the case he fails, he'll take all the blame.
I doubt that.
Do you think President Do will leave Master Kim alone?
He's been waiting for an opportunity to get rid of him.
If the operation fails,
he'll quickly grab...
that opportunity to hold Master Kim responsible.
Which is why we can't afford a failure.
Failure?
We shouldn't let that happen, then.
Don't you think so, Dong Joo?
The patient is a 72-year-old man with terminal lung cancer.
Putting him under anesthesia for a long time alone...
is a great risk.
Which is why we shouldn't go over six hours.
You know better than us that it's impossible.
So what? You can't do it?
No. I'm opposing it.
Okay.
One person opposes.
What about you, Dr. Nam and Ms. Oh?
Okay. You two are on hold.
And you, Dr. Yoon? Are you against it as well?
No. I'm in favor of it.
- Seo Jung.
- Okay.
One person in favor.
All right.
You two can let me know once you make up your mind.
If possible,
I'd like you to be in favor.
Until then.
I guess he's really going to perform the surgery.
He probably made up his mind since the beginning.
We should be stopping him.
How could you support his decision?
Because it's Master Kim's decision.
Will you die if he tells you to?
I told him that I'd at least pretend.
What's the reason behind it?
What's the reason behind your implicit faith in him?
Respect?
If you respect him, you should've been more rational.
The doctor you respect is about to perform a very risky surgery.
Not only Master Kim himself,
but he could put everyone at Doldam Hospital in trouble.
The fact that Master Kim is so confident...
must mean that he's gotten it pretty much figured out already.
What if he actually finishes the operation in six hours? What then?
It's absolutely impossible.
I think trying to finish under six hours...
will more likely to lead us into mistakes.
Even after taking every variable into account...
I really want to...
be a part of that operation.
It might be an operation...
of my lifetime.
This is a very rare case of an operation.
More importantly, when do you think...
I'll get another chance to witness Master Kim performing a surgery?
Don't you think so?
But still, the risk is too high.
I think it's a risk worth taking.
And what if he fails?
I don't even want to think about it.
But even if he does fail,
I'll be grateful...
for that I could be a part of the process together with Master Kim.
I think that alone has meaning.
That lunatic.
So are you saying he's pressing on with the operation?
Okay.
Get me the list of the staff members.
Has Boo Yong Joo decided to perform the surgery?
Yes, apparently.
With how things are panning out,
you'll need to come up with a plan in case of an emergency.
- What kind of emergency?
- Chairman Shin...
is 72 years of age. Furthermore,
he has terminal lung cancer.
He'll have to withstand a 8 to 9-hour-long surgery...
under general anesthesia.
That alone puts the operation at a very high risk.
The operation might be successful.
Regardless of its success or failure,
the mere fact that he's undergoing surgery is meaningless...
with the condition he's in.
I mean...
You shouldn't worry too much.
I have a plan.
I'll go to Doldam Hospital...
and offer him two propositions.
I told you not to come down here ever again.
Have you forgotten about what I said?
Why come here? For what purpose?
I just heard about Chairman Shin's surgery.
And?
Are you going to try to stop me again?
That won't be possible...
with Chairman Shin being so stubborn.
I'm thinking about supporting you...
so you can do it properly.
- Support me?
- Let's start by...
replacing all of your staff members.
What is this nonsense I'm hearing?
Just to be clear,
this wasn't my order.
It's a request made by Director Shin.
Consider yourself informed.
What are you talking about?
The staff members are to be replaced with the staff from Geodae Hospital?
President Do came down here to say that in person?
Yes. On top of that, he said that it wasn't his order.
It was a request made by Chairman Shin's daughter.
The staff members will be replaced?
With the staff from Geodae Hospital?
Yes. President Do came here and said that in person.
I understand. I'll get down there.
Okay.
You too know that...
Geodae Hospital is famous for its thoracic surgery department.
Do you want experienced staff?
Or young and skilled fellow doctors?
Right.
You'll need an anesthesiologist as well.
I took a look at the list of your staff members.
I saw Dr. Nam's name on it.
Letting someone in a medical lawsuit to be in charge of...
Chairman Shin's anesthesia is... How should I say this?
I don't like it.
It's not like it was a simple medical accident.
It involved someone dying.
Oh, there's something else. I'll also send you...
two skilled scrub nurses.
They're on a whole another level...
compared to nurses at a cottage hospital.
Look at you all yapping about.
Will you shut your mouth before or after I punch you?
Right now,
I'm doing you a favor out of kindness.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but nobody else other than my own staff members can be in my OR.
A request made by Director Shin?
What a joke.
Go back and tell her that I don't care about what she says.
Your staff members...
are all a bunch of people with disqualifications.
In case that the operation doesn't go well,
you wouldn't want room for controversy.
Hey, President Do.
I just need you to stay out of my way.
Then, there won't be any problems.
If you can't change the staff,
you have to accept another offer.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Another offer?
What another offer?
Live surgery.
Live surgery?
What?
They'll perform my surgery in front of an audience?
Yes, Father.
Whose idea is this?
Is this from President Do?
The ones watching the surgery are...
people from the hospital, me,
and cardiothoracic surgeons of Geodae Hospital.
I think I'd feel safer...
if I watch and see if your surgery is going well.
Please, say yes.
Choose one.
Change your staff members,
or choose to go with live surgery.
If you choose to do the live surgery,
all the cardiothoracic surgeons from Geodae Hospital will come...
and observe the operation.
Unbelievable.
What will you choose?
Will you change your staff members?
Boo Yong Joo...
won't change his staff members.
Will you choose to do a live surgery?
What happens...
if he chooses to go live?
Like I said,
it'll be like digging up...
his own grave.
Which one will you choose?
Will you change your staff members?
Or will you do live surgery?
What kind of an awful man is he?
How can he ask you to choose between the two?
What kind of a threat is this? Isn't that right, Master Kim?
Well, we can't say that it's just a threat.
This operation is so rare...
that Geodae Hospital would want to take a part in this.
But his intention isn't so innocent!
To be frank,
that just means he wants to keep his eyes on our operation.
Also, why did he have to pry...
into Dr. Nam's medical litigation?
On top of that,
he called me an old nurse who only works at the cottage hospital.
He didn't say you were old.
Calm down.
Anyway, I am...
deeply offended, Master Kim.
I believe you should turn down both conditions from President Do.
I have another idea, Ms. Oh.
This can be a chance for us.
This isn't a chance!
Is this our chance to be angry?
It's a chance for us...
to show the world how good of a surgeon Master Kim is.
What do you think, Master Kim?
I don't know. Well...
Why don't you change your staff members?
Like President Do mentioned,
we shouldn't leave any room for a dispute.
The verdict isn't out,
but it is true that I am in the middle of a litigation.
If the surgery goes wrong by any chance,
my situation...
can affect you in a bad way.
Dr. Nam.
We can't be a burden to Master Kim, Ms. Oh.
We have to think about how we can help...
Master Kim.
I'll reduce five minutes from my part.
Do you think that'll help?
Okay.
You are in.
Two of you agreed including Dr. Yoon.
What about Dr. Nam and Ms. Oh?
Oh, my goodness.
Are you still undecided?
Master Kim, please hear me out.
Stop talking nonsense.
Let's do what we always do.
That's how you can help me.
But Master Kim.
I have no one else to depend on if you are not there.
If I have someone else in the operation room,
I won't be able to focus because I'll be more nervous.
If I can't focus,
the operation time will be delayed.
I can't even miss a minute now.
Do you think I should waste my time like that?
And you too, Ms. Oh.
Why are you getting so angry...
at President Do's nonsense?
The only scrub nurse...
who can work up to my speed is...
just you, Ms. Oh.
And you already know that.
Well, yes.
That's true.
I thought I could do this under six hours...
because I knew...
I would be doing the operation...
with the staff right here.
My gosh.
Dr. Nam, should I state out...
the obvious like this?
Should I be doing this, Ms. Oh?
It sounds warm and nice.
What will you do?
Dr. Nam and Ms. Oh.
Will you join the operation or not?
What can I do?
I'll be there.
I'm the only scrub nurse who can work at your speed.
Dr. Nam.
- What about you?
- Are you really okay..
With doing this live?
You are so frustrating.
President Do.
Let's do live surgery.
Satisfied?
It's just as I thought.
Yes.
He has...
chosen to do live surgery.
Our next step is...
to destroy him for good.
So,
when is the operation?
In five days.
We'll start at 9am.
I see.
I heard my daughter...
asked for something troublesome.
I don't mind.
It doesn't matter if I go live or not.
I'm only concerned about...
reducing the operation time.
That's my only concern.
Thank you, Master Kim.
I'll hear that...
after the operation, Sir.
You have made a difficult decision.
I hope you'll do well.
Well, I know that you will.
Is there...
anything that Chairman Shin has not shared with me?
Why do you ask?
Well,
it seems like he's hiding something.
I was wondering if that has something to do with the operation.
Do you know anything?
I'm sorry.
He has told me not to say anything to you.
So there is something.
You can hear it from him...
after the operation.
We only have five days...
to prepare.
Our task is...
to figure out...
where we can reduce an hour and 30 minutes.
It's an hour and 25 minutes.
I already reduced five minutes from my part.
- Dr. Yoon.
- Yes, Master Kim.
Make sure you study his CT scan...
and find out where you will perform cannulation.
Wait, no.
Put the CT scan in your head and memorize it.
Yes.
Ms. Oh and Mr. Park.
Could you check and see if we can reduce any time...
while circulating in the operation?
- Yes.
- Yes, Master Kim.
- Dr. Kang.
- Yes?
Make sure you finish your part within 25 minutes.
- Keep your time, okay?
- Yes, Master Kim.
Okay.
Dr. Nam.
Let's prepare this well for the next five days.
- Yes.
- Yes, Master Kim.
Tell all cardiothoracic surgeons to be here in 10 minutes.
- No exceptions. All of them!
- Yes, President Do.
The aorta is close to the sternum. Do you see that?
The space is too small.
One false move...
and you could cut the heart or the aorta.
What should we do...
in case we can't cannulate the aorta?
We should cannulate the aorta femoralis.
That's right.
Once the operation begins, make sure to disinfect the aorta femoralis.
Yes, Doctor.
Dr. Jin. Liaise with the live shooting team.
- Yes, President Do.
- It starts at 9am.
So you should be there at least one hour earlier.
- Yes, President Do.
(DOCTOR'S OFFICE)
Bring me the suture set.
Okay.
You are not busy, are you?
Pardon? Were you talking to me?
- There is no one else but you.
- Okay.
If you are not busy, come assist me with the suture.
Okay.
Short for subcutaneous and long for skin, you know that, right?
Yes, I know.
Cut.
Were you really a resident in GS? You are not doing it right.
I'm sorry. I was too nervous.
Cut.
Gosh. Make it shorter.
Okay?
- I'm sorry.
- I told you to be good, not sorry.
Wipe up the blood, too.
Am I bleeding?
Please don't move.
Blood gathers...
when the needle goes into the wound.
Okay.
Let me do that.
Please go check the other patients. I can take care of this.
What are you doing?
He just asked you to go check the other patients.
Yes, Doctor.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Cut.
(EMERGENCY ROOM)
Hey.
What?
Did something happen between Master Kim and you?
You are not attending the conference...
and Master Kim is not talking to you.
Did something happen after we fought?
You even left the team.
Nothing happened.
I just told him that I didn't want to join it.
Gosh. You begged Master Kim to let you be the first assistant.
Why did you change your mind?
When did I do that?
I didn't beg him to let me be the first assistant.
Did Master Kim tell you that?
I just overheard it.
Why did you change your mind?
I told you. I just don't want to do it.
I'm tired.
I thought the operation was about replacing batteries,
but it became too complicated.
And I don't have an important position.
What if you can change the position?
Do you want to join the team again?
What do you mean?
I have to cut the surgical time down from 30 minutes to 25.
If I do that with you,
I think we can save five more minutes.
I will replace the batteries, and you will replace the controller.
What do you think?
Are you asking me a favor?
- Why?
- I...
just want to cut down the surgical time.
Listen.
For a general surgeon, it is a great chance to expand your experiences.
Just having your name on the operation will have...
a huge influence on your career.
Now that we are doing it, it will be even better if it ends successfully.
What do you think?
Do you want to join me?
I will replace the batteries, and you will replace the controller.
I'm in.
Okay.
In Beom.
Are you sure you can do that in 20 minutes?
I want you to have...
In Beom join the team again.
If we work together,
we can finish it in 20 minutes.
It includes suture process, too.
Of course.
Okay. In Beom is in.
Yes!
I will have the same.
I heard an interesting rumor.
Is Dr. Boo Yong Joo coming back?
Yes.
I'm afraid so.
Do you think it's okay?
I tried to stop him,
but Chairman Shin was too firm about that.
Is he replacing Chairman Shin's artificial heart?
If the operation proves to be a success,
you will be in trouble.
How can such an immoral person like him succeed?
That's just ridiculous.
It will just dispirit...
innocent hard-working people like us.
That's not how the world is supposed to work.
Why don't you...
take the opportunity...
to realize justice?
Where are you going?
I'm just going home.
- What about you?
- I'm going home, too.
Why? Is there a problem?
You don't have to go home together though.
What's the matter? We are going the same way.
Do you live in the same neighborhood?
We live in the same house.
In the same house? Do you live together?
Yes. We live together in the company house. Why?
You should have told me that.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I thought you already knew.
Most of the hospital employees live in the company house.
Didn't you know that?
No, I didn't.
Where did you think I was staying?
I didn't even think about that.
And I didn't even imagine that you two would sleep together.
Seo Jung, wait for me.
I'm going home with you.
Why? You don't like the company house.
You said you liked the staff room better.
I changed my mind.
Wait for me.
Don't move an inch.
Are you two going home?
Yes. Are you going home, too?
I'm a little nervous about the operation tomorrow.
I'd better go home early and get some rest.
Me, too.
What is that? Is it the prayer book?
There will be...
Wednesday service tonight.
For the historic operation tomorrow,
I should say my prayers.
Gosh. Since when did you do that?
Since last Sunday.
I may not look like that, but I'm a believer.
Seo Jung.
Do you want to grab a bite to eat at Dr. Nam's restaurant?
A glass of beer will be fine as well.
Beer?
I'm afraid I'll have to say no since the operation is coming up.
Let's drink after everything is over.
Instead, why don't we go to Dr. Nam's place for some ramyeon?
- Ramyeon?
- That's good, too.
I forgot to do something.
Go on without me.
- Let's go, Seo Jung.
- Okay.
With the weather so cold...
some ramyeon will be so good.
And a glass of beer with that would be...
Where did she go?
Did she leave already?
Manager Jang. Have you seen Seo Jung?
I know where she went.
(PRAYER BOOK)
Follow me.
What?
- For Master Kim!
- For the artificial heart!
This is...
I feel really bad.
I happen to be the only one who doesn't need to operate.
Instead of a blessing from the above,
you're celebrating with beer.
Gosh, don't talk like that.
I thought you didn't go to church before.
Did you start going lately?
The last time you went to...
Oh, that's right.
There was that newly possessed shaman.
That lustful female shaman.
Gosh, stop intervening...
in my religious life.
That's private.
Sure, whatever you say.
All right. This is your order of budaejjigae with extra noodles.
Ramyeon is coming soon as well.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Thank you.
By the way...
I've never heard about Dr. Nam's medical litigation before.
Can I ask you about it?
Later.
You have a big surgery tomorrow.
Let's talk about that some other time, Dr. Kang.
Okay. I understand.
By the way...
Dr. Kang and Dr. Yoon...
look beautiful together every time I see you.
Aren't they like a couple of hospital bugs?
Bugs.
I'm asking just to be sure.
I know the possibility is like the Earth colliding with...
a planet in the Andromeda Galaxy,
but I'm only asking just to be sure.
Are you two...
dating?
Is it true?
It's not like that.
We're not.
We're really not.
Why would you think that?
I've known him for a long time. That's why we seem close.
Didn't I tell you?
When he came to work as an intern at the ER five years ago,
he used to be my underling.
Isn't that right, Dong Joo?
It is true.
You were the arrogant,
- untouchable intern.
- I love you, Seo Jung.
I love you, Ms. Oh.
Me?
I love you, Manager Jang.
Dr. Nam. I love you.
Gosh.
You know how it is.
We love each other and care for each other.
What we have as Doldam Family...
is thicker than water.
Isn't that right, Seo Jung?
Dr. Nam. Ramyeon please.
Right. Okay.
Oh, I forgot kimchi.
I should drink some more beer.
I don't know why I feel so thirsty.
I love you.
- What do you think you're doing?
- It's thrilling, isn't it?
You can expect more of it.
There will be more.
Do you want to die from the cold or from my beating?
It's too cold to die outside.
And it'll hurt to get beaten by you.
I love you.
Gosh, please.
They are dating for sure.
They really are.
- I'm sure of it.
- I agree.
I love you.
What are you doing here?
I've been waiting for you.
- Why?
- I...
will be going into the operating room tomorrow.
So I've heard. And?
This time, it's not because of my father.
Based on pure intentions to reduce the surgical time,
Dong Joo asked me to.
That's why I'm going in there.
I don't want you...
to take things the wrong way.
You have 20 minutes.
If you don't perform...
or if you don't finish in 20 minutes,
I'll chop your hand off.
Consider yourself informed.
(DOLDAM HOSPITAL)
Manager Jang.
Hello, President Do.
How are the preparations? Are they going well?
Of course. We didn't schedule any appointments today.
The walk-in patients will be sent to the emergency room.
- What about Chairman Shin?
- He's still in his room.
Master Kim went to see him just now.
The people from Geodae Hospital are here.
Chairman Shin. How are you feeling today?
You know how it is.
I literally feel like...
being on an operating table.
Don't be so nervous, Chairman Shin.
We will try our best.
Of course you should.
Hello, Chairman Shin.
Well.
What brings you here, President Do?
How could I not come...
when you're about to undergo a big operation?
I see.
How thoughtful of you to come.
I hope I can see you in a healthy condition...
after the operation is over.
Thanks. I hope so, too.
(DOLDAM HOSPITAL)
(NO OUTPATIENT TREATMENT TODAY. THE EMERGENCY ROOM IS AVAILABLE.)
Let's take him to the operating room now.
Yes, Master Kim. I'll go with you, Chairman Shin.
All right.
- Mr. Goo.
- Yes?
We'll take him to the OR.
I wish you luck.
I don't know about that.
I'm not sure...
which way would be the luck for your sake.
Which way would be luck for you?
Today will be a long day for us.
Ms. Eom, you're in charge in my absence. You know that, right?
Yes, Ms. Oh. Please don't worry.
Every surgeon in this hospital will participate in this surgery,
but Dr. Kang and Dr. Do...
can come out once they're done removing the battery.
So in case of an emergency, call on the operating room.
Yes, I will.
Let's make it through today safely.
Dr. Jung, please take care of the emergency room.
You have nothing to worry about since I'm here.
I am the one who protects the emergency room.
Chairman Shin is coming down.
- Ms. Oh, let's go.
- Okay.
See you later, guys.
I'm getting nervous.
I can do this.
- We can do this.
We have an emergency patient.
He's complaining abdominal pain.
That's early.
Dr. Woo, what are you doing?
Yes, Dr. Jung.
Aren't you checking the patient?
I always give young doctors a chance to examine patients first.
What a nice way to make an excuse.
Who will ever understand my true intention?
Yes, Honey.
Good morning.
Sir, what's troubling you?
I have heartburn.
- How long have you had it?
- I have had it once in a while...
since a couple of months ago. I had a drink last night,
and my stomach hurt this morning.
Did you vomit or have diarrhea?
I felt nauseous, but I didn't throw up.
I'll examine your abdomen first.
He has severe oppressive pain.
His abdomen is too hard, too.
Is it ulcer perforation?
Sir, we'll give you an analgesic, and take an x-ray.
Inject 1 ampoule of pantoprazole and 1 ampoule of tramadol, please.
Yes, Dr. Woo.
Chairman Shin, we'll put you under anesthesia now.
Think it as a good, long nap.
When you wake up, the surgery will have been done.
Everyone,
thank you in advance.
Please inject 120mg of propofol...
and 40mg of rocuronium.
Yes, Dr. Nam.
Has it begun?
Yes, they just put him under anesthesia.
For those who haven't had breakfast yet,
we prepared refreshments such as bread, coffee, and drinks.
Please raise your hand if you'd like some,
and I will serve you.
Who would you like some coffee, tea, bread, or drinks?
Thank you.
By the way, I heard that your son will...
participate in this surgery, too.
I'm sure he'll just observe it.
What would he be able to do?
Start from an incision. to the cannulation.
And set up the heart-lung machine, too.
Our target time for all these procedures are two hours.
Be in standby and come in once I call you, okay?
Yes, Master Kim.
- That really is Boo Yong Joo.
- That's him.
- I haven't seen him in 10 years.
- Exactly.
I think he's been working here ever since.
He's starting the surgery.
You showed up at last.
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
We'll conduct a time-out.
Shin Myung Ho. 72-year-old male.
With a median sternotomy,
we will begin the artificial heart replacement surgery.
I'm the lead surgeon, Master Kim.
The first assistant is Dr. Yoon Seo Jung.
Scrub nurses are Ms. Oh Myung Sim and Mr. Park Eun Tak.
The anesthesiologist is Dr. Nam Do Il.
The perfusionist is Mr. Park Jong Chul.
Everyone, are you ready?
Let's make it work.
Scalpel.
Gauze.
Wire holder.
Why is it tied so tightly?
Needle holder.
Saw, please.
- Needle holder again.
- Needle holder.
- Let's open it now.
- Retractor.
The adhesion is more severe than I expected.
I don't think he'll succeed.
Clamp.
Hold this.
It's hard to tell them apart because of the adhesion.
This is the aorta.
- It seems weak, so pull it gently.
- Yes, Master Kim.
Master Kim, his SBP dropped. It's 60 over 70.
His cerebral oximetry is dropping below 40.
I will increase it and start transfusing blood.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry, Master Kim.
It's okay. Stay calm.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Yoon.
Dr. Yoon, look at me!
It's okay.
We still have enough time. Don't panic.
In order to finish in six hours... Hold on.
That means we can't afford to touch a single artery while...
excoriating the tissue through sternotomy and cannulation.
Even then, we'd barely be able to finish in time.
Dr. Yoon, stay focused.
Focus.
Yes, Master Kim.
Prolene number four.
He still has amazing techniques.
Am I wrong?
My eyes are getting old.
- Cut.
How many minutes did we lose?
At least 10 to 12 minutes.
Dr. Kang, we have an emergency.
We need you there.
I think it's ulcer perforation.
- Ulcer perforation?
- Hey.
If that's the case, shouldn't we undergo an operation right away?
Suction, please.
Six hours.
I have to finish the operation in six hours.
How much time do we have until we go in?
About an hour to an hour and 20 minutes.
Can we do an operation...
for ulcer perforation within an hour?
No matter what happens,
I have to finish within six hours.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(DR. ROMANTIC)
We have about an hour and 20 minutes.
Don't you think you and I can do an operation for ulcer perforation?
He will do risky things...
to reduce his surgical time.
We're going into an operation.
Don't tell Master Kim.
It's bad news for Yong Joo,
but I think the sky is still on my side.
What do you mean? He's not awake?
Do you know what time it is?
People want to know the truth.
If you do know the truth,
do you have the courage to tell it to the world?