This is the aorta.
- It seems weak, so pull it gently. - Yes, Master Kim.
Master Kim, his SBP dropped. It's 60 over 70.
His cerebral oximetry is dropping below 40.
I will increase it and start transfusing blood.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry, Master Kim.
It's okay. Stay calm.
Yes.
Prolene number four.
Dr. Kang, we have an emergency.
We need you there.
I think it's ulcer perforation.
Ulcer perforation?
Who told you to notify of a patient that way?
- Where did you get your training? - I'm sorry.
The patient is a 34-year-old man...
and had intermittent abdominal pain once in a while for a few months.
He came in complaining abdominal pain this morning.
He has no special medical history. According to ROS...
Are you presenting a case or what?
So what's his condition at this moment?
He's showing abdominal rigidity...
and severe tenderness.
I did a CT scan as I couldn't find out the cause.
It's here.
Hello? What happened?
It is ulcer perforation. He needs an operation right now.
How are things going there? Did they start cannulation?
Not yet.
I will operate on the patient with perforation. You stay there.
I can't finish the whole procedure...
within 20 minutes without you.
It's already been delayed by 10 minutes with the damaged aorta.
It can no longer be delayed.
But this patient can't wait until then.
If something goes wrong, it may lead to sepsis.
They are still working on vessel dissection here.
It'll take about 1 hour and 10 minutes until they have...
the heart-lung machine connected.
Including the time delayed,
it will take about 1 hour and 20 minutes.
- What do you mean? - Within that time,
we can operate on the patient with ulcer perforation.
If we work together.
Laparoscopy or open?
If we find the perforation quickly, it will be easier with laparoscopy.
But if not, we will have to cut the abdomen open.
We don't have time to take a risk.
- Okay. You will be cutting it open. - Okay.
- Ms. Eom. - Yes.
Is Dr. Yang on standby today?
Yes, he's in the company house.
Call him. We will have an emergency operation for ulcer perforation.
Yes, Dr. Do.
- Dr. Woo. - Yes.
Move the patient to the operating room immediately.
Yes, Dr. Do.
- This is operating room. - Just listen to me.
We have an emergency patient with ulcer perforation...
and I'm operating on him.
Don't tell Master Kim.
I will be back before he has the heart-lung machine connected.
Just keep me updated on your progress every 10 minutes.
Okay.
I will do that.
Can we start?
Yes, please.
Scalpel.
Pad.
Bovie.
Kelly.
Scalpel.
Retractor.
Irrigation.
Keep at irrigation.
Dr. Nam.
Give him heparin.
Injecting heparin.
(They started cannulation.)
They started cannulation.
Do you see it?
I think it's around lesser curvature.
Bovie.
Prolene number four.
Cut.
Scalpel. Pass me cannula.
Dr. Yoon, clamp on.
Suture.
Cut.
- Connect the suction line. - Irrigation.
Keep at irrigation.
That's it. Clamp off.
Let's do the venae cava inferior.
Yes, Master Kim.
He's fast.
Dr. Shin.
What do you think? Is it going well?
Yes, he's going by the text.
He's really fast, though.
It's been only 80 minutes, but he is already working on the posteava.
He will do risky things...
to reduce his surgical time.
You can't miss that point.
Okay.
I found it. Suture.
Cut.
- Cut. - Cut.
(They started cannulation of superior vein cava.)
Dr. Kang,
Master Kim just finished the cannulation of inferior vena cava.
He's starting the cannulation of superior vein cava.
They'll catch up to us at this rate.
- Cut. - Cut.
Cut.
Okay, all done.
Apply irrigation for 10 minutes and finish up.
After that, close him up in 10 minutes.
Irrigation.
Pad.
Hemovac, please.
Doctor. She says you have to come back in 10 minutes.
- Suture. - Should I use a stapler?
Yes.
Maintain tension by making fine subcutaneous stitches.
Use a stapler to stitch up.
- Cut. - Cut.
Doctor, you have to come right now.
Stapler.
Okay.
Dr. Woo. Please finish him up and dress him.
Yes, Dr. Kang.
Follow him to the ICU.
Call us if anything happens.
Yes, Dr. Do.
- Are you ready? - Yes, I am.
Pump on.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Pump flow down.
Cross-clamp.
Pump flow up.
Turn off the artificial heart.
We will now take out the artificial heart.
Are you ready, Dr. Kang and Dr. Do?
Yes, Master Kim.
Changing positions.
Removing the batteries and the controller.
Scalpel.
Bovie.
Dr. Do looks...
very good on screen, President Do.
- Army detractor. - One more, please.
Do you need coffee?
Would you like something to drink or some snacks?
Where's the washroom?
Keep going straight and turn left in the middle of the hall...
and turn right from there.
Thank you.
(Doctor's Office, Master Kim, Head of General Surgery)
You really made up your mind, didn't you?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
The batteries have been removed.
The controller has also been removed.
Finally, I will pull out the TET.
This is good.
They finished two minutes faster than we expected.
Good job, both of you.
Metzenbaum.
From now on,
we'll be going non-stop.
This is quite amazing.
Isn't it magnificent?
I'm not a doctor myself so I don't know very well,
but what I do know is that...
what they're doing is amazing.
What's your role at this hospital?
I'm the manager of this hospital, Jang Gi Tae.
(Manager Jang Gi Tae)
If you're the manager,
you must know everything about this hospital.
It's a bit awkward for me to say,
but you could say that...
I'm the shadowy power of this hospital.
I see.
The connective unit, please.
Long forceps.
Prolene number four, please.
The artificial heart, please.
How's the pump flow?
It's 5.8 liters.
I will remove the air from the artificial heart.
Increase the volume, please.
Turn on the artificial heart.
All right.
How is this possible?
What? Did you find a fault?
No, it's not that.
Every part of the procedure was done by the books.
There is something abnormal about this.
What's abnormal about it? What is it?
It was...
so quick.
It was quick?
If the adhesion is too severe like that,
it takes at least 3 to 4 hours until pump on.
However, it took him...
only 4 hours and 5 minutes to change the heart.
- This is just... - Is that all? Is anything else odd?
There is one more.
What is it? Tell me.
It was...
too perfect.
I knew it.
You are still not worn away.
Dr. Yoon.
Touch it.
Me?
This is the first artificial heart...
you've ever changed.
It took another two hours...
to control bleeding and to stitch him up.
The entire operation was...
finished in 6 hours and 2 minutes.
It took 6 hours and 2 minutes.
Everyone, great job.
- Great job. - Great job.
Great job.
Here.
Great job, Dr. Nam.
Great job.
That's how Master Kim...
and we...
created yet another miracle.
(Chapter 17, Moment of Truth)
(Intensive Care Unit)
You're here.
- Where's my father? - He's resting inside.
It looked like the operation went well.
One of his veins...
was touched during the operation.
We'll have to wait and see how he recovers.
He's doing very well.
His blood pressure, CVP, ABGA, and VBGA are all stable.
Okay.
What about the patient with ulcer perforation?
Dr. Kang just checked in on him.
It looks like the operation went well.
Make sure you check in often until the chairman wakes up.
If anything happens,
call me right away.
I'll stay by his side.
I'll take turns with Dr. Yoon, so don't worry about it.
- Thanks. - Sure.
Yes.
How is my father doing?
He's doing well so far.
All of his vitals are stable.
It'll take...
about 6 hours to 12 hours for him to wake up.
It'll be either late tonight or tomorrow morning.
It looked like...
you touched an aorta by mistake.
President Do.
You don't know much because your specialty is internal medicine.
Sometimes we touch an aorta during a surgery...
if there is an adhesion in veins.
You even brought a heart surgeon with you.
Didn't he tell you about that?
The moment the aorta popped,
the oxygen saturation of his brain dropped below 40.
It did drop, but it was around 38.
Then it went right up.
What if something goes wrong because of that?
I doubt anything will go wrong because of that, President Do.
I surely hope so.
Especially if you don't want any trouble.
Why?
You should go and pray on it.
Pray that he won't wake up.
What are you talking about?
I am worried about the chairman.
You surely are.
Excuse me.
Please do not misunderstand.
- I was honestly worried about... - I know.
Great job today.
Call me as soon as he wakes up.
I'll be at a hotel nearby.
Won't you go in?
I don't want to see...
my dad lying around ill.
Call me when he's up.
Chairman.
The operation went well.
I made...
a mistake in the middle.
But nothing went wrong because Master Kim covered for me.
If you don't give up,
you'll be up in no time.
Okay?
- When he was unconscious... - Did you see him?
- Doctor. - Doctor!
- Doctor, are you okay? - Aren't you tired?
- I'll make a visit soon! - May I take a picture?
- Sir! - Doctor!
- I respect you! - Can you wait?
Everyone, calm down. Master Kim just finished...
a very difficult operation.
I do apologize that he can't make any time for you all today.
Please do return to your posts. Thank you for understanding.
- Doctor! - Open the door!
Okay, I will let you see him.
Please return to your seats.
Yes?
Master Kim.
I'm so sorry to intrude.
What is it?
First of all, I'd like to congratulate you...
for a successful operation.
It was such a touching live operation.
Master Kim, you truly are good.
Right?
What's the occasion?
Oh, well. It's...
There is someone here...
who wants to interview you...
about this special artificial heart operation.
No, thanks.
Don't say that. Could you do this for the publicity of...
of Doldam Hospital and yourself?
No, I don't talk to any reporter.
Hello.
I'm sorry a mere reporter like me came to bother you.
Mr. Oh, you said you'll walk in when I give you the sign.
You can't do this.
It's been a while, Dr. Boo.
I haven't seen you since Jang Hyeon Joo's incident, right?
What's wrong?
I think it's infection. He has a 38℃ fever.
Ms. Cho.
Check his vital signs...
and give him propacetamol.
Yes, Dr. Yoon.
Go and have a meal. I will stay here.
I'm okay.
I heard you skipped breakfast.
You should eat something.
You will be working at night, too.
Thank you.
Did you call me?
What's the difference between chest PA and chest AP?
They are taken in different positions.
PA is taken in a standing position and AP is taken in a lying position.
What should you do with the patient with ulcer perforation, then?
In a standing position.
Then is it PA or AP?
Of course it is PA.
Is this PA or AP?
What?
This is AP.
And you reported me that there was no free air.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake giving an order.
I told you to be good, not sorry.
- I told you to be good. - I'm sorry.
- I will do it right from now on. - That's it. Just go.
Don't you think you went too far?
- What? - I know she made a mistake,
but you didn't have to rebuke her.
It's not that Dr. Woo made a wrong diagnosis or something.
She notified you of the ulcer perforation,
and had the patient undergo an operation before it was too late.
Mr. Park.
You are just picking on everything she does.
You are not just pointing out her mistakes.
You keep insulting her character.
I'm saying it's too much and I can't watch it anymore.
- Mr. Park. - Excuse me, Mr. Park.
Mind your own business.
This is doctors' business.
This is none of your business. You are a nurse.
This is my area.
I'm sorry, Dr. Do.
I will talk to him.
We have patients here. Can we stop now?
- You were wrong on this one. - Ms. Oh.
I know you don't like the way he works,
but you can't complain about it like that.
You know what I mean.
Hi.
President Do.
Hello.
Manager Jang.
Get him out of my office.
Pardon?
Did I make you feel uncomfortable?
Yes, you did.
Why?
Do I remind you of some bad memories?
Do you two know each other?
I'd say yes,
but we are not friends or something.
I don't even know...
what President Do said to incite you.
I just don't want to talk to a journalist like you.
Get out of my office now.
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
This is your problem.
You treat journalists like dirt...
as if they'd do anything for money.
It is very offensive.
You are like dirt.
I'm not worse than you who killed a patient...
by having your junior doctors perform a surgery for you.
At least I didn't kill a person.
There is more than one person...
who suffered...
and turned their back on the world because of your ridiculous reports.
So I'm telling you to reveal the truth with evidence...
instead of avoiding me.
If you keep shying away from it,
it will just breed more misunderstandings, Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
Why would I...
explain myself with evidence to a jerk like you?
People want to...
know the truth.
The truth?
So...
If you know the truth,
do you have the courage to tell it to the world?
He is...
Dr. Ahn Woo Yeol, thoracic surgeon at Geodae Hospital.
It seems he was very impressed by the operation.
He praised you a lot.
It was Master Kim who did a good job.
It is true that he is good,
but he couldn't have done it without a good first assistant.
I guess you saw I made a mistake.
It was delayed...
by more than 10 minutes because of my mistake.
You are very modest.
She is a talented doctor I've supported since she was young.
She is my friend's daughter,
but I feel like she's my daughter.
I'll take this moment...
as the end of our relationship.
We recently had a conflict.
Are you still upset with it?
No, that's not it.
I just scolded you once as a senior and a father.
You can't treat me like this because of that.
I've put a lot of efforts into making you a decent doctor.
Young kids are all like that these days.
It is just our generation who tried everything...
to humbly beg pardon and pacify their seniors.
But young people these days break off contact instead.
I'm sorry.
I should have given it more thought.
I'm pleased to meet you, anyway. Dr. Yoon.
I want to talk to you about the operation...
when we get a chance.
Well, actually, you are single, right?
In fact, Dr. Yoon too is a single...
who only thinks of her job.
Just like you.
I think you two would...
make a cute couple.
Don't you think, President Do?
Spare some time to come visit me.
Let's have dinner together with Dr. Ahn.
Excuse me.
Dr. Yoon, what are you doing? Master Kim is looking for you.
Master Kim?
You should hurry. It seems to be urgent.
Okay. Please excuse me.
Where is Master Kim? Is he in the office?
He's in the staff room.
In the staff room?
What's going on?
You didn't have lunch yet, right?
You said Master Kim wants to see me.
What do you want to eat? Jajangmyeon or pizza?
It is all we can order for delivery.
Next time you are in such a situation,
just leave the place without hesitation.
You don't have to hear all the nonsense.
Do you want me to hang up a sign on your back?
"Yoon Seo Jung is taken."
"Do not touch her." Like this.
If the same thing happens again,
I will go tell President Do everything.
"Seo Jung has a boyfriend."
"I'm her boyfriend."
I will say that.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why? Do you think I won't do that?
Do you want me to tell him now?
I will have pizza.
I want to eat pizza. I'm starving.
I knew it.
You must be hungry.
Let's talk about that again after eating lunch.
What do you want to drink?
Anything.
Do you want coke or sprite?
That has to be the most difficult answer to work with.
I can't order pizza like this.
Excuse me, Mr. Park.
Yes?
About your taking my side earlier...
I do appreciate it,
but I hope you don't do that in the future.
I have much to learn...
and I still make a lot of mistakes.
Getting corrected even in such a way...
is a big help for me.
Getting corrected and getting looked down upon...
are two different things.
Either way...
I think it's something I have to cope with.
- That being said... - But still, I don't think...
it's right for you to be mistreated.
That's the way...
I was taught here.
No matter how young, I was respected.
I was scolded when I made a big mistake,
but I was never looked down upon as a person.
People will do it more if you just let them.
They think it's okay.
I didn't say that to Dr. Do to take your side.
If I saw any other person being treated like that at this hospital,
I would have done the same.
This is the emergency room.
Ms. Oh. It's me.
I need to see you in the president's office. It's an emergency.
Reporter Oh?
What about him?
He's blackmailing me saying he'll expose Master Kim of his past.
Starting with how he got kicked out of Geodae Hospital...
and he went on about a woman named Jang Hyun Joo.
Why did you take that reporter to Master Kim's office?
I didn't know this would happen.
All I wanted was publicity for our hospital...
by letting the word out on the success of the operation.
I only did it for our hospital's recognition.
Chairman Shin hasn't even woken up yet.
Why did you get ahead of yourself?
That's a bit harsh, Ms. Oh.
How is that getting ahead of myself?
President Yeo, why would you leave in the middle of a conversation?
I forgot that I need to go down to Sokcho.
I'm sorry. I'll have to leave early.
Why would you go to Sokcho at a time like this?
Gosh, you're so gullible.
My goodness.
I'm not doing this for my own good.
I'm doing everything for the hospital.
Gosh.
That person, Jang Hyun Joo,
really follows Master Kim wherever he goes.
It wasn't even his own will to make others to operate on her.
Why do you think he's not even trying to justify himself?
Boo Yong Joo. That's the kind of a man he is.
He's unfriendly and stubborn as a rock.
I think he feels somewhat responsible...
for the death of Jang Hyun Joo.
Even so, it's not something that should be buried.
What President Do and Geodae Hospital...
did to Jang Hyun Joo and some of the patients there...
and how they put all the blame on Master Kim...
Isn't it about time we put the matter in its true light?
It won't be easy.
It's highly unlikely that they left any evidence of what they did.
But still, I can't understand...
why Master Kim is keeping quiet about it.
Moreover,
it involved the death of his favorite pupil.
Rather than mourning the deceased,
he made an inevitable choice to save some child's life.
Let's just say that's the case.
Some child?
Who's that?
That's as much as I can say.
I made a promise to Master Kim that I'll take it to my grave.
- Let's take a CT scan. - Yes, Doctor.
Sir.
We'll go take a CT scan shortly. Please sit tight.
Are you busy?
He's experiencing right flank pain.
There's hematuria and he's waiting for his turn on the abdomen CT scan.
It looks like an ureter stone.
I think so, too.
That ulcer perforation patient in the morning...
I heard you performed the operation.
I'm sorry. They said it could develop into a sepsis.
I made the decision without your permission.
- You did good. - Okay.
What?
Forget it if you didn't hear.
- Please continue. - Yes, Master Kim.
You found this in Master Kim's room?
I think that's what Boo Yong Joo wanted to do...
at Doldam Hospital.
Boo Yong Joo, you swine.
Some malicious dream you've been dreaming.
I can't believe he's been plotting such nonsense.
It's not impossible, so to speak.
If this operation finishes successfully,
Chairman Shin will completely have...
Boo Yong Joo's back.
That won't happen.
It's bad news for Yong Joo,
but I think...
the sky is still on my side.
He's not waking up.
BP, CVP, ABGA, and VBGA...
Everything is stable.
How long has it been since the operation?
It's been nine hours.
We should wait and see...
until the 12-hour mark.
Patients of old age...
tend to take longer to wake up.
I understand.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean? He's not awake?
Do you know what time it is?
(Director Shin)
Yes, Director Shin.
As soon as I got the report saying he's yet to awake,
I'm on my way to Doldam Hospital.
I'll have to go there...
and get a grasp of the situation.
Yes. I understand.
Dr. Nam.
Where are we on propofol and pentalene?
I stopped the injection after the 12-hour mark.
Just in case.
Every indicator was in the normal range all night.
There was almost no bleeding, so we started giving him heparin.
He hasn't had any crisis.
Why is he not waking up?
- Master Kim. - Yes?
Chairman Shin's guardian is outside.
I'll go.
No, you should keep by his side.
Let's go.
Page Mr. Goo.
What happened?
Why hasn't my father woken up yet?
You said it'll take 12 hours at most for him to wake up.
It is 10am now.
19 hours have passed since his surgery ended.
It rarely happens, but it's not impossible.
We have to wait at least for 2 or 3 days.
Why did you suddenly change your opinion?
You said 12 hours. Why are you changing it to 2 or 3 days?
In most cases, patients wake up in 12 hours,
but when they don't,
we need to check their condition for between 48 and 72 hours.
That's what I meant.
All you do is check his condition?
You should be doing everything you can. You'll just check on him?
I did everything I could do during the surgery.
The surgery went well,
and we minimized the hours of putting him under anaesthesia.
In this situation, all we can do is...
wait for the patient to wake up.
There's nothing else we can do.
That's not true.
The fact that he hasn't woken up yet means...
that there may be a problem in his brain.
You should take a CT scan immediately.
I am his doctor.
Therefore, I'm the one who decides whether to take a CT scan or not.
How dare you?
What do you mean by that?
Are you trying to stall for time or something?
Can't you see what are connected to his body?
Four infusion pumps,
2 tubes from the artificial heart, and 4 chest tubes.
In total, there are 10 tubes connected to his body.
What if something goes wrong while we take a CT scan...
with all the tubes connected to him,
would you take responsibility?
- This is your biggest problem. - What?
You only rely on your ability.
You never admit what you did wrong.
I'm sure all you thought of was a perfect surgery.
You finished such a difficult surgery in 6 hours and 2 minutes.
It's something you can draw attention with. But!
I guess you didn't consider the possibility...
that Chairman Shin would not wake up.
So you are flustered...
and you can't accept reality. Am I right?
Stop beating around the bush. Make it short.
What's your point?
I've been curious...
why you pushed ahead with such a risky surgery...
even though he has terminal lung cancer.
Did you take such a big risk just for this?
Just for this?
This is a mere shabby affiliated hospital,
and you are working with...
an anesthesiologist who is going through a medical litigation,
a fellow who has been kicked out from Geodae Hospital,
an ER doctor who had PTSD in the past,
and the staff members of a small countryside hospital...
who haven't even worked in a general hospital.
What did you dream of with such poor team members?
A trauma center?
Was that what you wanted from Chairman Shin...
in return for his surgery?
A trauma center?
Is that why you operated on him...
even though he has terminal lung cancer?
(The Bizarre Case of Surgery Fraud at a Countryside Hospital)
(The genius surgeon Boo Yong Joo pushed ahead with a surgery, )
(and caused the chairman to fall into a coma.)
As of this moment,
you are disqualified from your position as his doctor.
- Dr. Shin. - Yes, President Do.
You're in charge of Chairman Shin from today.
Take a CT scan immediately.
Yes, President Do.
If the result shows...
that he has cerebral infarction,
you will not only go through a medical litigation,
but also lose your doctor's license.
- What are you doing, Dr. Shin? - Yes, President Do.
Could you please move aside?
Please let me go in.
Did you wash your hands?
Are you really going in there...
wearing these?
In the ICU?
- Mr. Goo. - Yes?
From now on, don't let anyone...
enter the ICU without my permission.
Especially...
this man and this man...
shouldn't go in there.
Don't let anyone go through this door.
Yes, Master Kim.
What are you doing?
I'm protecting my patient as his doctor.
- Why? - Are you really...
going to let him die?
Here.
Can you read this?
(I hereby authorize Master Kim to make decisions until I wake up.)
This is the letter Chairman Shin wrote...
by himself for me before the surgery.
The full decision-making authority...
in every possible situation that might happen after the surgery...
has been given to me.
I have been given the full authority.
That's what this letter is about.
I am the president of the parent hospital.
How dare a mere surgeon at the affiliated hospital...
stops me only with a letter?
How dare you?
I'm sure he had it notarized.
I guess that means...
it has a legal effect.
Am I right, Ms. Jo?
The corporation lawyer has notarized the letter.
I was there, too.
You were there, too?
The fact that it has a legal effect...
means that it carries legal binding force, I guess.
So stop interfering my work and get lost.
Can you not understand what I said?
I said, get lost.
As soon as Chairman Shin regains his consciousness,
we will get in touch.
You...
should have stopped him when he was doing this.
Were you helping him instead?
He trusts Master Kim more than anyone else.
So do I.
If things go wrong for him,
you will be finished, too.
(The Foundation Plan of Trauma Center at Doldam Hospital)
The era of rampant facts.
The world where what powerful people say is considered as a fact,
while powerless people's words are considered as a wild rumor.
Hello.
- What brings you here again? - I just...
came here to have udon.
Can I have a bowl of udon?
With their own opinions and lies...
that distort the truth,
people insist their opinions are the facts in this world.
(The Bizarre Case of Surgery Fraud at a Countryside Hospital)
(Photos, Doldam Hospital)
(Personnel Records, Kang Dong Joo)
(Personnel Records, Yoon Seo Jung)
(Student ID, Jang Hyun Joo)
If you find out the truth,
do you have the courage to tell it to the world?
Hello?
It's me. Oh Seong Jae.
What if...
I say that I have the courage to tell the truth to the world?
Will you tell me the truth?
The truth is...
always rooted on facts.
Can you tell me the truth?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
But not all the facts are...
always right.