Hello?
It's me. Oh Seong Jae.
What if...
I say that I have the courage to tell the truth to the world?
Will you tell me the truth?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
In our lives,
there are things you can only see...
after the lapse of time.
Such as why such things happened to me,
why I met those people,
and why that coincidence even happened?
Okay.
(Geodae Hospital)
What's your major?
Are you close to Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
There are the moments that I had no regard for.
You are the doctor.
Aren't you?
You are Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
And soon, they start to have significance one by one.
Why do you keep prying into Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
What is it you want to know?
I respect him.
I want to...
learn from you.
I want to study hard...
and become a good doctor like Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
I want to carry out a collaborative...
surgery with you some day.
At some point,
it started making a path.
That's enough.
Can you...
tell me the truth?
What happened 14 years ago?
Why did Jang Hyun Joo die like that?
And why did Dr. Boo Yong Joo...
get kicked out of Geodae Hospital all of a sudden?
There's no such thing as truth.
14 years ago, Boo Yong Joo...
was a coward.
He stayed silent...
and ran away.
That's all.
(Chapter 18, Whether You Want It or Not)
(The Foundation Plan of Trauma Center at Doldam Hospital)
(Head of General Surgery, Master Kim)
Manager Jang, may I have a word?
I'll leave the room for a moment.
What is it?
The person who gave President Do Master Kim's document...
Was it you?
Why do you think...
I did that?
Dr. Song promoted you as a manager...
as soon as he got here from Geodae Hospital, right?
Were you not conciliated back then already?
What an unfair accusation.
The promotion I got was a rightful compensation...
for my hard work.
Then why did you...
go in Master Kim's room that day?
Which day?
When do you mean?
- Manager Jang. - From what I heard from Dr. Yoon,
you told her that you were emptying Master Kim's garbage can.
But don't you think that makes no sense?
Why doesn't that make sense?
Am I not allowed to empty a garbage can?
I know you, Jang Gi Tae.
You come from a wealthy background...
and you don't even put the garbage in the correct bins.
You don't even clean up after eating ramyeon.
And you're saying a person like that...
emptied a garbage can that's in someone else's office?
Don't look away.
Look at my eyes and tell me.
Master Kim's document.
You handed it over, didn't you?
- No. - You really didn't do it?
It wasn't me.
I, Jang Gi Tae, is absolutely innocent on this one.
Then who was it?
Who gave that document to President Do?
Who?
I...
don't know anything.
I don't...
remember anything.
This is not a hearing.
I told you I'm only here for udon.
Please give me that udon.
(The Bizarre Case of Surgery Fraud at a Countryside Hospital)
(Casino kingpin Shin Myung Ho rumored to be in poor health)
(Send)
How is the chairman's condition?
Is there any pain response?
No, nothing yet.
He should awake by now.
It's been over 24 hours since the time of operation.
The fact that he is still not awake...
means that a cerebral problem has developed.
In worst case scenario,
Doldam Hospital will have to be closed down.
We can't keep treating patients...
at a hospital that will eventually close.
Don't you think that's too extreme?
There's already a word...
going around the stock market on Chairman Shin.
(Chairman Shin Myung Ho brain-dead after artificial heart surgery.)
Brain-dead?
Who on earth is spreading such a false rumor?
After all, people prefer...
stimulating news over facts.
From now on, you should think only about the chairman.
There's no more time to waste.
Doldam Hospital emergency room.
Where are you calling from?
Well, we don't...
Please hold.
Ms. Oh. A reporter is asking...
if this is the place Chairman Shin underwent operation.
Hello. This is emergency room.
We don't have much knowledge over such matters.
We'd appreciate it if you could contact the administrative office.
Doldam Hospital emergency room.
Excuse me for a moment.
Ms. Oh. I got a similar call.
A reporter is asking about Chairman Shin.
Hello. This is emergency room.
We only answer calls about emergency patients.
If you keep calling, the people who really need our attention might...
Well, I don't know. Stop calling.
What on earth is going on, Ms. Oh?
Ms. Oh.
I think a rumor has been spread.
A rumor?
(Chairman Shin Myung Ho, brain-dead after artificial heart surgery)
What rumor?
What are they all up about? There's a rumor going around?
Apparently, there's a rumor...
on social network that Chairman Shin is brain-dead.
Where did you hear that nonsense? It's nothing like that at all.
I said I can't disclose that information.
I'm hanging up.
What's going on all of a sudden?
How should I know?
I feel like I got bombed.
What's all the fuss about?
It's really not true.
- What's going on? - It's... It's nothing.
There's a ill rumor going around...
on Chairman Shin's condition.
The reporters are on it and calling us as we speak.
Don't worry.
I won't let any information get out.
President Do.
You're here.
- Is President Yeo at his office? - He's...
Is President Yeo upstairs right now?
The president is currently out.
Yes, Manager Jang. What is it?
President Do of Geodae Hospital is here right now.
One moment, please.
It's me.
What makes you come down here unannounced?
I'm here to give you the last notice.
Doldam Hospital...
will be closed soon.
In the board meeting that will take place tomorrow,
we will come to the decision.
So stop stalling...
and arrange the chairman to be treated at Geodae Hospital.
If you want a spot...
at the sanatorium that will be built on top of this,
you should do as you're told.
Now that I delivered the message, I'll hang up.
I should go see the chairman now that I'm here.
President Do. President Do.
Has the closing of Doldam Hospital really been decided?
Does that mean I'm going back to Geodae Hospital? Yes?
I'm going back, right?
Master Kim.
What are you saying?
The closing of Doldam Hospital has been decided?
President Do just came here and said so.
Everyone including Ms. Oh is panicking.
What should we do?
What happens to the staff?
It's time to come back.
By tomorrow, the decision will be made to close this place.
As soon as the decision gets made, we'll take appropriate measures.
Why...
do you have to...
Why do you have to do this?
From the viewpoint of the board,
this is a worthless hospital experiencing deficit every year.
We're worthless?
Chairman Shin will be transferred to Geodae Hospital within today.
I want you to follow him...
and look after him with us.
I'll make that happen...
so come back to Geodae Hospital.
You're closing down the hospital?
What do you think you're doing right now?
You're neglecting my father waving that notarized letter in your hand.
I can't just stand and watch as the daughter.
I'll transfer my father even if that means I have to close you down.
Look, Ms. Director.
Do you know how many people...
come here from all over the country because of the casino you built?
8,500 people on average a day.
And then we have over 30 to 40 traffic accident cases...
coming into our emergency room every week.
Will you really shut this hospital down?
Where will those people go, then?
Do you want them to die on the streets wandering around...
looking for an emergency room?
I heard from President Do...
that it's been running in a deficit of a million dollars every year.
This year, the deficit recorded to 1.5 million dollars.
We're talking about patients.
Will you really bring in money?
Us at Geodae Foundation...
have no more intention of taking Doldam Hospital's deficit.
And that's the hospital...
where your father received an operation.
And he hasn't...
woke up.
It's 72 hours...
- Can't you even wait 48 hours? - Wait 48 hours?
The longer the time goes, the higher the chance of a brain death!
Who says he's brain dead?
I'm his doctor, and I didn't say that. Who says that?
Is everything...
you people are concerned about is money right now?
"Would it be better for him to die now?"
"Would it be better for him to hold out a bit longer?"
"Which would make it easier for me to inherit his assets?"
What?
You must be insane.
If not,
just shut up and listen to what I say as his doctor.
After I let your father live,
you can decide to close this place or do whatever you'd like.
Are we really shutting down?
This is driving me insane.
- This is awful. - What shall we do?
Are we really going out of business?
Should I look for another job?
Hey, be quiet. Hello.
Ms. Oh, what happened? Are we really shutting down?
Nothing has been decided.
Just stay focused as always.
Ms. Oh, how can you work under such a circumstance?
Like I said, I'm not hurt.
Darn it. Let me go home.
Sir, you just said that your stomach hurts a lot.
You need to take a CT scan.
What happened?
He's been drinking a lot, and he has stomach pain.
I asked him to take a CT scan, but he won't.
I don't need to take it.
Why would you waste money on CT scan or whatever that is?
If I had the money,
I'd rather drink it away.
Sir, you're a patient.
- You need to listen to the doctor. - I'm not a patient.
Move away. I'm going home.
- Sir. - Move. Move away.
Move.
What do we do? Should we go and grab him?
Leave him alone.
It's not like he's the only drunk we get.
(Intensive Care Unit)
What are you up to?
I was just resting.
I'll go back soon.
Are you okay?
Our hospital may close down.
How can I be okay?
What is this?
It's Master Kim's.
He's been...
painting such a picture.
Did you know?
No.
I didn't.
(The Foundation Plan of Trauma Center at Doldam Hospital)
I didn't know he had this in his mind.
He did.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
President Yeo.
Are you okay?
Well, there is no reason...
for me to be okay or not to be okay.
I haven't got much power, either.
I'm just an old man in the back room.
But still,
I wanted to become an old man...
who can take the side...
with what's right and give them the power.
What are you talking about?
Just now,
I was informed that they will shut down Doldam Hospital.
It was from President Do.
It's really weird.
We all know that President Do is wrong.
We all know that he is doing something very wrong.
But why does he still...
have such a strong power in his high position?
Thanks for the udon.
Where have you been?
An ambulance and doctors will be here soon to pick up Chairman Shin.
Oh, they should be here soon.
Who says?
Who do you think? President Do.
You should just give up now.
When tomorrow comes,
it'll be shut down, anyway.
Do you still think...
that Chairman Shin will wake up from his coma?
No way. I doubt that.
Manager Jang.
Yes, Master Kim.
Can you get this garbage out of my sight?
- Garbage? - Oh, and...
make sure none of...
those guys from Seoul set a foot in this hospital.
- Did you just call me garbage? - Hey.
You are garbage, aren't you?
You're a doctor...
who doesn't want a patient to wake up.
I'm just saying that this is a done deal.
I feel bad about how you are holding onto that hopeless man.
Whoever it may be,
don't you dare come anywhere near the ICU.
I'll take all of your names and file a lawsuit.
- Understood? - Yes.
Listen to me, Manager Jang.
Did you say yes?
You of all people can't say that.
You should take the right side. Which side are you on?
Will it be Doldam or Geodae? Understand?
Oh, yes.
My goodness.
I am so furious.
We worked so hard to get so far.
Master Kim and all of us...
worked so hard to get this far.
(The Foundation Plan of Trauma Center at Doldam Hospital)
Let me check your pain response.
We can't give things up just like this, right?
So...
please come around.
Please, Chairman Shin.
Ms. Eom, about Lee Kang Jin...
I'm not sure if we'd be paid on time.
I know. I even got a new house around here.
- Ms. Eom. - Yes?
Yes.
Aren't you answering the phone?
It might be a reporter asking about Chairman Shin's condition.
What if it is for a patient?
Hello? This is the emergency room of Doldam Hospital.
Okay.
A patient with glass embedded in his abdomen is coming in five minutes.
Didn't you hear me? A patient is coming in.
What is going on?
Why are you staring at me doing nothing?
I heard they will shut down Doldam Hospital.
They are so distracted that they can't do anything.
Is it true that they are shutting it down?
I want to hear it from you.
Please tell me.
That's what I want to ask you.
Did you choose...
to leave Doldam Hospital already?
- That's not it. - If it's not that,
why are you...
standing here idly as if the hospital is closed down?
Ms. Oh.
Why do you look so down?
I'm...
not about to have the hospital shut down.
Just like yesterday,
I will be here...
today and tomorrow...
waiting for the patients...
who need my help.
That's my decision, Dong Joo.
- Dr. Boo. - So...
just do your job as usual.
As we always did,
let's focus on the patients, Dong Joo.
We have an emergency patient.
He is a 37-year-old man with glass embedded in his abdomen.
What happened?
He was changing the fluorescent tube on a ladder,
and he fell down to the window.
It seems a piece of glass sliced into his abdomen.
- Let's move him to the hybrid room. - Okay.
- Ms. Eom. - Yes? Okay.
Master Kim said.
The strongest resistance in the world is...
pushing on undaunted to finish your job...
no matter what the circumstances are.
- Dr. Woo, cut his clothes open. - Okay.
His vital signs are 110 over 70 and 70 beats per minute.
Oh, no. Dr. Woo!
You are not supposed to cut a duck-down parka.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that.
Give me the dressing set. I will check his wound.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Set up IV lines and execute a full drop.
Give him antibiotics and do a CT scan on him.
Okay.
Master Kim might...
have already known that...
our worries and fears...
could be even lighter than a feather.
Gosh.
What's the matter?
(Doldam Hospital)
Please come on in. I was waiting for you.
Manager Jang. It's good you are here.
Please show them the way.
What are you doing? I told you to show them the way.
What do you think you are doing?
I was instructed not to let anyone into the Intensive Care Unit...
by Master Kim.
No one can't get in there.
What? Gosh.
Step aside.
Get out of my way.
I can't move.
No, I won't move.
How dare you!
What is that?
What?
I can't believe this.
(Intensive Care Unit)
Dr. Yoon.
Did Chairman Shin come around?
Yes, Master Kim.
Nearly alert. It seems to be GCS of 10T.
Chairman Shin.
Can you hear me?
If you hear my voice,
please move your finger.
Chairman Shin.
Master Kim.
Good job.
What are you talking about?
Are they shutting you out?
Master Kim, that jerk told them...
not to let anyone into the Intensive Care Unit.
Even Manager Jang is with them to block the way.
Are you talking to President Do?
Yes, President Do.
You promoted him to manager, but he's just ungrateful.
He's such an encumbrance.
We have no time to waste.
Just push ahead. Do anything you can...
to take Chairman Shin out of the hospital. Now!
Okay. I will take care of it.
Let's stay calm.
You will go this way, and you will you that way, okay?
Hold on.
Gosh.
I wasn't going to go this far.
Attack!
Stop them!
Move!
No!
What are you doing?
What do you think we're doing? We're following orders.
We're making our way to Chairman Shin.
Are you some street thugs?
What do you think you're doing at a hospital?
You shouldn't have told them to stop us in the first place.
Do you think I want to do this? I don't want to do this at this age.
Shut it.
All of you...
- Get lost from this hospital. - Gosh, you're stubborn.
I said we have to take Chairman Shin with us.
He's awake.
Exactly. Since he's awake, we should...
He's awake?
The chairman is awake.
So do shut your mouth...
and get lost from this hospital. Okay?
Father did?
The chairman...
Did he awake?
Yes, okay.
No, I'm on my way right now.
Father is awake.
He recognizes everyone and is very conscious.
How's my father?
You should go in there.
Chairman Shin.
How are you feeling right now?
Did the surgery go well?
Of course.
It was a success, Chairman Shin.
Good work,
Master Kim.
All right.
Father.
- Are you all right? - Yes.
- I'm all right. - Dad.
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
Thanks, Dad.
It's okay.
Hello.
That cocky swine.
President Do. What do you intend to do now?
The chairman is awake and...
Anyhow, the dispatched staff will return by tomorrow.
- I will also go back to Seoul... - No.
- Stay here for a little longer. - Pardon?
My game isn't over yet.
So until Doldam Hospital closes down,
be prepared to completely devote yourself to this hospital.
Devote myself?
I said I'm sorry, Honey.
They said I was going back to Geodae Hospital tomorrow.
I even packed all my things.
Now they're saying the decision has been changed.
I'm not happy about this either.
Do you think I want to... Hello?
Who am I talking to?
Oh, no.
Your wife must be really upset.
It's either one of the two.
Either I hand in my resignation or I get divorced.
Why don't your wife and your baby come down here and live with you?
My daughter just started walking...
and she's the kind of woman who is already looking into pre-schools.
I see. I guess she won't come.
In Soo.
Let's go to Dr. Nam's restaurant after work.
I'll buy you a glass of beer.
- I'm in. - I'm in.
Do they have good food there?
Dr. Nam's ramyeon is delicious.
Their signature dish is ramyeon?
There's beer, too.
What is it?
That patient with glass penetrated through the abdomen...
The CT scan result came out. Do you want to go look at it?
It's not a common case.
We could take a look at it together.
I'd like it more if you could be my assistant.
What does that mean?
What do you mean?
Everyone here is suffering...
because of my dad.
So what?
Aren't I not the target of hatred as well?
To be honest,
President Do sure is hateful.
Even so,
that's not your fault.
If I were you,
I would be embarrassed by my dad.
- Are you criticizing him again? - Forget it.
Are you going to be the assistant or not?
The patient is waiting. Make up your mind.
Gosh, forget it then.
Fine, I'll do it.
You have a thing for shoving people around.
Next time, you're the assistant. Got it?
Punk.
Dr. Kang. Right on time.
You got a registered mail from Geodae Hospital.
Registered mail?
- For me? - Yes.
(Operation Record)
(Dr. Boo Yong Joo)
April 29th.
Who sent this?
I'm not sure.
I didn't check who sent it since it's from Geodae Hospital.
Did you send that thing I told you to?
Yes, President Do.
I sent the registered mail.
It should be delivered by today.
Okay. You can go now.
(Geodae Hospital)
The scariest thing in the world...
is the seed of doubt.
When you plant one,
it grows well by itself.
(Operated on 2002, April 29th by Dr. Boo Young Joo)
Mr. Kang Eun Young has passed.
Father.
Honey.
(Operated on 2002, April 29th by Dr. Boo Young Joo)
(Intensive Care Unit)
I'll come back shortly after.
The board won't be discussing closing this place down for a while.
But it's only as long as my father is here.
You do know that, right?
Yes.
Whatever you say.
To be honest, I still don't approve of you.
But this time,
I'm really thankful.
I mean it.
Okay.
Not every rich person is blinded by the inheritance.
I'm the type of rich person...
who wants to live under her father's shadow as long as possible...
to live comfortably.
So I hope my father will live a long life.
I'm going to Florida to see my children,
but I'll come back early next month.
Until then,
please take good care of my father.
Of course. Have a safe trip.
Good day.
Oh, right. I have something to ask you about.
Please go ahead.
Why did you name yourself Master Kim?
What is your name, Doctor?
My name?
I have a very common name.
It's Kim Somebody.
I see. Dr. Kim Somebody.
Dr. Kim Somebody! Are you busy now?
Why do you ask?
When you use the Billroth two for a gastrectomy,
should you leave the front part as a cul-de-sac?
I'm just curious.
Hello.
Dr. Kim Somebody.
- Are you going home? - What is it this time?
It's about the Roux-en-Y bypass.
If you connect the stomach and the jejunum,
you leave the duodenum as it is, right?
It contains videos of the operations you asked me about.
Both gastrectomy and Roux-en-Y bypass.
Did you perform those operations?
Why do you ask so many questions?
Just watch the videos.
Gosh. You are so talkative.
Get well soon.
Thank you. You are my master from now on.
This is...
what my daughter gave me before her surgery.
She said it's a gift for you.
(Student ID, Jang Hyun Joo)
(To Master Kim)
Dear Master Kim.
Master Kim, you must have been annoyed by me so much.
But you answered all my questions and taught me kindly.
Thank you for that.
In fact, when I first met you I knew...
that you are Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
Excuse me.
Do you happen to know Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
I was so nervous to see you.
That's why I asked that instead.
I will never forget the times I spent...
with you in the hospital.
Thank you for operating on me.
After the surgery, I will visit you when I regain my health.
I'm dreaming of the day...
when I perform a surgery with you.
Sincerely, your student Jang Hyun Joo.
I see.
Do you think she knows...
that the name she gave you...
changed your life?
I don't know.
(To Master Kim)
The CT scan result shows that there isn't serious damage in arteries.
It seems he has intestinal injuries.
Does it mean he'll be okay after the surgery?
Dr. Kang.
Yes?
We can't be sure before we begin the surgery.
There might be damaged artery by the glass we can't see now.
I see.
Let's take him to the operating room first.
Okay.
What's wrong? Do you have worries?
It's nothing.
We have a patient.
To the bed number four.
What's the problem?
He started to have acute chest pain right before calling us.
Chest pain?
We administered sublingual nitroglycerin twice,
but it didn't help to relieve the pain.
- What were his vital signs? - It was 160 over 100, and 100.
Ms. Oh, please check his vital signs again.
- Please take an EKG, Dr. Woo. - Yes, Dr. Kang.
- His BP is 100 over 60 now. - Pardon?
Why did his BP suddenly...
- Could you check his right arm? - Yes, Dr. Yoon.
I thought you went up to the ICU.
I did, then I came back down.
- Do we have the EKG result? - Here it is.
It's certainly not STEMI.
His BP is 160 over 100 on his right arm.
Is that so?
Sir, can you describe your chest pain for me?
It feels like my back is being torn.
No way.
- Aortic dissection? - Aortic dissection?
Please help us!
Please save my husband, Doctor.
- Oh, no. - Goodness.
Where does it hurt?
He says his stomach is aching.
He even had blood in stool.
I think I'm dying.
Help me.
He came here earlier, but he refused examination,
and self-discharged.
- He just left the hospital? - He was completely drunk.
His BP is 90 over 60, and 130 beats.
Did you say he had rectal bleeding?
He went to the bathroom saying his stomach hurt.
He stayed in there too long, so I checked on him.
He looked so pale sitting on the toilet. He couldn't move at all.
I helped him stand up, and I saw...
so much blood in the toilet. I can't believe this.
I am worried.
- What should I do? - My stomach hurts so much.
The wall motion seems fine.
I can't see the aortic root clearly.
It's aortic dissection.
- Is it? - Yes. Right here.
It's hard to see the abdominal aorta.
I think it's Stanford type A.
How are you feeling now?
I'm feeling good.
Maybe because I'm feeling good,
I think it's much easier to breathe now.
By the way,
all these tubes connected to my body...
They're so annoying. When can I remove all these?
Gosh. You are as impatient as ever.
I will get rid of all the tubes including the chest tubes.
Thank you for your effort.
Thank you.
Please don't say that. I should be thanking you.
Our hospital could have been closed because of you.
What?
Really?
I guess I really am an influential man. Right?
They want me at the emergency room.
Oh, sure. Go ahead.
Okay.
- What's going on? - We've three emergency operations.
Three patients?
One of them has an abdomen penetrating injury.
He has glass shatter in the wound,
but he isn't bleeding much.
I think the patient with an aortic dissection is more urgent.
Do we have someone with an aortic dissection?
- Do you have his CT scan? - It just came out.
It's type A and it has already ascended.
- What's his blood pressure? - Initially, 160 over 100...
on the right and 100 over 60 on the left.
After we injected esmolol,
his BP on the right side dropped to 120 over 80.
- What about his EKG? - We took a look.
- How's aortic valve regurgitation? - A bit, but not much.
- What about the other patient? - His CT scan is coming up.
- It's ischemic colitis. - Ischemic colitis?
We have the CT scan of the ischemic colitis patient.
This is bad.
I even see pneumatosis intestinalis.
We have to cut it out.
Yes. It seems so.
All three of them are emergency cases. What should we do?
It's not like we can...
send any one of them to another hospital.
Master Kim, let's start with the aortic dissection case.
It'll take us a while to prepare fully for the operation.
I believe we should begin with the ischemic colitis patient.
The aortic dissection patient is the most urgent case.
That patient came in first, too.
If we have to go by the order which they came in,
we have to go with the abdomen penetration.
The most urgent case is...
the aortic dissection patient. Isn't that right?
Why are you so hung up over that case? You're a GS.
What's wrong?
Let me know if you need anything else.
Sure. Thank you.
Excuse me, I have a question.
- Yes? - About 14 years ago,
didn't your son go crazy in the ER of Geodae Hospital?
Who are you?
Why do you...
bring up something that happened 14 years ago?
I've been gathering news about this one guy.
Here.
(Reporter Oh Seong Jae)
But some of the puzzles do not seem to line up.
I'm having a difficult time trying to make...
all of the pieces match.
I know that your husband...
went into the emergency room...
and passed away within an hour.
It was a problem with his aorta, right?
Seo Jung.
How long will it take for you to prepare for the surgery?
It'll take me about 30 minutes to get the pump ready, too.
Okay.
Until then, hold the aortic dissection patient.
Let's move the ischemic colitis patient to the operating room.
- Yes, Master Kim. - Master Kim.
Dong Joo, you are a general surgeon.
You should focus only on your patients.
Seo Jung and I will take care of the cardiac patient.
Did you lose him like this back then?
That day,
you are the surgeon...
who did the operation on the VIP...
who walked in after my father.
Don't be so nervous.
What I want to know is this.
I know that the hospital bill was very high at that time.
I heard it was around 200,000 dollars.
I want to know who helped you pay that back.
Can you tell me who that is?
Can you tell me?
Why did you...
push my father's operation back?
Dong Joo.
Tell me the reason.
Who...
is it?
Why can't you answer me?
Why did you push my father's operation back?
Why?
(We thank Kim Hye Eun for her special appearance.)
(Dr. Romantic)
Do you know what is the easiest thing in this world?
It's breaking a relationship.
You can do it with a word.
You are being fooled right now.
Yes, I remember that operation.
I made the decision on that one.
You have covered your fault with Boo Yong Joo's name...
14 years ago, and his name is now nowhere to be found.
What do you mean, you'll fight against the hospital?
Do you think you'll win?
Why? Are you nervous?