Can you tell me?
Why did you...
push my father's operation back?
I'm asking you. Why did you push my father's operation back?
I just heard...
that the hospital would take care of it. That's all I know.
Why?
Was there anything else?
I heard the amount of the damage was...
around 200,000 dollars.
Right. It was about that.
It was 14 years ago...
and It was an obscene amount of money back then.
Did they let it slide without charging you any of it?
We were investigated by the police, though.
In the meantime, we were informed of their decision.
They said they'd drop the charges and wouldn't seek compensation.
All of a sudden?
Did they say that with no apparent reason or trigger?
Well...
Maybe that was because my husband died in the hospital...
or my son was too young.
Things just worked out like that.
That's all I know and nothing more.
I see.
Okay.
Thank you anyway.
Right.
- What is your son's name? - Pardon?
He's Kang Dong Joo, right?
He used to work at Geodae Hospital,
and he is now working as a surgeon at Doldam Hospital.
Do you know what is the easiest thing in this world?
It's breaking a relationship.
It doesn't require...
any money nor effort.
You can do it with a word.
You are being...
fooled right now.
Did you know...
the patient whose operation was pushed back...
was my father?
Did you know that?
Yes, I remember that operation.
I was on duty that night.
Two patients with dissection and cardiac infarction...
came in at five-minutes intervals.
Then...
was that you...
who pushed my father's operation back for a VIP patient?
It was not President Do.
It was you, right?
Yes.
It was my decision.
The risk of death for a patient...
with acute aortic dissection rises by one percent every hour.
There were a patient with cardiac infarction...
whose probability of dying within one hour was 99 percent...
and a patient with dissection whose probability rises gradually.
They both came to the hospital at a five-minute interval.
If you were there,
which patient would you operate on first, Dong Joo?
It was not because he was a VIP patient.
I made that decision...
in the order of emergency.
That's the truth.
Did you call Dr. Yang at Jungil Hospital?
Yes.
He said he'd be here in 10 minutes.
Ask Dr. Nam...
to take care of the patient with colitis.
Dr. Yang will treat the patient with aortic dissection.
Yes, Master Kim. I will go tell them.
Can you...
perform an operation now?
If you can't,
ask Dr. Do to perform it.
I will do that.
I will perform the operation.
Are you sure? Can you do that?
Don't worry about me.
I just want you to take good care of...
the patient with dissection.
Dr. Kang.
Okay.
I will do so.
Ms. Oh.
Can you go with him?
I'm asking you a favor.
Okay.
Are you all right, Dong Joo?
Dad. Dad!
Why...
Why?
- Cut. - Cut.
I'm all about romantic ideals.
- You did a good job. - Pardon?
Why?
Dong Joo,
are you really all right?
Let me finish the operation first.
I will think about it after the operation.
I don't even know if I'm okay or not now.
I will determine if we should use stomy or not...
after excising the intestine...
with necrosis. Scalpel.
(Chapter 19, Doctors and Righteous People)
What are you doing not treating an injured person?
We have other urgent patients.
There's glass embedded in my husband's stomach.
What's more urgent than this?
Your husband is urgent, too.
But as emergency room staff, we have no say in the order of operations.
Transfer him to another hospital if you're not going to operate on him.
Within an hour radius from here, there aren't other hospitals...
that can perform surgeries.
We've been here for over an hour!
Dr. Kang, Dr. Jung is calling.
What is it, In Soo?
Dr. Kang.
How much longer do you think your operation will take?
- Why? - The patient with abdomen...
injury's guardian is very upset.
She's saying we're neglecting him when we said we'll operate on him.
Could you hurry up?
I told you to explain to her that there's a more urgent situation.
I did, but she's still upset.
Even if I finish as quickly as I can, it'll take another hour.
I suppose so. You just opened him up.
All right, then.
This is ridiculous.
Dr. Kang. Don't rush and take your time.
If Master Kim finishes early, he will perform the operation.
No, I'll do it.
We'll have to dissect this much.
I have to hurry. Bovie.
Hey.
Pad.
Where is it coming from?
I think I touched one of the mesenteric arteries.
Hemostatic.
I'll grab it with the hemostatic. Get ready to tie it.
Master Kim, Dr. Jung from ER...
is asking about the progress of aortic dissection operation.
The guardian of the abdomen penetration injury patient...
is making complaints asking why we're not operating on him.
Pump on.
Tie.
Master Kim?
- Cut. - Cut.
Okay.
What should I do next?
Wait for the body temperature to fall...
and commence circulatory arrest.
We wait until the temperature falls to 24°C.
Yes, Master Kim.
Master Kim's operation doesn't look like finishing soon.
He hates it when he gets interrupted in the middle of an operation.
Does he?
Are you not listening?
How long are you going to keep him like that? I'm going crazy.
- I'm about to go crazy. - A doctor just went to ask.
Gosh.
What's taking you so long?
I found it.
Tie.
- Cut. - Cut.
Releasing hemostatic.
There's no bleeding.
How are his vital sings?
His heart rate got faster,
but it's fine. We should continue.
Resuming to functional end to end. GIA.
Commencing arrest.
We won't be applying selective perfusion today.
We have to finish in 30 minutes.
Pump on.
Give me GIA again.
Cut.
Suction.
Metzembaum.
Specimen.
One more, please.
Let's move on.
Cut.
- Cut. - Cut.
Get the Hemovac ready, please.
Irrigation.
Cut.
All right. Clamps.
Pump slowly.
I'll insert Hemovac and finish up.
Full flow.
Raise the body temperature please.
- It took 28 minutes, Doctor. - Okay.
You failed to disappoint me yet again, Dr. Kang.
I'll finish up in 10 minutes...
and proceed with the abdomen penetrating injury patient.
Please tell them to prepare the next patient.
Okay.
- Cut. - Cut.
Dr. Yoon.
The proximal is ready to be tied up. Come here and do it.
You want me to do it?
We have a lot of time until the body temperature rises.
Take your time and do it with precision.
I'll assist you. Come over here.
Prolene number four.
- Cut. - Cut.
Okay.
Now, release the air and release the clamps.
Clamps off.
Good job.
- The operation went well. - I see.
Blocked blood vessels resulted in intestine necrosis.
We had to cut 30cm of it out.
That much?
We should wait and see how things go while putting him under medication.
Thank you.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
The operation went well, right?
Yes.
When I was signing the surgery consent,
they said it could take up to two hours or more,
but you finished in less than an hour and a half.
I was wondering...
The duration of the operation doesn't matter that much.
We tried our best...
and the operation was a success.
- Thank you. - Excuse me.
He'll be all right.
You get...
more patients than I thought.
You didn't know?
This hospital...
is pretty famous...
around here.
The doctors are skilled.
And sometimes,
they let you pay on strap.
You must have...
had heart surgery.
What?
How did you know that?
I have a bad heart, too.
I can tell.
(Restricted Area)
CT scan shows his bowel injury isn't severe.
- We'll suture him up and finish. - Okay.
Let us begin. Scalpel.
It's all cold now.
(Mother)
Hello?
Isn't this Kang Dong Joo's phone?
Yes, it's Dong Joo's phone.
Hello, it's me. Seo Jung.
I see.
It's you, Seo Jung.
Dong Joo is in an operation.
Is this urgent?
No, it's not like that. I just...
Is Dong Joo doing okay?
Of course. He's fine.
That's all, then.
- It's been a while, so I called. - I see.
Right.
What happened to the side dishes...
I brought the last time?
The side dishes and kimchi, right?
We finished them a while ago.
Actually, I ate most of them because they were so good.
I'm sorry, Mother.
I mean, Dong Joo's mother.
No, Mother?
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure how I should address you.
You should call me Mother.
Dong Joo's mother is...
- a bit too cold. - Right?
It's a bit cold, Mother. Right?
Should I send some more side dishes?
Really?
The burdock dish was delicious.
Really? What else?
I liked stir-fried anchovies and stir-fried fish cakes.
Do you like beans cooked in soy sauce?
Really? I love them.
Oh, corns are very famous here in Gangwon Province.
Should I send some over?
I feel bad that I'm only taking food from you.
(Dong Joo Dumplings)
Really? Okay.
Okay, that sounds good.
Is that why you helped me that day?
When I turned the ER upside down.
Did you know I was the patient's son who died because of your priorities?
Is that why you were kind enough...
to treat me, too?
What do you want to hear from me?
Have you ever...
regretted the decision...
you made at that time?
In the end, someone died because of your decision.
Have you ever...
regretted the decision?
There's a patient dying right in front of you.
Then there is a patient you are not sure about.
Even after a long time,
I believe the choice I made was an inevitable one.
I see.
But why do I feel so awful?
I understand...
what you are saying with my head.
But why do I feel like I've been fooled?
As a doctor,
I know what the situation is like.
But as a son,
why do I keep getting upset?
That's not for you to ask me.
I think you should be asking that question to yourself.
You are no longer...
a helpless kid who lost his father.
You're a doctor.
Why did you say that to Dong Joo?
- What? - You did not know...
that the dissection patient...
had come in before.
You went into the VIP's surgery without knowing that.
Even if I knew,
my choice would have been the same.
Telling him that I didn't know...
won't comfort him a bit.
It would only sound like an excuse.
What if...
he turns his back from you for good?
He finally became a doctor worth keeping.
Sometimes it's better to face what you have to face...
instead of finding out the truth which sounds more like an excuse.
(Geodae Hospital)
The marketing team put together these articles.
Okay, put these out.
Yes, Sir.
(Geodae Hospital)
(Geodae Hospital successfully replaces an artificial heart.)
President Do is really something.
He betrayed them just like this.
President Yeo. President Yeo.
Look at this article. President Do is playing dirty.
Does this make any sense?
(Geodae Hospital successfully replaces an artificial heart.)
(The First Successful Artificial Heart Replacement Surgery in Korea)
I'm sorry, we're not open yet.
It's been a while, Ms. Noh.
Do you remember me?
Who are you?
I'm reporter Oh Seong Jae, who covered the case...
of Jang Hyun Joo 14 years ago.
You were reading that article.
That surgery was...
actually done by Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
But the article is weird, right?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo did the surgery,
but his name is nowhere to be found on that article.
14 years ago,
he covered up everything as Dr. Boo's fault,
and now, his name is nowhere to be found.
What do you think?
I have nothing to say.
I won't write any articles.
I have no voice recorders.
I won't write it in my note, either.
Can you...
tell me what exactly happened on that day?
Tell me the truth.
Why is that so important?
The important thing is to stop the rumors.
Think about those ill-rumors about Chairman Shin.
I can't overlook those.
I also can't bring out Doldam Hospital...
for the sake of media exposure.
But still, how can you steal Master Kim's work like this?
Don't be disappointed, President Yeo.
We have written the names of other surgery staff members...
in that article.
I am thinking about...
rewarding those staff members in a separate occasion.
If we can,
I am considering...
bringing them to Geodae Hospital.
Goodbye, then.
I'm a bit busy.
What does he mean?
How can he take them all?
What about Doldam Hospital?
In a word, we are doomed.
That's what I say.
It's like Master Kim beats the bush...
and Geodae Hospital catches the birds.
They are stealing the young competent doctors...
whom Master Kim has taught.
Something must be done here. Don't you think so?
Like what?
We should tell Master Kim all about it first.
He already knows.
Does he?
What did he say?
Just forget about it.
How would I forget about it?
It's like...
one man sows and another man reaps.
Why should that worry you?
Still, our hospital is already full of patients.
We don't have...
enough beds in the Intensive Care Unit anyway.
Master Kim!
Do you know...
what is the best thing I've done in my life?
The fact that I gave up my real name, Boo Yong Joo.
It took a load off my shoulders.
Also, I became free after emptying my mind...
and dream of success.
I'm happy with the way I'm living my life now.
Master Kim, still...
All of us?
Yes. President Do invited...
all of you.
He'd like to praise all of you for your hard work.
So I hope every single one of you will come. Okay?
Is Master Kim coming, too?
Do you think Master Kim would accept President Do's invitation?
Of course not.
Then I won't attend.
There's no reason to go there.
I didn't even participate in the operation. I'm sorry.
The three of you are the key figures anyway.
You are coming, right?
Dr. Song, what about me?
Right. I want you to go on duty in the emergency room...
while they are out of the hospital. Okay?
Okay.
I'm afraid I can't be there.
I have patients to take care of.
Dong Joo.
We can't do this without you.
I should go treat Chairman Shin.
I can't leave the hospital.
Dr. Yoon.
You can't do this.
What? Dr. Do, are you leaving, too?
I can't go there alone.
I don't think that's what my dad really wants.
Gosh.
This is not the way it's supposed to be.
- Hey! - Dr. Song.
He's treating me like I'm not around.
Am I invisible or what?
When do I get to go home?
Why don't you answer me?
When are you going to neglect my husband just like that?
Ma'am, we are not neglecting your husband.
He's supposed to be in the Intensive Care Unit after the operation.
Why do you let him stay in there instead?
Like I said, we don't have a bed available in the ICU yet.
That's enough.
Where's my husband's doctor?
I need to talk to the doctor.
Did you make up with Master Kim yet?
You don't wish to talk about that, right?
I get it.
By the way, your mother just called.
She asked if you were doing okay.
Did you talk to my mother on the phone?
Yes.
I heard your phone ringing.
I was going to tell her you were in the operating room.
Was there anything else apart from that?
She talked about some side dishes...
and corns?
Can you have a conversation about those things?
Of course.
Why?
Dr. Kang. We have a problem. A patient is having a fit.
What happened?
He started struggling all of a sudden. It seems he's having a fit.
Administer 4mg of lorazepam through IV line.
Okay.
Administered.
- He suffers from alcoholism, right? - Yes.
I think it is delirium tremens.
Dr. Kang, his heart rate is 180.
Administer another ampoule of lorazepam.
Yes, Doctor. Kang.
His heart rate is not dropping.
Administer another ampoule of lorazepam...
- and inject 200mg of phenobarbital. - Okay.
Inject 100mg of scyamine, too.
Okay.
Sir. Sir!
Gosh.
- Ma'am, may I speak with you? - What's wrong with my husband?
Did something go wrong with the operation?
No, there's no problem about the operation.
But...
he's showing serious alcohol withdrawal symptoms.
It's called delirium tremens.
Delirium tremens?
We are trying to control it with medication.
But it's not working well.
If the condition continues,
- he may have a cardiac arrest. - Goodness.
Please save my husband.
He's not a good husband, but I can't live without him.
Doctor, you are here.
Excuse me, until when are you going to neglect my husband in the ER?
- Pardon? - I mean,
I'm already upset with the fact that his operation was pushed back.
And now he can't be treated in the ICU?
Ma'am,
didn't the chief nurse explain about that?
We don't have any bed available in the ICU now.
We have patients who had an operation before your husband.
And they both are in a critical condition.
Then you shouldn't have accepted a patient in the first place.
We had no choice as two emergency patients came in at the same time.
We asked for your understanding already.
And your husband is making good progress after the operation.
So we were going to move him to a patient's room anyway.
That's it.
Send my husband to the Intensive Care Unit now.
- Right now. - Excuse me.
- This is just too much. - What did you say?
My husband didn't have...
an operation on time because of your husband.
And now you want to take his bed in the ICU?
What does that mean, ma'am?
I heard what the doctors said yesterday.
I heard that...
you'd give my husband's operation a lick and a promise because of him.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
My husband's operation was pushed back because of your husband.
You are the one who cut in line.
- What did you way? - Don't be ridiculous.
- Excuse me. - What's that?
Calm down.
Ma'am, there seems to be some misunderstanding.
I never give an operation a lick and a promise.
I told you that we did our best.
Ma'am.
It's a doctor who determines the order of emergency.
That's it. That's enough.
Just send my husband to the Intensive Care Unit right now.
Otherwise, I will sue this hospital.
Send him immediately.
Dr. Kang. He's having a cardiac arrest.
My goodness.
Bring me the VPB and defibrillator now.
Okay.
What should I do?
Let me.
Charge 200J.
Step away. Shock.
Gosh.
Give him 1mg of epinephrine every three minute.
Okay.
I'll check his heart rhythm.
- Ventricular fibrillation. - Charge 200J.
Shock.
What's going on with him?
- I will switch with him. - Okay.
Honey.
It's been almost an hour.
Are you injecting epinephrine every three minutes?
Dr. Kang.
Honey.
Patient Lee Dong Soo...
has passed away.
No.
Why did you say he needs operation...
if you weren't even going to save him?
If you performed the operation well,
my husband wouldn't have died.
Bring him back.
Bring my husband back now.
Now.
Doctor.
It wasn't because of the operation. It was because of alcohol.
He died of delirium tremens.
He walked in here just yesterday.
I can't believe this happened over the night.
Please.
Bring him back.
Bring my husband back.
Please.
Please bring him back, Doctor.
Please calm down.
We will give you time to say goodbye to him.
You should say your last farewell.
Honey.
I guess, now,
your husband can be moved to the ICU.
What was with your attitude back there?
Why would you get angry with the guardians?
She kept doubting the operation I performed.
I tried my absolute best.
I tried my absolute best to find the bowel infarction...
and I tried my absolute best to remove that piece of glass.
It's not my fault that the ICU is full.
It's not my fault that he drank a lot.
Why would she put the blame on my operation? Why?
I know.
You want to yell at me like I did.
You want to say...
you had no other option to make that decision about my dad.
That you tried your absolute best as a doctor.
And that I shouldn't blame you.
That's probably what you're thinking right now.
I know that very well.
I know very well and the anger is driving me insane.
I want to blame you so much,
but I can't anymore.
Because I'm a doctor.
Do you know...
what the thing surgeons hear the most is?
"Why did you operate if you weren't even going to save the patient?"
Do you know what the second most thing they hear is?
"The patient was fine before the operation,"
"but the operation worsened the condition."
What we do here...
is to save lives.
But inevitably,
we have to take criticism and blame...
at the same time.
After all,
we're cutting people with knives.
As soon as you get yourself together,
go back there and apologize to them.
Doing that concludes the treatment.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
I can't...
accept that right now.
Dr. Kang.
May I have a word with you?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo didn't do anything wrong.
If he didn't do anything wrong,
why did he get kicked out of the hospital in such fashion?
It was probably because he felt responsible.
What do you mean, you'll fight against the hospital?
If I back down like this without saying anything,
you will never realize it.
What you did wrong...
and why you should never do something like that again.
So...
If we fight,
do you think you'll win?
Do you think...
I can't?
You'll get hurt.
I'm not scared.
Not you.
The seven staff members who operated for you.
(Geodae Hospital)
No matter how much noise you make,
you won't be able to touch me.
The person who will get hurt and kicked out...
will be those seven staff members.
Which hospital do you think will hire...
medical staff with such scarlet letter?
Are you sure...
you can be responsible for all of their lives?
Among them, three are heads of their households with family to feed.
So keep your mouth shut and leave.
If you just disappear,
those seven people can live in peace.
What do you say?
So because of...
those seven people,
Dr. Boo Yong Joo took all the blame...
and left the hospital?
Yes.
As far as I know.
Why are you telling me...
something like that?
What does Master Kim's past...
have to do with me?
Other than those seven people,
Yong Joo covered for...
one another person.
On the day of Jang Hyun Joo's funeral,
some middle-schooler barged into the ER...
and created a scene.
The hospital charged that kid's mother...
with all kinds of claims including property damage.
The kid's mother was charged with 200,000 dollars.
They even tried to...
push criminal charges against that kid.
Because he was over 14 years of age,
it was definitely possible.
What are you...
talking about right now?
Have you never found it curious?
How could nothing have happened...
after causing such a scene?
Back then,
we weren't courageous.
No.
"Cowardly" fits better.
We were relieved...
that Dr. Boo Yong Joo took all the blame...
and left the hospital.
Let me ask you one more thing.
If Boo Yong Joo wasn't the person...
who made you operate under his name, then who was it?
The person who was vice president at that time.
This man.
If you find out the truth,
do you have the courage to tell it to the world?
You should make this world...
a place of justice.
(The List of People Who Performed Ghost Surgery)
(Operation Record)
(Operation Record of Jang Hyun Joo)
What is this?
They're the patients who were operated by ghost surgeons.
Some of them know that their surgeries were performed...
by a ghost surgery.
You can also see the amount of hush money Geodae Hospital gave them...
right before the lawsuit.
Why did you give this to me?
The statute of limitations on this case has expired,
so there's nothing you can do.
Still, it can be...
a useful weapon against President Do.
Congratulations on your return.
Bye, then.
(Doldam Hospital)
Even though I couldn't tell the truth to the world,
I wanted to give this to the person who should know the truth.
Honey, you'll be all right. Don't worry, okay?
I'll be waiting here.
(Intensive Care Unit)
I am sorry.
I apologize...
for what I did before.
However,
I hope you know just one thing.
Every patient in Doldam Hospital...
is equal.
The doctors here are more sincere than anyone else...
about saving our patients.
I never said that you weren't sincere.
I don't know why you're talking about something I didn't say.
Gosh.
Good for you.
Hi, Dr. Yoon. Can I see you for a second?
I don't think it's right to let it go like this.
President Do arranged the celebratory event for you guys.
I don't know about the others,
but you shouldn't do that to President Do.
Even so, Master Kim is not going to attend the event.
We can't go there by ourselves.
Goodness.
He wouldn't attend it even if he was invited.
- Invited to what? - You startled me.
What would I not attend even if I was invited?
President Do invited...
all the staff members of Chairman Shin's surgery...
to Seoul today.
- Why did he do that? - Why do you think?
He wants to celebrate the efforts of the staff.
Wasn't the media manipulation enough for him?
Why would he make them go to Seoul when they're busy?
Please don't be like that.
They can't say they will go even though they want to...
because they don't want to upset you.
Seo Jung.
- Are you not going because of me? - No.
It's not like that.
See? She is obviously trying not to upset you.
That's not true, Dr. Song.
Don't be like that and tell everyone that you don't mind.
Let them go if they want.
In fact, Ms. Oh and Mr. Park were invited, as well.
But since they're on your side, they wouldn't accept the invitation.
Then, why have I not been invited?
What?
You said it's a celebration for Chairman Shin's surgery.
I'm the lead surgeon of that surgery.
Why did you leave me out?
Stop it. You wouldn't attend it even if you were invited.
Invite me to see if I go or not.
Pardon?
I said, try inviting me.
Would you like to come?
- Sure. - Sorry?
Dr. Yoon, you're going with me.
It would be good to go to Seoul for a change.
You don't mind, do you?
No, I don't.
Hold on a second.
I wonder if Ms. Oh has free time.
Move aside.
What has gotten into him?
- Pardon? - Pardon?
Why are you so surprised?
Geodae Hospital invited us to congratulate us.
We should all go to Seoul and receive congratulations.
Ms. Oh, please go with me.
- Dr. Nam. - Yes?
You, too.
Manager Jang, would you like to join us?
- Can I go, too? - Dr. Do.
You're going, too.
What about the emergency room?
We have Dr. Jung and Dr. Woo.
The GS on call...
will be Dr. Song.
Me? I have to go to Seoul with you. What are you talking about?
Did you perform Chairman Shin's surgery?
No, I didn't, but...
So you should stay at the hospital.
Only then, we can go.
Dr. Kang.
You will go with us, right?
Yes, I will.
I'm going with you.
If you go,
I will go, too.
This is good. We could use a trip to Seoul for a change.
- Let's go, Ms. Oh. - Okay.
What should I do?
What should I do? What am I supposed to do?
Should I tell him or not? Wait.
I can't tell him.
He would tell me to stop Master Kim.
How can I stop Master Kim?
I can't tell him. I can't.
What are you going to do?
It's obvious.
I couldn't do this 14 years ago.
I will do it this time.
(Geodae Hospital successfully replaces an artificial heart.)
(The Day of the First Artificial Heart Replacement Surgery)
You're here.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
It's me. Where are you now?
Hello?
They must be almost there.
They? Aren't you coming?
Pardon?
Oh, I can't...
Actually, I have enteritis.
Oh, no. My stomach hurts.
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry, President Do.
I need to go to the bathroom.
President Do, please smile.
Oh, right.
- Let's take a picture together. - Yes, President Do.
When will they be here?
I was just told they're almost here.
They will arrive any minute.
Wait. Who is that?
- Isn't that Boo Yong Joo? - That's Boo Yong Joo.
- Look. - I think he's Boo Yong Joo.
Boo Yong Joo?
(The First Successful Artificial Heart Replacement Surgery in Korea)
"The first..."
"successful artificial heart replacement surgery in Korea."
(The First Successful Artificial Heart Replacement Surgery in Korea)
Why are you here?
I thought it was a party for the artificial heart implant.
I should be here.
We are the heroes and heroines of this surgery.
Do you know what the hardest thing in this world is?
It's to overcome yourself.
14 years ago, Boo Yong Joo...
was a coward.
He just...
didn't know how to win.
He stayed silent.
He didn't want to make excuses.
Then he ran away.
He thought...
that's how he should take the responsibility.
What are you trying to say?
I think...
it'll be hard for you, President Do.
What are you saying?
So what?
- Are you trying to fight me? - Why do you ask?
Are you nervous?
(The First Successful Artificial Heart Replacement Surgery in Korea)
(Geodae Hospital)