Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 2]
The caller you are trying
to reach is unavailable...
Are you awake?
You fractured your right ankle,
so I put a cast on it for you.
It'll be good as new
in two to three months.
The problem, though,
is with your wrist.
The fracture on your
right palm is quite severe.
I did put some pins in there via surgery
but you won't be able to make
more than a 70 percent recovery.
Is the angulation bad?
Are you a medical professional?
I was a fourth-year
resident working at an ER.
Your recovery may vary...
but in the worst-case scenario,
you won't be able to go back to work.
- That'll be 3,000 won.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
Two orders of dumplings here, please.
Why don't you head home
and eat rice instead?
I came here because
I was craving dumplings.
Don't they even feed you
at that hospital?
How is it that you look so malnourished?
I'm eating properly.
It's just that my schedule is
unconventional since I work at the ER.
So why did you insist on being a doctor?
It's not like your dead father will
come back to life because you do that.
And you had to go to the hospital
your father died at, of all places.
I know you're my son and all,
but you sure are peculiar.
Just live your life the way you want to.
Meet up with your friends
and date women.
You got that?
Sheesh.
[October 2016]
The two doctors who will be joining
our hospital's surgical department
are Kang Dong Joo and Do In Bum.
Doctor Kang, in particular,
got the highest score
on the surgical specialization
exam in the entire country.
I have high expectations
for both of you.
Do your best, okay?
Thank you!
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
- I'll do my best.
- Yes, let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
- This is my son.
- Wow!
- Wow, I guess talent runs in the family!
- This is great!
- Take good care of him.
- Yes, sir!
An era of discrimination.
This is my son,
whom I mentioned last time.
Please come with us.
An era in which your family ties
dictate your place in the world
more than your skills.
Even in a hospital, where people
are supposed to value human lives
and help others overcome struggles.
There is a monarchy-like
hierarchy prevalent in society
even in the 21st century.
There are only two ways to
turn this situation around.
One, be reborn as the
hospital director's son.
Or two, save some super-level
VIP from the brink of death.
There's no way they'd assign
a VIP as my patient.
That's right. They never will.
That's why things will never
change around here.
I'll be going.
I have a surgery in 30 minutes.
Again?
Hey, aren't you overworking yourself?
Doctor Kang Dong Joo.
The hospital director is looking for you.
Go to his office.
We just scheduled an
emergency surgery for a VIP.
It's Assemblyman Go Man Suk, the former
Speaker of the National Assembly--
I'm sorry, but I already have an
operation scheduled for today, sir.
Hey, stop being so difficult!
You should take care of
rearranging your own schedule!
Don't you know what it means to
have a VIP patient entrusted to you?
He must be a real piece of work, then.
And you probably need someone to
take the fall if the surgery goes awry.
And I seemed to be the easiest person
to take advantage of among everyone.
Am I wrong?
Look here, Doctor Kang Dong Joo!
I'm going to operate on my
original patient first.
He's a sepsis patient so he could be
in danger if we push back the operation.
Goodbye, then.
Hey!
Why did you become a doctor?
The fact that you studied like crazy
means that you wanted to be successful.
So you should take
the opportunities offered to you.
You're the one who came to the ER
once and went on a rampage, right?
Yeah. This patient is quite a
difficult case, just as you said.
He had a HCC rupture
so there's only a 30 percent chance
that your surgery will be successful.
But you need to take on that much risk
if you want to grab this opportunity.
You're not standing here,
wanting to face off against me
without even risking
that little, are you?
Right?
If you really want to get revenge,
become a better person than those people.
What do you mean,
push back the surgery?
Is there a problem with
my father, by any chance?
I have to prove myself through
my skills, no matter what.
I'll monitor his progress for a few more
days before scheduling his surgery again.
I'm sorry.
Doctor!
My father is okay, right?
Yes, he will be.
I'll definitely become a better
person than those people.
And I'll definitely prove that.
Doctor Oh,
I'll be cutting him open now.
His BP will drop as soon as I do.
Scalpel.
Respirator.
Suction.
Retractor!
Do the suction properly!
Pad! Hurry!
Apply pressure here for now.
We're doing the left
hemi-hepatectomy now. Focus.
Is the patient okay, Doctor Oh?
His heartbeat is getting faster,
but he's still okay for now.
Suction! Suction!
I can't see where this
blood is coming from!
- Scalpel!
- His vitals aren't looking good, Doctor.
His BP is 70/30 and falling quickly!
Suture.
Cut.
Respirator!
Do it properly!
I can't get a clear look!
It looks like he has disseminated
intravascular coagulation too, now.
It'll just get worse if they
keep messing with it.
Success rate of 30 percent?
What a load of crap.
After opening him up it was clear
that it was less than five percent.
I did my best, but...
I failed.
Hurry up and get the defibrillator!
200 joules!
Ready, sir.
Move!
Go!
Again! 200 joules!
Move!
Go!
Doctor.
Time of passing: 17:25.
The patient died due to excessive
bleeding during surgery.
The former Speaker of
the National Assembly
Assemblyman Go Man Suk
passed away yesterday.
Go here for the time being.
[Transfer notice to: Doldam Hospital,
Gangwon-do, Jungsun - General Surgery]
Doldam Hospital?
Where is this place?
It's a small hospital located in Jungsun.
I'll call you back here
when all of this blows over
so don't do anything stupid
and just relax there for a bit.
Think of it as getting some rest.
Got it?
So in other words, I got screwed over.
[Transfer notice to: Doldam Hospital,
Gangwon-do, Jungsun - General Surgery]
Whoa, what is this place?
[Doldam Hospital]
[Mother]
What are you staring at?
I thought we had a guest,
but it looks like he's leaving.
Maybe he made a wrong turn?
Damn it.
Dong Joo, did you get to Jungsan okay?
I'm sure you're busy trying to
get used to this new place and all
but call me as soon as
you get less busy, okay?
I'm curious to hear about everything.
Make sure you don't skip meals and
get three square meals per day!
Okay?
[Transfer notice to: Doldam Hospital,
Gangwon-do, Jungsun - General Surgery]
[Letter of Resignation]
Excuse me, can I get
more chicken, please?
[I, Surgeon Kang Dong Joo]
[from this day onward]
Hereby forfeit my position...
Hey! Wake up! Hey!
Call 911! Hurry!
Excuse me!
- Do you work here?
- Yes.
You don't have an automated
external defibrillator here?
We do. I'll bring it now.
Here you are.
- Do you know how to use it?
- No.
I did receive training,
but I don't remember.
Keep applying pressure right here.
- Use two hands, and press hard.
- Yes, sir.
What are you doing? Can't you see that
I'm in the middle of treating someone?
Are you crazy?
Move your damn foot!
What are you doing
when someone is dying here?
Are you trying to kill this person?
- Hey.
- Yes?
Stop doing that and set him upright.
Don't stop, and keep going!
Didn't you hear me?
Stop doing that, and set him upright!
I'm a doctor at Geosan
University Hospital.
Don't stop. He'll die if you do!
If you want to play doctor,
don't get plastered.
Or if you got drunk,
don't offer your help.
This is why you got transferred
to a hospital in the boonies.
Hey.
Set that man upright unless you
want to clear a corpse off the floor.
What's wrong with you?
Damn it, what a hassle...
Move.
Will you take responsibility
if this person dies?
What are you going
to do if I save him?
I'll bet my life
that you definitely can't.
Okay. Deal.
You little punk.
Move.
- I said move!
- Yes, sir!
- Grab him.
- Yes, sir.
- And pull him up.
- I'm holding him.
- Stand him up straight!
Yes, sir.
Here's his xiphoid process.
Pull the part below that up slowly
and steadily while applying pressure.
And then...
That's why you should chew
properly when you're eating!
Thank you, sir! Thank...
Oops! He lived!
Huh?
Let go of me!
What are you doing?
What are you doing,
and in my kitchen, man?
Let me borrow some tools.
Hey guys, hold this down, okay?
Let go, damn it!
What do you need tools for?
This guy bet his life, but lost to me.
Hey, I think you're going a bit
overboard with your joke, here.
Who said I was joking?
You have to pay up since you lost.
The wrist is a pressure point too, so...
Hey, come on.
Sharpen your knives will you?
Look at how dull this is!
I tend to depend more on my strength
than the sharpness of the knife, so...
That's why your knives
get dull so easily.
You can't get a nice, clean cut
without a sharp blade.
Make sure that there's not
too much blood splatter, okay?
Do you know how annoying it was
to clean up after you last time?
Blood?
There we go. Much better.
You're really going to cut my hand off?
Really?
A man should stay true to his word.
That's what real men do.
No objections, right?
Who are you?
Are you in a gang?
Well, I'm skilled with a knife.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't worry, kid.
It might hurt a little,
but it'll be over real soon.
All right. I'll slice straight
through the muscles and bones.
I'll slice through it in one go.
Hey, what are you doing?
See him out.
Um, please call the authorities.
What?
The police! Call the police!
Here you are!
Damn it, where are my keys?
Damn it! Taxi!
Taxi! Taxi! Taxi!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Where are you headed?
Sir? Where are you headed?
[Doldam Hospital]
Um, excuse me.
We're no longer seeing patients today.
I'm not here for that.
Are you here to be discharged?
Please move over to
window number two.
Um, my name is Kang Dong Joo.
I'm a doctor.
A surgeon from Geosan Hospital.
I was transferred and I'm supposed
to work here starting today.
Do you have a notice stating that
with you? Could you show it to me?
Well, that is...
something happened on
the way here and I lost it.
If you call Geosan University Hospital--
It's 8 p.m. now.
Nobody will be there to pick up my call.
You'll have to wait until tomorrow
so that we can confirm this.
Wait, then...
I rushed over here, so I haven't
found a place to stay yet.
Could you help me with that,
by any chance?
I apologize, but we only offer such
amenities to our hospital's employees.
I can't offer you a place to stay
when we can't confirm your identity.
What's going on?
Where... am I?
Don't worry.
The surgery was a success.
Surgery?
I got your right hand.
No!
I finished speaking to the
other hospital just now.
What?
Please come with me,
Doctor Kang Dong Joo.
This is the director of Doldam Hospital.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Yeo Woon Young.
I'm Kang Dong Joo.
I'm a general surgeon.
Why didn't they send me an
internal medicine specialist
if they were going to send someone?
Excuse me?
I'm not saying that I have any
particular issues with you, Doctor Kang.
We already have our chief
for our surgical department
And we do have a
surgical specialist, too.
I'm just saying.
Despite how we look, we're a general
hospital with all the bells and whistles.
We have an internal medicine department,
a surgical department, family physicians
and even a dedicated emergency room.
You'll be shocked to see
how many patients we get!
Rembrandt, the celebrated painter,
did a couple of self-portraits.
He did one of himself
as a young man
which resembled his son's
funeral portrait quite a bit...
At any rate, we welcome you to
Doldam Hospital with open arms.
I'm Jang Gi Tae,
the chief of administration here.
Sure, whatever.
You don't need to worry about me.
I have no intention of
staying here too long.
I'm expecting to be here for a month,
but no longer than two months.
And if I can't go back to Geosan
University Hospital by then
I'll look into getting hired at a
much bigger hospital in Seoul.
I thought it'd be best for me to
tell you this now rather than later.
I see.
I completely understand
what you're saying.
Does he not really care
for our hospital or something?
He won't even be able
to last a week here.
He has a good look about him,
so I quite liked him.
Three days!
I'll bet you 100,000 won that this
will all be settled within three days!
Good morning.
And if it's not a good morning
for you, then never mind.
Doctor Yoon doesn't have
many days left here, right?
Stop sticking your nose into
other people's business.
So, about that handsome male doctor.
Where is he now?
He said he wanted to get changed,
so I dropped him off at the staff wing.
Get... changed?
Oh my.
Senior.
[Chapter 2: The Last Days of
Adrenaline Hypersecretion]
Why... are you here?
How did you get here?
That's what I want to ask you.
How are you...
Since when have you been here?
I asked you first!
How did you get here?
I was assigned to start
working here yesterday.
- Assigned here?
- Yes.
So I'll be working here
for the time being.
That's what happened.
For how long?
How long are you staying here?
It's your turn to answer
my question now.
Since when have you been here?
I asked you how long
you're staying here.
Have you been here since
that incident, by any chance?
You've been here for five years
straight since that incident?
Whatever. If you don't want to
answer me, then never mind.
Why didn't you call even once?
I sent you texts and voicemails
for over a month after you left.
Did you even read or listen to those?
No.
[Doldam Hospital]
Doctor Park, we've got a guest.
- Get ready.
- Yes, ma'am.
Pass that to me.
Let's move him to the ER.
Please undo the seatbelt.
Can you hear me, Mr. Patient?
Mr. Patient!
What the hell?
This is my car!
Damn it!
Over there!
I think he's still conscious.
- What about his vitals?
- BP is 70/40 and heart rate is 140.
His lung sound is getting weaker.
- Doctor.
- It's tension pneumothorax.
Give him 10 liters of oxygen through
a mask and get an IV and hydrate him.
And get a 24-gauge on a dressing set--
If he crashed his car,
there could be some hemorrhaging.
Get me a 16-gauge, please.
Yes, ma'am.
What's wrong with your right hand?
Did you injure it?
Please get a chest tube ready.
Yes, ma'am.
What are his vitals?
BP is 80/40.
Heart rate is 140.
I'm not sure, though, since
he's receiving fluids now.
What are you doing?
The patient has abdominal damage!
I thought you were a GS!
Why are you using formal speech
with me all of the sudden? It's weird.
You want a resident to talk informally
to you, though you're a specialist?
I'll do that, then,
if that's okay with you.
What do you mean by that?
How can you still be a resident when
you've worked at the ER for five years?
What do you mean by that?
I'm in the process of becoming a
double-certified cardiovascular surgeon.
Can you focus on the patient now,
Doctor Kang Dong Joo?
He already has severe muscle guarding.
This means that he has
severe internal hemorrhaging.
It'd be best for us to put a chest tube
in and move him to a bigger hospital.
There's a limit to what we can do
at this tiny hospital, after all.
If you need an ultrasound machine,
we have one here, too.
Our hospital has pretty much everything,
despite our appearance.
So he does have severe internal
hemorrhaging from his spleen.
Right?
I think the hemorrhaging
is more severe than we thought.
- What should we do?
- What do you mean?
We shouldn't delay any longer
and get him to a bigger hospital.
How far is the nearest large hospital?
Two hours, by car. Or one hour and
30 minutes, if you really floor it.
He'll probably die due to an excessive
loss of blood on his way there.
Let's just treat him here.
This isn't an injury that can be
treated at a hospital of this caliber!
Can't you tell?
Are you sure that's not your
lack of confidence talking?
Even if I'm a doctor,
cutting open his stomach
in an under-equipped hospital like this
is pretty much attempted murder!
It's not that I can't.
I just won't!
Hey, keep it down!
Vitals?
BP at 60/40.
Heart rate is 128.
He currently has internal hemorrhaging
in his lower abdomen.
We don't know his identity
nor the reason for his injuries.
He drove himself here and crashed
into another car in our parking lot.
His car is totaled, too.
Why are you standing around?
Get back to doing what you were doing.
Oh... yes, sir.
Perform an intubation first.
Hook him up on a ventilator
and make preparations
for performing a ligation.
You're not planning to try and stop
his hemorrhaging here, are you?
All right, 20 miligrams of that.
They're fast.
Put a propofol continuous infusion in him
and get some some rocuronium, too.
Yes, sir.
Put the ventilator on CMV mode.
Pass me the tube.
Hey, don't waste time.
Just use the trocar!
Pass me the trocar, please.
A trocar?
They have that here?
How many cc's of blood
do we have now?
400 cc's now, and we've still
got more coming out, sir.
Okay. My turn now.
Hey. Hey!
Move.
If you're not going to do it yourself,
hurry up and move out of the way.
You're going to cut open
a patient's stomach here?
This isn't an OR or even a hybrid room!
It's not sterile enough here--
Hey, Nurse Park.
Get this thing out of my face.
What did you just say?
"Get this thing out of my face"?
What kind of...
Let go of me! Let go!
- Scalpel.
- Stop that right now.
Are all of you people crazy?
There will be lots of blood, so be ready.
Are you even a real doctor?
Suction.
All right. Suction.
Okay.
Ah, yes. I found it.
He found it already?
All right. Hemostat, please.
Hold on to this.
Surgical string number three.
All right, focus.
What's with those hands of his?
What am I seeing here?
All right. Cover it up with film for now.
Move him to the operating room.
Finish treating his
splenorrhagia there, okay?
- Yes, sir.
Who is this man?
What, you have a problem
with my work or something?
That was reckless,
irresponsible, and dangerous.
Really?
Well, clearly this situation
left us with no other choice
since the patient's life was in danger.
Do you think you'll still be okay later
after you tell the patient
how he was treated just now?
Are you talking about patients' rights
that doctors are to respect?
Don't argue about things
like that with me.
I only care about one thing.
Saving the patient!
Saving the patient, no matter what.
And screw everything else.
Prepare 10 packs of RBC and
8 packs of fresh frozen plasma, please.
I'll go and prepare
the operating room.
Just what is this place, exactly?
[Surgery in progress]
You're not heading in?
I can't. I'm forbidden to.
Why didn't you oppose it back there?
Cutting someone's abdomen open
in an ER is utterly ridiculous behavior.
And it was totally unsafe
for the patient to undergo that.
What about you?
You pushed back your own patient's
surgery to perform surgery on a VIP
who ended up dying
on the operating table.
You were sent here because you tried
to gain recognition but were blindsided.
Is that kind of surgery
okay to perform, then?
Do you keep in touch
with Senior In Soo?
I heard from one of the department heads.
Looks like they heard pretty much your
entire history from someone they know.
It couldn't be helped.
If I didn't take on that risk,
I would've lost my chance.
What chance?
A chance to prove my skills.
To whom?
Are you really asking me that,
as if you don't know?
The higher-ups who were
watching me, obviously.
Everything there depends on
connections. Don't you know that?
People like me who have to hit the ground
running need to do anything we can.
We have to side with the right people or
save a VIP patient to gain recognition!
What happened to you
in the past five years?
You've become such a coward,
full of excuses.
Why did you change so much?
Was it that hard to get by?
You said you'd be here a month,
but no longer than two months?
Do your best, even though I'm
not sure you'll be able to last here.
I like you, Senior.
This is your last year
as a resident, right?
Let's get married as soon
as your residency is over.
I'm sorry.
You think you can hide your
feelings just by doing that?
What, is your heart beating fast
now that you've run into him again?
This is just an illusion.
I want to speak to you for a second.
Hey, I'm tired, kid.
Save it for later.
Madonna definitely
sounds best on a casette player.
I told you that I wanted
to speak with you.
A patient's rights,
a doctor's integrity...
you may not care
about any of that, but--
How many people did you kill
before you ended up here?
I'm not talking about
when you were a resident.
How many patients died under your
knife after you got your specialization?
One person. Right before I came here.
Now add 10 to that.
Kill that many more people
before you come mouthing off to me.
I'll hear you out then.
Oh, yeah. You still have my
right hand on you there, right?
Take good care of it, because
I'll come for it when I need it.
I'm sorry, but I'm not staying here long.
I'm going to leave this wretched place
in a month, or even sooner if I can!
And do you even have a place that'll
take you, if not this wretched hospital?
I'll go back to where I came from.
Did they say that
they'd even take you back?
I didn't get sent away to a place
like this because I lack skill.
I just got really unlucky!
I didn't study hard, do practicals,
and perform all those dissections
while pulling all-nighters all the time
just so I could be stuck
in some crappy hospital in the
boonies for the rest of my life!
Yeah, yeah.
So what's your point?
I'm going to go back there
by any means necessary.
Doctor Kang Dong Joo?
A call for you, from Seoul.
She says she's your mother.
She said she kept calling your cell
but you wouldn't pick up
so she decided to call the hospital.
[Senior In Soo]
Later.
Tell her that I'm busy,
and that I'll call her later.
Yes, Senior? It's me.
Doctor Kang's mother?
Yes, hello.
Doctor Kang is busy right now.
Oh, really? All right.
I'm sorry for being a nuisance.
What did you say?
Director Do and Director Yeo are friends?
Yeah!
Director Do Yoon Wan here
and Director Yeo from there
have been best friends since college!
Oh, really?
You did greet Director Yeo properly
as soon as you got there, right?
You have to make a good impression
on Director Yeo, no matter what.
If you want to change Director Do's mind,
you have to make Director Yeo like you.
You get what I'm saying, right?
Oh, I also managed to hear
this info from someone I know.
Apparently, Director Yeo
really loves Baduk.
And also, he loves oriental orchids.
Senior. I'm terrible at Baduk
and I know nothing about plants.
Ugh, you're so frustrating!
Do you want to be stuck at
Doldam Hospital forever?
What brings you here?
Um, well...
It's fine. Just tell me what you need.
I was way out of line this morning
so I feel like I didn't
properly greet you.
I'd like it if you could forgive me
if I offended you in any way, Director.
No, it's fine.
You didn't really offend me.
Oh, really?
Oh, yes! I did hear that you
met Teacher Kim, though.
Pardon? Teacher Kim?
You know, the Chief of the
Surgical Department.
Oh... is that how people refer to him?
He may not make a good first impression,
but there's a lot to learn from him.
Well, I don't know about that.
Be polite, no matter what, so that
he gets a good impression of you!
Got that?
Yes, sir. I'll do my best.
All right, then.
You can go now.
Yes, sir.
What is it?
Was there something else you
wanted to discuss, too?
Well, um, to be honest...
Director!
Doctor Yoon Seo Jung
is having an epiosde again!
Again?
- Hurry and let Teacher Kim know!
- Yes, sir.
Senior.
Doctor Yoon?
Put that down, right now.
It's best to stay back.
Trust Nurse Oh.
You've been doing so well up until now.
You'll be able to re-enter the
surgical room in a few days, too.
I died because of you.
The voices won't stop!
It's because you think
that you can still hear them.
You've made a full recovery now,
Doctor Yoon, and you're fine now.
So, here. Give that back to me.
Give me the scalpel.
Help me.
Please, help me.
I died because of you.
Senior...
Stay back!
What's wrong? What's going on?
Why are you holding a scalpel?
That's dangerous!
I like you, Senior.
Give it here.
Hurry.
No!
No. No, Senior!
Get some gauze, now!
Good job.
It seems that she
took too many sedatives.
Her vitals are bad, too.
It seems that the blade
damaged her artery, doesn't it?
Let's hydrate her and move her
to the operating room quickly.
Yes, sir.
All right. Tourniquet.
It's ready, sir.
- Set the pressure to 205.
- Yes, sir.
Turn the tourniquet on.
The wound is small, but deep.
She's cut through an artery,
a nerve, and two tendons. No, three.
So we have to reconnect five things.
Have you ever done this before?
I asked if you've done this before.
No. I've only ever seen the
procedure done in videos.
This is the first time
I've actually done it.
If you make even a single
mistake from here on out
I'll cut your hand off and
stick it on Doctor Yoon.
Got that?
Let us begin.
You fool.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Doctor Romantic]
Why is Senior in a
strange place like this?
What was she doing here for five years?
You're the one making things
more complicated for me.
- You don't understand that?
- Get away from that patient!
I can't entrust a patient to
a person who harmed herself.
I tried so hard for the past five years.
You have no right to be at this hospital.
Why did you come to
Doldam Hospital?
Why did you have to
appear before me again?
Who are you really, Doctor?
Bu Yong Joo.
That punk is back.
I asked you who you really were, Doctor.
- Tea...
- You'll never come back to Geosan again.
- cher...
- You'll never practice in Korea again!
Kim.
Because I'll make sure you
never find work in this field again!
- Your real identity...
- You have Kang Dong Joo there, right?
Use him well.
I'm Doctor Teacher Kim. Happy now?