(Episode 3)
Her wound is small but deep.
An artery, a nerve, and two tendons.
It's 3 tendons. We have to put 5 together. Have you done this?
Have you?
No, I've only seen a video.
It's my first time.
If you make a single mistake,
I'll cut off your wrist and give it to Seo Jung.
Okay?
Let's begin.
Mosquito.
We will perform a dissection for the next five minutes.
I will operate on her for neurological rehabilitation,
arterial reconstruction, and tenorrhaphy within 30 minutes.
Is that even possible?
Hook.
Hold this.
Suction tip.
Median nerve partial and radial artery.
Flexor pollicis longus, flexor carpri radialis,
and palmaris longus complete.
Is he really going to do everything...
without any additional incision?
The 10,000-hour rule.
It says if you work on something for 3 hours a day for 10 years,
you will become an expert.
It sounds somewhat plausible.
If so,
how long will it take you to become a specialist?
It will take 20 hours per day for 11 years,
which is about 80,300 hours in total.
You will only become a specialist after spending 80,000 hours in...
studying and slaving as a resident.
You'll also have to pass the board exam.
You must also try all your best so that you can complete in 11 years.
However...
(Doldam Hospital)
I didn't spend my entire life...
studying, practicing,
and dissecting to get stuck here...
in some small hospital...
in the countryside.
Things are still unsettled.
So what are you getting at?
That's why I'm still anxious about the future.
No matter what happens,
I'm going back to Geodae Hospital.
Whatever happens,
I will go back there.
That's how I felt.
We have five minutes left on tourniquet.
I will start arterial reconstruction right away.
Lupe.
Insert.
Prepare nylon eight.
The suture is so thin that you can't even see it with the naked eye.
But...
he's being unbelievably fast.
Who...
on earth is he?
Dr. Kang.
Cut.
Do you want me to cut your wrist off?
- We have 20 minutes left. - Cut.
I will start neurological rehabilitation immediately.
I will perform tenorrhaphy at the same time.
Stay focused.
Cut.
For the next five minutes,
I'll perform tenorrhaphy of tendon.
- What? Within five minutes? - Let's start.
Needle.
To the right.
That's not it. Stretch it upwards.
It's been five minutes.
Okay.
We have two minutes left.
Cut.
He's fast.
- Cut. - He's unbelievably fast.
We have one minute left.
Cut.
Suction.
I'm sorry.
We have 19 seconds left.
Cut.
The nurse prepares everything...
in advance as if she knows what he'll do in the next step.
Everyone in this operating room...
is working in perfect order without making any unnecessary moves.
- Time's up. - Cut.
Turn off the tourniquet.
- What about bleeding? - She's not bleeding.
The vital sign is between 70 to 100. The oxygen saturation is stable.
Okay.
Close it up. You can do that much, right?
It's upsetting.
Good work.
But I couldn't say anything to him.
His operation...
was the most perfect one that I have ever witnessed in my life.
I was...
like a fool more than ever.
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Darn it.
Yes?
We finished up on Dr. Yoon and moved her to the ICU.
- Okay. - About Dr. Kang...
Well, he seems totally lost.
Okay. I'll do that.
Master Kim must have pushed him so hard.
He just did everything as usual.
You know his style, right?
And just like the other doctors,
this one will leave, too.
He'll also curse Master Kim just like the others.
I need an explanation.
Who on earth are you?
What are you talking about?
I can't understand at all, no matter how hard I try.
- About what? - The man who tried to...
cut my wrist off at a casino...
turns out to be a chief surgeon stuck in the ER.
My private life and hobbies...
are none of your business.
The operation in the afternoon was definitely a general surgery.
But the angiorrhaphy was way too professional...
for a general surgeon.
Are you complaining about how good I am?
Seriously, what is your area of specialty?
Are you a gambler or an ER doctor?
Or are you a surgeon?
If you are a surgeon, you must be specialized in a particular field.
Are you a general surgeon? Are you specialized in blood vessels?
What is your main area of field?
Saving lives.
That's what I'm specialized in.
Don't play games with me.
I'm asking very seriously.
Are you sure you're not just embarrassed of yourself?
What are you talking about?
You were embarrassed of yourself back there.
That's not all, right? You're a doctor,
but you wasted your time at a casino bar early in the evening.
You tried to use a defibrillator...
on a patient with dyspnea, too.
What do they do in university hospitals these days?
How do they teach their medical students?
Don't patronize me.
I passed the board exam with the highest score in the country.
That's exactly my point. What good is it when you can't even tell...
the difference between...
cut and suction in the operating room?
There wasn't anything wrong with me.
Your hands were just way too fast.
Do you know why...
surgeons wear masks in the operating room?
It's to prevent contamination.
You're wrong. It's to keep the mouth shut.
It's to keep the mouth shut so that they can speak with their hands.
Don't make an excuse for yourself...
in front of a patient who is on an operating table.
Don't try to rationalize yourself.
Surgeons don't get second chances.
You were the one who couldn't do well in the operating room.
Do you get that?
You didn't answer me yet.
I asked you what you really are.
Why this little...
I'm the master.
Master...
Kim.
What?
That's me.
I'm Dr. Kim. In other words, I'm Master Kim.
All right?
Did you hear what Dr. Kang just said?
He passed the board exam with the highest score in the country.
I heard that. Why?
I see.
Strange people.
And a strange doctor.
This is Search Team Three.
We're at Doldam Hospital.
We found a vehicle of suspected hit-and-run.
Strange hospital.
(Intensive Care Unit)
What are you doing...
in this strange place?
What were you doing here...
in the last five years?
(Chapter 3, Friday of 13 People)
(Emergency Medical Center)
No. Don't do that, Seo Jung!
What?
What did you say about Seo Jung?
Are you talking about Yoon Seo Jung who disappeared five years ago?
Are you saying that the Crazy Whale is there?
Yes, she is.
What a surprise. My goodness.
This is unbelievable.
This is such big news. So how is she doing there?
Is she married? Does she have kids?
What?
Is she preparing for the double board certification? Why?
I don't know why she's wasting her time like that.
No.
I can't put her on right now.
By the way,
can you find out about someone called Master Kim?
What? Master Kim?
What's that? Is that a name?
I don't know for certain. Everyone calls him like that.
He's a chief surgeon here at Doldam Hospital.
Please find about his real name, which school he went to,
and what his field of specialty is.
Also, I want to know what he's doing here at Doldam Hospital.
In Soo. It's me, Seo Jung.
Seo Jung?
You Crazy Whale! Are you alive?
Kang Dong Joo has no idea what he's talking about.
Forget what he said.
Why didn't you call me?
Hello?
My gosh, Crazy Whale.
She hasn't changed a bit.
Who's the Crazy Whale?
Her name is Yoon Seo Jung.
You probably heard of her...
as the Queen of Forefinger.
She used to be the legend of ER.
- She must have been skilled. - Of course.
She used to be the star player of our department,
but she disappeared after she got in a car accident.
Anyway, she's been at Doldam Hospital all this time.
Doldam Hospital?
It's the place where Kang Dong Joo got sent off to.
It's a hospital in Jeongseon.
I'm not saying that the president did anything wrong.
He probably deserved it.
Have you heard of someone called Master Kim?
No, right?
Well, then to whom should I ask?
I think I'll ask Dr. Ahn.
Doldam Hospital.
What are you doing here?
I'll ask you the same thing.
Are you spying on him now?
Why do you want to find about his background?
What do you need it for?
You shouldn't be walking around. Don't you know about that?
Your artery, nerve and three tendons were damaged.
The operation was successful, though.
But you still need to take some rest.
Don't ever try to question him.
Don't cause any trouble.
You may get infected with the slightest touch...
and that may lead to an artery blockage.
I'm telling you as your doctor.
Please return to your bed without complicating the situation.
You're the one who's complicating the situation. Don't you get it?
Do you know how hard I worked for the last five years?
Do you know how hard I worked to return to this place?
Forget it.
Let me ask you for a favor.
I'm not sure how long you'll stay here,
but let's please treat each other like we're strangers.
Let's not even talk to each other unless it's work-related.
- Seo Jung. - Please don't talk to me, Dr. Kang.
Also,
stop prying into Master Kim's private affairs.
He's not someone you can treat like that.
Do you get it?
Do you like him?
Is that why you were here...
for the last five years? Is that so?
You're insane.
My gosh.
- He's insane. - Hey, Dr. Yoon.
- How's your wrist? - Completely insane.
Me?
You're insane. You're crazy.
Why did you ask her that?
I'm so embarrassed.
This is embarrassing. So embarrassing.
Darn it.
You must let Dr. Kang stay no matter what.
What are we missing here at Doldam Hospital?
Money, equipment, and doctors.
- Everything. - She's right.
Everything is bad.
That is our reality.
We need Dr. Kang...
to overcome this reality.
You said he would leave in less than a week.
He won't even last a week. I'll bet 50 dollars.
Wait. Was it three days?
I'll bet 100 dollars. He'll leave in 3 days for certain.
I didn't know who he was back then.
I came to know...
that he passed the exam with the highest score in the country.
He's like a jewel to us.
We can't just let him go.
The important thing is...
his willingness.
I have heard...
that he wishes to leave...
this dreaded hospital as soon as possible.
See?
That's why we should do something to keep him here.
He's the top of his class,
good looking, and young.
If we just let him stand around,
people around the area,
especially the ladies,
would be crazy about him.
I can't believe what you said just now.
It was really awful.
Hospitals are all about providing services nowadays.
The doctors...
at our hospital are...
too old.
What do you think, Ms. Oh?
Shouldn't we ask for Master Kim's opinion?
Master Kim can do his own thing.
Don't you think it's about time to have a normal doctor?
- In that case... - Yes, President Yeo.
- First, - Yes?
let's hear from Master Kim.
Can you do a checkup?
He's not here yet.
I mean Master Kim.
I see.
Did you have lunch?
It's Friday.
Of course I ate. I ate twice as much.
- Check this again. - Okay.
Are you allowed to walk around?
Does your doctor approve?
It's Friday.
I couldn't just sit around.
I mean, I'm on the board for emergency surgeries.
This is Doldam Hospital Emergency Room.
Yes. I'll get it ready.
It's a motorcycle accident. Five patients will...
arrive in five minutes.
All right.
He's from the motorcycle accident.
He doesn't have external bleeding, but he's unconscious.
His blood pressure is between 70 to 100. He has minor scratches.
We'll begin with the intubation.
Set up IV lines and execute a full drop.
Stick two pints of emergency pack RBC on him.
He's a hit and run driver.
The guy who drove into...
your car.
He ran away after hitting two middle school students.
Don't worry.
I will talk to the insurance company...
and make sure the expenses for your car are fully paid.
Do you want some?
No, thanks. I don't like juice.
Is that so?
(Mom)
Doctor.
It's a call from the emergency room for a patient from a car accident.
Okay.
My dear Dr. Kang doesn't like...
juice that much.
He doesn't like to answer his mom's call, either.
It's hemoperitoneum.
He needs a surgery now. Can you do it?
- Is his guardian here? - On their way.
They'll be here in an hour.
He needs a surgery now, though.
I'll get his guardian's consent when they get here...
and then begin the surgery.
It'll take them about an hour.
He may get a shock from excessive bleeding.
Do his surgery first.
What may go wrong is your wrist.
You should go back and get some rest.
I'll take care of him.
No, thanks. I'll take care of it.
The general surgeon is the one to call a surgery and I give orders.
Wait until we have his guardian's consent, Seo Jung.
I mean, Dr. Yoon Seo Jung.
Are you scared that things will go wrong?
I'm sticking to the rules.
Doctors are responsible for things happening in an unconsented surgery.
You should be thinking about ways to save him...
instead of being worried about things that didn't happen.
I've seen many doctors...
who fought and got sued by the guardians after they did that.
I'm not even at Geodae Hospital.
Why would I get myself into such a trouble?
Are you serious?
- You're no fun at all. - I'm sorry,
but I've always been like this.
I always stick to the rules.
I'm not sure if you remember.
I see.
I'm sorry I didn't know, you jerk.
- What? What did you say? - Forget it.
We're taking him to the operating room.
Let go. This is my patient now.
- My goodness. - Both of you, stop.
Go to the operating room and tell Dr. Nam to get ready.
Yes, Master Kim.
Not you.
You.
What are you doing? Get the operating room ready.
I will go. I can do it.
No. Go away, Seo Jung.
I'm fine now. I'm okay.
I can do it.
Get away from this patient!
According to the Medical Law article 8, clause 1...
and the Mental Health Act Article 3, Clause 1, a mental patient...
cannot perform as a doctor.
You have hurt yourself.
I can't let you be with a patient.
You are disqualified from this hospital as of today.
- Master Kim. - That's the end of my decision.
I won't reconsider it, so don't bring it up.
Leave.
What are you doing?
Go and get the operating room ready.
Don't you think it was too harsh?
How could you say she's disqualified?
Eun Tak. Eun Tak!
Yes, Doctor.
Tell Dr. Nam to prepare for an operation,
and move this patient to the operating room.
His guardian hasn't arrived yet.
Get the consent over the phone.
- Yes, Doctor. - Good.
Hey.
You'll be on call at the emergency room tonight.
Pardon?
Didn't you see me kicking out the emergency medicine specialist?
You should fill the position since the specialist isn't here.
That's nonsense.
Surgeons are never on call for the emergency room.
I'm not asking for your opinion.
I'm giving you an order.
It seems like you like taking orders.
This is a special order I'm giving you as the head of General Surgery.
So you'll be on call tonight.
Today is Friday, so you should stay alert.
This is ridiculous.
What a jerk.
I'm going to cut the abdomen open now.
Scalpel.
You are disqualified from this hospital as of today.
(Dr. Song of Geodae Hospital)
Yes, Dr. Song. Kang Dong Joo speaking.
Hi. How are you doing?
I'm dying to leave here.
Since you left,
I've been feeling so bad.
There are no fellows as good as you in General Surgery.
I'm playing golf with President Do right now.
Do you think you can join us for dinner tonight?
Pardon? Did you say tonight?
Yes.
Come say hello to him and beg him to have you back.
I'll text you the time and place.
It'd be better if you bring him a bottle of kaoliang wine.
You know what I mean, right?
Dr. Song, what are you doing?
I'm coming, President Do.
- You must come, okay? - Dr. Song...
(7pm, Sanjeongsik in Jeongseon, Gangwon Province)
(Recommended route, 37.7km, 48 minutes)
It takes 48 minutes from here.
I have to leave at 6pm at the latest.
What should I do?
Hello? Okay. I'm on my way.
This is driving me crazy.
I can't believe what just happened.
Please hold him.
This is unbelievable.
Children, you shouldn't run in the hospital.
We were on a family trip.
Of course, we're in the hospital.
What happened?
They were on a family trip.
They've been having abdominal pain since they had lunch.
Are you all right? Doctor, why are you standing there?
My father is suffering.
- Who's in Internal Medicine? - It's President Yeo.
- Please call him. - Yes, Doctor. Follow me.
Sir, please lie down for a second.
What did you say? You're responsible for this. Let go of me.
Hey, you!
- I'll be right back. - Doctor.
It's your fault.
What happened to them?
They're car accident patients. They are arguing over who's at fault.
Please calm down.
Sir, let me check your wound.
Don't be late. Do you hear me?
(Restricted Area)
It's not as hectic as I expected.
I thought there would be a long line of patients.
How's the newbie doing?
Do you think he'll be useful?
He's a jerk.
That's disappointing. He looked like a nice person.
Hold on. I forgot.
I heard...
you told Seo Jung to leave the hospital.
- Who told you that? - Myung Sim did.
- You didn't mean that, right? - I meant that.
I won't let someone deluded like her be with a patient.
Still...
Hey, where are you going?
Hi, Master Kim. I heard you finished your operation.
Why did you bring that orchid?
This one grew up so beautifully.
I brought it so you can appreciate it in your office.
Do you have something to say?
You know...
It's about Dr. Yoon Seo Jung.
You're not going to kick her out, are you?
- Who said that? - Ms. Oh did.
You're not serious, are you?
Are you stepping out?
Yes, I am.
I'm going out to enjoy my hobby.
But it's Friday.
I left the work to Dong Joo.
Still, it's Friday.
Don't you think it'd be difficult for him to handle alone?
It's not so bad to deal with too much work sometimes.
He would be able to build up his experience.
Are you serious about...
what you told Dr. Yoon?
Yes, I mean it.
This time, neither President Yeo nor Do Il...
won't change my mind.
So you should give up, too.
Right.
I'm sure he didn't mean it.
He wouldn't kick me out.
I should implore him again.
I don't mind kneeling down, too.
Is Mr. Lee Chang Geun's guardian here?
Who is Mr. Lee Chang Geun's guardian?
- Mr. Lee Chang Geun's... - When is my grandfather's turn?
What's his name?
- It's your fault. - No, it's your fault, you jerk.
Did you just call me jerk?
- Take him for an X ray. - Yes, Doctor.
(The VIP has arrived.)
Please lie down slowly.
You're going to take an X ray. Please move slowly.
Excuse me. Master Kim! Master Kim, where are you going?
May I help you?
(Intensive Care Unit)
Well...
There's a car accident patient in there, right?
I'm his family. Can I see him briefly?
Please wash your hands with this and come inside.
This is intensive care unit.
Mom!
No!
You jerk.
Gosh. What are you doing?
Stop it.
You killed my son.
You don't deserve to be alive.
- I will kill you. - Go get someone. Hurry.
You can't do this.
Stop it, please.
My son died.
You killed my son.
Ma'am.
You are even worse.
You shouldn't have saved his life.
Why did you save his life?
He is a murderer who killed my son.
Why did you save his life? It's all your fault.
Let go of me, please.
Get off me.
Let go of me.
Why did you save his life? He killed my son.
I will kill him.
I will kill everyone.
- I will kill him. - Wait.
Ma'am. There seems to be a misunderstanding.
He's not the person who hit your son with a car.
The hit-and-run driver was moved to a patient's room a while ago.
He was...
just carried to the hospital from a motorcycle accident.
You almost killed an innocent man.
Take her out.
- Are you all right? - I'm okay.
- Fortunately, he is fine. - Gosh, Dr. Yoon.
- How are you feeling? - I feel much better.
Please wait until the fluid is fully injected.
Okay.
What should I do?
I should leave now to be there on time.
Don't be late. Do you hear me?
Forget about your pride.
Just think about yourself going back to Geodae Hospital.
- Ms. Woo. - Yes.
Put the metro on bed number eight.
Kang Dong Joo.
You should go.
You should walk out that door right now.
We have an emergency patient.
He is a 48-year-old man.
It seems he drank pesticide.
- My goodness. - Are you all right?
- Dr. Kang. - My gosh.
- Dr. Kang. - Wake up!
No.
- Don't look back. - Wake up!
This is your last chance.
It is your last chance to go back to Geodae Hospital.
As soon as I turn around,
it will ruin my life.
Dr. Kang!
Please save my son.
Doctor, please.
Please save my son. Doctor.
Please.
Please save my son.
Please help me.
Doctor. Please.
I'm begging you.
Please save my son.
Doctor, please.
Darn it.
A 48-year-old man drank pesticide as he was drunk.
- Did you check the bottle? - It's organophosphate.
Prepare charcoal...
and check how many vials of atropine...
- we have in stock. - Yes, Doctor.
- Let's move him to the hybrid room. - Excuse me.
Please wait outside the room.
- Thank you, Doctor. - This way, please.
He will be all right.
This way, please. He will be fine.
Who else is coming?
In fact,
Dr. Kang Dong Joo is coming.
It's not that he is competent.
But we need more fellow doctors in Department of General Surgery.
You know what's happening in Department of General Surgery.
Young doctors these days don't prefer to become a surgeon.
The hospital is full of patients and lacks fellow doctors.
It's not for Kang Dong Joo.
It's for me, President Do.
What about the list of cardiothoracic surgeons...
- for the operation on the chairman? - Please don't worry about it.
We will have the best cardiothoracic surgeons for the operation.
You know there will be a board meeting in two months, don't you?
Of course I do.
I will do everything I can for your second consecutive term.
Please.
Please let me express my gratitude.
- How many liters is it? - It's 7L.
Do you have the result of arterial blood gas analysis?
It's here, Doctor.
Is it 6.8pH?
Bring me five ampules of sodium bicarbonate.
- I will perform the intubation. - Yes, Doctor.
- Thank you for coming here. - It's my pleasure.
Thank you.
Let me check his heart rhythm.
I will do it again.
It's ready.
Shock.
- The number you have dialed... - Is he out of his mind?
Dong Joo. What do you think you are doing?
It's almost 9pm. Why aren't you coming?
Did you have a car accident or something?
Or are you trying to get smart with me?
Are you leaving already?
I'm tired tonight. I can't stay any longer.
Well... President Do.
Dong Joo. You idiot.
You are doomed. Do you understand?
Please.
Dr. Kang.
You should pronounce him dead.
It is...
9:29pm now.
Why should I?
Your son...
passed away.
Doctor.
Would you mind speaking a little bit louder?
We were in such a hurry,
so we forgot to bring hearing aids.
I said your son passed away.
What did he say?
I can't hear you.
Doctor.
I know my son is a bit old,
but he should meet someone nice and get married.
Please treat him well.
Please, Doctor.
Why should I do this?
Your son passed away.
Your son died.
He passed away.
Doctor.
I want to see...
my daughter-in-law before I die.
Please.
He's...
my one and only son.
Please save him.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Why am I...
How could this...
Not like this.
Dong Joo. You idiot.
You are doomed. Do you understand?
Press one for the next voice message.
(Mom)
Hello?
Dong Joo? It's me.
Have you been busy all day?
You didn't call me.
It's tough, isn't it?
Thanks to Dr. Kang, this Friday went by smoothly.
But still, it was unnecessary for you to leave the ER...
entirely up to him. You should come back right away.
I still have things to take care.
I'll come back as soon as I'm done.
I heard you put up a fight...
against that person who caused a scene at the ICU.
With that hand.
You don't have a fever.
No swelling.
No heat sensation.
This is looking better than I anticipated.
What are you doing right now?
I'm just checking on my patient.
I want a different doctor. Please get me someone else.
There aren't any other doctors in this place.
Do you want me to call Master Kim for you?
That wouldn't go very well, right?
He disqualified you in your face.
Do you want to die?
I thought you two were very close friends.
I guess I was very wrong.
Hey.
Why are you here at Doldam Hospital?
Why are you in my life again?
I didn't come here because I wanted to.
You just happened to be here when I got here.
Don't you think this is wrong?
You and me...
in a same hospital?
No, you're wrong.
You're not even working here any more.
You're such a jerk.
Why did you change so much?
I was always like this.
Perhaps you don't remember,
but I've always been straightforward.
Good for you.
Why did you take a sedative?
Leave me alone. I'm tired.
I said get out.
I don't want to see you here. Leave me alone.
I missed you.
I'm serious.
Kang Dong Joo speaking.
We have burn patients. Four in total.
We need you down here.
Burn patients?
Did she say burn patients? How many?
Four.
The patients are here. Please hurry, Dr. Kang.
What are you doing? Get down there.
I've never treated a burn patient.
What?
A patient with a 1st-degree burn and 2 with 2nd-degree burn.
There's 1 patient with 3rd-degree burn all over the body.
Third-degree goes to the hybrid room and the rest go over there.
Okay.
Dr. Kang. Please start with the third-degree burn patient.
What are you doing? Go after them.
Secure the airway first and start the intubation.
Intubation.
Please.
The trachea is already swollen.
Then perform cricothyroidotomy.
- Prepare for cricothyroidotomy. - Okay.
- Hold on. Give me the tube. - What do you need the tube for?
Hey. What are you doing?
Kang Dong Joo.
Okay.
Fix it to 23.
That's enough.
Set up IV lines with 2L of hydration.
Okay.
- Warm saline. - Please prepare warm saline.
You're doing good so far. You have to dress the burn wounds.
Don't forget to measure the area of burn on the back.
Okay.
Hold this.
Take deep breaths.
Please check on the carboxyhemoglobin.
Okay, Doctor.
The patient's saturation is dropping.
It must be a respiratory tract burn. I'll proceed with the intubation.
Move over.
Doctor.
What's wrong with your face?
Dress the burn wounds.
Where's the third-degree burn patient now?
He's in the hybrid room with Dr. Kang.
Are you okay, Master Kim?
Call the burn center.
We need a chopper fast.
Okay.
He should be hospitalized for at least four weeks.
Where did he get beaten?
I'm not sure.
Okay, you're doing well.
What?
Dr. Kang.
What is it?
His blood circulation isn't well.
His hand is blue.
Burn contracture has began.
Perform the escharotomy immediately.
- Escharotomy? - Cut open his skin.
What are you doing?
If you don't, his skin will shrink and block his blood circulation.
It'll build into necrosis.
You're so frustrating.
What's with him?
Master Kim.
Our Friday night is...
not over yet.
(Dr. Romantic)
Why are you so scared? You haven't done anything wrong.
You didn't bring Seo Jung in because of the patient.
You needed her for yourself.
That must be why you are so obsessed with...
staying as a doctor at Geodae Hospital, you idiot.
You don't know anything about me. Don't talk about me like that!
You don't even know what it's like to live well.
Stop trying to teach me how to live right.
You disgust me.