Master Kim.
Master Kim, the thing is...
(Episode 4)
Scalpel blade number 10.
I asked for her help.
I don't have any experience with burn patients,
so I asked for Seo Jung's help.
Inject tetanus vaccine.
Prepare everything as soon as possible.
Finish dressing the burn wounds.
Okay.
- Master Kim. - Did you call the burn center?
Yes. The chopper will be here in 25 minutes.
- Master Kim. - Master Kim.
Master Kim.
Young Do. Gyu Yong.
- Calm down. - Young Do.
What should I do?
Master Kim.
Are they going to be okay? They will be fine, won't they?
Geon Soo. We should take care of your wounds first.
- Ms. Oh, dress the wounds. - Okay.
Where is Young Chul? Where is he?
He's not in a good condition right now.
You can save him, right?
Master Kim.
You even brought a dead person back to life.
I saw you doing that many times.
Young Chul.
Please save his life.
We'll do the very best we can here.
Then we will send them to the burn center.
Let's do that.
Young Chul.
This way, please.
Are the kitchen staffs all right?
Burn patients can never be okay.
They will suffer from serious aftereffects, too.
The entire medical expenses...
will be covered by the company.
It's no surprise.
Chairman Shin wants to see you again.
Would you like to come with me once the emergency is over?
As you can see, I'm quite busy here.
Then are you available tomorrow?
If he wants to see me, he should come here.
By the way,
this wound. I will charge you for this with a medical certificate.
Just for your information.
Isn't she the general manager of the casino?
Why is she here to see Master Kim?
(Three hours ago)
Times of money.
It's the time where money makes you a boss.
The world is full of those who are willing to do anything for money...
and those who believe there is nothing they can't do...
with money.
I guess you've been here for so long.
It's been about two days.
Excuse me. Thank you.
Have some water.
Okay. Thanks.
Security. Please call 911.
We have a stroke patient here.
Stroke?
What are you doing? Call 911 now.
Call 911. We have a stroke patient. Hurry up.
Look at my fingertip.
Look at this.
Wait. Please pass this on to the doctor.
- Okay. - Thank you.
You just saved a precious life once again.
What good is saving a life...
when it doesn't do me any good?
It's only good for other hospitals.
Come with me. The chairman wants to see you.
I'm sorry. This is an order from the chairman.
Why did they cook steak with such tough meat?
Hey.
Are you Master Kim?
You didn't have to beat me up to see me. I'd come anyway.
Why did you beat me to a jelly, chairman?
You jerk.
I heard you hustle money from sick people.
Do you call yourself a doctor?
You cheated my VIPs to take their money in my casino.
I was just trying to help sick people.
But you are extorting money...
from poor people without even lifting a finger.
According to the seriousness of the crime,
you are worse than me.
Is it true that...
you are a skilled doctor?
Get off me. You jerks.
It is true that the lives I've saved are more than the ones I've lost.
I heard that...
whatever you do,
it will bring a dead person back to life.
I'm not a master of life or something.
There's no way I can bring a dead person back to life.
If you are meant to live, you will live.
And if you are meant to die, you will die anyway.
I want you to work for me.
Stop looking for a patient in the casino.
You should be my doctor.
I will pay you as much as you want.
What's the maximum amount you can pay me?
Hey.
Bring me more streaks.
This is not enough. It's not a cookie.
Yes, sir.
Hello?
Okay.
Listen. We just got an order for more steaks from the chairman.
- Put the pan on the heat. - Okay.
- Bring the meat. - Okay.
- Prepare Filet Mignon. - Okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's acting up again.
Young Chul!
How much money do you have, chairman?
Is it about one billion dollars?
If you give me all the money you have, I will think about it.
If it's not that, you can't just buy me.
I might not look like it, but I'm a quite expensive doctor.
If you are done,
I will leave you alone.
You know, it's Friday.
Ma'am, we have a problem. A fire broke out in the kitchen.
What?
Go get a fire extinguisher.
Extinguisher!
Master Kim. Master Kim.
- Geon Soo. - Go find Young Chul.
- Go and help Young Chul. - Help!
(Chapter 4, Necessary and Sufficient Condition)
Don't worry. They will be fine. Just go.
Avoid spicy or strong-tasting foods.
- This is the way to the cashier. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
Mr. Park.
I'll send these two to the burn center tomorrow.
We'll take care of them at the ICU until then.
Yes, Doctor.
I have something to tell you.
It's about Seo Jung.
Like I said, it's not her fault. I asked for her help.
I've never dealt with a burn patient.
I have nothing to talk about Seo Jung with you.
Go on.
What should I have done, then?
I had an emergency burn patient...
and I had no idea what to do about him.
Should I have left him to die?
The only person on the emergency medicine board here is her.
Should she be just sitting around doing nothing for the patient?
That's not right.
I should do anything and everything at such an emergency.
Nonsense.
What?
Hey.
It looks like you believe you were really heroic...
to bring in Seo Jung for help in such an emergency.
That's nonsense.
You're a coward who can't react quickly.
Here you go again.
Did you just call me a coward?
Look. You have worked so hard to become the top of your class...
and you can't let go of Geodae Hospital's name.
It's all because you're a coward.
If you don't have those to fall back on,
you're just anxious.
Are you done?
Why? Are you angry?
Then don't ever be pretentious in front of me.
Pretending to be someone. Pretending to know.
Pretending to be a righteous doctor.
Pretending to be a hero after doing just your job.
I never did any of those.
Hey.
You didn't bring Seo Jung in because of the patient.
You needed her for yourself.
You didn't want to look like a fool while treating that burn patient.
You didn't want to be ashamed in front of our staff.
And now you're here pretending to look out for Seo Jung...
and pretending like it was for the patient.
Stop blabbering about yourself.
Understood?
You idiot.
Master Kim.
What's with you? What?
If you got nothing, I'm leaving.
Forgive me, Master Kim.
Please give me another chance. I promise I'll do well.
I'm serious. I will never put you down.
I promise.
- Get up right now. - No.
I'm not moving an inch...
until you forgive me.
I won't move.
Go ahead, then.
You coward.
You idiot.
Kang Dong...
Stay here.
Don't step in.
What are you doing?
That's enough, okay?
What do you know?
You don't know anything about me. Don't talk about me like that!
I know you're older than me,
but it doesn't mean that you're wiser.
If you're old, can you ignore young people like this?
No.
You don't even know a thing about me.
If you're an adult, you shouldn't talk like that.
Exactly. Adults shouldn't talk like that.
I am older, but I may not be the wisest.
And I don't know anything about you. However,
if you reach my age,
you'll begin to see something.
You'll be able to see if someone's sincere or not.
You'll also be able to see if someone as a future or not.
Are you saying...
I'm not sincere?
And that I don't have a future?
You probably know that better.
Hey, let go.
Let go.
- Seriously... - Let go. Let go of me.
Mr. Go, let go of him.
Let go of me!
Calm down, Dr. Kang. You're at the hospital.
I'm going to kill him today.
Darn you. I'll kill you.
Stop it!
Myung Sim started again.
What? Started again?
This is the moment when Myung Sim looks the sexiest.
What are you two doing?
This is a hospital and we still have patients.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Okay, Mr. Go. Get rid of him.
Stop it, Master Kim.
Do you know how hard Dr. Kang worked...
at the emergency room today?
Do you know how hard he worked...
in this lagging environment with lagging equipment...
with his lack of experiences?
No one else could have done better than what he did.
You should be praising him, not bashing on him.
You were getting beaten while he was working.
Come on, Ms Oh. That's true, but...
Look at Dr. Yoon's incident.
President Yeo asked and Mr. Nam asked.
On top of that, Dr. Yoon kneeled down with all sincerity.
You should step back...
after a while, too.
How can you be so harsh?
Dr. Yoon has worked with us for so long.
Is this who you are?
Come on, Ms. Oh. About that...
I don't want to hear it.
Please reconsider your decision...
on Dr. Yoon.
Hey, Ms. Oh.
- You can't ask me to do that... - I will consider it as yes.
Master Kim.
The end. Everything is over.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying that you'll probably be fine.
Oh my goodness.
(Geodae Hospital)
See you.
- See you. - Thank you.
I saw Dr. Jo of Seonil Hospital...
walking out of the head surgeon's room.
We can't leave Dong Joo's spot open forever.
We're on a schedule here.
Scouting from the outside?
Yes, exactly.
Two doctors just did their interviews.
What are you going to do?
I think your spot will be taken over by someone else.
You are doomed. Do you understand?
You're finished. Do you understand?
(Letter of resignation)
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for his decision.
They're all discussing my matter.
Oh my goodness.
There is nothing to consider.
We need all the doctors we can get.
I feel bad about what happened to Dr. Yoon,
but I have faith that she'll overcome her difficulties.
Don't you think so, President Yeo?
What are you going to do?
Are you crazy?
I'm done with this place anyway.
I want to speak out something before I go.
If you're going to go, just go.
Don't cause any trouble in there.
Come in.
Goodness, Dr. Kang.
We were just talking about how you excellently handled...
the Friday night shift.
You must be tired from working all night. What brings you here?
What's this?
- It's my letter of resignation. - What?
Dr. Kang.
I don't think I'm the right doctor...
you're looking for here at this hospital.
I'm not cut out for it, too.
- That's all I needed to hear. - Please, Master Kim.
You can't do this. Please think about it again.
There's so much for you to do here at this hospital.
I completely understand why you're upset.
At least stay here before you go back to Geodae Hospital.
I'm looking for other places rather than Geodae Hospital.
I already got offered by a couple of hospitals.
That's good news. Off you go, then.
Master Kim. Sit down.
Please.
You can't make the man stay just because you want him to.
Kids like him are good for nothing.
Please think it over. You must.
Thank you for your help. I owe you much for your kindness.
I almost forgot.
I get that you're a great doctor...
and that you're a big shot,
But...
you're the one who thinks you can lecture other people...
after just doing your job.
You're right about me.
I'm a stupid coward like how you said.
I studied so hard because I was anxious about having...
Geodae Hospitals' name to fall back on.
I did try to flatter in order to climb up the ladder.
Also, I'm not proud of every decision I've made in my life.
But you must know this.
Old fossils like you...
are the ones who made me live like this.
You shaped this world so that people with no background...
can't become anything unless they live like me.
And you look down on us...
calling us idiots and cowards.
Dr. Kang.
You don't even know what it's like to live well.
Stop trying to teach me how to live right.
You disgust me.
That'll be all.
Where are you going, Dr. Kang?
Why are you so scared?
You haven't done anything wrong.
What's so great about this hospital to make you be like that?
Anywhere is better than here.
Do you want me to look for your position as well?
Dr. Kang.
Let's calm down and talk this out.
Let me know when you change your mind.
It's not hard to find open positions.
Dr. Kang. Dr. Kang!
- What are you going to do? - I'm not sure.
What should I do, indeed?
Dr. Kang, you shouldn't decide things with your emotions.
I know Master Kim irritates people.
I know that. He's done it to me, too.
But still,
it's not right for you to quit just because of one person.
It's not just about him. I hate everything about this hospital.
Really?
Tell me what you don't like about this hospital.
I can't even tell whether it's a surgery department or an ER.
The nurses come in and out...
from the operating room to the emergency room.
Nothing is organized here.
I don't even know who are responsible for what.
That's simply because of lacking manpower.
There are no departments here.
Everyone works together.
That's why I want to work at a hospital where...
I can put my specialty to good use.
A big and clean hospital...
with the latest technology and equipment.
I admit that our hospital lags a little in some areas...
compared to big hospitals in big cities, but...
That's not a little.
We're lagging way behind.
The building is old.
The system is out of date.
Also, the equipment is just awful.
So stop wasting your time in a place like this...
and find a different hospital to work in.
And then what? Live like you?
You value the opinions of higher ups more than of the patients.
All you care about is how to climb the ladder faster.
It's either that or being stuck in a place like this forever.
- You're a disgrace. - Dr. Yoon.
How are those the only things you think about...
with all your capabilities?
Because nothing works out for me even with these capabilities.
Of course nothing would have worked out with that victim mentality.
What did you say?
Break it up, you two.
I heard you loud and clear, Dr. Kang.
I'll discuss with President Yeo and improve the working conditions.
Do you need a raise? A house to stay in? You name it.
There's no need for that. He won't even feel grateful.
Why are you doing this, Dr. Yoon?
Help me out here, okay?
I'm really fine, Mr. Jang.
Like what she said just now, those things won't change my mind.
- Dr. Kang. - See? He's like that.
Dr. Yoon.
I wish you the best of lucks...
in this rubbish place you call a hospital.
Mind your own luck. I don't need you to worry about me.
My goodness.
- Please, Dr. Kang. - Let go of me.
- Please. Just this once. - Let me go!
This hospital is really noisy.
What are you two on about...
in this early afternoon?
Ms. Jo. What a pleasant surprise.
- Is he your father? - He's Chairman Shin.
Nice to meet you, Chairman Shin.
I'm Jang Gi Tae of Doldam Hospital.
I've been meaning to say hello. Thank you for coming down here.
Is there something wrong with Chairman Shin?
He's here to see Master Kim.
What? To see Master Kim?
These are the candidates for the operation on the chairman.
One of them are Dr. John Woo.
He is a renowned surgeon in the US.
This will surely guarantee...
your third consecutive term. Congratulations in advance.
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
We still have two months left before the board decision.
I'm not getting ahead of myself.
I'm just stating the obvious, President Do.
Give Ms. Jo a call.
I'll go down to Jeongseon myself.
Okay.
What brings you here?
I thought you said I should come if I wanted to see you.
I'm the desperate one here.
I'm here to see you now.
If you want me to be your doctor,
it's like how I already told you.
It's been about two years since the operation, right?
You're exactly right.
How does it look?
Do you think the operation went well?
It must have done perfectly since you're alive and well.
It's been two years now since I've been living with...
electric wires inside of my body.
The way I look at it,
there's something wrong with...
the battery inside my body.
It feels uncomfortable when I'm not even doing anything.
They told me that I have to live like this...
unless I get a heart transplant.
Who knows when...
that's going to happen?
You've lived so well with all that money.
Isn't it about time for you to start giving away to other people?
Try to do something good for a change.
Who knows? If you start to live like that,
the sky may be touched and send you a perfect heart.
Even if I do find a perfect heart,
the problem is this.
I don't have the perfect doctor.
What about the one who gave you that artificial heart?
He died.
He died with a heart attack.
He was in a heart surgery to save someone else's life,
but he got a heart attack and died.
Funny, isn't it?
It's sad.
Will you do it?
I heard you used to be a cardiothoracic surgeon.
Why me?
There are many other qualified doctors.
I know that there are millions of qualified doctors.
However,
not many of them are real.
Do you think I'm real?
How do you think...
I made this much money?
It's all because I have an eye for people.
I can see...
who is real.
In that case,
your eye for people probably grew old.
Why? Don't you want to perform...
my surgery?
Is it because I'm trashy?
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
Please let me introduce some of our tea menu...
prepared just for our VIP patients.
We have Earl Grey tea, English Breakfast, and Ceylon tea.
We also have three different types of green tea.
You can have them in both hot or iced,
or as a milk tea if you wish.
What would you like?
Have you ever...
thought about me?
Have you ever missed me?
Can't you hear me?
What's with you?
What?
What did you say?
Did you say something to me?
Have you ever missed me?
For the last five years,
have you ever thought of me?
I got lost in the mountains.
I slipped on a slope and hurt my wrist.
My focus was only rehabilitation for the next three years.
Thankfully, 90 percent of my wrist is back to normal.
That's how I got on the emergency medicine board.
After that, I wanted to be certified as a cardiothoracic surgeon.
Most of the patients in the emergency room have...
heart or lung problems.
That sounds like you did not have any time to think of me.
Is that right?
Okay. I get it.
I heard you.
I missed you, too.
I don't know why,
but I thought of you from time to time.
Are you saying this because I'm leaving?
Are you pitying me?
Did it sound like that?
If so, I can't help it.
(Master Kim)
I have to go.
Goodbye.
Succeeding and advancing in your career.
They're all great.
But hey, Dong Joo.
We're doctors.
So what?
We're doctors, so what?
We're only doctors,
but we're still doctors.
Don't forget that.
Are you off duty?
No. I am leaving.
Did you say goodbye to President Yeo?
I turned in my resignation. That's enough.
I'm so sorry,
but we have a hand laceration case in the emergency room.
I know you're leaving, but can you stitch it up?
Please.
Where's the patient?
The patient is waiting in the hybrid operating room.
I'm ready to hear.
I will comply with whatever decision you made.
I mean,
I will comply...
with anything but getting fired.
Come closer.
- Pardon? - Let me see your hand.
Okay.
Are you doing okay?
Yes, I am.
You're good.
You would have made a great plastic surgeon.
Are you saying that because I'm slow?
I'm complimenting you for your precision.
What do you hate so much about Doldam Hospital?
Pardon?
I asked you to tell me three reasons...
why you want to stay in this hospital so much.
First of all, I don't like Master Kim.
I want to learn from you.
Second, I don't like this hospital.
I can't see my future in this hospital.
I want to learn...
from you.
I want to carry out a collaborative surgery with you some day.
It is my wish.
I want to become the best doctor, not a good doctor.
That means...
this isn't where I belong.
Is that so?
Then, let me ask you one more thing.
From your perspective,
is Master Kim a good doctor or the best doctor?
Which one is he?
Is Master Kim...
a good doctor...
or the best doctor?
These are the best doctors.
Please take a look.
I feel so bad.
You came all the way here for nothing.
Pardon?
Actually,
I've already found a doctor to operate on me.
He's a talented doctor.
May I ask who recommended you the doctor?
Chairman Shin, it's a call from Master Kim.
Okay. I'll take it.
Yes, Master Kim. It's me.
Have you made up your mind?
First, I need a new ultrasound machine. The latest model.
Are you asking me for that instead of the surgery fee?
No.
This would be the settlement money.
As a result of being beaten up yesterday,
I have injuries requiring 2 or 3 weeks of medial treatment.
As I've already told you, I'm worth a lot of money.
All right. I'll buy you the latest equipment.
Then, will you take up my operation?
In order to change the battery of your artificial heart,
we need a new ultrasound machine to begin with.
We also need the latest model of operation table, anesthesia machine,
and a heart-lung machine.
If you consider a heart transplant in the future.
I'm listening.
We'll also need a clean room for the immunosuppression therapy,
but... Gosh. How can I say?
These are very expensive equipments. I'm worried.
I wouldn't mind how much it'd cost. Don't worry about it.
No matter how much it'll cost me,
I'll buy you the latest equipments.
If I do that, will you operate on me?
Once we get the equipment, I'll set the date for your surgery.
You heard that, right? Master Kim said...
he'll operate on me.
I'm glad to hear that.
Chairman Shin.
Have I done...
anything to upset you?
What are you talking about?
You've been doing a great job in running Geodae Hospital.
Then, why did you refuse all the doctors I recommended you...
and let an unknown doctor operate on you?
- Do you want to know? - If I may,
I'd like to hear the reason.
Ms. Jo, show it to him.
Yes, I will.
- What do you see? - It looks like the scene of a fire.
Is this the kitchen in the casino?
The fire broke out last night.
What do you see?
It seems that the staff members in the kitchen got severely injured.
Right. What else?
This man...
That's right.
That's him.
He jumped into the fire...
to save other people's lives.
I don't think I'm following you.
Usually, when people get hurt,
doctors only care about the treatment of their wounds.
But he tried to help them get injured less.
He might have lost his own life,
but he still jumped into the fire.
Do you still not understand...
the difference?
No, I don't think I do.
This man is the doctor who's called Master Kim.
He's the true doctor whom I can trust...
with my life.
It looks like you finally recognized his face.
You're right. That's him.
He's in ventricular fibrillation. Sir. Sir.
Move him to the hybrid operating room and bring the defibrillator.
- Give him epinephrine. - Yes, Doctor.
Did you meet Master Kim?
Seo Jung.
What did you say?
What did he say? Did he say you can stay here?
Actually...
You can stay here if you want to.
Thank you.
I won't forget that you gave me the second chance,
and I'll do everything in my power to repay your generosity.
However, I can't allow you...
to treat patients yet.
If I don't treat patients,
what should I do here?
You'll work as an orderly.
- Orderly? - Yes, I'm an orderly.
Did you just tell me to work...
as an orderly?
I need to be sure if I can let you be with the patients or not.
Until you become able to control yourself solely...
with your willpower without taking medications,
the only job you can get in this hospital is...
to be an orderly.
Why? Can't you do that?
No. It's not that.
Did you accept it?
I asked him for some time to think about it.
Why would you say that?
You should have refused it.
Right?
- Working as an orderly is... - Really? Can't you do that?
You can just leave this hospital if you can't do it.
- I won't stop you. - I didn't say I can't do it.
You can't make her work as an orderly.
This is the best offer I can give to her, Ms. Oh.
Don't try to change my mind.
You heard him. I should go now.
Charge 200J.
It's ready.
Shock.
- Fill me in. - He's from a car accident.
He has right-sided hemopneumothorax and his right hip is dislocated.
He went into ventricular fibrillation while being hydrated.
Please hang in there.
I'll check his heart rhythm.
- Let's try it again. 200J. - Yes, Doctor.
It's done.
Shock.
- How long has it been? - It's been about three minutes.
Please, please.
I'll check his heart rhythm.
Doctor, his pulse is back.
Print out the electrocardiogram and prepare the central line.
- As for the blood transfusion... - You said you'd quit.
Why are you still here?
I'm considering him as my last patient in Doldam Hospital.
Did you get his CT scan result?
He has multiple rib fracture and right-sided hemopneumothorax.
I put in a tube and he's not bleeding much.
Simple dislocation on the right hip...
and compound fracture on the left humerus was also found.
Have you ever dealt with hip dislocation before?
No.
I know how to do it, though. Do you want me to do it?
Mr. Park.
Bring me a sheet.
What are you doing?
Tie up the other side.
Are you doing it alone?
Is it done?
It's done.
What about his vital signs?
- It is stable. - Okay.
Next up is the humerus.
Which one are you?
What do you mean?
Are you a good doctor...
or the best doctor?
Wait.
(Kang Dong Joo)
I only want to hear it from you.
Are you a good doctor or the best doctor?
If the patient lying down here gets to choose one of them,
which one do you think he will choose?
- The best doctor. - Wrong.
He will need a doctor who can treat his injury.
What this patient would need so badly...
is an orthopedic surgeon who can treat fractures.
So I'm playing all my cards...
to be the right one for him.
Does this answer your question?
You can blame the system and the world.
You can blame all the people who messed up the world if you want.
I know you can.
But nothing will change even if you try so hard to blame everything.
Those people won't even...
remember your name.
If you really want to win, become a doctor who can serve.
Stop blaming them and pay them back with your capability.
As long as you don't change,
nothing will change.
Do you understand?
As long as you don't change,
nothing will change.
Okay?
That's it.
I will let you finish up on the last patient...
at Doldam Hospital.
No way.
Is that him?
Dr. Kang.
He will be back. Let's just wait.
(Dear Dr. Boo Yong Joo, this is Kang Dong Joo)
Master Kim.
What? Is there any further business?
You are him, right?
You are the doctor.
Aren't you?
You are Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
Is that him?
Is Master Kim at Doldam Hospital...
Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
Well, I don't know.
President Yeo.
I don't know the real name of Master Kim.
There's no way for me to confirm it.
Hey, Woon Young!
Answer my question.
I'm sorry, but there is nothing I can tell you.
President Do, I have to go.
(President Yeo Woon Young)
What a jerk.
How dare you betray me?
Please tell me.
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
You are him,
aren't you?
Hey.
You bonehead.
I already told you who I am. What are you talking about?
Master Kim.
I'm Dr. Kim.
I don't have any other names.
Happy now?
Dear Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
My name is Kang Dong Joo.
When I grow up,
I want to be a good doctor like you.
Excuse me.
Where should I go to meet Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo?
He doesn't work here any more.
What do you mean?
Do you know where I can find him?
I don't know that.
Excuse me.
Hello. This is Geodae Hospital.
Yes. Okay, I will.
So that...
there will be no patients treated unfairly...
like my father.
I'm sure.
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
He's the one.
(Dr. Romantic)
- You said you would quit. - You said you missed me.
Do you know why he got kicked out from Geodae Hospital?
There must be a reason...
when such a great doctor casts away his name...
and stays here in hiding. Don't you think so?
He killed a person.
He killed his student who followed and trusted him.
- It's been a long time. - Hey, In Beom.
There is something I'm dreaming about.
What on earth is that?
May I ask why you tried to keep me at this hospital?