Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
A 97 percent success rate of all operations.
(OPERATING ROOM)
The one and only surgeon with triple board.
His touches bring even the near dead back to life.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Even the wealthiest people...
line up with bags of money...
to receive his treatments.
He's the legendary surgeon.
After he made a name for himself,
he disappeared all of a sudden...
and nobody knew of his whereabouts.
That's him, right?
I don't know.
(EPISODE 5)
I know I'm right.
- I don't know what you're...
- Master Kim's true identity.
It's Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
Isn't it?
Tell me I'm right.
I'm sorry.
But I simply can't give you an answer on that matter.
You still have my letter of resignation, right?
- Are you looking for this?
- If Master Kim turns out to be...
Dr. Boo Yong Joo,
you can shred it in pieces.
Does that mean...
you'll be staying here at Doldam Hospital?
Is that the correct interpretation of what you just said, Dr. Kang?
Only if Master Kim really is Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
I wasn't expecting you so early, President Do.
Did everything go well with Chairman Shin?
Is there something wrong?
Did something happen in Jeongseon?
What is it? Did Chairman Shin give you some bad news?
- It's him.
- Pardon?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
He's back.
He's at Doldam Hospital.
That's where he's been staying at.
Times when climbing up the ladder is all that matters.
Suction!
The bleeding won't stop.
- Did you not hear me?
- Okay.
People turn their backs on conscience and even human lives.
Such things aren't taken into calculation.
Bring the defibrillator. Hurry!
Charge 360J.
Shock.
- Charge 360J.
- Again.
Shock.
Doctor.
She's gone.
Darn it.
They justify the sacrifice of others by...
saying it couldn't be helped.
How could you?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
The powerless people...
don't want to act against the will of powerful people.
They don't fully neglect the truth.
All of those people...
formed a group of vested interests and are ruling over the world.
Shouldn't we do something about this?
How can Chairman Shin make a decision like that...
when the board decision is coming up?
That operation should not happen no matter what.
Dr. Kang is down there, right?
What?
Give it up already.
That's him, right?
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
Right?
I can't say anything.
Seriously, I didn't say anything.
No, you didn't.
You should use Kang Dong Joo.
If he wants to come back to Geodae Hospital,
he will need to do something.
Don't you think?
Yes, President Do.
I understand.
(CHAPTER 5, PRINCIPLE OF RELATIVE)
- What?
- Orderly?
Yes, orderly.
Are you really going to do that?
I have no choice. I can't go to another hospital.
I made a mistake.
I should make up for it.
With patience, endurance, backbone, and indomitability.
Did you talk to Master Kim?
Of course I did.
- Will you do that?
- Yes.
I'm willing to do anything,
whether it is an orderly or something.
- Are you?
- Of course.
I will make sure to control my condition no matter what.
What did he say?
He just said...
Okay.
You may go now.
Unbelievable.
I know. That's too harsh.
Master Kim is being too harsh to her, don't you think?
I think so, too. He is very kind to us.
Maybe I'm on his blacklist.
Are you sure you will be okay?
I should be okay.
Will I be okay?
I've made the right decision, right?
Please say yes.
Gosh.
There you are.
I have good news.
The thing is Doctor Kang Dong Joo...
who passed the board exam with the highest score in the country...
has decided to remain at Doldam Hospital...
after many complications.
It wasn't easy, but he made a bold decision.
Please welcome him with a big hand.
Why is everyone so quiet?
Could you explain...
I have to get back to work.
What's wrong with Dr. Yoon?
Is something wrong?
Can't you tell just by looking at her?
Did Master Kim really kick her out?
Is that it?
He made an even worse decision.
What is worse than kicking her out?
What would that be?
An orderly?
Are you really going to do that?
There's no reason I can't do that. I work for the hospital anyway.
I see.
Does that mean I can give you orders from now on?
Don't even try to boss me around.
What's the matter? I'm doing it for the hospital.
Why did you suddenly change your mind, by the way?
You said you would quit.
You would go to a better hospital.
Why do you want to stay here rubbing salt into my wound?
Why is that?
Master Kim.
I need to learn more about him.
Excuse me. Don't you remember?
Just a few hours ago, you lashed out at Master Kim...
in a fit of rage questioning his manner.
You were going to threw up your job at this lousy hospital.
Now you are saying what?
"I need to learn more about him".
Did you just say that?
I was going to quit because I didn't know who Master Kim was.
I heard he is Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
He's the only person in the country...
with the triple board and a success rate of 97 percent in operation.
He is a living legend in the surgeon world.
How did you know that?
I knew it.
Everyone knows that Master Kim is Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
You knew it but pretended not to know the whole time.
So what are you going to do?
It's obvious.
I will stay here and learn from him for a while.
Master Kim is not easy to deal with.
He has the most ferocious temper ever.
He's not someone you can just push around.
You said you missed me.
If I leave the hospital like this, I will never be able...
to find out why you missed me.
That's another reason.
We are in a hospital. No romance allowed, okay?
Can't we have a romance?
You are being ridiculous.
If you have time for a romance, just go take a nap.
Or go eat something.
We can do that together.
We can take a nap or eat something together.
That's a romance. There is not much more to do.
It's your fault.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I died because of you.
It's your fault.
You killed me.
It's okay. I will get that.
(NURSES)
Hello? The emergency room at Doldam Hospital.
How many?
A truck smashed into people riding bicycles.
It seems to be drowsy driving. Three people are killed already.
It was a scene of devastation.
It's spreading through the Internet.
There are news-people from the local papers outside the hospital.
They are trying to film everything here.
Prepare warm saline for the hybrid room.
Pad splint and fluid, too.
Okay.
There are 7 patients here and 4 more are on the way.
Also, 1 of the 7 patients has died on route to the hospital.
Two have slight wounds.
The other one has hemopneumothorax in left side with spleen injury.
Lung sounds are diminishing on the left side.
What about thoracic hemorrhage?
It's about 1,000cc on the left side.
I will put in a chest tube and move him to the operating room.
Okay. I will begin the operation immediately.
Can I assist you in the operation?
I'd like to watch your operation.
Didn't you say you would quit?
That's what I heard.
I guess you haven't heard of it.
I decided to remain at Doldam Hospital.
Can I assist you in the operation then?
I need someone to call Dr. Nam.
Someone called me already and I have just arrived.
It's hemoperitoneum. Go prepare for an operation.
Of course I will.
Orderly. Just in case,
call Dr. Yang at Jungil Hospital.
Yes, Doctor.
He's in cardiac arrest.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What are you doing, Dr. Kang?
Aren't you putting in a chest tube?
Yes, I'll do that.
We have a patient.
What's the problem?
He hurt his right knee and pelvis.
His vital signs are between 50 to 90.
- Does your stomach hurt?
- My pelvis hurts.
Mr. Park.
Doctor!
(EMERGENCY ROOM)
Excuse me, make way, please.
Did I...
do this?
How could this be?
No way.
Did I really...
Are you okay?
We're ready.
Get ready.
Shock!
Let's see.
One more time. Charge 200J.
We're ready.
Ready, shock!
Nothing.
We have more patients, Master Kim.
Two have minor injuries,
and one fractured his collarbone but his vitals are stable.
The other one has pelvis pain,
and it looks like he fractured his pelvic bone.
Master Kim.
Time of death...
is 3:16pm.
What's his case?
He has pelvic pain. It looks like his pelvic is fractured.
Give me some sheets.
That jerk.
It's you, right?
You're the driver.
You are.
Why are you here?
How dare you lie around here?
You jerk!
Sir, please.
- Calm down.
- You jerk!
You're not even a human.
You're just a murderer.
- Sir.
- Let go of me!
You shouldn't be taking me!
- Excuse me, Sir.
- Catch that murderer!
- Let go of me!
- Who is he?
He's the driver.
He hit his chest on the handle, but it's nothing serious.
I always tell them...
not to bring the assailant and the victim to the same hospital.
Check his vital signs,
- and take an X-ray.
- Yes, Master Kim.
To the X-ray room.
Officers.
This is the murderer.
He's the guy who killed all of my friends.
Sir, how do you feel?
You don't need to treat someone like him.
Just let him die!
I think I hit my chest.
But I can't remember clearly.
Don't you remember?
You killed so many people. Why don't you remember?
How dare you call yourself a human being?
Lie him down.
Be careful.
What were his first vitals?
They were between 70 and 100, and 95 beats per minute.
What about now?
They are between 20 and 80, and 120 beats per minute.
This is a murderer.
Do not revive him!
Please get him out of here.
Let go off me. I'm hurt!
That jerk killed my friends!
I'm going to sue you all!
I moved the patient with fractured pelvic bone to the X-ray room.
- What does this look like?
- Pardon?
His cardiac sound is dropping.
His jugular veins are swelling, and his blood pressure is dropping.
That's Beck's triad.
Could it be cardiac tamponade?
But cardiac tamponade is rarely caused by a blunt injury.
Yes, it is rare.
There is only one thousandth of a percent of this case.
But does a doctor rule out such a case...
just because it's rarely seen?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think far enough.
I expected you to not think that far.
You're just an orderly.
Get him ready for a surgery.
And find out if someone got a hold Dr. Yang or not.
An orderly...
will perform only the tasks right for an orderly.
Yes, Master Kim.
Kang Dong Joo.
You are doomed.
Hello? This is Kang Dong Joo.
- Where are you?
- At Doldam Hospital. Where else?
It's a Saturday afternoon. Are you still at work?
Exactly.
This hospital is so lousy that it keeps around...
someone who was on a night shift last night...
until late today afternoon.
We need to meet. When are you free?
I'm sorry. I have to go into a surgery.
What?
Sir, did you know this, too?
There is a very famous surgeon here at Doldam Hospital.
Did you...
meet him?
Of course. That's why I want to thank you.
Thank me? What do you mean?
You led me to a great teacher.
I'll return...
after learning everything from him. Goodbye.
- What about the surgery?
- We're ready.
What?
A teacher?
Darn it!
Pardon? Me?
Why not?
What about you?
Sir, Dr. Yang just got here.
The patient will be anesthetized in five minutes.
This is a cardiac tamponade case.
I'll take his heart.
You take care of the hemoperitoneum.
Yes, Master Kim.
Hey.
Don't fall asleep.
Don't fall asleep, okay?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Let's begin.
- Knife.
- Scalpel.
C.S.C?
What does this mean?
They were members of Cancer Survivors Club, C.S.C.
Does that mean all of the members here...
have a history of cancer?
That's correct.
What about the one in the surgery room?
Do you know if he has a history of cancer?
I'm not sure.
It was his liver.
Liver cancer.
He even went through chemotherapy,
and he finally got better.
Liver cancer?
Long forceps.
Scalpel.
Metzenbaum.
Suction.
Everything is good so far.
Retractor.
Pad.
Pass me more.
Sternal saw.
Spreader.
Scalpel.
Suction.
That's the point of bleeding.
Thankfully, none of his major vessels are damaged.
Let's stitch him up.
Suture.
- Cut.
- Cutting.
Focus.
Yes, Master Kim.
Pick up the phone.
- Master Kim.
- Yes?
There's Mr. Jang at the door.
It's an emergency. Hurry.
- Cut.
- Cutting.
You're going to make me come in there, aren't you?
I told you to pick up the phone, Master Kim.
You know I don't do that during operations.
I told you it's an emergency.
The patient in the other room has a history of liver cancer.
- So what? Cut.
- Cutting.
Dr. Kang was kicked out of Geodae Hospital...
because of a liver cancer patient.
What's this?
It's bleeding.
- Where is the bleeding coming from?
- Is it...
ruptured hepatocellular carcinoma?
Wake up, Dr. Kang. You have to stop the bleeding.
Suction.
There's bleeding in thoracic cavity, too.
It could result in disseminated intravascular coagulation.
Suction. Bovie.
The patient died from excessive bleeding during an operation.
What's going on, Dr. Kang?
You're in the middle of operation.
I can't.
- I can't stop the bleeding.
- The bleeding won't stop.
Get it together, Dr. Kang.
You're the only one who can save this patient.
Dr. Kang!
Get yourself together, Kang Dong Joo.
Listen to me carefully.
That patient lying down there...
made a full recovery from liver cancer five years ago.
I think there's been a recurrence.
It's ruptured hepatocellular carcinoma.
He's bleeding too much.
And there's even bleeding from the thoracic cavity.
I think disseminated intravascular coagulation is taking place.
Dr. Nam. How is the bleeding?
It can be under observation for a little longer.
Okay.
Dr. Kang. Are you listening?
You're calling the shots on that operation.
If your decision is to give up and call it done,
nobody's going to blame you.
But if you do so,
you'll look back on that moment for the rest of your life.
I'm sorry.
I don't feel confident enough to save this patient.
Dr. Kang.
Do you know what's worse than death on the operating table?
It's the regret you get thinking...
you might have been able to save the patient by not giving up.
That thought will haunt you for the rest of your life.
If there's something worse than failure,
it's regret.
What do you say?
I'm sorry. I really can't.
You really can't do it?
I'm sorry.
Close it up, then.
Master Kim.
If you don't think you can do it,
close him up before you give him more suffering.
Like I said, you're the one calling the shots.
Do as you wish.
Hang up now.
Cut.
Hello. Hello? Master Kim.
How can you hang up like that?
Cut.
Come on. Don't be like that.
Mr. Park. Switch with me.
Dr. Kang.
I've been through harder operations than this...
with Master Kim.
There were patients who died on us,
but they tend to hang in there longer...
as long as we don't give up until the end.
The patient's not in the worst condition yet.
He's still hanging in there. What should we do, Dr. Kang?
Do we give up now?
This is your operation.
We will follow your order.
Suction.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Are you going to close him up?
- Or...
- No.
Let's commence the left hemihepatectomy.
We have plenty of blood left. Don't worry about me.
Dr. Kang. Let's try everything we can do.
Suction.
Hemostatic.
Vascular clamps.
Suture.
Dr. Kang is back on the operation.
Do you think Dr. Kang can...
- Cut.
- Cutting.
The heart operation is done.
You should finish up.
I know you're just an orderly, but you can do it, right?
What? Yes, of course.
Don't leave a needle in there.
Of course.
Where are you going?
Master Kim.
Put pressure on there.
Nice timing.
Are you still struggling with the bleeding?
I was on it.
It's not too late for me to step in if you want.
I'm on it.
Bovie.
Pad.
Irrigation.
Suction.
Tying the left hepatic artery and the portal vein.
Hemostatic.
Suture.
Cut.
Commencing lobectomy.
Bovie.
The bleeding is starting again.
There's nothing wrong with the tied blood vessels.
What about the hepatic vein?
I'm going to commence resection and ligation.
Stopping the inflow is enough to stop the bleeding. Isn't it?
No.
There could be a case of back flow from the veins.
What do you do, then?
You have to block the hepatic vein first.
- Right.
- Hemostatic.
Hold on to that.
Suture.
Suction.
Cut.
Irrigation.
Suction.
Pad.
I think I can control the bleeding.
How does it look, Dr. Nam?
Vitals are between 50 to 90.
Heart rate is becoming more stable.
Okay.
What are you waiting for?
You need to do recession.
Okay.
- I'll be there soon.
- Okay.
How did it go?
It was such a touching moment.
I guess Dr. Kang did well.
He did better than well.
Him and Master Kim stopping the patient from bleeding was...
like a scene from a movie.
I knew he had to be good when I heard he was...
the top of his class.
Right?
What?
Jeongseon?
Tonight, Sir?
Yes.
Aren't you close to Dong Joo?
We'll go and make a drink with him.
- Make him come out.
- But Sir.
It's finally my day off today.
I promised my family that we'd go to an aquarium together.
So what?
I guess I'll have to push it back.
I'll come along. Let me call my wife.
May I join you?
Do you want to come?
Are you friends with Dong Joo as well?
- We went to school together.
- Really?
That's great. The more, the merrier.
- I'll see you in 30 minutes.
- Yes, Doctor.
Hey, this is between doctors in your department.
Stop dragging me into this.
Don't you think he's overstepping his authority?
I thought that Crazy Whale is also in that hospital.
You wanted to meet her.
Seo Jung. You're right.
Hello, I am Lee Jun Hee, a reporter of SBN.
Could you tell us about the accident and the patients in detail?
The staff at Doldam Hospital are...
Could you first tell us the number of the deceased and injured?
I am getting to it.
The staff at Doldam Hospital are...
made up of very excellent doctors.
Our new surgeon is a very talented young man...
who passed his board exam with the highest score.
He is a great addition...
What were you going to do...
if I had given up?
What if I really gave up...
- and stitched him back up?
- Nothing.
I wasn't going to do anything.
Nothing?
It's not my responsibility that you gave up and killed him.
You're the one who will live your life...
filled with guilt and regrets.
Excuse me.
I really don't get it.
May I ask you why you wanted to keep me...
in this hospital?
- Why would I want to keep you?
- Then why did you say that?
If you don't change,
nothing will change. Do you understand?
You knew I'd figure it out once I heard that.
You knew I wouldn't leave once I figured it out, too.
Didn't you expect that?
Is that why...
you've been acting like a fool?
A fool?
Hey.
Why didn't you run a CT scan on him?
If you had done that,
you probably could've seen his medical history.
I thought he may die if I didn't hurry.
Even so, how could you not check his medical history...
before the surgery?
His stomach was swelling up.
I thought he would go into a cardiac arrest if I didn't hurry.
I did make a mistake by not checking his history.
But it was an emergency.
I thought stopping his bleeding was the most important thing to do.
That's what I do.
That's not your style.
Hey, I thought you were all about rules.
Rules...
never change under any circumstances.
Changing your words...
according to people and circumstances is...
not a rule, it's merely an excuse.
I was just being flexible.
Didn't you almost kill him...
as you tried to follow me?
You're making too many assumptions after a single mistake.
Stop making excuses.
Your single mistake almost killed someone.
It's up to you...
to stay or go. Do what you'd like.
However, if you are expecting something from me,
you should stop dreaming.
To a guy...
who bends his rule according to the situation,
I have nothing else to give...
other than neglecting, mocking, despising, and swearing at you.
See?
I told you about his temper.
I told you he wasn't going to be easy.
But you know what?
I kind of envy you.
You did something I've been wanting to do...
for the last five years.
You did a combined operation with Master Kim.
It wasn't a combined operation. He took over.
Also, he made sure...
you knew about your mistakes.
He didn't make sure. He just blamed me.
I wish I could be blamed at.
It's better to be blamed...
than to be ignored.
I am sure...
that he has a personality disorder.
Either that, or he's a sadist who enjoys torturing others.
Or it might be because of his hurtful history.
There must be a reason...
when such a great doctor casts away his name...
and stays here in hiding. Don't you think so?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
You idiot.
Who told you to perform that operation?
You jerk, answer me.
Who is it?
- Who told you to do that?
- Doctor, please.
- Let go of me!
- Doctor.
- Get him.
- Let go!
Okay, I'll calm down. Let go.
You idiot!
- Doctor, please.
- I'll get you.
Doctor.
Let go!
Let go of me!
Let go. Was it you?
Did you let him...
perform that operation?
What are you talking about?
You killed the patient.
- What?
- You are the one...
who was in that operation room...
and operated on her.
That's what the record will say.
Our staff members...
will testify the same way, too.
Dr. Boo.
No one who knows about that surgery...
will take your side.
This is why...
you should have been tamed...
while we still liked you.
How dare you lift your head and bark at us?
Who do you think made you who you are?
You should...
kneel down and apologize.
- If so, I can...
- Jang Hyeon Joo.
All she wanted to do was...
hold a scalpel in an operation room...
while playing Madonna's music.
Jang Hyeon Joo, a third-year at her medical school.
If you treated her with medicine...
in Department of Internal Medicine,
she would have lived her dream.
She wasn't supposed to die because of someone like you.
You are the one...
who has to kneel down and apologize to her mom.
You can no longer work at Geodae Hospital.
Not just this hospital, any other hospital in Korea.
No hospital will hire you.
I'll make sure...
that you can never work in this industry.
I will!
(DOLDAM HOSPITAL)
I think we're here.
Is this Doldam Hospital?
It really looks lousy.
- Call him.
- Pardon?
- I said, call Dong Joo.
- Okay.
Should I wake him?
He was on call last night and carried out a surgery today.
He must be exhausted.
He needs to get some sleep. Let him be.
Yes, Ms. Oh.
- He's not answering.
- Really?
- Is it not off?
- No. He's just not answering it.
The number you are calling is not available right now...
It's Saturday afternoon. Could he be in the hospital?
He must be. He said he was going to do a surgery.
Then, I guess he's still in a surgery.
Hey.
Think before you speak.
Do you think it's possible to do a major surgery in that hospital?
I think it's impossible.
I'll go in and find him.
Would you?
I'll go help him.
Are you hurt?
I could have. What would you do if I was hurt?
- Are you a pianist?
- I'm a doctor.
Are you a surgeon?
Aren't you going to apologize?
You're not hurt.
I could have.
Then you should be more careful.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
It was nothing.
- What a jerk.
- Jerk?
In Beom, wait up.
President Do, it's me.
I'm at Jeongseon right now.
Boo Yong Joo is here.
I just confirmed it.
That little rat.
He even changed his name...
to hide in such a place like this.
Mr. Jang.
You're tired, aren't you?
Why wouldn't you be?
Please drink this for your fatigue.
I'm good.
- I don't like it.
- I see.
You have a visitor.
Maybe because it's surrounded by mountains, it's very dry here.
That's true.
(INTENSIVE CARE UNIT)
- In Soo.
- Dong Joo.
Dong Joo!
What are you doing here?
Obviously, I'm here to see you.
It hasn't even been a week since you left.
It feels like a year passed.
Are you really here to see me?
Of course, I am.
In Beom is here, too.
Do In Beom is here?
What brings you here?
I didn't know you were here.
I asked you why you're here.
I'm here to see...
Dong Joo.
I adore him.
Then, why did you send him to the hospital in the countryside?
You should have helped him stay at your hospital.
You know how President Do...
shifts responsibility to other doctors.
Hey.
Are you still living like that?
What's wrong with you?
I'm the chief surgeon now.
I have a high social status.
Don't look down on me.
If you have a high social statsus,
why were you crouching in the back seat to hide yourself?
It was because of my back pain.
I crouched because my back hurt.
Weren't you just afraid to see me because of what you did?
Please be careful of what you say.
I'm not the person you used to know.
I'm the head of General Surgery of Geodae Hospital.
Exactly!
What is such a high ranking person like you doing here?
What's the true purpose of your visit?
I have no idea why he came all the way here with us.
He just said we could have a drink with you.
No. I can't leave right now.
I have to monitor the patient I operated on until he wakes up.
Hey.
Still, you should at least show your face. Dr. Song is here, too.
Yes, Kang Dong Joo speaking.
Yes. Okay. I'll be there shortly.
I should go now. We have patients in the emergency room.
You're a surgeon. Why would you go to the emergency room?
We're short-staffed here. A surgeon is no exception.
- Please say hello to Dr. Song.
- Dong Joo.
Dong Joo!
This is driving me crazy.
What should I do?
- The number you are calling...
- Why isn't In Beom answering?
Where on earth are you?
Dr. Yoon?
She must have gone for bed sheets.
Bed sheets?
Does a doctor do that in this hospital?
She's in a situation.
This isn't right.
I'm an ER doctor and a cardiac surgeon.
Why am I folding bed sheets?
I have no choice. I'm an orderly.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I don't remember when, but I started to
Look down on the ground more than I look up at the sky
It's hard to even breathe
I reach out my hand, but there's no one to hold my hand
I'm a loser, I'm a loner
I'm a coward pretending to be strong
I'm a mean bully, I see myself through the mirror
I'm a loser, I'm a loner
I'm an idiot pretending
What's wrong? What is it?
You startled me.
Who are you? Why are you standing there?
I just... I'm lost.
Excuse me?
She fainted on the street, and someone called paramedics.
Her pupil reflex and breathing are weak.
Let's intubate her for now.
Set up IV lines and give her normal saline.
Prepare for a brain CT scan, too.
Hold on a second.
Give her some food.
Excuse me?
I said, she needs to eat.
What are you talking about?
Trust me, Dr. Kang.
What she needs is food.
Go through the fire exit over there. It leads to the lobby.
Go right from there, not to the left.
- I see.
- Okay, then.
Gosh. I can't use this one.
I should take this to the laundry room.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Do you know someone called Crazy Whale?
Here's food.
Wake up and eat, please.
I think we should set up IV lines...
Slow down. You might have indigestion.
Eat slowly and chew well.
There are some homeless people around the casino who starved...
for days, and they are carried into the hospital.
I see.
Drink it.
Take your time.
If you need anything, please call Mr. Park.
Hello, I'm Park Eun Tak.
- Ms. Woo.
- Yes?
Do you know where Ms. Yoon is?
- She's in the linen room.
- Thank you.
How do you know...
Crazy Whale?
I've heard so much about her...
that she was a legendary doctor at Geodae Hospital.
I think I heard that she's working at Doldam Hospital.
I'd like to meet her.
Do you know her?
Yes.
I know her.
That's me.
I see. You are her.
You are...
the Crazy Whale.
Who are you, by the way?
I don't suppose you have come a long way just to see Crazy Whale.
What brought you here?
Hey, In Beom.
What are you doing here?
I just got lost looking around the hospital.
Do you know him?
- Who is he?
- He was my colleague.
We went to college and worked as a surgeon at Geodae Hospital together.
Unlike me, he is a son of the privileged at Geodae Hospital.
A son of the privileged?
How is President Do doing?
Is he doing good...
after kicking me out to Doldam hospital?
What are you talking about?
Explain it in language I can understand.
President Do of Geodae Hospital...
is his father.
Why aren't you answering me?
What's the reason you are here?
I heard you would perform the operation on the chairman.
What? Who?
Chairman Shin Myung Ho. The big shot of casino.
He is the foundation chairman of Geodae Hospital.
We have not much time left until the renewal of the presidency.
The chairman has...
the final say.
And you will be operating on him.
Do you think President Do will let it slide?
You'd better back off now.
Otherwise, it will backfire on you.
President Do will do anything...
to stop you from operating on him.
That's President Do Yun Wan.
I can't believe this.
Darn it!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(DR. ROMANTIC)
What are you supposed to do? Master Kim and I aren't there.
You are the only one there. Do you want the patient to die?
I can't waste any more time.
Since when has an orderly...
- have the authority to give orders?
- I'm sorry.
Did you operate on my brother?
I'm sorry for everything.
The patient might die in any minute...
- if you didn't operate on him now.
- Aren't you a doctor?
If I were put in the same situation,
I would have made the same decision.
Whether you acknowledge me or not,
I'm a doctor.