(Episode 7)
What is going on?
I need you at Doldam Hospital.
Do you want me to work there, President Do?
Form a team of your followers...
and go down there.
After that,
prevent Boo Yong Joo from operating on Chairman Shin.
Hello.
Staff in Doldam Hospital.
We have been dispatched to Doldam Hospital as a of today.
I'm the head of General Surgery, Song Hyun Cheol.
I will appreciate your help and support.
If you can,
please keep Boo Yong Joo quiet.
I want him out of my life once and for all.
I will not let him...
live a life of a surgeon.
But how, President Do?
That's what I need you for.
You must...
find a way.
I'll try my best, President Do.
How should I interpret this situation, President Do?
I looked around the hospital...
and noticed that you're short on staff.
So I sent some of our staff to support you.
Support me?
- Is that all? - Why do you ask?
Do you have any problem with my decision?
Even if you have, don't dare to mention it.
That should be the best for you.
Times of unlimited competition.
You either kill, or you die.
It's a battle of survival.
We are going to...
Doldam Hospital for an innovation.
Don't forget that the future of Doldam Hospital...
lies on our shoulders.
Okay.
- We can do this! - We can do this.
- We can do this. - Louder.
We can do this!
The name's Ji Min Jung.
I've worked at Geodae Hospital for 10 years.
I was the head nurse there.
I'm Oh Myung Sim.
I've worked here for 18 years.
I'm the head nurse here.
I'll be in charge of distributing workloads.
You don't have a problem with that, do you?
We are the face of Geodae Hospital.
We must never...
let them have the upper hand...
in taking the initiative.
No.
I will be the one...
distributing the workloads to my nurses.
It's only reasonable.
I know much more about them...
than you do.
You don't...
have a problem with that, do you?
They take pride in beating their opponents.
And the world encourages them to do so.
Prove yourself.
You always came second to Dong Joo...
both at school and at the hospital.
For once.
Go and win against Dong Joo just once.
Father, I...
I don't want a loser son.
Do you understand?
If you don't beat your opponents, you're looked down upon.
The fear of becoming a loser...
drive people into the world of competition.
Brace yourself.
Dr. Boo Yong Joo.
(To Dr. Master Kim.)
Try me.
(Chapter 7, Unstable Factor)
Do you really not know?
- Are you sure? - I really don't.
I didn't even have time to pack because of the short notice.
Thanks to that, my wife is very upset with me.
My kids were crying all night.
Even my mother-in-law paid us a visit and...
But you're not making any sense.
You all burst into here...
and yet, you say you don't know the reason for it.
That's exactly my point.
How can they reassign so many people like this?
Hey. It's not like the hospital will take responsibility...
if I get divorced.
Hello, In Beom.
Which one is mine?
Do you want to use this one?
I think this one is the best one here.
What is going on?
Why are you here?
Is that because of the surgery? Is that why?
Excuse me.
Can you please stop talking to me as if you know me so well?
Well...
I was just curious.
I don't want you to curious about me. It makes me uncomfortable.
Hey.
Why are you being rude?
I'm sorry if I made you uncomfortable.
In Beom, wait. Are you upset?
What was that?
Your junior was rude to you.
- Aren't you going to do something? - You think?
Was he that rude?
Maybe.
What is going on between you two?
Aren't you going to tell me?
Things are just like you and me.
He is my junior and you are my junior.
How could you even compare me to that jerk?
There is something special between you and me.
Is there anything special?
What is that?
We have...
a special bond.
A special bond?
Don't you think so?
Why?
What?
Nothing.
You are adorable.
You can't say that to a grown man.
I'm not a child.
You are a child. Didn't you know that?
- Am I? - Yes.
You just act like a teenager.
Did you not really know that?
- Seo Jung. - Let's get back to work.
You know what?
I'm not sure why you feel uncomfortable around me.
But now that you are here, I just want to get along with you.
If you have any questions, you are always welcome to ask me.
And I know some famous restaurants...
around here.
Never mind.
How old is the file cabinet?
Vintage furniture is popular these days.
I'm sorry.
We are short of money.
I will buy you a new one if you want.
That's okay. I won't be here that long.
- Pardon? - By the way.
This is for you.
Congratulations on your promotion, Manager Jang.
Manager Jang?
(Letter of Personnel Appointments)
You were asked to perform an important role as a manager...
for Doldam Hospital by President Do.
Let's give it our best shot.
I will make sure to do my best.
I'm ready to put my life on the line for the future of Doldam Hospital.
- Speaking of which, - Yes, sir.
I'd like to know more about Doldam Hospital in detail.
- Pardon? - Like some inside stories...
or hidden bottleneck problems.
Also,
it seems...
Master Kim is a pivotal figure in this hospital.
Is there any unstable factors of him?
Unstable factors?
Me? Are you talking to me?
Yes, you.
What is your position in this hospital?
Well, I am...
- Orderly. - Orderly.
You are an orderly.
on the board for emergency medicine.
Actually, on the double board for cardiothoracic surgery.
Maybe you are a hidden medical expert in this hospital.
No, I wouldn't say that. I just try to work hard...
Okay, then.
I will consider that for further tasks.
It doesn't matter what it is.
If you have anything that can finish Master Kim,
I want you to share it with me.
Finish Master Kim with a single blow?
If things go well with that,
I will recommend you for a position at Geodae Hospital.
Just think about it.
We still have plenty of time.
Are you not going to do anything with them?
Just let it go.
It is so obvious...
why they came all the way here.
But what can we do? They say they came to support us.
Are you going to let them stab you in the back again?
You are not alone this time.
The whole staff of Doldam Hospital is at stake.
I know that. You just startled me.
Are you sure you know that?
I'm sure I know that. So please just forget about it.
Do you know that there will be no hospital you can go...
other than here?
Where are you taking that device?
Now that we have a new one, I'm taking it to the storage.
Who is she, by the way?
She will be working here for a while.
Her name is Woo Yeon Hwa.
Hello.
Hello, it's nice to meet you. I'm Yoon Seo Jung.
Where is the new device?
- It's in the hybrid room. - Okay.
She is my second favorite person at the hospital after Ms. Oh.
I see.
Look at the ultrasound device.
Is this hospital beyond the space and time?
It's not the Stone Age now.
I just saw the old device earlier today.
- This is so cool. - Is it a relic of the past or what?
Chest portable device? Are you here, too?
It's so nice to see you again.
I'm so happy.
It is a miracle that you could actually save a life in here.
What is that?
It's an external cooling device.
Therapeutic hypothermia is popular these days.
It became famous after they used it for a president of a conglomerate.
Hello, you are new. It's nice to meet you.
Let me ask you a question.
Why have you been stuck in this hospital for the past five years?
Beautiful mountains, clean water, and fresh air.
- Hey. - And Master Kim.
Have you heard of the name? He is a legendary surgeon.
He was once a legendary surgeon.
He is still a legendary surgeon.
I know things will get tough, but once you get through it all,
your life will be changed.
No, I don't want a change.
Me being here...
is the worst change that has ever happen to me in my life.
The whole thing is a complete mess. I don't want to go through anything.
Where do you want to put the ECMO?
ECMO?
Do we have a new ECMO? I can't believe this.
It's so pretty.
Look at that.
She's dancing.
- I feel like crying. - Please put it here.
This is so good.
- Are you happy? - Aren't you happy?
Where should I put this?
Hello? This is Master Kim speaking.
Did you...
receive the devices?
Yes, I received them all.
My work is done here.
If you try to mess with me again,
I won't let you get away with it.
So,
when will you schedule the surgery?
I will give you a call as soon as we are ready.
Just make it quick.
Give me a call.
He's such a jerk.
He's never scared of me.
That's why you like him.
This is jujube tea.
Jujube tea?
He killed someone.
And it was a student of his.
In a word,
he's a psychopath.
I'm more used to using a knife.
Are you really a doctor?
How many patients have you killed?
(On Your Way)
Hello, this is Doldam Hospital.
Yes. Yes, okay.
We need to perform a CPR on a patient in three minutes.
Master Kim.
- What happened? - It's a stab wound.
He was lying in front of my restaurant.
Do Il, are you okay?
This is his blood. I'm fine.
- Dr. Yoon, scissors. - Okay.
We should call the police first.
- Vital signs? - It's 100 over 70 and 130 beats.
Set up IV lines and execute a full drop.
These three wounds on his right side aren't too deep.
But these two on his left are punctured.
Check for hemoperitoneum with a sonogram.
This is our new equipment.
Doctor, his saturation is at 88 percent.
Hey, Dr. Geodae. Perform an intubation.
Me?
Okay.
You're too slow!
Yes, Doctor.
It's done.
His blood pressure is at 80 over 40.
Okay.
Get two packs of emergency red blood cells.
Get rapid infusion system ready.
It's here.
We have a new portable chest X-ray.
- Should I get it ready? - No, we need to take a sonogram.
If his blood pressure rises above 100,
- take a CT as well. - Okay.
We need the portable chest X-ray.
Yes.
We have an emergency patient.
Let's move him. In 1, 2, 3.
Dr. Yoon, cover up his wound,
and figure out his personal information.
Call the general surgeons.
- Both Dong Joo and the new guy. - Okay.
- Hey, Dr. Geodae. - Yes.
- Both of you can follow me. - Yes.
I need a dressing set...
- and a six-inch eb. - Okay.
Also, can you see if he has a wallet...
- and a phone? - Okay.
Can anyone call the general surgeons for me?
- Call both Dr. Kang and Dr. Do. - I will.
I will get them.
She's very quick.
Yes, and she's nice.
- You shocked me. - I'm sorry.
We have an emergency patient.
An emergency patient?
Hello, Dr. Kang.
This hospital is worse than I thought.
How can he think of doing a surgery for the chairman here?
So,
have you made your decision?
Which side will you take?
Me or Boo Yong Joo?
Hello, Dr. Do.
Are you all settled in?
What about the office? Is it okay?
It's fine.
I knew it.
It's just fine.
What can we do? We should do our job as long as we are here.
Let's get to work.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
Are you still taking sides?
Then what are you doing here?
I haven't got any connections or families,
but your father is the president.
How did you end up here?
I did not end up here. I'm just here for an experience.
I can go back whenever I wish.
Unlike you.
Apart from your father,
is there anything that's better than me?
If you have anything, show me.
Prove yourself.
For once.
Go and win against Dong Joo just once.
You're awful.
I'm just awful, but you're awful and terrible.
Why?
Do you want to hit me?
You're not even worth it.
It'll only hurt my hand.
You don't need to save your hand. You're bad at surgeries.
Excuse me.
You are wanted at the emergency room.
Your lips are bleeding.
Excuse me.
Aren't you a general surgeon?
Master Kim wanted you there, too.
Ventricular fibrillation. Compression.
Give me 200J.
- We're ready. - Move away.
Shock.
Compression.
Let's perform intubation.
Tube, please.
Okay.
Stethoscope.
Move away.
Okay.
Give him 1mm of epinephrine every 3 minutes.
Also, squeeze an ambu bag every 6 seconds.
Okay.
Two minutes passed.
Switch hands and check his pulse.
Yes.
No pulse, he's in PEA.
You, compression.
When was he reported?
It was 3:48pm.
He was at a bus stop, and he suddenly collapsed.
Someone called the 911,
and the witness was performing a CPR on him.
What was his initial treatment?
We performed ventricular fibrillation on him twice.
That's 17 minutes before he arrived here.
Do you have his information?
He had an ID, so we talked to his wife.
She's on her way here.
Okay. Thank you.
Dr. Kim, he has another wound on his back.
- Hey, Dr. Geodae. - Yes, Dr. Geodae here.
Continue to perform compression until he comes back.
- Don't give up. - Okay.
Let's check his pulse.
He's still in asystole.
My gosh.
It looks like it's somewhere in the thoracolumbar junction.
I felt something hard inside.
I think this is a knife blade.
It must have broke when he was stabbed.
Where are the surgeons?
They are so slow.
Drag them if you have to.
Yes, Master Kim.
Why are you so late?
- What's his case? - He's a stabbed patient.
He was stabbed five times in his stomach,
and there is a knife blade stuck in the thoracolumbar junction.
What about nerve injuries?
Both of his lower motors do not seem well.
What's wrong with your lips?
- What about his stomach? - He has two bowel perforations.
We can't see if it's his small bowel or large bowel through the CT.
His sonogram showed that the wounds are close to his vessels.
It's toward his vessels as well.
- Did you fight with someone? - I'm not a kid.
What's with him?
Is he sulking because of that?
Yes, Dr. Song.
We need you in the emergency room.
- Dad! - Honey!
- Honey! - May I help you?
We got the call saying my dad collapsed at a bus stop.
They said he was transferred to Doldam Hospital.
Our doctors are treating him right now.
Please wait over there.
How could this happen?
- My goodness. - Don't cry, Mom.
Checking heart rhythm.
He has a pulse. It's an ROSC.
The blood pressure is between 60 to 90.
Nice.
- He needs saline, too. - What?
Right. I need saline.
- That's the one. - Right.
It's not looking good.
Dr. Kang is here.
Why did you come alone? Where's the other guy?
The other guy? Who?
Medical team of general surgery from Geodae Hospital came down here.
I wasn't expecting that from President Do.
I asked you where the other guy is. We paged you both.
I don't really know where he is.
I'm here.
He's a John Doe.
He has five wounds in his abdomen.
The three on his right are light wounds, but the other ones aren't.
He has perforated bowel.
Blade of the knife broke...
in the right side of his abdomen.
Will this call for combine operation?
Yes.
- Where should we start? - With his abdomen.
He might not be able to walk again,
but at least he won't die.
Okay.
I'll go prepare for a different operation, then.
Hold on.
I just got the call.
Are you going to operate on a John Doe patient?
My goodness.
His injuries are too dangerous to be operated here.
Don't waste your time on him.
I suggest you transfer him to a bigger hospital.
It doesn't matter how big or small a hospital is.
It's the surgeon who treats the patient.
I'm just worried that it might go wrong.
What will happen if we operate without the guardian's consent...
and the operation doesn't go well?
It's not like we can ask you to take...
full responsibility and resign.
Excuse me.
According to the Emergency Medical Service Act,
in case the emergency patient is not capable of making decisions...
and when there isn't a guardian to ask for consent,
an exception is made to ask for consent.
I'm just saying.
Hey. Did you hear that?
It's the law.
What should we do?
Move him to the operating room. Can you set the place up?
Okay.
- Do In Beom, was it? - Yes.
You will perform the surgery. Dr. Kang is the assistant.
Why am I the assistant?
What are you saying?
Are you not up for it? Suit yourself, then.
Can I fill in his spot?
You should help them treat the cardiac arrest patient.
I'll treat the spine. That will be all.
Did you see that?
He's like that.
The smell of human blood makes him go crazy.
Like a mad man.
Let's move the patient, Mr. Park.
Yes, Doctor.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Hey. Be careful.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing? Go after Master Kim.
I can take care of my own business. I'm not a child, you know.
You're one to hold grudges.
Are men all like that, Mr. Park?
I'm not sure.
Gosh.
Excuse me.
Watch where you're going.
Are you blind or something?
Gosh.
It's waterproofed. Bandage up your hand.
You can't go in the operating room with an open wound.
Did I do something wrong to deserve this?
I won't know if you don't tell me.
What don't you like about me?
Your very existence.
Satisfied?
Hold on.
Why would you say that?
Did I do something wrong?
- Let go of me. - Tell me.
Why don't you like my very existence?
Are you asking because you don't know?
Is there something I should be aware of?
Are you playing innocent or just plain rude?
What are you talking about?
I understand.
Even when your dad is the president of Geodae Hospital,
you won't be comfortable with other people knowing...
that you're born out of wedlock, right?
What?
It's okay. I understand.
I'll pretend to understand.
So stop bothering me from now on.
Born out of wedlock?
Who?
Me?
What?
Does he think...
Don't use your fist when you get in a fight in the future.
If you really feel like beating someone up, just kick him.
Or you could just take the beating.
Why me?
What are you talking about?
You had me come down here.
And now you're asking me to perform a surgery.
Why? Do you think I'm trying to...
use you to get back at your father?
Aren't you?
Stop your nonsense and focus on the operation.
Where's Dr. Kang? Why isn't he here?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Page Dr. Kang again.
- Okay. - There's no need.
I'll be the assistant today.
Master Kim as an assistant?
Master Kim.
He's here. Dr. Kang.
Sorry I'm late.
Get out of here. We don't need you here.
- Master Kim. - I said we don't need you here.
Let's get started.
- Master Kim. - Show me what you've got.
Let's see how good you are.
Commencing operation.
Scalpel.
Bovie.
Focus.
Okay.
His heart is back,
but I don't think he will wake up.
Even if he does, he won't be able to perform normally.
- What about his brain? - There is no hypoxic damage.
If his brain is fine,
- shouldn't you try TTM? - TTM?
That's too expensive. It won't be easy.
I'll talk to his wife.
What?
- Targeted temperature management? - Yes.
If one's heart stops for whatever reason,
there is a high chance it will stop again within 24 hours.
So we performed a blood test and a brain CT scan...
to find out why it stopped.
A brain CT scan?
Isn't that expensive?
Mom, what are you saying?
These are the necessary procedures.
And the result showed...
he didn't have much brain damage.
There is something...
called targeted temperature management.
We keep the patient's body temperature lower than normal...
to prevent further brain damage.
Will he wake up if we do this treatment?
There is no guarantee.
But to speak with numbers,
when someone's heart stops outside of a hospital,
only 4 out of 100 survive.
Among them,
only 1 out of the 100 can carry on...
a normal life.
My goodness.
What if we do this treatment?
The chances are twice as high.
We'll do it.
The problem is...
the cost.
How much does it cost?
The cost of only the materials are 1,600 dollars.
We are actually very poor.
We are eligible for medical care type one.
But the materials of this treatment aren't approved by the medical care.
You won't be covered for these.
You have to pay this.
What do we do?
What are we going to do?
Please perform the treatment.
- Seon Hwa, please. - Mom, don't worry.
I'll find that money.
We probably have a lot to pay as of now.
Mom.
Dad became like this after giving his everything for us.
How sad will his life be if we can't do this for him?
Okay.
Doctor, please do your best.
Please save him.
We'll do our best.
No.
That treatment is not insured.
Exactly.
Why is this important treatment still uninsured?
This isn't a plastic surgery.
I don't know what they do in those high offices,
but no.
We're spending money on a patient with no hope.
What if he doesn't wake up?
His chances are only 8 to 100.
If the chances are...
as low as 1 to 100, should we try everything?
What if it doesn't work?
What will you do about his family's financial strain?
What if they say that they can't pay?
What will you do about the damages to the hospital?
That's not for me to worry about. That's for those high officers.
We treat patients,
and people in high offices fix this world.
If you don't like what they do,
you should one of them to fix this broken world.
A doctor doesn't have the time for that.
Someone like you should step up, Mr. Jang.
I'm Manager Jang, not Mr. Jang, Dr. Yoon.
I've been promoted as a manger as of today.
Really? Congratulations.
Thank you.
I will treat him, okay?
No way.
Never. Not in this life.
- Mr. Jang. - Manager. I'm Manager Jang.
I'm sorry, Manager Jang.
We have police officers here.
I think they are here for that stabbed patient.
Okay.
No. Understood?
Mr. Jang, I mean, Manager Jang.
Darn it.
- Let's do this. - Are we really doing this?
Do you trust my instinct?
I have a strong feeling that he will wake up. Let's do it.
Will you take the responsibility if something goes wrong?
Will you do this?
Thank you very much.
I've just been called.
- Thanks! - Hey.
Seo Jung!
She's a Crazy Whale.
I knew I should have never met you again.
Where is this place?
Who am I?
Darn it.
Miss.
Shouldn't you be taking care of me?
What's his case?
I'm not sure. He's asking us to give him a vitamin IV.
We're already busy enough.
- Is it him? - Yes.
Yes, it's me.
He's in a surgery right now.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of this.
Make some soup, will you?
Make sure you put in beef.
Okay.
Sir, how are you doing?
Bad.
Why?
You look okay.
You can go home.
Be quiet.
Give me some IV.
Don't you have them with vitamin A, B, C, D, E, F, and G?
Come on, get them on me.
Let me fill up on my vitamins.
If you want nutritional IV, go to the outpatient clinic.
You are awfully talkative.
Just put me on IV if you don't want to die.
You're the one who should leave while I'm still nice.
If you don't, I'm calling the police.
Do you want them here?
- Do you really want to die? - No way.
I'd like to live a long life.
- Mr. Goo. - Yes.
My gosh.
He's leaving. Help him.
Who is this Mr. Goo?
Why are you here?
Is the surgery over?
- I was kicked out. - Kicked out? Who kicked you out?
Who would kick me out of the operating room?
Hey.
You shouldn't walk out like this. You should have stayed.
Let me see that.
Master Kim always yells and embarrasses everyone.
I thought you would be used to him by now.
That kind of a surgery is so rare.
It would've helped you if you stuck around...
to just watch what he does. Isn't that right?
Go out with me, Seo Jung.
What are you saying?
I'll forget about...
how you called me as a kid and a teenager.
Go out with me.
You can't speak to me like this.
You're very bold.
Is that a no?
Forget about it.
Go back to the operating room...
and tell him that you are sorry no matter what he says.
Tell him that you'll do your best...
even if all you do is assisting him.
The third time's a charm.
I'll ask you out two more times.
So think about it.
You did not listen to anything I said, did you?
Goodbye, then.
One of them is asking me out all the time,
and the other one is caught up in a family affair.
My life became so tiring.
Things got very annoying thanks to that weird girl.
What a witch.
The fine day will come
Another glory day
Hey, Sir.
Yes?
Do you have a lighter?
I don't smoke.
It's a non-smoking area.
That doctor is such a jerk.
Where is Mr. Jang?
He stepped out with the police officers.
- The police were here? - Yes.
The patient who was stabbed with a knife. Remember?
They assume that he got involved with gangsters.
Are you blind or something?
He's a stabbed patient.
He was stabbed five times in his stomach,
and there is a knife blade stuck in the thoracolumbar junction.
The fine day will come, another glory day
Where are Mr. Jang and the police officers?
They're at the emergency room.
Where on earth are they?
Dr. Kang, what are you doing here?
Mr. Jang.
As of today, I'm the manager. I've been promoted.
Where are the police officers?
What? They already left.
Do you have something to tell them?
I think a gangster came into our hospital.
A gangster?
Do you remember the stabbed patient?
The police said he might be involved with gangsters.
- Yes. So what? - Just before, I saw a man...
with something like a sickle wrapped in papers in the bathroom.
Ask the police to come back, and tell all the staff members.
I'll go to the operating room.
- Okay. - Okay.
Hello? Is this the police? I'm calling from Doldam Hospital.
Dr. Song, it's me again.
It seems like a lot happen in this hospital.
They got involved with gangsters this time.
(Restricted Area, Operating Room)
Whom are you looking for?
Where is Dr. Yoon?
She's in the hybrid room with a patient.
I see.
I think a suspicious man is in our hospital now.
Please protect everyone in the emergency room.
Okay. Mr. Jang... I mean, Manager Jang already told me.
- Please don't worry. - Thank you.
- I'm counting on you. - Okay.
Hurry up and find the man.
Have you seen a man with a weapon?
Please stay calm.
Come out.
Come in. Hurry.
Search the room in every corner.
I think it's the small bowel.
Irrigation.
Suction.
Pad.
Bring five more packed RBCs.
Yes, Doctor.
- How is his condition? - Good so far.
I found the bleeding focus.
Hemostatic forceps.
Forceps to tie it.
Dr. Kang.
What are you doing here?
I told you to leave. Why did you come back?
We have an emergency.
Emergency? What do you mean?
I assume that the gangster who hurt this patient is in our hospital.
Why?
Are you afraid that gangster might barge in here?
You never know.
- We should stay alert... - Forget it. Get out of here now!
I'll stay.
What? Hey.
Even if the gangster comes in here,
you wouldn't be of much help.
So just stop bothering me and get out of here.
I'll stay here.
Go back and tell hi that you are sorry no matter what he says.
What did I do so wrong?
I was late only for a few minutes. Is it that wrong?
You were late,
and you were even preoccupied when you came in here.
I wasn't preoccupied.
What were you thinking after I told you to assist Dr. Do?
You were frustrated and upset. You didn't want to do that.
"Should I do this or not?"
That was all you thought about.
Listen. This isn't your playground.
Whether you two fight or whatever, leave it outside.
Once you entered this room,
you should've cleared your mind and focused on the patient.
How dare you throw a tantrum...
when you started an operation without clear mind?
Do you think you can do your best when you're preoccupied?
You don't deserve to be in here and even to breathe.
Get lost.
I stopped the bleeding.
I'll conduct a segmental resection,
and then end-to-end anastomosis.
I'll close it up as soon as possible and move on to the spine.
Okay.
Babcock Forceps.
I hope he'll get through this.
- Let me ask you something. - What is it?
You could've ordered the targeted temperature management.
Why did you try to convince me?
It's because he's your patient.
No. I think there's some other reason.
What is it? Tell me.
There's no other reason.
Why would there be?
- I'll go drink some water. - Why all of a sudden?
She seems so suspicious.
Doesn't she?
She says she's in charge of ER and Cardio,
but she behaves passively like an intern.
As I thought, something is wrong.
Don't you agree?
I don't know.
How could I say that I'm working as an orderly?
I can never say that.
(Operating Room)
(In Operation)
I wish I was in there.
Where did he hide? Why can't we find him?
- Have you found him? - No, we haven't.
Did you search thoroughly?
Don't you think Dr. Kang was mistaken?
Do you think so? Gosh.
Excuse me.
Are you still here?
He's in there, right?
- Excuse me? - The guy stabbed with a knife.
He's undergoing a surgery in this room, right?
Am I right?
I'll be done after one more stitch.
We'll switch the positions once he's done.
Dr. Nam, how's he doing?
He's better since Dr. Do stopped the bleeding.
- Prone position? - Yes, please.
Would he be okay with the pressure on his abdomen?
I think he'll be okay if we raise his pelvis a little.
- Cut. - Cutting.
- I'm done. - Okay. Let's switch the positions.
Hey. Hey.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Seo Jung.
This is ridiculous.
Hey.
How dare you come in here looking like that?
I'm sorry, Doctor.
It's not that I wanted to come in here.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Get in there slowly.
Walk slowly.
You might get a cut on your neck.
You.
Step back. Now.
Seo Jung, are you all right?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Who are you and why are you doing this in the operating room?
Who is the leader?
Who gives orders in this operating room?
That's me.
What's the matter?
Stop the operation right now.
If you don't stop it right now,
I will kill this woman.
Get off the patient right now.
No!
(Dr. Romantic)
I don't want to give up on the operation.
Again, in the worst-case scenario, you might get disqualified.
Just let them deal with me.
Don't drag innocent people into this like a coward.
Dr. Boo Yong Joo is disqualified from any medical practice as of now.
The technical term for this is bluffing.
In fancier words,
it is romantic ideals.