Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[EPISODE 9]
You're downstairs already?
I heard that you were being interrogated.
I'm sure that it didn't end so soon.
How dare you try to do the chairman's
surgery in your lowly position?
Look at the mess you've made.
Looks like you'll lose another precious
disciple because of your stubbornness.
Oh my.
Why, you little...
Doctor!
You have a guest.
A guest?
Teacher Kim!
Hey, there. I'm here.
I heard you told me to
admit myself to the hospital.
I contacted the chairman with
the news just as you told me to, sir.
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry up and escort me to my room.
Who told you to do something
stupid like this, you bastard?
I'm sorry, Chairman.
I think that there's been a mistake here.
We're not ready to
accommodate you here yet.
What?
- Teacher Kim.
- You've come such a long way.
I'm sorry to have to
send you back like this.
We'll admit you as soon
as we're ready...
What are you doing right now?
I'm sure I told you that
you're forbidden from working.
Forbidden from working?
Hey... hey.
I cannot allow you to treat any patients
until we're done with our investigation.
And if you disobey us, you could
suffer an even worse punishment.
Who the hell are you punks?
What do you mean,
he's forbidden from working?
Says whom?
I'll explain, Chairman.
- What happened is...
- Look here, Teacher Kim.
You explain this.
Tell me what's going on here, exactly.
And who are those punks?
The hospital is under
investigation right now, Chairman.
Hey, hey, hey, Kang Dong Joo!
We have no idea why Geosan sent
investigators down here to us
and we have no idea why they're
putting pressure on us, either.
Hey. Shut your mouth.
Why should I shut my mouth?
We're the ones being treated unfairly
when we didn't do anything wrong.
Kang Dong Joo!
Chairman.
You're the Chairman of the Geosan
University Hospital Foundation, correct?
Could you possibly file
a complaint with Geosan
for pressuring Doldam Hospital
like this for no reason?
Manager Joo.
Yes, Chairman?
- Call Director Do, now.
- Chairman.
Tell him to come down here now and
explain this situation to me in person.
Right now!
Yes, sir.
Tell me what I did wrong.
Why did you call the chairman here?
I couldn't just sit and watch while
Seo Jung was being treated unfairly.
And I figured that we needed someone
to resolve this situation for us.
Do you really think that Chairman Shin
will be the one to resolve this?
To be honest, the only one who can
pressure Director Do is the chairman.
Furthermore,
Chairman Shin is on your side.
If I'd known that you
were such an idiot before...
But you know, you really are ignorant
to the ways of this world, aren't you?
You're really naive, huh?
What?
What? Chairman Shin has summoned me?
Yes, but...
you needn't put yourself
through the trouble, sir.
I'll just watch over the situation
and do as I deem fit, sir.
No, there's no need.
Pardon?
What do you mean by that, sir?
Our opponents just gave us a
light jab to see how we'd respond
but you took that as an opportunity,
and thus escalated the situation.
I was actually wondering how that
old fart would find out about this.
Good. They've set the
stage for us themselves.
All I have to do now is go
and report the facts to him.
Well, this might actually end up
being a good thing for you.
You'll score some points with
Director Do, at the very least.
Even though Yoon Seo Jung is screwed.
Aren't you being a bit too harsh, sir?
What do you mean, she's screwed?
You have no idea what kind of
person Director Do really is, do you?
He'd be willing to do anything and
everything to get what he wants.
And Chairman Shin is someone who made
a guy like him the hospital's director
and sits idly by while
reaping the benefits from that.
He's on my side?
Give me a break.
He doesn't need me.
He needs my operation.
That's all he cares about!
You fool.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
We received word that
Director Do Yoon Wan is on his way here.
What are you planning to do?
I'll just have to bear it.
And if worst comes to worst,
I'll have to leave.
Well, there's not exactly
anything that I can do for you...
but have this when
your blood sugar gets low.
How did you come to know Bu Yong Joo?
Were you introduced
to him by someone, or...
He saved me. Twice.
Can you be a bit more specific?
One time, he saved me while
I was passed out in the mountains.
And one time, he treated my wrist
when it had almost lost functionality.
That's how he saved me twice.
Wait, no.
He saved me one other time, too.
I survived this time around
because of him, too.
So he's saved me three times now, then.
Do you still have random moments
in which you feel like you wish to die?
I'm asking you if you still get
sudden urges to commit suicide.
An age in which people
ignore others' pain.
People who don't care about others' pain
as long as they can get what they want.
People who don't care about such things,
as long as they can maintain authority,
And...
I asked you if you still
have any suicidal urges.
It's all your fault.
It's all because of you that I died.
People who can't even get a good
look at the nature of their own pain.
I'm sorry.
Because all of them justify themselves,
saying that they didn't have time
to worry for others when they had
their own situation to deal with.
[EPISODE 9: THE LIMITS OF GOODNESS]
It's bad enough that those inspectors
barged in here so early in the morning
but now the Chairman of the Foundation
and Director Do are involved, too.
What in the world is going on?
Maybe that Chairman Shin guy
called Director Do to yell at him?
Who knows?
We even heard that Teacher Kim isn't
allowed to work for the time being.
I heard that this all happened
because of Doctor Yoon Seo Jung.
Return to your positions
and get back to work!
Don't make things worse when
the situation is already bad. Got it?
- Yes, ma'am.
There's no need to worry.
All you need to do is act as you did
before, as if nothing happened.
You know that, right?
Why do you keep doing
these unnecessary things?
I told you to send equipment here,
not some damned inspectors.
Please don't misunderstand
my intentions, Chairman.
I've even sent important people
from Geosan down here to obey you.
- However...
- Yeah?
I heard that things at this hospital
are a bit messier than we'd realized.
Go on.
They must have managed this place poorly
if a person broke into the OR and
held someone hostage with a sickle.
That's not all.
They even left that criminal alone
with a patient who had been operated on.
And because Teacher Kim was the one
to handle the situation, nobody was hurt.
And they performed an expensive treatment
on a patient who cannot pay for it.
Saving the patient is our priority.
The hospital bill can be
taken care of after that, Director Do!
And how are you going
to explain the fact
that the doctor who ordered
the treatment has PTSD?
PT what? What's that?
It refers to post-traumatic
stress disorder, sir.
Doctor Yoon Seo Jung made
a full recovery two years ago.
I heard that there was a drug overdose
incident involving her recently.
And Director Yeo and Bu Yong Joo
were both aware of that.
Yet, they were keeping it hidden.
As such, these two have
been negligent of their duty.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Stop beating around the bush
and get to the point.
What is it that you truly wish to say?
I can't just sit by and watch
as these abnormalities occur
at this poor excuse of a hospital.
That's what I truly wish to say.
You mustn't entrust such an
important thing as your surgery
to this sorry excuse
of a hospital, Chairman.
Please reconsider entrusting
your surgery to Bu Yong Joo, sir.
So that's what it is.
You caused an uproar just to stop
Teacher Kim from performing the surgery?
Watch your words, Director Yeo!
Oh, whatever. That's enough.
Chairman.
This is my surgery, and I've already
made up my mind regarding this.
So stop arguing about it, already.
I'll have things proceed as originally
planned, so just be aware of that.
And let's end things here by firing
that doctor who caused all this trouble.
Now stop causing such a
ruckus at this hospital.
We can't, Chairman!
Doctor Yoon Seo Jung is...
Let's just end things there.
Okay, Director Yeo?
Oh, wow.
You really don't get what's
going on here, do you, Chairman?
What did you just say? Hey.
The one Director Do
really wants to fire is me.
That's what he really wants.
Isn't that right, Director Do?
At the very least
you must take responsibility for
letting a PTSD patient treat people.
Oh, you got the neuropsychiatrist's
clinical notes already?
PTSD, huh?
Or did you already decide the results
of her evaluation from the start
and just have her
interviewed as a formality?
You won't be able to avoid shouldering
your part of the blame, either.
The duty of ER doctors is to save
dying people, no matter what it takes.
Asking them why they used an
expensive treatment on a patient
is the same thing as asking why someone
falling from a plane used a parachute.
So? Do you even know how much
the hospital will suffer in losses?
Stop giving a doctor
lessons in economics.
You can't get by nowadays
by merely being a skilled doctor.
A doctor can only survive
if his hospital does.
Wow, you say these things and yet
you call yourself a hospital director?
No, the order is all messed up there.
The patient needs to survive
for the hospital to survive.
Those are the basic
principles of being a doctor!
Oh, really?
I didn't realize that you valued
fundamentals and principles so much.
Fine, then.
Let's do things that way.
We'll maintain our hospital's principles
and continue with the investigation.
And we'll issue proper punishments
for employing a doctor with PTSD
after the official diagnosis comes out,
as per our principles.
Look here, Director Do.
As the one in charge of Geosan Hospital
and in an attempt to rectify this wrong
I'll do what I must to defend our
principles until the very end, Chairman.
Have you finished your
conversation, Director?
Make sure you get them good this time.
No matter how long this may take.
Yes, sir.
What is it that you wanted to say?
I'm sorry for continuing
to disappoint you.
The reason I became a doctor
was because I wanted to be
acknowledged by you, above all else.
Because you saw potential in me
and made me want to become a doctor.
And yet, you went ahead
and backstabbed me instead.
Just let him have this one, Teacher Kim.
I understand that you
treasure your disciple
but you can't have this hospital
shut down just because of her.
What should we do?
I really don't see a way
out of this one, Teacher Kim.
Why did it have to be
Bu Yong Joo, of all people?
Why were you hiding behind
someone like him, of all people?
There was an incident.
And he helped me through that.
And did he tell you to hide
the fact that you have PTSD?
I received treatment for three years
and thought I made a full recovery.
I'm asking you what the
hell he told you to do!
Teacher Kim didn't do anything wrong.
It's all my fault that the
situation got this out of hand.
It's because I'm lacking and incompetent.
So... if someone needs to
take responsibility, I'll do it.
I...
will quit working here.
How unfortunate.
At the very least, I thought
of you as my own daughter.
I guess you never saw me
as a parent, though.
If you had really needed help,
you should've come and sought me out.
Director.
Regarding Doldam Hospital, I'm
going to go by the book to resolve this.
And as for you...
you're dead to me now.
Are you looking for something, sir?
Do you want me to help you?
No, it's fine.
Um... you haven't seen
Senior Seo Jung, have you?
Senior Seo Jung?
I haven't seen her since she
dropped by the ER a little while ago.
Oh... really?
All right.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Do you want me to call you
if I do end up seeing her?
Um, yes, could you? Thank you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Excuse me, have you seen
Doctor Yoon Seo Jung?
No, I haven't.
Oh, really?
Has his condition
improved at all, Doctor?
No, we'll have to keep
monitoring his progress for now.
How much longer does
he have to remain like this?
It almost feels like
I'm clinging to false hope.
The fees for this treatment and for
the ICU are overwhelming enough.
I feel like we'll only end up
being a burden to our kids.
I'm sure that things must be hard,
but please don't give up until the end.
And continue talking to the patient
and telling him pleasant things.
Am I really doing
the right thing right now?
Did Doctor Yoon Seo Jung
come by here, by any chance?
It seemed that she
stopped by the ICU for a bit.
I'm not sure if she's
still there, though.
Are we ever making the right
decision in front of our patients
while they teeter
between life and death?
Yoon Seo Jung!
What brings you here?
Am I someone who is perfectly prepared to
take responsibility for someone's life?
What do you mean, you don't see
Yoon Seo Jung around anywhere?
We looked everywhere for her today,
but we can't find her anywhere.
She won't pick up her phone, either.
I think she heard about you being
suspended from duty back in the ER.
- Oh, Teacher Kim.
- Yeah?
Yoon Seo Jung stopped by my
restaurant not too long ago
and wanted me to give you this.
[LETTER OF RESIGNATION]
A letter of resignation?
When did she give this to you?
About 10 minutes ago.
[TEACHER KIM]
Where are you headed?
The caller you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
She's not picking up?
Of course she wouldn't.
If she even wrote a letter of resignation
she's really made up her mind about this.
Go and get her back here.
How would he know where to look?
Regardless of that,
we have to start searching first.
But...
bring her back by the end of today.
If you can't bring her back
by the end of today
I really will accept this letter.
You got that?
Oh, Doctor Kang Dong Joo!
Good thing I ran into you.
- Your car just got here, so...
- That's great.
- Well, actually...
- I'm busy right now.
Let's talk later!
That's... a new car.
We're here.
Where are you planning to go?
I don't know.
I did come all the way out here,
but I feel a bit lost now.
Maybe I should take this
chance and go to Seoul?
Or maybe I should go to the East Sea
and enjoy the oceanside?
You have nowhere else to go?
No, I don't.
And there's nobody
for you to meet up with?
No, no one.
What a hard life you have.
I know, right?
It seems bad from the surface, but it's
actually a lot worse than you'd think.
Can you not say things
like that so nonchalantly?
It seems like you're
made of steel or something.
Isn't it better to seem that way
than to seem pitiful?
Well, if you're going
to Seoul, I'll drive you.
Aren't you going to the hospital?
- I'm taking my monthly day off.
- Your monthly day off?
His monthly day off?
Doctor Do In Bum is taking the day off?
Yes, that's what he said.
Then call Kang Dong Joo
and tell him to take over.
Doctor Kang was on duty last night
so he's not working today.
Call Teacher Kim, then!
Did you forget?
Teacher Kim was ordered to
be off duty as of today.
Wait, then I'm the only general
surgeon at this hospital now?
Yes.
Looks like things ended up
this way somehow.
Doctor Jung!
Please come here.
- Ow, it hurts!
- Wait just a bit, ma'am.
- Ow!
- Doctor, over here, too!
The caller you are trying
to reach is unavailable...
Seo Jung?
Hey, how would I know?
I just saw her for the
first time in five years!
Hey, Doctor Jung!
Are you done treating the patient
with the right lower quadrant pain?
Hey, I'm busy with a patient.
Talk to you later!
I'll check right now!
[ASSHOLE KANG]
Do In Bum.
It's me, Kang Dong Joo.
Go ahead. What do you want?
You said that you knew
Senior Seo Jung from before, right?
I have to find her right now.
Do you know where she might have gone?
She's next to me right now.
You're on speakerphone.
Say what you need to say.
Where are you right now?
We're on our way to Seoul.
Turn your car around right now
and come back to the hospital.
That's going to be a bit difficult.
I'm already on the highway.
Are you listening, Senior?
I know it's hard for you right now.
I know that, but... come on.
A letter of resignation?
You wrote a letter of resignation?
Turn the car around right now.
Come back, Senior.
Senior!
Hey, why did you tell him
that I was with you?
Well, you didn't tell me not to.
And why did you tell him that
we're heading to Seoul?
Well, he asked me where I was.
Sheesh.
Why did you write a
letter of resignation?
None of your business.
Just drive properly.
Wow, you sure are
coming on strong, Big Sis.
I told you, I'm not your older sister!
Seoul? Where in Seoul?
I don't know the details.
I'm just following them there for now.
Hey, aren't you a bit too tight on
time to drive to and from Seoul?
But still, I have to do as much as I can.
All right, then. But you know,
things are kind of crazy back here, too.
We all forgot because of Director Do,
but today is Friday.
What are you doing? I told you to
bring a suture set and lidocaine here!
It's been barely 10 seconds
since you asked me to do that.
Ugh, seriously. I'm not someone
to be treating people like this!
You should take off your necktie.
You concern yourself with
doctors' neckties now, too?
Nurse Park!
Whoa, whoa! Are you okay?
Please lie down.
Do you think that it may
be something you ate, ma'am?
I had cold rice and soup this morning.
But I guess I ate it really fast.
My insides are killing me.
And you didn't have any diarrhea?
My stomach is rumbling,
but I haven't had diarrhea yet.
I just vomited a couple of times.
Are you feeling pain anywhere else?
My chest, a little.
It may be due to esophageal
damage from vomiting a lot.
It seems to be just stomach pain for now,
so we'll give you an injection.
Give this patient some metoclopramide
via IV, and hydrate her.
Yes, sir.
It's okay. I can do it.
I'll get her cleaned up.
You hurry and give her the injection.
Thank you, Ms. Yeon Hwa.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What are you doing?
What? Oh, I thought there
was something on her neck.
We have an emergency patient
who was in a traffic accident!
She's bleeding from her right calf,
and her BP is 90/60.
And it's falling quickly!
Damn it, I'm going to go crazy!
Yes, this is Doldam Hospital's ER.
Yes. Yes, I understand.
A person who attempted suicide
will be here in five minutes.
They jumped off the Yeonggye Bridge.
What?
Boerhaave... Boerhaave...
Ms. Woo Yeon Hwa?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
You're not working today?
Well, the folks from Geosan
told me not to.
You do know that today is Friday, right?
We have an ER specialist
from Geosan here now, too.
And even the chief of the surgical
department is down here now.
So why are you so worried?
Those people are doctors, too.
It's a patient who attempted suicide!
He fell off a bridge!
Doctor! Please come over here!
You call yourself a
board-certified ER doctor?
Do your job properly!
Oh, yes. Do you think that Doctor
Yoon Seo Jung will come back?
Well, the groundwork has
been laid out already, but...
I'm so happy!
Don't you feel an endorphin rush
just from looking at this?
Oh, hello there.
Are you serious? You're
eating pizza with a fork and knife?
Come on, you're being
rude to the pizza!
You're supposed to hold
pizza in your hand, like this.
And give it a big old bite!
Got it?
You're a mama's boy, aren't you?
You've never just rolled in
the dirt to have a good time
or disobeyed your parents, have you?
My gosh, "disobedience"? What's that?
Is it something you can eat?
Were you always this chatty?
Me?
No.
I tend to be more quiet and stoic.
Who's the one who's been talking
all by herself for all this time, then?
Well, that's because you
chose not to say anything.
I didn't want there to be
an awkward silence.
I'm just being considerate to you,
to help you avoid feeling awkward.
Are you sure it's not
because you feel uneasy?
Um, why would I feel uneasy?
Aren't you worried, now that you've left
after writing a resignation letter?
And I bet that you're concerned
that Kang Dong Joo called, too.
And the fact that you're here with
me now concerns you a bit too, right?
And you're just saying anything that
comes to mind so I don't find out.
Whatever. Let's eat.
Yeah, I'm worried to death.
I couldn't even say a proper farewell to
those people, who were like family to me
and I feel so bad about running off
after just leaving a letter behind
that I feel like I'll die.
Why did I do that?
I should've been more persistent
and begged him to spare me.
Why did I go and write
that letter of resignation?
I have nowhere to go
but Doldam Hospital.
I... really have nowhere
else to go but there.
So why did you get scared and run off?
Nothing has been decided yet.
It's not like that psychiatrist's report
has been released yet.
And that patient undergoing TTM
hasn't died yet, either.
Am I wrong?
[DIRECTOR'S SON]
[ASSHOLE KANG]
Hello?
Where are you?
Are you still with Senior?
Give the phone to Senior.
Hurry up and give the phone to her!
I'm afraid I can't do that.
What?
She ran off while we were eating.
She said she suddenly remembered
something that she had to do.
[GEOSAN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL]
Hello, Doctor.
What brings you all the way here?
I came here because of the question
I couldn't answer for you before.
You're a bit too late for that.
I just sent my report to the Director.
I've never had that though.
I've never once thought
that I wanted to die.
Not when my mom died.
Not when I got into the
accident with Doctor Moon.
I...
wanted to live,
even through all that.
That's why I was so miserable.
Because my desire to live was stronger
than the guilt I felt for being the
only one to have survived.
Because, despite all that,
I wanted to live.
And I felt so bad about feeling this way.
Doctor Yoon Seo Jung,
why did you become a doctor?
Because I thought that,
if I became a doctor...
I'd be able to have my existence
acknowledged by someone.
Did you ever have a moment in which
you wanted to quit being a doctor?
Many times.
Every single time...
I had to make a decision
for the sake of the patient.
I see.
Could you give this to Teacher Kim
at Doldam Hospital?
It's my report regarding your
mental health evaluation.
I thought it'd be good for your
hospital to have a copy, too.
Goodbye, then.
This patient's outburst
was due to stress from this past year.
She does not exhibit the DSM-5
defined symptoms related to PTSD.
Furthermore, there is no need
for her to be supervised closely.
This bastard!
I've handed my report over
to Doctor Yoon myself.
Thankfully, I was able to hear the
answer that I wanted to hear from her.
I almost did something
quite immoral as a doctor.
Is Hyun Ji doing well?
You still remember my child's name?
Hey, of course I do.
She was the youngest
patient that I'd ever had.
You know, about Doldam Hospital...
I think I understand why
you're remaining there, Senior.
Please do a proper evaluation of her.
This is a life-and-death issue
for Senior Seo Jung, as a doctor.
Please give her a proper evaluation,
despite what Director Do said.
Doctor Yoon is someone we
must have at Doldam Hospital's ER.
Please don't screw her over
with a false evaluation.
Here.
These are thank you letters that
Doctor Yoon's patients have given her.
I thought you may want to refer
to them as you write your evaluation.
We'll entrust our Doctor Yoon
to you, then, sir.
If you write anything strange,
we'll file an appeal against you.
Please don't do something to make you
ashamed to face her, doctor to doctor.
Well, figures.
They're all such strong-willed people.
Don't lose to Director Do
this time, Senior.
I'll be going, then.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Thank you.
How did you know I'd be here?
I just received word, so I rushed here.
What about you, Senior?
Did you take care of
everything you needed to?
Yeah.
All right, then.
Let's head back now.
You're not coming?
Are you crying?
No!
It's just so cold out here.
You know how if you suddenly
walk into a bright or cold place...
You know how it is. You tear up.
It's just that, is all.
Oh man, it's so cold!
Right?
Huh?
Is this the first snowfall of the season?
It seems that way.
It's pretty.
Yes, it is.
Your hands are cold.
I'll hold your hand
just until it warms up.
That's okay with you, right?
But you know...
isn't today Friday?
Ugh, seriously!
Why did they bring me to the hospital?
Just let me die, already!
Damn it, I want to die!
Hey, how can you say that
when we barely brought you back?
Geez, you're driving me crazy, old man!
I want to draw something, but I haven't
been able to for three years now!
If you can't help me draw again,
just leave me to die!
- Why?
- Hey.
Mr. Go!
Please let go!
This is why I told you to
take off your necktie in the ER.
- Hey, Doctor Jung!
- Yes, Chief?
You take care of him.
I can't do this anymore!
- Please, stop!
- Let go!
Sir! Teacher Kim
is in the ICU right now!
Why? What's he doing in there?
He's... just sitting there.
What should we do?
What do you mean? He's just sitting.
What do you want me to do?
- Hey, Nurse Ji.
- Yes.
Can't you see what's going on here?
Don't you see how chaotic
it is in here right now?
Not a single person is helping me out.
Ma'am. Ma'am?
I'm going to die.
It seems that she has a lot
of gas trapped under her skin.
Miss. Miss, please...
What's the matter?
You can't breathe?
Miss!
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor!
Miss.
Doctor. Doctor!
Ms. Yeon Hwa.
Nurse Park.
Go and get Teacher Kim.
He should be in the ICU.
Go get him now. Quickly.
The Seoul region, Gyeonggi-go region,
and parts of the Gangwon-do region
have seen their first
snowfall of the season.
The snow stopped after an hour or two
but there will be a
chilly breeze starting tonight...
I'm glad that there won't be
a heavy snowfall, at least.
Isn't that right, sir?
You can't be too sure.
Snowfall at night is the worst!
The roads just freeze over, like icicles!
Man, what's with this snow?
It's making it harder for us to work!
Let's just finish this up quickly and go.
Oh man, it's quite slippery!
- Yeah.
- Be careful.
Whoa. Why is the road this slippery?
Cheer up, baby! Cheer up, baby!
Cheer up a little more!
A girl cant give her heart too easily.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
- The ER?
- Yes, Doctor.
There is a problem there.
I think you'll need to
head there for a bit.
This seems like subcutaneous emphysema.
And this young lady did this?
Yes, we believe so.
What were the doctors doing
that they missed this? Huh?
All right. Give this
patient antibiotics first.
Call Chief Song and
contact Doctor Nam, too.
Tell him that we've scheduled
an emergency surgery.
Yes, sir.
Let me die! Let me go!
Hey, you punk!
Keep it down!
I can't diagnose the other patients
properly because of you!
Oh... you're here, sir?
Just receive treatment quietly
and head home, all right?
Yes, sir.
What... what just happened?
This guy is a regular at our ER.
He says that he's a webtoon artist,
but I've never seen his work.
Oh man, what do I do?
Um, I think you'll need to
disinfect this spot here.
Get me a d-set, please!
Ms. Woo Yeon Hwa.
Yes?
Can you explain to me what happened
with that patient out there?
We should be there in 20 minutes.
I wonder what Teacher Kim will say.
Isn't it obvious?
He'll probably say,
"You idiotic punk."
"How are you going to be a doctor
when you're so damn weak-willed?"
"You still call yourself a doctor
after doing this?"
"Wait, no, you're not.
You're just non-clinical personnel!"
"How dare someone like you
just hand me a resignation letter?"
What are you doing?
Oh, that was bad, wasn't it?
Don't ever do that again, Yoon Seo Jung.
Don't disappear
without a word ever again.
Okay?
Look at you,
messing with your senior again.
Don't do it, okay?
Fine, whatever. I'll let you
off the hook just for today.
Huh?
You said that you were Chinese.
Is that right?
Yes.
Are you a medical student?
Ms. Yeon Hwa,
we're not trying to scold you.
We just want to know the truth.
You must answer our questions honestly.
Doctor, Chief Song
won't pick up our calls.
He won't pick up his cell,
and he's not at the hospital, either.
To the city. To the city, please.
I think he's left work.
Left work?
What is wrong with him?
He's well aware of the situation
at the hospital right now, too!
So how could he just leave?
All right. I'll take over for today.
Please prepare the patient for surgery.
Will you be all right, sir?
We're not in a situation
to be discussing that now.
Get her ready, please.
Well, well, well.
So you disobeyed us.
I definitely told you what would happen
if you ignored our command.
Nurse Park.
Get the patient to the OR, now.
And prepare her for surgery.
Yes, sir.
Stop right there!
Are you going to take responsibility if
something bad happens to the patient?
Get out of the way!
It seems that you're trying to wiggle out
of this by using the patient as an excuse
but I can't let you do that.
I told you to get the hell
out of the way, now!
And I told you that I won't!
Why, you little bastard...
Are you all right, Senior?
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine. I'm not hurt.
What about you? You're not hurt?
Stay in the car.
I'm going to see what's going on.
What's the matter?
What is it...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[DOCTOR ROMANTIC]
There's only one way to know if
a doctor is doing a proper job.
Through the way they treat their
patients. That's the only way.
So is this the "painting" that
you were working on, Teacher Kim?
It's just a sketch for now.
What do you think about Bu Yong Joo?
You think he's a good person?
Or do you think that
he's a genius doctor?
Are all of those people
going together, too?
How about it?
Want to team up with me?
I'll have to look into it starting now.