[One Percent of Something]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 10: Hate-Love
"Should I Spare Them?"]
It's strange.
I can't get used to this.
You want me to come to the hotel?
We can see each other
tomorrow if you're busy.
No, we can't do tomorrow!
I'm busy.
What a nasty temper.
Don't you know what "fair" means?
I even sat in on your class last time.
I'll go there with a huge sign with
your name on it! Look forward to it.
Oh, geez.
Sure, I'm fine with that.
Later.
Um...
I heard bits and pieces
from your grandfather.
So one of the conditions in his will
is that you have to date that woman?
Yes.
How amusing.
I'm sure that I don't need to worry,
but don't fall for her too hard.
People like us can't marry just anyone.
Especially you.
You know that, right?
Yes. I do.
All right, then.
Where's your sign?
Can you come up with me for a bit?
I think 20 minutes will be sufficient.
- I'll wait for you at the coffee shop.
- Hey.
It's okay for you to come up with me.
No, thank you!
This is your workplace.
I'm sure there are tons of people
watching you as it is.
If a woman is hanging around,
people will talk crap about you.
I don't care, as long as they
don't say anything to my face.
As long as I don't hear it myself,
I don't care.
Um, I'll keep that in mind.
But still, I won't talk crap
about you, and wait for you.
Don't go anywhere then, and wait here.
Don't go wandering too much.
I'll be back really soon.
So you're dating Jae In, huh?
Excuse me?
I'm Jae In's aunt.
I saw you at that concert.
The chairman himself will be present
at the info session
regarding the Shanghai trip.
And we'll be taking care of all the
promotional materials regarding that.
But last time, during the
bid for Youker, we...
Then, shall we attend to the
Chairman himself, and go to Shanghai?
Oh, no! Um, the promotional materials...
I'll do my best if it kills me, sir.
Yay, overtime work!
Um, do you need to be somewhere?
Yes. When the draft for the
presentation comes out
get it looked over by the general
manager and proceed thusly.
I'm going to get something to eat.
Yes, sir.
See you later, sir.
Wow, we sure dodged a bullet there.
My father...
I mean, Jae In's grandfather...
he introduced you two, right?
Well, yes.
Figures.
My father didn't mention Tae Ha?
Tae... Ha?
What brings you here?
Oh, I had some business to
take care of here, so I stopped by.
What, I can't even chat with a guest?
Then go meet your guest,
instead of doing this.
What's wrong with you?
Let's chat again later.
I have more questions for you.
Um, yes.
Goodbye.
What was that? You should
be polite to your elders!
Give-and-take.
She reaps what she sows.
What was she talking to you about?
What do you mean?
I couldn't even greet her properly
because you butted in so rudely.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
I don't have much time.
Just a second.
Wait, is this not the place?
Oh, I found it!
[Countryside Grandma's Grilled Fish]
How did you find a place like this,
when you always get lost?
I came here often with Hyun Jin.
She doesn't eat at home much, either.
Hurry and eat up!
What?
Fundamentally, people work to
afford their living expenses
but here you are, with barely
any time to even eat.
It's not like this every day.
We have a VIP event
coming up all of a sudden, so...
It seems like it is
like this every day, though.
You should head back
after you're done eating.
My father didn't mention Tae Ha?
Oh yeah, Mr. Jae In.
Who's Tae Ha?
Why?
Did my aunt say something to you?
No, you just mentioned
him to me last time.
So, who is he?
My cousin.
He's my aunt's son.
Listen up.
If Tae Ha ever approaches you,
let me know right away.
And ignore him no matter
what he says, okay?
How could I act like I know him, when
I don't even know what he looks like?
That's a relief, then.
At any rate, don't ever meet with him.
Ignore him from the moment
you hear his name, got it?
Sorry I can't drop you off.
It's fine.
You're busy.
Will you be able to get home by yourself?
Just take a cab home.
I was actually going to take
a cab to Hyun Jin's shop.
I can find my way home from there.
Good thinking.
I don't know when I'll be done,
but I'll try to finish as soon as I can.
And I'll take you home from
there later, if I have time.
Sure, if you want to.
What kinds of colors
do you wear most frequently?
- Well, bright...
- Bright colors?
Well, how's this, then?
You have a cute face, so...
- Do you have any other colors?
- Other colors? Ah.
Here you are.
A yellow one.
So we meet again.
Yes... Ms. Han Joo Hui.
It seems that you're
still seeing Jae In.
Looks like you've lasted a
bit longer than his other flings.
Jae In has dated tons of women before.
And none of them
have lasted too long.
The shortest he's seen
someone is a month
but he hasn't seen anyone
longer than six months.
He goes out with people, but
they break up sooner or later.
Because the person he's going to marry
has already been predetermined.
Really, now?
Isn't that obvious?
Wait, you weren't thinking that
you'd possibly marry him, were you?
I'm warning you now,
for your own sake.
Don't fall too hard for Jae In.
Well, I don't know.
Who can predict what'll happen
to two people who are dating?
I have a guess as to why you're going
out of your way to say all this, but...
we'll take care of our own
relationship, thanks.
- Can I try these on?
- Yes, of course.
I'll help you.
Hmm, these are a bit uncomfortable.
I'm sure that Jae In is just like
a shoe that doesn't fit right, to you.
No, Mr. Jae In is a lot more
comfortable to be with than you'd think.
Not that you'd know
anything about that.
These are nice.
You never know with shoes
until you try them on, after all.
Ugh, should I kill that guy,
or spare him?
Just what the hell does
he go around doing, anyway?
What if she's lost somewhere?
Sir, we have the first draft
of the promo video
ready for viewing, in
the conference room.
All right.
I'm coming.
So you're saying that there was
a woman who kept saying, "my Jae In?"
Yeah. And her body language
wasn't too subtle, either.
Who could she be?
I know all the regulars at my shop.
[Mr. Lee Jae In]
Hmph!
I'll never pick up.
I'd totally pick up, if I were you.
Aren't you curious about
who that woman is?
Of course I am!
But this guy needs to be punished today.
That's only fair.
Oh, that's cute.
Oh yeah, that!
"Being fair!"
Why weren't you picking up?
I had a lot to think about.
What is it now?
You're not the type to be mad just
because I didn't take you home.
No, I am mad about that!
I never would've run into that nasty
woman, if he'd taken me home.
Get it together, Kim Da Hyun.
He's not a big deal.
Is that why he wanted to
date for six months?
Well, I guess he's dated me
longer than anyone else, then.
It's not like I was planning to have
a long relationship with him anyway.
But, still! Why do I have
to deal with that bitch?
Oh, Mr. Ji Su!
What's up?
You're doing well, right, Teacher?
Yeah. You're doing well, right?
The person you're trying to
reach is in the middle of a call.
You will be taken to voicemail...
She's driving me nuts.
Let's hurry!
I hope this goes well!
Hey, Mom.
Um, yeah.
I'm heading to class now.
Love you, Mom.
Talk to you later!
Isn't our Ji-sus just so amazing?
I know, right?
He's so cool!
Yes, I made a good choice.
My dream is in Korea!
Sorry, Mom.
How was I today, Teacher?
Didn't you hear the applause earlier?
You were totally amazing!
Oh, um, hello.
Yes, so we meet again.
Are you Mr. Ji Su's manager?
No, that's not it.
I'm the president of his fanclub...
Well, um, you can just
think of me as his guardian.
But, um, what brings you here?
Oh, I'm in charge of
SH Mall's PR department.
We were the ones who planned for him
to have a concert here today.
Oh, thank you!
He's still a trainee, so he hasn't
been able to perform much.
Oh, it's nothing. It's not like it
was a huge concert, anyway.
It's just a small concert.
I felt that Mr. Ji Su's concept went well
with ours, so the response has been good.
Thank you!
This is great!
Thank you.
But, um, it seemed that you're
having an event here next week, too.
Oh, we already have someone
for the main mall, but...
our malls in Gangnam and
Busan should still be available.
Thank you.
I feel like I've been seeing
Chairman Han around quite often.
Well, that old man has tons
of greed and time, so...
that's all there is to it.
Get back to work.
Where have you been?
Ji-sus's concert.
He's signed to an agency already!
So why are you doing this?
Well, it's because I'm the
president of his fanclub.
Goodbye.
What do you want?
Open the door.
Did you want to talk about something?
I'll tell you if you open up.
Okay, then.
What's the problem?
I won't know unless you tell me!
So tell me why, at least.
I won't be able to solve this or give
you an explanation otherwise.
Why are you mad?
How many women have you dated before?
Do you usually date
them for at least a month
but don't date anyone for longer than
six months, or something like that?
Are you really jealous,
or are you just testing me?
I'm testing you!
Don't you dare be cheating on me.
When would I even have time to
see another woman?
I'm busy enough as it is,
just with dating you!
Stop spouting nonsense.
If you have time to do that,
call me first instead.
How come you never call me?
Wait, no. How come you never pick up?
Why is it that I always have to
be the one to call you first?
Well, um, I'm busy.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I'm at least twelve times
more busy than you are!
Yes, Hyun Jin?
What is it?
I'm busy.
I have to head to work.
I know.
I know, but...
Look at your phone.
Why? Did Ji Su have a scandal?
No, not Ji Su--
DaDa. Should I kill
Mr. Lee Jae In for you?
What is she talking about?
Just a second!
[Lee Jae In, Grandson of SH Group's
Chairman Lee Gyu Chul, To Wed]
[Lee Jae In Engaged to
Han Joo Hui of Hanjoo Chemicals]
No, I think I'll have to kill him.
Hey, did you see today's paper?
My breakfast meeting just ended.
Why, did Grandpa say something again?
No, the chairman isn't
the issue right now.
Wait, you're driving right now, right?
Just read it when you get to work.
Way to write a great article.
"A couple is born in
the financial world."
"Lee Jae In, the eldest grandson of
Chairman Lee of SH Group is engaged"
"to Han Joo Hui, the only daughter of
Chairman Han of of Hanjoo Chemicals."
[Lee Jae In, Grandson of SH Group's
Chairman Lee Gyu Chul, To Wed]
Now you're even getting engaged,
right in front of my face?
He's not here right now, so I'll call
you back after confirming with him.
Yes, hello.
No, we haven't confirmed yet.
- Hello?
- Yes.
- Before an official statement is made...
- What's going on?
No, I can't reach him, either.
Yes, goodbye.
Yes, we'll call you first.
Wait, sir, um....
That... that woman...
[Lee Jae In, Grandson of SH Group's
Chairman Lee Gyu Chul, To Wed]
What is this?
It's not true, is it?
Of course not! Why would I be
engaged to Han Joo Hui?
Our phones are blowing up
because of this article!
Our shares have taken a hit, and
there are tons of posts online!
Make sure you get this information
out before the stock market opens today.
If you don't, we may be charged
later for stock manipulation, too.
Then, this is... I'm sorry to say this,
but the main branch needs to handle this.
Yes, I'll get in touch with them.
Yes, Secretary Jang.
I was actually about to call you now.
No, it's completely false.
I know I have branched off on my own,
but I'd never get engaged like this.
Yes. I'll find out who started this rumor
and take legal action against them.
And please take care of
explaining this to the media.
[Mr. Lee Jae In]
Oh, damn it.
- Yes, yes. No, it's not true.
- Yes, we'll be in touch.
Tell them I'm not here, no matter what.
Yes, sir.
Yes, we're reporting this to the police.
This isn't true. No. We've confirmed it,
so you don't need to call us anymore.
Teacher!
I picked all these
pumpkins and mugwort!
Can we eat this now?
Yeah, we can eat this now.
We'll cook it, and make it
into something delicious!
But... I thought you didn't like
pumpkins, Kyung Eun.
But I'm going to eat these anyway.
Good thinking.
Jae In.
You shouldn't be here,
when things are like this.
It's not all that bad.
You really are the
lowest of the low.
I'm the one who saved you
from marrying me last time.
So I think you owe me
this much, at least.
No. I don't owe you anything!
And you were opposed to
getting married back then, too.
Follow me.
I don't want some weird rumors to
spread by having you hang around here.
Let me make this clear to you
before I say anything else.
I only have one reason
for seeing you right now.
And that's to take care of this mess.
Tell the media to release
a corrected statement.
Are you that against this?
What's the reason
that we can't get married?
Han Joo Hui!
Tell me. Why are you acting this way?
I...
think I love you.
Would you still love me if
I weren't Lee Jae In of SH Group?
You don't love me.
You love SH Group.
You did three years ago,
and you still do now.
Fine, I do want to become the wife
of the future chairman of SH Group.
But...
I want you, too.
Let's just leave it at that, okay?
I'm not your toy.
Don't you dare think that you can
manipulate me however you want.
I'm really not okay with that.
Oh yeah.
Also, don't refer to me so casually.
Fine. Just "Jae In" is
a bit too casual.
I'll refer to you as "Mr. Jae In"
when we're in public.
No, that's even worse.
There's no nickname that
you're allowed to call me by
so just don't even refer to me at all.
Lee Jae In.
If you act this way,
I can become really vicious.
As vicious as you!
I can be ruthless too, you know.
Hey.
Issuing threats is for people who
actually have the power to back it up.
And you have to keep an eye on
the other person while doing so.
I'll pretend that I didn't hear
what you just said.
You really are a skilled player,
aren't you?
- Goodbye, Teacher.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
Whatever.
Damn it.
Excuse me.
Ms. Kim Da Hyun just left.
Oh, I see.
I thought I'd lost you.
Why do you walk so fast?
Don't go online for the time being.
And don't watch the news, either.
Too late for that. I already went online,
and watched the news, too.
Oh, damn it.
You have no redeeming
qualities about you!
You curse all the time, and just go off
and get engaged on your own!
I didn't get engaged!
Contract Article Twelve!
"If one party starts seeing another
person, the contract is null and void!"
Congrats on your engagement!
I told you, I'm not engaged!
You want to see the screenshot I took?
Why would you take a screenshot
of something useless like that?
Why are you getting mad at me?
You're the one in the wrong!
Do I really seem like
that kind of person to you?
You think I'm the type of guy who'd
get engaged to another woman
even though I'm dating you?
I.... I don't know.
Don't believe anything that didn't
come out of my own mouth.
Trust only me, okay?
Well then, make me trust you!
What's gotten into me?
The contract period will
be over soon, anyway.
Then... it won't even matter if
you're engaged to that woman.
Hey. Don't get ahead of yourself.
You sure have a lot of thoughts
running through your small head.
Trust only me, and
think only about me.
I won't ever hurt you until the
contract period is over, okay?
Also, please pick up your phone.
Why are you laughing?
Go.
Hurry and go.
Bye.
Are you sure you don't need
me to come up with you?
Get home safe.
Did you see everything?
Yep.
You two might as well have
been shooting a movie!
I'm jealous, Kim DaDa!
Hyun Jin.
It looks like... I've developed
a type of love-hate for him.
What do I do?
What else?
Date your heart out
during the time you have left
so that you're not left with any regrets.
What if I can't bear to break
up him afterward, then?
What are you worried about, exactly?
Are you worried about breaking up with
him, or not breaking up with him?
I mean, it's not like you're
committing adultery.
And it's not like you'll get
married, and then get divorced.
Why are you worrying
about the future now?
Yeah, you're right.
Also, don't you worry, sweetie.
Big Sis here knows what she's
talking about, since she has experience.
Breaking up with someone
really isn't a big deal.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Really!
The end!
Really?
That'd be really nice.
Aw, innocent little sweetheart.
Get over here.
I don't know what's gotten into me.
The contract period will
be over soon, anyway.
The first reporter to write about this
was Kang Jin Young from the Koryo Times.
But they refuse to tell me
who gave them the information.
How much did the prices of Hanjoo
Chemical's shares rise yesterday?
We issued a rebuttal, but it
still went up 6.28 percent.
And is there any evidence that
Chairman Han sold any shares yesterday?
I haven't received reports
about that yet.
Watch the prices of Hanjoo Chemicals'
shares for the time being.
And keep an eye on their
board of directors, too.
Yes, sir.
Something is definitely off.
I have all the pieces of the puzzle,
but they don't seem to fit. Strange.
Wow, it must be a nuisance having
a strict schedule for dates!
Wow.
It's the weekend.
Aren't you two going on a date?
I have to meet Ji Su.
And apparently hotels are
busy on weekends, too.
I bet that guy will come running
if you tell him you're seeing Ji Su
no matter how busy he may be.
That's why I'm not planning to tell him.
You sly girl!
Thank you.
Even Seo Jin cast me aside for Ji Su!
Section Chief?
Ji Su told me about it.
SH Mall is doing a lot of philanthropic
work right now as well, so...
And I figured that there would be some
synergy between this and a small concert.
He even said that he'd be providing
us with scholarship money.
Thank you!
Wow, you sure are doing
great things, Ji-Sus!
- Isn't that right, Director?
- Yeah.
You don't need to head back
to the company dorms today?
I got permission from my manager.
He said I could stay overnight.
All right, then.
Good work.
I bet the kids will be
really excited tonight.
I'll come back next week, Director.
You should hurry and head back.
It'll probably be a long trip.
And don't get lost either, okay?
I'll drive you back.
Oh, no. It won't take long
if I take the bus.
There aren't many roads here, so I don't
think that the bus will be here soon.
Yeah. It's late, too. Get a ride to the
train station, at the very least.
Well...
Go on.
You can just drop me off in front
of the subway station.
Where do you live?
I live near Bundang.
Oh, me too!
I'll drop you off near Bundang, then.
Where are you?
On my way home.
Yeah, so, where are you, exactly?
I'm on my way home from the orphanage.
Oh. When are you getting back?
I'll be done with work soon.
Should I come get you?
No, I told you.
I'm on my way home.
See you on the weekend.
What's going on? How come she didn't
ask me to come get her, even as a joke?
That's the boyfriend you mentioned
last time, I presume?
What?
Oh... yes.
Are you two going to get
married, by any chance?
Oh, pardon my rudeness.
I shouldn't have asked such a
personal question, but I was curious.
No, it's fine.
We are dating,
but that's about it for now.
Oh, you can just drop me off
in front of that crosswalk.
We're already here, so I'll just
take you all the way home.
No. I'm thankful enough
that you brought me this far.
It's really okay, though.
Thank you.
Da Hyun?
Mr. Jae In!
Subtitles by DramaFever
So ridiculous! He doesn't
even know what he did wrong!
You're even more ridiculous!
Wow, this man really won't
reflect on what he did wrong.
I won't just let it slide this time.
If you don't want to be fired,
you better run over here now.
What do I do? I think
Da Hyun is really mad.
Buy her some flowers or act cutesy!
I don't know what he may be planning, but
he definitely won't marry that teacher.
Yeah. I think it's about time
that you two met.
Who know what'll happen
with Da Hyun.
Well, how do you feel?