[One Percent of Something]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 15: I Love You - The True
Feelings That He Revealed Too Late]
Hey, don't drink too much.
I'm not.
I'm not drunk.
I'd like to be drunk, though.
Just wait.
Time heals all wounds.
I'm sure you'll forget
about everything, with time.
About what you just said...
don't believe that drivel.
It's a lie.
I don't believe that.
Hello.
Um, what brings you here?
You said that you weren't interested
in my Grandpa's fortune, at all!
I don't have any interest in
that husband clause, yes.
But still, a deal must
be fair to both parties.
But you know, both parties need to keep
a promise for it to have any meaning.
How about we save sleeping
with each other for later?
You must be out of your mind!
Who said that I wanted
to sleep with you?
- What's with you?
- Ow!
Ow.
Happy birthday to you!
Congratulations on your birthday!
Come on, smile! These will
all be treasured memories.
I think that I might
like you, Mr. Jae In.
I like kissing you, too.
Nobody can make me forget her.
- Back off.
- Hey!
Wow, he's gotten a lot more handsome.
Big Brother!
Oh, you're here?
Oh, it's Ji-sus!
No, I have to resist today.
Let's go, Big Brother.
Do you really need to be
holding onto me?
- You're not letting go?
- No!
How does this look, Big Brother?
Oh... yeah.
It looks fine.
Big Brother!
It looks nice on you.
Buy that.
You're really not going to go home?
I told you, I have an audition tomorrow!
Yeah, but it isn't an audition
for potential fashion models!
You better go back to Canada
if you fail this audition!
Canada, Canada!
You're really being too much.
I'm trying so hard like this on my own
without relying on your money, though!
The least you could be doing is praising
me, and yet you're saying this?
Oh, fine.
Good job.
You really did a good job.
But still, you're going back to
Canada if you fail this audition.
DaDa. Ji Su has really
become a lot more skilled!
Should I go and get some
autographs from him?
What are you staring at?
Why that...
those little... ugh!
That rotten bastard!
DaDa. Want me to go down there
and kick him hard for you?
It's fine. Let's go.
I'm hungry.
This is why I'm saying that you
need to see someone, too!
Go on some arranged dates, or something!
I'll have tons of great rich guys
lined up, just waiting!
It's fine. I'm not even
completely over all this yet.
So it'd be unfair to the other person.
Unfair, my ass!
You can only win against
a man with another man!
Let's go.
You're not going to give me a
"good job" stamp this time?
Good... job.
There's nothing here.
It's not like I did anything to deserve
getting a "good job" stamp, though.
Pardon?
Oh, it's nothing.
If I had known that this
was going to happen
I would've given it my all
when I was dating him.
I would've done everything that
everyone else does, with him
so that I wouldn't have any regrets.
No...
Rather, I shouldn't have made
any memories with him.
So he really ended things with Da Hyun?
Yes!
He's really a lot scarier
than I'd thought!
Of course he is.
He's my grandson, after all.
One's work life and dating life
should be kept separate, after all.
A long, long time ago, there was a salt
merchant travelling through the hills.
And then, he ran into a scary tiger.
The tiger rushed at the salt
merchant, and swallowed him!
All right.
Relax, and take it easy.
Okay, right turn.
Wait, you have to signal!
Um, right turn?
Just keep going straight.
And the salt vendor received
a huge reward in the end!
After you finish your scheduled
activities for the morning, you...
The chairman called and told me
to remind you, sir, that...
you're having lunch with the second
daughter of the chairman of Ganghan Inc.
Looks like our chairman
is doing just fine.
Tell him that he needn't worry about it.
Are you... really going to marry
this person right away?
I'm the only direct descendant
of the Lee family line.
My grandfather won't stand for it
if I don't get married.
But if you marry the wrong person
we'll potentially have a
terrible Madam to worry about!
Please consider your options carefully.
My hands are tied, though.
We'll sign pre-nups
before getting married.
Of course, we must sign an M&A contract
for our companies before doing that.
Aren't you speaking
a bit too matter-of-factly?
I don't think there is any need
for either of us to waste time.
Aren't those the terms you agreed to
by coming out here, anyway?
But still, I thought you'd
maintain a basic level of etiquette.
A marriage isn't a
business venture, after all.
How old are you?
28.
I'm sure you've been to plenty of
meetings like this by now, at your age.
And yet you still aren't
familiar of the rules of our world?
This marriage is a deal.
It's strictly business.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Let's stop things here.
I feel like neither one of us can
fulfill the other's expectations.
Yes, Jae In is quite picky when
it comes to women. And so am I.
I'm sure you were well aware of the fact
that SH Group is a formidable force.
Director Lee didn't go home
yesterday, either?
No, ma'am.
I'm so worried for him,
he's overworking himself so much!
Don't worry!
That amount of work won't kill him.
Father-in-Law!
I'll be going, then.
Father-in-Law.
I... did the right thing, didn't I?
They broke up because that's all
their relationship amounted to.
They only liked each other
that much, is all.
So don't beat yourself up too much.
They have nobody to blame
but themselves.
Good work today everyone!
Gather around!
Make sure you all get home safe, okay?
- Yes, Teacher.
And watch out for cars!
- Goodbye, Teacher!
Bye!
Oh, Ru Mi!
Let me straighten that up for you.
- Goodbye, Teacher.
- Bye, now!
Okay!
Don't worry. I can guarantee you
this friend of mine is a good guy.
Is he really good-looking?
Yeah, totally!
He's like Won Bin and
Jo In Sung put together!
But the most important thing of all
is that he's an herbalist!
You're not lying to me, are you?
I'll kill you if he ends up being
a mommy's boy or a player!
Hey, DaDa.
I told you, I did an
initial scan of him already!
Man, I'm full.
Just try meeting him.
And if it doesn't work out
even after you've dated around a bit
I'll take responsibility for you,
so don't worry.
- Just leave it to me.
- Geez.
I told you, no players!
So stop it with that, already!
Hey. It's because of you
that I can't get married!
You should eat more.
Give me an employee discount, okay?
It's on me.
It's a gift from me to commemorate
you overcoming your heartbreak.
Wow! Wait, since you're
buying me things already...
Um... oh!
Buy me this, too!
Geez!
Don't make me yell at you!
I broke up with a guy, and
I was in tons of pain, you know!
Wow, you were never this sly before!
So you're not going to buy this for me?
Fine, fine!
What's wrong? She eats well now
and even smiles nowadays.
Da Hyun doesn't like cream spaghetti.
She usually can't even finish
an entire plate of it.
Oh my goodness!
Just ask me to buy you all
the clothes here, why don't you!
Wow.
[Lee Jae]
[Lee Jae In]
Yeah, Mom?
Oh, it's Dad's acquaintance?
Then sure, I'll meet with him.
Okay, I'll do well.
Okay.
Oh... it's raining.
I think...
that I might like you, Mr. Jae In.
Are you really thinking of finding
a school to work at in Jinju, too?
Ms. Da Hyun.
I'm sorry.
I'll drive you home.
It's raining, after all.
No, I can just catch
a cab right outside.
Um...
I'm sorry about today.
I haven't fully recovered yet.
Goodbye.
Thanks for bringing me to your hotel.
I'd heard that she was sick.
Did she lose weight?
Who are you?
My name is Jung Hyun Jin.
I'm your cousin's
ex-girlfriend's best friend.
So, um, Kim Da Hyun is my friend.
Excuse me.
You should be showing
interest in this issue, you know!
You kidnapped my Da Hyun, after all.
I'm not the one who kidnapped her.
I saved her!
Let's be real, though. You didn't save
her because you wanted to.
You only did it because of that
high-and-mighty cousin of yours.
What is it that you want to say?
You know that Mr. Lee Jae In
and my friend broke up, right?
Well, I think I did hear
something about that, yes.
Those two were really good together.
So what?
How about we do
a good deed for those two?
I'm not that good of a person
to be interested in such things.
Also, I have no interest in
others' love lives.
Wow, what an asshole!
Fine. I guess Da Hyun can see other
men without any worries now.
It's not like Lee Jae In is the
only man on this planet!
- You have such a young-looking face.
- Oh, thank you.
Well, I like to read.
What do you enjoy doing?
Well, I like exercising and watching
movies. And watching movies alone.
Oh.
Shall we go somewhere else?
That'd be for the best, right?
If we stay, it'll just be
uncomfortable for both of us.
What?
- You know, Cousin...
- I told you to call me Big Bro.
You're only seven months
older than me, though.
Well, anyway.
Big Bro.
It's the first time I've seen you
be considerate of someone.
I have a debt to repay to that woman.
I've done all that I could.
Man, that stubborn ass.
Oh, I don't mean you.
I'm talking about your cousin.
Man, really.
I guess that's why he makes
so much money, huh?
Because he's so stupidly stubborn!
But still, my Big Bro -- no, I mean, my
cousin -- held himself back a lot.
Does he really not have any
feelings left for her, then?
Thank you for today.
I guess he didn't love Da Hyun
as much as I thought he did.
I guess I misunderstood.
Wait, no, that works out
for the best, then.
Since she can meet someone better
with no regrets.
At any rate, I've done all that I could.
So if I hear anything about contracts
or a kidnapping through the media
you'll have to take responsibility
for all that, Ms. Jung Hyun Jin.
My cousin is quite a
scary fellow, you see.
Sure, sure.
I know.
Also, I also know that it won't
benefit Da Hyun in any way
for rumors like that
to get around, either.
So I had no intention of posting
an exposé about this online.
At any rate, thank you.
Goodbye, now.
Wait.
Wait, so are you saying
that you deceived me?
It was bad enough that
you threatened me!
Oh, what do you mean, threaten?
I was just a bit desperate, is all.
[Will you delete this photo?]
[No]
The meeting is starting, Director.
All right.
I've prepared a simulation
of what it'd be like for us
to achieve 80 percent
of our marketing goals.
First, we'll establish an infrastructure
geared towards Canadian tourists.
And we'll prepare something
that most Canadians like...
Director!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's end the meeting for today. Can
you take care of the rest, Chief Park?
Yes, sir.
Is it okay for me to contact you again?
Sure.
Do you like that man?
Why are you asking me
something like that?
Is that why you told him that it's
okay for him to contact you again?
He's a good person.
It's about time for me to see
other people now, too.
That way, I'll be able
to get married, and--
Don't talk about other men.
This is none of your
business, Mr. Jae In!
What are you...
If just you can bear it, DaDa,
then so can I.
You'll have to quit
your job at the school.
There will always be security
guards around you
and there will be tons of reporters
bothering you all the time.
And I can't be with you every day,
like other men can.
My mother will be on my side,
but she might be mean to you.
But you can just ignore what
everyone else thinks, though.
You might not be able
to do anything for me.
Are you okay with that?
How... could I possibly
be okay with that?
But still, try and bear it.
Just do this for me, just this once.
I'll be good to you later,
when we're old.
There's...
nothing that has changed
about the two of us.
So... will we be able to start over?
You're positive that
nothing has changed?
That's a relief, then.
I want to marry you.
Mr. Jae In.
I... I don't have the
confidence to say yes.
What a terrible guy.
I'd almost forgotten all about him, too.
I've been trying to forget about him,
so why is he here now?
What does he want me to do?
What are you so surprised about?
You're making me feel bad.
I didn't know
that I'd run into you here.
Well, what else was I supposed to move?
You wouldn't budge,
so I had to come to you.
Come on, just come with me.
I really don't have the luxury to be
considerate of your circumstances.
Oh my.
Do I have to drag you?
Are you seeing anyone?
No.
Good. I'm not dating anyone either.
You really aren't?
I don't think that's quite true.
I told you, I'm not seeing anyone.
Unlike someone, who has someone
who drops her off at home and such.
I really didn't do that.
Well, I, at the very least, didn't go
shopping with someone all giddily!
What are you talking about?
What did you even see?
When did I ever go shopping?
Oh!
"Oh?"
What, you saw that but you didn't see us
going into the same hotel room?
Stop the car.
She's my younger sister!
She's from Canada.
You said hello back then to
my aunt's husband, right?
Oh!
So, what's your answer?
Wait, no.
Your answer isn't that important.
Because no matter what
anyone says, I'm marrying DaDa.
We can't get married just because
the two of us want to.
You don't have to tell me that.
I already know.
Sheesh, you're such a preachy teach.
That's "Teacher," thank you!
I've told you that so many times,
and yet you still don't know?
Yes, Teacher!
Don't think too long and hard about it.
This isn't exactly a simple matter,
you know.
Do you really want to see me get married
to another woman and live a happy life?
I don't want that, either.
I don't want another man by your side,
or another woman by mine.
I don't know how you've been,
but I wasn't okay at all.
I wasn't okay either!
Then just stay by my side.
Let's stay together.
Other people break up because
they don't love each other.
So I don't know why we have
to break up because we do.
What... did you just say?
I love you, Da Hyun.
What is it?
You're such a terrible person!
Why are you only telling me that now?
My job is important to me.
And make sure you get
your family's blessing!
What?
I can deal with everything you said,
but not those two things.
I worked hard for ten years
to become a teacher!
So I'll think about it after I've been
a teacher for ten more years!
Okay.
It doesn't really matter to me. I'm just
worried that it might be tough on you.
I'll let you know if it is.
And... no matter how much
I may like you...
I don't have the courage to be hated
by people who'll become my family!
So you have to get
your family's blessing, okay?
Then... you'll marry me?
You mean that, right?
Wait, no. You already said
you would, so no backsies.
Okay.
I love you, too.
Um, aren't you leaving?
Can't I sleep over?
No, you can't.
We're going to live together
when we get married, anyway.
Who knows what'll happen later on?
We'll have to actually get
married to know that for sure.
So, are you saying that you're
not going to marry me, then?
I told you, yes!
I will.
But only after we get
our families' blessings.
I'll take care of that, okay?
I barely got a wink of sleep
this entire time.
So can't you let me sleep here?
That company sure is strange.
They don't even let people sleep.
Go home and sleep.
No, the reason why I didn't get
any sleep is because of you.
Just stay by my side, okay?
That's the only way I'll
be able to fall asleep.
Um, I don't have any clothes for
you to change into at my place
and it'll be really
inconvenient for you.
It's not too late for you
to go home now, and...
Is it mine?
Oh, are you awake?
So it is you.
Geez, you!
What are you doing?
I thought that it was just
a dream this time, too.
It's not a dream.
Yeah.
I don't think it is.
What a relief.
I'm tired.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Are you dating her again?
I can't bear to see her dating
and marrying another man.
- No way.
- You saved my life.
But... this is the first time
I've ever met you.
You really don't know him?
Marriage?
As if!
Never!
I want you to marry an average guy.
Mr. Jae In is a good person.
Everyone likes each other
at the very beginning.
And that's why people get married!
But it's not like that anymore after
you live with one another for a while!
The more different your partner is from
you, the more difficult it'll be for you.
[One Percent of Something]