[Episode 4: Business Relationship;
"So, You Better Not Fall For Me!"]
Um... what...
Isn't it only natural that our
relationship makes some progress
since we're really dating?
But, I gave it some thought,
and I did have a strict upbringing
so I'm not okay with sleeping with you
after the first date.
Nobody was offering, you know!
You...
Ow!
What are you doing?
I... I should be saying that right now!
Don't you dare ever bring up anything
like "making progress," or whatnot.
You were basically asking for a beating!
You're not even going to say bye?
Get home safe. Or not.
I don't care.
Ow!
What were you thinking, Lee Jae In?
Why did you go and do that?
Geez.
Asshole.
He's a total player!
Yeah?
You have to stop the reporters.
That's a part of the contract, after all.
How is a lawyer like me
supposed to stop them?
SH Group itself should
be stopping them, instead.
Do things that way, then.
You're the one who caused this mess
and yet I'm the one who
has to clean up after you?
So, why did you even...
show up to an official event
with a woman?
Didn't you know that the reporters would
be chasing you like bloodhounds?
I wasn't completely unaware of the fact.
Also, I did it because I knew that
you'd be able to stop the reporters.
So take responsibility, and make sure
they don't publish anything about us.
Wow. You really are a sly one.
Oh? You're smiling?
No, I didn't.
Yeah, you definitely did!
Come on, what is it?
What's going on?
Fill me in, man!
There's definitely something up.
No, there isn't.
[CEO LEE JAE-IN OF SH ALPEZIA ATTENDS
MUSIC EVENT WITH AN UNKNOWN FEMALE]
[CEO LEE JAE IN OF SH ALPENGIA APPEARS
AT CONCERT WITH BEAUTIFUL WOMAN]
What is this?
What is Jae In doing?
But, um, thankfully,
this happened late last night
so this article is only on a couple
of sites and newspapers.
Attorney Park was going around all night
trying to keep them from publishing...
Wow, Jae In.
I told him to keep me in the loop,
and this is how he does it?
I'm sorry, sir. It was quite late at
night, so it was hard to deal with.
It's fine. How could you stop that kid,
especially when he has a plan?
You're not worried, sir?
At this rate, the news about their
relationship will spread like wildfire.
With things like this, it'll make it
easier for them to get married! Right?
And if that happens,
I'll be the winner.
Oh...
[SH MUSEUM]
[CEO LEE JAE IN OF SH ALPEZIA APPEARS
AT CONCERT WITH BEAUTIFUL WOMAN]
Ugh, it was just an accident!
Forget all about it!
Yeah!
Yes, Mother.
The article isn't completely wrong, no.
No. We're not getting married.
Don't worry.
Yes.
Oh, Soo Jung!
Have you got a girlfriend?
Are you going to get married?
I'm not getting married!
And speak in Korean!
How's Aunt's health?
Are you really going to get married?
I told you, I'm not getting married!
Bye!
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Oh yeah, Deputy Han.
Did you see that article?
Apparently, CEO Lee
finally has a girlfriend.
When has he ever not had a girlfriend?
No, no! I don't think
it's just a fling this time.
He brought this woman to the classical
music concert our hotel sponsored.
Team Leader Kang.
What kind of woman is she?
I don't know.
How would I know?
There's only, like,
two sentences in that entire article.
I need to know who she is!
Why?
Do you have a crush on the CEO,
or something?
Are you crazy?
I was going to take a lunchbox to that
crazy girl, and ask her to reconsider!
Hey, come on. I'm sure he'll change
a little, now that he has a girlfriend.
Really?
Of course! There's always a
balance of yin and yang in this world.
He wouldn't just get mad for no reason.
We'll be having a meeting in 10 minutes.
Tell the general manager and Director
Hwang that they need to be present, too.
Um, sir.
It's lunchtime in 10 minutes, though.
So what?
Um, yes, sir!
Of course!
Who said that he got a girlfriend, huh?
Yin and yang, my ass!
Does that asshole seem like a guy
who just got himself a girlfriend?
If anything, he's more of
an asshole than before!
Can't you say that a bit more nicely?
It's not like you to speak so brashly.
CEO Lee Jae In?
"With beautiful woman"?
Damn this guy!
Well, it's not like that's untrue.
I am a beautiful woman, after all.
It's true, but... oh man!
Try to act like you don't know me.
Don't turn your head this way, either.
Oh, that bastard!
Should I just kill him?
If I'd known that he'd do this,
I would've kicked him more yesterday!
I can't bury him in the
ground either, right?
"Did he break up with
Lee Soo Jung, then?"
Wait. Lee Soo Jung.
Lee Soo Jung.
Are they talking about
the actress Lee Soo Jung?
"Lee Jae In."
Wow, this guy is a total player!
Kang Mi Ra? Lee Soo Jin?
Yeon Seo Hui?
All of his girlfriends were
singers and actresses, huh?
If you collected all his ex-girlfriends,
you could establish a solid agency!
Teacher.
Oh, Ji Su!
What's this?
Hey, you didn't need to give
me anything like this.
The fan club's president should be buying
you flowers, not the other way around!
When I become a real star, I'll send you
a huge flower arrangement instead.
Oh yeah.
Teacher.
Thank you.
That attorney told me that I won't
have to worry about anything.
And he said that it was
definitely an illegal contract.
I'd still seriously consider burying
that until your issue is solved.
Burying what?
Oh, nothing, really!
It's just a problematic thing
I've come across, is all.
Anyway, don't worry too much about it.
I was told that the attorney
is the best in Korea.
Make sure you properly
review your contract next time
before signing with
another agency, okay?
Yes, I will.
That's why I was thinking I'd use
this time off to study really hard.
Good thinking.
Is there anything that you
wanted to ask me?
Did you solve all the
problems from last time?
Oh yeah.
[CEO LEE JAE IN]
[THE GENERAL]
[DADA]
We're working together with
the people in Hawaii right now
toward an MOU to purchase
the land for the new facility.
All right, then. Let's end our
meeting here, for today.
As for the land for the new hotel
let's get a contract signed by
the end of next month.
We'll fine-tune the details
and review this again later.
That'll be all for today's meeting.
Oh, General Manager.
Yes, sir?
Does our hotel's Japanese restaurant
not offer any simple a la carte dishes?
Do they only offer prix fixe options?
Well, that is...
Yes, sir.
[DADA]
Oh, now he's not even
picking up my calls?
Figures. If he had a shred of
morality in him, he couldn't pick up.
Wait. He seems like the type
who has no morals, though.
Teacher!
Let's go eat something delicious.
You don't have any other plans, right?
Oh, I do have to see
someone today, actually.
Who?
Just someone.
He's so annoying. He never
listens to what I tell him to do
and I'll have to work really hard to
shape him into a decent human being.
Maybe I don't really need to see him.
Let's go!
This teacher... No, the
president of your fan club
will buy you something
super delicious.
Let's move out!
- Make sure you have everything.
- Yes, ma'am!
What's this?
[FROM DADA]
CEO Lee?
About lunch...
About... lunch...
[DADA]
What's going on?
It hasn't been a week yet.
Oh yeah.
You better not stomp on me again.
I won't stand for it if you do!
Hello, there.
It's quite hot today, isn't it?
You got home safely that night, right?
It's proper manners to start off
with pleasantries like these.
Didn't you know that?
Didn't they teach you that
in elementary school?
Also, you're not in the position to be
yelling at me like this right now.
[CHAIRMAN KANG]
You knew that there were
reporters there, didn't you?
And that they'd write articles about me.
Well...
a little.
That's why I warned you beforehand!
I told you not to look at me,
or smile at me!
You should've made it so that
things like this didn't happen
even before you supposedly warned me!
Right? As you said...
"I'll take full responsibility if the
press releases information about us."
Go ahead and take responsibility, then.
What are you saying?
I thought you didn't want to marry me.
And I definitely don't
want to marry you!
I hate women who just kick me
like it's nothing!
Did I say "let's get married?"
Huh? Did I?
That's not what I'm saying!
Why are you so self-centered?
You didn't even think of
apologizing, either.
You still don't understand
what you did wrong?
No, I don't.
Oh, yeah!
Is this...
because of that kiss?
I'm sure that it must have felt
nice for you too, though.
Ow.
Are you really going
to be like this? Huh?
Teachers aren't
supposed to be so violent!
They teach us to do this
when we encounter a pervert.
I could kick you where
it really hurts, instead.
Want me to do that?
We need it by tomorrow.
Yes.
Well, um, yes.
I'm supposed to be
at work right now, sir.
I'm busy right now,
thanks to your grandson!
That punk ignored my call again!
We're getting calls from
everywhere right now!
I think that he's meeting
with that teacher again today.
And they met yesterday, too?
He's doing great, then!
He'd be a fool to let Da Hyun
slip through his fingers.
But, um, why do you like her so much?
I mean, I'm sure that we
could find a woman
who's kinder, smarter, and
shapelier than her, if we look.
I'm sure that's true.
But those women won't
be able to change Jae In.
In this world, there are certain people
who make the people around them
change just because of their presence.
Just like my late wife.
Da Hyun will be able to
set that kid straight.
The CEO won't change easily.
He's changed quite a bit already.
He's the only one unaware of that fact.
What an idiot.
This is the first time I've ever
received texts like these.
You know that those emoticons
are stand-ins for curse words, right?
It's not something to be laughing about.
Where did you get this
bouquet of flowers?
I'm pretty sure you didn't
buy them for me.
It's not like you've
made yourself easy to love.
Then... did you get these
from a guy, by any chance?
Why are you curious about that?
I'm sure you didn't go on a blind date.
So who could it have been, then?
It's not like you'd know,
even if I told you.
And does that man know about me?
Do you explain your arrangement with me
to every woman you're seeing?
So... what you're saying is
that you met up with a guy.
And not too long ago, at that.
You know, I do think there's something
that I left out of the contract.
Yeah.
Let's rewrite the contract.
What do you mean,
let's rewrite it?
No cheating on each other. Never.
No putting on an innocent act,
only to stab me in the back later.
You will not see any
other man besides me.
When did I ever cheat on you?
Define "see any other man."
Don't even try to lie to me
and tell me you have male friends.
So everyone else besides your family
is off-limits.
Keep your distance even from guys you
may randomly encounter on the street.
Then... are you going to keep your
distance from every other woman
besides the women in your family
while dating me?
You don't really have
to do that, though.
So you're not going to see Lee Soo Jin,
Kang Mi Ra, or Yeon Seo Hui anymore?
You should only believe one-tenth
of what you read online.
Which one of them were you
actually dating, then?
Is it true that you have a kid, too?
I heard that you're having
your kid raised in the States!
Do you want to be sued for defamation
and the spreading of false rumors?
Well, fine, then. It's not like I'll be
your kid's mom, anyway.
In exchange, you'd better
keep your hands off me.
Don't grab my wrist
without permission, or k...
Well, anyway, no physical contact!
Why are you laughing?
You've never dated a guy before,
have you?
That's not true!
Then did you only ever date eunuchs?
You seem like you're unaware of this,
so let me fill you in.
When a man and woman are dating, they
hold hands, kiss, and sleep together.
That's what all couples do.
It's all perfectly natural
among couples!
How did I end up with
a playboy like you?
You seem like you're unaware of this,
so let me fill you in.
That's not what people
do when they're dating.
That's what people do when
they actually like one another!
So, what you're saying is...
that you don't like me?
Well, of course!
Fine.
Just keep being that way, then.
Don't you dare fall for me!
Things will get quite
complicated if you do.
That's what I want to say!
Well, whatever.
We've met today, so let's count this
as our official meeting for the week.
I don't think so.
We have to meet more often
than once a week.
It's not based on the
frequency of our meetings.
What's important is establishing
and maintaining some regularity.
It's a bit stuffy in here, let's go.
Hey, that's mine!
Hey! That's my bouquet!
No! Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
Do other people know
how terrible a person you are?
Yeah.
But I don't care.
Why a concert hall, of all places?
My hotel is a sponsor.
What now?
Do you hate musicals and plays
on top of classical music, too?
No.
That's not it.
You've never dated a woman before,
have you?
What?
Figures, since you still look like you're
a normal person, despite everything.
So you did date women.
But you always got dumped, right?
Is that why you're so
damaged a human being?
What kind of ridiculousness is that?
I've never been dumped by a woman
in my life.
You probably got dumped without
realizing that you got dumped.
Let me be real for a second.
I'm sure that those women
probably didn't like you much, either.
They probably liked your title, though.
And how are you so sure about that?
Because you're doing work
in the middle of a date!
Who'd like a man like that?
I mean, this is something
that I have to do, anyway!
I'm killing two birds with one stone.
And I'm saving time.
What a relief.
Why?
Because you most certainly
haven't fallen for me.
There isn't a single
person on this planet
who tries to be frugal with their time
when seeing someone they like.
If anything, they go out of their way
to make time.
Well, fine.
Keep being like that.
Don't you dare fall for me.
I'm sure that won't be
an easy feat, though.
Why are you laughing?
Well, whatever.
Let's go.
Wait, where?
We went to the concert last time like
you wanted, so it's my turn to choose.
That's only fair.
Come on.
I should've said hello to the
stage director, at the very least!
You can go do that by yourself later.
How dare you hold my hand!
Wow.
Hello.
What are you doing?
Go up.
You... want to go in here?
We have to save time, after all.
Killing two birds with one stone.
- This is what you really want?
- I told you, yes!
It's not like you're a child!
You're not 10 years old!
The kids that I teach are 10 years old.
Come on.
Let's go.
You should really reconsider this.
Why? I feel like this will be fun.
You never did things like this
as a child?
No, I didn't.
What did you do, then?
I took lessons in violin, cello,
golf, swimming, ballet, and Spanish.
Wow, that's totally different
than what I did growing up.
What did you study?
I played soccer, took piano
lessons for two months
watched cartoons,
and played with paper dolls.
It's okay. It's my first time
making a model, too.
So then, why did you...
Because the kids in
my class will like it.
Buy me that, Mom!
I want it!
No. Let's go.
But I want it!
If you keep misbehaving,
I'm just going to leave you here!
You want to live with the owner
of this store? And I'll get a new son?
But still!
Buy it for me!
No!
- Come on!
- Hey! Let's go.
Hurry it up!
What are you doing?
Are you sleeping with your eyes open?
No, I'm not asleep.
You're not sick, are you?
Or do you hate doing this that much?
Should... we leave, then?
No, it's fine.
Just keep working on this.
I'll go buy some drinks.
He's such a weird guy.
Hurry up and buy it for me, Mom!
You're really not going
to listen to your mom?
Come on!
Buy it for me!
No!
Here kid.
Make sure to obey your mom, okay?
Thank you.
It seems that Jae In has himself
another girlfriend.
You saw them, too?
Yes, I happened to stumble upon them.
How is it that he has a different girl
on his arm almost every day?
It'd be even weirder for him to not
have a girlfriend at his age.
It's not bad for him to do
everything he wants to do
before going to work
at the main SH Group branch.
The main SH Group branch?
Of course. Jae In won't be at
that hotel forever, you know.
No matter what anyone says, Jae In
is the eldest son of this household.
I'm my father's child too, you know.
It's not just my older brother
who's my father's child!
Tae Ha is a blood relative of
my father, just like Jae In is!
Did I ever say otherwise?
What's important is his skill, anyway.
You know, Jae In is my
brother's son, not yours.
You two don't even share
a single drop of blood.
He won't become your son just because
you keep hanging around him.
Young Miss!
Watch your words.
It won't benefit you in the slightest
to get on my bad side.
I have SH Mall shares too, you know.
Stop it, already!
How annoying.
Geez.
Why are you still here?
Were you planning to eat here
before you left?
I'm sorry, sir.
As I told you before,
Jae In is my son now.
And he's also the grandson of the
chairman of Daehan Electric.
I'd like it if you didn't forget that.
Why does that punk
take after you so much?
He might as well have been
born from your belly instead.
Don't worry.
That punk is ten times
more wicked than I am.
Is a piece missing?
Why won't it fit?
Drink up.
Did you know that kid
you bought the model set for?
No.
Then why...
Because his whining was so annoying.
When are you planning to leave?
It's been an hour already.
I think the instructions are wrong.
Everything is rolling around!
Don't do this in front of kids.
Kids think that their teachers
are good at everything, after all.
Wow, it looks like you
really have a knack for this!
Even kids can make these just fine.
It's just you that can't, DaDa.
[SUITABLE FOR AGES 10 AND UP]
Oh, it looks like a sudden downpour.
Looks that way.
It'll probably stop soon, right?
Here, a present.
It's new, so try making this
when you have some time.
Who knows?
It might be fun.
I'm busy.
Yeah, so when you have time.
Oh, it's not stopping.
Should we just make a
run for it to the parking lot?
Just a second.
- Did you borrow that?
- Yeah.
You should've borrowed one more!
What for?
Oh my!
I heard that working on model figures
is good for concentration and creativity
Geez!
Does that mean you lack both
concentration and creativity, DaDa?
Why, you...
Oh, you really are horrid, you know!
It'll just be your loss
if you try to run off, you know.
You're the one with bad concentration!
I'm creative, though, so it's okay
if I lack concentration.
Oh, geez!
I heard you got yourself a man.
Your mom is over the moon about it.
But still, she said that you two can't
live together before getting married.
I'm really busy as of late because of a
really important and serious matter.
Bye.
Lee Jae In of SH Group?
- Lee Jae In?
- The Prince?
Did you look into the woman
who's dating Jae In?
Forget about everything else.
We need to know more about her.
My younger sister is
DaDa's best friend.
We don't exactly have an
average relationship, either!
Isn't that right?
- You're like the Demon King!
- Demon King?
You two have kissed already though,
right?
Um, what are you doing?
Kissing you.