(All characters, organizations, places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 11)
Hi, I'm just about to leave.
Have fun.
I'm going to go home and rest. Bye.
(Park Morgan)
He insists on going to the reunion?
Ms. Jung.
Ta Mi.
You look really pretty today. Where are you going looking so nice?
I'm on my way to meet my first love.
Your first love? My gosh.
Which way are you headed?
I'll give you a ride if it's on the way.
I never saw him after I graduated.
It's been over 10 years already.
I can't believe you're on your way to meet your first love.
How does it feel?
Like I'm getting a parcel I've been anticipating for 10 years.
I guess your heart's fluttering like crazy.
I don't know who he is, but he's one lucky guy...
to have a pretty woman like you get so excited over him.
You should just leave if he doesn't look as good as he used to.
Of course.
Something feels missing. I wonder what it is.
I know what it is.
These will make you look prettier. Do you want to wear them?
Yes, I want to wear them.
But you have to return them to me. There's a story behind them.
Of course.
How do I look? Do I look okay?
I think I might start liking women now.
I really envy that first love of yours.
There's my first love.
I can recognize him in an instant.
I think I should go inside.
Thank you, Ta Mi.
You shouldn't say that.
I only said that because it's you.
Da In?
Hello.
- Hey, Da In. - My gosh, it's so nice to see you.
My gosh, you guys haven't changed at all.
Hey, it's been so long.
Is that really you, Da In?
I thought you were in Germany. When did you come back?
It's been a couple of months.
It's so nice to see you all.
Morgan, it's been so long.
Yes, it has.
He hasn't contacted me once.
What? Why do I suddenly see a fish tank?
I'm going to continue tasting the samples.
I just raided the pork belly corner, so it's time for dessert.
I'm in just the right place.
I'm going to try this delicious watermelon.
Thank you.
That will be the end of today's show.
Something urgent came up.
I know you saw me.
Why are you ignoring me like I'm a stranger?
I saw you eating watermelon. Was it delicious?
Yes.
Is Morgan still very handsome?
When are you going to break up with him?
Maybe today.
Nice. Already going through a rough patch.
Ta Mi, do you know you're setting a good example...
by dating a younger guy for young women like me?
You know the expression "to set an example"?
I'm only pretending to be dumb. People dig that kind of stuff.
Anyway, I'm also going to date a guy who's 20 years younger than me...
once I grow old and become famous.
But I can't do that right now. I can only do it once I'm old.
But you can date a guy who's 20 years younger than you.
You can date a guy who's younger than Morgan.
So just break up with him.
What kind of logic is that?
And I'd be dating a minor if I date someone who's 20 years younger.
Really?
I'm not really good at guessing old people's ages.
They're all just old to me.
Let's just drop it.
I'm sorry, but I can't break up with him today.
(Park Morgan)
010356550...
- I missed the last two digits. - Hello?
My gosh, that was so close.
No, I'm outside.
I think we'll all go home in about an hour.
It's the weekend, so we should meet. I miss you.
I also need to meet someone today.
So I don't think we can meet.
I'm a little busy.
Okay, have fun.
- I need to go to the bathroom. - It's over there.
Have you been well?
It's been 13 years since I've asked you that.
How was Australia?
Now that I look back, it was nice.
How was Germany?
Now that I look back, it was difficult.
You've grown so tall.
Yes. Someone even wishes to be 2m tall because of my height.
Just a second.
You should go.
Okay. Let me give you my number.
Let's stay in touch.
My cell phone's on the table. Just a second.
A business card?
You're an adult now.
"Millim Sound"?
What kind of music do you make?
- Please sign this. - Please sign this.
- Thank you. - Please sign the petition...
to oppose Brian's resignation.
We're signing a petition to oppose Brian's resignation.
Please sign it.
Please sign the petition to oppose Brian's resignation.
Please sign the petition.
Please sign the petition...
- to oppose Brian's resignation. - Please sign it.
Please sign the petition to oppose Brian's resignation.
We're going to make it look more simple and intuitive.
The current main page looks as if we prepared everything...
because we don't know what our users want.
But we're going to change it so that it clearly shows...
that we're aware of what they want.
First of all, there are way too many categories...
on the main tab.
We're going to delete two categories to make it look more simple.
You're starting with the most controversial issue.
You're going to discard two categories?
Even if there aren't many users, it'll affect our sales...
if categories get deleted from the main page.
We picked out the top three services that have the lowest users...
and sales profit.
And they turned out to be Games, Books, and My Homepage.
You're saying you want to get rid of two of them.
But wouldn't the people in those teams raise an issue?
They'll just have to bear with it.
We can't risk the regression of our main page because of that.
Times are changing very quickly.
A portal site shouldn't chase after change.
It should take the lead.
The market share is back to how it used to be.
And you want to change our image by reforming the main page?
I'm not quite sure. I don't know if making small changes...
will act as a solution.
Kevin, is there something you'd like to suggest instead?
What do you think the company wants? It wants an increase in sales.
What's the category that has the lowest sales?
My Homepage.
Then that should be the first one to get deleted.
Go ahead and proceed with what you have in mind.
Let's end the meeting here.
Kevin.
You should attend the TF Team's meetings.
I'd like you to make decisions right on the spot.
We need to reform the main page in just two weeks.
Having to report to you like this is inefficient and time-consuming.
I'm not Brian. I have my own methods.
I like how things are right now.
The doors are opening.
Who sent you?
You just delivered the photos.
I'm just a delivery guy.
I don't know anything.
You'd better answer me if you want to leave quietly.
My gosh, I love this music.
Will this company be in charge of our game's soundtrack?
Yes, we're going to contact them.
It's Millim Sound, the company that recently worked with Unicon.
Millim Sound? Park Morgan?
I don't like this song.
But you just said you like it.
I'm saying I don't like him. I really don't like that guy.
- I like him. - Me too.
- Me too. - Me too.
All his works are amazing, and we all wish to work with him.
We should sign a deal before he becomes too popular.
Music should have...
- some class... - What's this?
We're going to be exempted from the main page?
They're going to delete two categories...
from Games, Books, and My Homepage.
- What? - What did you just say?
These jerks.
It's an educational lecture service we'll be working with.
They have a lot of popular instructors.
Listen to the marketing lectures. You'll learn a lot.
(The power of making the impossible possible)
(Wella)
My gosh, I didn't know this guy would be on here too.
I'm Charlie, Senior Manager of the Book Service Team.
I'm Michelle, Senior Manager of the My Homepage Team.
- Gaming Department... - I know who you are.
I know why you're here.
The decision had to be made...
to simplify the main page.
It's to benefit Barro, so please be understanding.
What decided the cut?
Sales or number of users?
Both.
Then how can you cut the Gaming Department?
You know the amount we bring in.
No one clicks on the game tab...
to access the games.
Users type in the name in the search bar...
or click on the shortcut icon.
That's right.
Besides, mobile games are leading the market anyway.
The Gaming Department should be cut.
What are you talking about?
Ever since we lost the contract with the online library service,
the Book Service Team has been low on revenue.
Besides, who reads books in this day and age?
Information is just a click away.
Books are no longer a profitable medium anymore.
In this new era, we are now listening to books instead.
Books are past their time?
- Games must've fried your brains. - What?
Web portals have a standard to maintain.
Barro is a web portal used by everyone...
and it must serve the public interest.
Public interest, yes.
If money is all that's important, we should only post ads.
Why bother with other services?
My Homepage Team,
you don't even provide any kind of service.
Who uses My Homepage these days?
It's just a poor little diary.
Scarlett, did you hear that?
Our passion as youngsters is what fueled My Homepage,
and he just mocked us.
- Well... - Who made Barro what it is today?
There was a time when My Homepage was more famous than Barro.
It was Korea's first social networking service...
and it had up to 15 million users back in the day.
My Homepage is Barro's pride and its history.
One who forgets his history...
will never have a future.
So?
How many users do you have left?
Stop trying to revive a service that is already dead...
and let it rest in peace.
You fool! What did you just say?
- You fool? - Yes, you fool!
- Did you really just say that? - I did!
How barbaric. Della, Bianca?
You're both too primitive to have a proper discussion.
Then just get lost!
Why should we?
Matthew isn't wrong, you know.
My Homepage has been on the downfall.
- Hey. - Shut it!
Is that the best you can do?
- No wonder you're a mess. - What?
This is why My Homepage has been on the downfall.
What?
Someone must be constantly sponsoring you...
considering how poor the quality is.
Oh, these?
It's the apartment Mr. Oh often visits these days.
We tried very hard to get the woman's face,
but we couldn't.
Go ahead. Take one right now.
What?
- Oh, so it's you. - Who was it?
Who ordered these photos?
Ma'am, come on.
As you know,
this line of business is entirely based on trust.
Did you ever consider that you could die?
I guess you didn't.
How much is it that you want?
I thought two big ones should suffice.
I'll give you four, so keep following me around.
- Keep taking photos too. - Sorry?
Send the photos to this person.
(Managing Director Song Ga Gyeong, 37-30 Sampyeong-dong, Bundang-gu)
Isn't this your wife?
Why are you sending her these?
Because they make good evidence.
What do you mean?
The more, the better, right?
It's a place that was empty for a long time.
Other than me and the cleaner,
you're the first visitor.
The passcode is your birthday.
The more, the better, right?
What has he been planning?
Tomorrow at noon, 77 Eonju-ro.
Be at the table if you wish to negotiate.
It's soy sauce.
Isn't it good? What do you think?
The sausages look great.
- Wait, hold on. - Are you kidding me?
- Seriously? - Sorry.
Looking good.
Morgan, there's a photo of a woman in here.
Who is she?
Is she your girlfriend?
Just eat, you punk.
He's in a relationship, so you should just dig in.
You're seeing someone?
But we've all been busy. When did it happen?
Being busy can never be an excuse.
You just have to be brutal, don't you?
Let's drink then.
Look at us having a company outing. We've sure come a long way.
You worked hard as well, Morgan.
- You too, guys. - Sure.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Forget about the hard work though.
I'm just happy we produced great music.
That's right. Once the game is launched,
we'll get so many project offers.
We already have one.
What?
We already have a new gig.
Be back at the office next week.
Next week?
- You took the job from Barro? - Yes.
Seon Woo, you'll start on the sketches tomorrow.
(Beyer No.77)
- I have one more round left. - What do I do?
Do I text him or not?
Wait. Haven't you texted him?
Go ahead. Nothing will happen unless you take action.
What should I say?
"Hello" is lame, isn't it?
"Did you get home safely? It was nice meeting you."
Things like that.
It's not difficult, you know.
Do you know...
how far my imagination ran after our reunion?
I imagined us getting married...
and even having a kid!
Gosh, I'm so lame.
You're adorable.
You went from mentor to child in a matter of seconds.
I wish you the best.
If things work out, it means that you'll end up with your first love.
I have something to apologize to you about.
Remember the earrings you let me borrow?
I lost one of them.
I looked everywhere, but I couldn't find it.
This is bad.
I'm so sorry.
I went back to the pub...
and searched every corner of my house,
but I couldn't find it.
It's okay. I must've fastened it too loosely.
Won't you send the text message?
- It's an emotional scene. - Okay.
Let's rehearse it first.
Let's run a rehearsal with Gi Tae and Min Hyuk.
Must we do that?
I've been around too long to rehearse with this nobody.
Please help me out, sir.
Forget it. Have him practice with someone else.
Also, I'm not ready to shoot this scene yet.
Let's shoot the later scenes first.
If we do this first, my emotions will get all messed up.
Aren't you going to consider my emotions?
Can't you work out a decent shooting schedule yet?
What got into him?
I don't mind. Shoot the other scenes first.
I'll wait.
It's an important scene and might take a while.
Darn him.
- Sorry, Ji Hwan. - It's okay.
Prepare for the next scene.
What was that situation I just saw?
Oh, that was...
It was nothing. You don't need to get angry.
How dare he...
How can I not be angry after what I saw?
Who does he think he is? Are you two close?
Is he a psycho?
I'm in more scenes than before...
and getting noticed.
As the male lead, he's not very pleased.
I get that he might not be pleased,
but why turn it into an attitude?
How dare he whine and pout when he's at work?
Does he bother you in other ways? Like, hit you...
He doesn't.
Too bad. If he hit you, I could hit him back.
I'll help you rehearse. Give me your script.
Where do I start?
Here, at the flashback.
"Flashback from before Min Hyuk's death. Gi Tae."
Read from there.
That's why you're Min Hyuk, not Min Jae.
I'll start then.
"The mother-in-law you're hitting on."
"Min Sook. Doesn't she seem familiar?"
"Darn you. Hey."
"I told you not to talk to me. Get lost."
"Min Sook is your dead wife's mother."
"Your previous mother-in-law."
"Hey. If Min Sook is my mother-in-law,"
"then I'm your father, you jerk."
"You don't have to believe me."
"So stay away from Min Sook."
"You and she aren't meant to be."
"You little bug. I told you to shut your mouth."
"Don't talk such nonsense or I'll kill you."
Sorry. That was too harsh, wasn't it?
You must be upset. Sorry.
Are you okay?
You're the wrong practice partner. Forget about this.
No, it's just that you're so good.
I already knew that, but still.
As you know, Min Hyuk's lines are usually like that.
While Min Jae's lines are sweet.
For example?
"The day we held hands."
"I hesitated a hundred times before doing it."
"This confession, I hesitated a thousand times."
"I think I like you."
My actor's really good.
That clutch. It's nice.
What brand is it?
Why are you suddenly asking about that?
Because I thought it was nice.
Ji Hwan.
You keep forgetting that I'm your fan.
Don't do this to your fan.
Fans get confused when a celebrity does that.
Are you a fan?
I don't know who's the one getting confused.
You're late. Come and sit down.
Welcome, Ms. Daughter-in-law.
We're almost sick and tired of waiting for you.
Sit down.
You held a press conference as if you represent Unicon.
You're practically the face of Unicon.
I finally got to eat with you.
I can rest assured now. I feel so much at ease.
My daughter-in-law is smart and good at what she does.
I had bad luck with my husband, but was blessed with her instead.
When she becomes CEO of Unicon,
you all have to serve her well.
Butter her up.
She'll become CEO soon?
She has to. I'll see to it.
My daughter-in-law is great at what she does.
You've rebelled enough...
for a woman in her 40s.
You made an old woman dance to your tune.
Pretend to give in.
I won't give in.
I told you clearly that I'll get a divorce.
You won't be CEO?
I said I'll make you one.
It's not up to you.
The US headquarters and board elects the CEO.
Do you think I can't manipulate the board?
Will the headquarters just let you?
This is not a time to show force.
I'm the one who holds the key.
How dare you call me here after all the dirty things you made me do?
The negotiation plan you must bring...
should state how much you'll give me...
and how the assets will be divided...
in return for my destroying all the evidence I have.
That's it.
That's a negotiation.
Did you think I would negotiate with you?
We lived as a family for 10 years.
I'm saddened that you know me so little.
Seeing that this is how you act, I really want to do it.
Show my force.
It was about others until now.
Experience it for yourself what happens...
when my force is aimed at you.
I'm hurt, Ga Gyeong.
I liked you so much.
He's so handsome.
What are you all doing?
Was it usually this crowded at this time of day?
Would you like some tea?
If you have a sweet tooth, we have cookies too.
No, it's fine. Thank you.
You probably maintain a strict diet.
- Welcome to Barro. - Welcome.
Hey, Hannah, Bella, Bianca.
We're at work. Shall we return to our seats?
Let's go.
Put more effort into your equipment instead of your looks.
The sound quality was terrible.
It's because it's a demo. Listen to the actual release.
You seem to think life is easy because you trust your looks.
It only lasts a while.
Do you know that? It means nothing when you're older.
I was pretty in my youth, so I know.
You're still pretty.
What?
That was too informal.
Hey. Are you teasing...
me right now?
Is this how you work?
Are you a gold-digger?
Does Tammy know you are a gold-digger?
When you were younger, were you a better person?
What did you mean by that?
We already started work on the project.
You'll get your demo in about two weeks.
Give me your feedback. I hope we get along in the future.
I'm near your office.
I'll be at a cafe.
Come see me for a second.
- Hello. - Hi.
What brings you here?
Did Tammy ask you to come visit her while she's at work?
No, I signed a deal with Barro.
Really?
- Does Tammy know? - Not yet.
Please keep it a secret.
Okay, sure.
Bye, then.
Oh, right.
I heard you went to a reunion.
Plus, I heard you even went to a coed school.
I'm not sure if you know, but she really hated that you went.
She really hated it.
Why is he asking me to come outside? I'm so busy.
He must think I have so much time.
Why are you here?
Did you have a meeting nearby?
- Don't you have something to say? - You're the one who called me out.
You should be the one talking.
I heard you didn't like that I went to the reunion.
- Who... Who told you that? - Who do you think?
I heard it from the person who saw you being jealous.
Hyeon...
Why would you get jealous in front of someone else and not me?
Are you nitpicking right now?
No, I'm angry at you.
- Why? - Why do you think?
You're dating me, but you got jealous in front of someone else.
Why can't I see you get jealous?
I'm the only one who deserves to see that.
It's just wrong. Don't you agree?
What?
- Show me. - Show you what?
I want you to get jealous in front of me.
You got jealous because I went to a reunion where there were girls.
Hey, do you know that you're really weird sometimes?
You're weirder.
Isn't it weird you got jealous in front of your colleague, not me?
Are you going to do it or not?
Do what? Get jealous?
Here?
Are you asking me to reenact the moment?
Why can't you?
You're still upset that I went to the reunion.
So show me how you really feel.
Will you stop talking nonsense?
Why would you ask me to get jealous?
Forget it, then.
I wasn't even asking for much.
You're making me sad.
I'll be off now.
You're really leaving?
What...
He's just going to leave?
Hyeon, you told him, didn't you?
What are you talking about, Tammy?
You told Morgan I was upset that he went to the reunion.
He's unbelievable.
I can't believe he told you that already.
- Where did you meet him? - At...
I ran into him near the company building.
Why would he get upset about this...
when he's the one who made a mistake?
Do you really need to talk about this kind of stuff at work?
Who are you to talk? You even went out with a colleague.
Why would you mention Pyo Joon Soo right now?
I'm not the only one who dated him.
Why would you bring that up?
We should take the game category...
out of the main page, right?
Yes, we should.
Right.
I have a question.
What did I exactly say when I was angry...
that Morgan went to the reunion?
You said you couldn't understand why he'd ask if he could go...
and that he shouldn't have gone.
"Why would he ask me if he can attend the reunion?"
"He should know better not to go."
- Is that how I said it? - No.
You looked a bit cuter than that.
Your eyes were so big.
- My eyes? - Yes.
Like this?
That looks cute too.
But it wasn't quite like that.
You're cute in a different way when you're drunk.
Why do you keep saying I'm cute?
Then stop being so cute.
My gosh, you little...
Oh no.
You should watch where you're walking.
What are you going to do about this?
I'm sorry.
I need to hand it in right now, but how am I going to do that?
My gosh.
But was it really my fault?
You wouldn't have dropped it if you had been more careful.
You wouldn't have stepped on it if you had been more careful.
Hey, what's your problem?
Why are you taking it out on her when you're the one who dropped it?
Look at how bad your painting is.
I guess you're here to slack off.
You shouldn't even call this a painting.
What? What did you just say?
Let's go, Ga Gyeong.
It was nice seeing you.
(Assemblyman Kwon Chang Hyuk)
Hello, sir. It's been a while.
Yes, of course. I'm doing fine.
Your nephew is doing very well.
He's very competent.
We're just grateful to work with such great talent.
You met Chairwoman Jang?
Ms. Song is going to become what?
I was surprised to hear from you.
I didn't think you'd call me today.
I want you to hold Ga Gyeong down.
This is interesting.
Every time you do this, it really gets me thinking.
I heard you're going to appoint Ga Gyeong as the CEO.
But you want me to hold her down?
I want an explanation.
Ga Gyeong wants a divorce.
But I'm not going to give her what she wants.
That's why I want you to hold her down.
If Ga Gyeong doesn't get a divorce,
you'll get rid of me and hand her the CEO position.
So I should support her in order to keep my place.
What's your intention behind telling me this?
What do you think will happen if she gets a divorce?
She'll no longer have the support of KU Group.
What do ex-daughters-in-law of rich families...
end up desiring the most?
Power.
They want power to protect themselves...
because they don't know when they might get attacked.
You don't seem to get it.
Let me cut to the chase.
If she doesn't get a divorce, I'm going to appoint her as the CEO.
But if she does get a divorce,
Ga Gyeong will become the CEO on her own.
Do you need a better reason to hold her down?
Today's the morning of the big day.
As we discussed yesterday,
talk to each team and come to an agreement.
Each team will have their own opinions.
But the most important thing...
is how Barro will be perceived through the main page.
Please don't forget that.
Scarlett, take the Branding Department.
Joseph and Jenny, you guys take the News Team.
Ellie and Alex, take the Advertising Team.
I'll go talk to Kevin.
Can't you tell the difference between this orange and this one?
They're obviously different.
It's so obvious.
They're completely different.
How are they different?
Can't you just change the color?
Who's going to notice the difference?
Do you know how many people watch the live baseball stream?
We compete with Unicon like crazy to increase the number of viewers.
But look here.
How many baseball games do we have a day? Five.
But look at the space for the scoreboards.
Is it enough for five lines?
Unicon provides all five of them at one glance.
If we don't do the same, we'll lose the competition.
But if we let you have more space,
there won't be enough for the sub-categories.
That's not what's important right now.
Baseball is key!
Baseball isn't life. Life is baseball for us.
Look here.
This is the current screen, and this is the revised one.
You want to push the ads down?
- Wait, David. - David!
Pushing the ads down will cost us severely.
You know that, Alex.
Yes, of course. But the direction of the new main page...
Are we starting a charity?
Advertisements bring in the money. It's our cash cow.
Its space is sacred and shouldn't be touched.
Just get out.
I'm done with this new main page.
Scarlett, you seem angry too.
It's why you're treating your skin.
I never imagined that changing the main page...
would be this difficult.
It's my third time, and I want to resign yet again.
I'd rather just die.
When I was in charge of the Marketing Team,
I butted heads with the Revision Team.
I'm in their shoes for the first time.
What goes around comes around.
So how do you think Tammy is doing?
She's probably taking on our biggest foe.
That's the so-called front line.
- No. - I won't take no for an answer.
- Tammy. - Kevin.
Like I said, web portals...
They must give back to society and be of public service.
I'm not saying we should get rid of the Donation tab.
How can it stand out if we don't deliberately expose it?
Our users can't know if we're doing good or not.
As you said, Barro is a company.
We need to advertise that we're giving back to society.
The main page...
is our best platform to generate sales.
Donations?
Barro's image? It's all good, so keep it up.
Before any social contribution,
I'd rather generate more sales and make sure all our employees...
get to keep their contracts.
That's not a good enough reason...
since Barro already makes enough money.
You want to prove yourself with numbers.
You want to prove that Barro can function...
without Brian.
Is that wrong?
Of course not.
However, you'll have to personally persuade every employee against you.
Barro's direction won't change because...
we had a change in leadership.
Barro has always been going...
in the right and proper direction.
"The right direction" can mean...
something entirely different.
If you wish to have the Donation tab exposed,
then make space for more ads.
We will now begin the disciplinary hearing.
On June 28, without the board's approval,
Managing Director Song...
held a press conference by herself.
She brought chaos to the company internally...
and revealed trade secrets...
and internal regulations to the public.
We find Ms. Song...
in violation of Article 11 of the Unicon Company Regulation...
and Article 15 which states her misconduct.
The violations are enough to relieve her of her position.
However, due to its positive outcome,
we will only place her with a two-month suspension.
Shouldn't you still be at work?
What are you doing?
I'm...
making dinner.
You know how to cook?
I lived alone when I was in New York...
and I barely had enough money to get by.
My mother cut me off when I went to film school.
I had to work two part-time jobs.
Maybe I should get one of those.
I'll be out of a job for a while.
The press conference was probably presented as the cause.
Still, it doesn't sound like you were fired.
My mother must really be fond of you.
She keeps giving you second chances when we'll be divorcing anyway.
I received some photos.
They were of the two of us.
I also found out who sent me those photos.
You worried about my outcome from this divorce before I did...
and I'm grateful.
- We should eat first. - Just so you know,
those photos...
hurt me sometimes.
We want nothing from each other,
we have no right to get upset about it,
and we're no regular couple,
but sometimes it felt like...
I was truly alone in this world.
Something like that.
I sometimes think like that too.
In order for you to not be alone,
you have to be alone first.
I apologize for the cruel approach.
Actually, I apologize for...
not being a decent person over the past 10 years.
I promise you this though.
I'll get you your divorce no matter what.
I haven't done anything for you in my life,
but that I'll make happen.
So what's that?
Today's our wedding anniversary.
I thought it'd be our last, so I bought you flowers for once.
Why did you buy so many though?
So it'll be hard to throw out.
Let's eat.
Related to what we discussed earlier...
we will now go back to discussing the methodology once more.
First, let's talk about phenomenons.
It's important to observe...
and perceive such things.
What can we say these phenomenons are then?
Data, right?
Every day, data is collected...
and accumulated. So all that massive data...
We should go out if you're done with your classes.
I told you we should meet outside.
Actually, I feel more comfortable here.
I don't like you spending money on me either.
Being indoors won't stop that.
Here you go, Mom.
I said I wouldn't accept it until you earn more than I do.
We might have to compare because I just got paid.
Businesses can fall at any second.
Do you have a savings account?
Don't worry.
My business will only thrive.
Then this is your allowance from me.
Seriously?
Receiving an allowance at this age...
Well, it feels great.
I like how thick it is.
Don't spend it all at once.
Sure thing.
Professor, the dean would like a word with you.
- About five minutes should do. - All right.
- I'll be back in five. - Sure.
(Son)
(Bae Ta Mi)
Why did you ask if you can go to the reunion?
Of course, you shouldn't have gone.
Just because I told you to go, did you really have to go?
Why go to a reunion where there will be women...
when you have a girlfriend?
You don't look handsome just to me.
Other women think so too.
You know that.
You know you're handsome.
How can you go there when you're aware of that fact?
Do you think I was cool with it because I acted cool?
I'm not cool with it at all.
The moment you told me, my fury reached maximum level...
that I almost blew up the earth, okay?
Be grateful you're still standing on it.
That was a rehearsal. I'll go again.
What am I doing?
I want to stay the night.
No. Go home.
Enacting that brought back the emotions.
I don't want to be around you.
I don't want to be around a guy who met his female classmates.
Don't you get that?
Say yes. Let me stay with you.
This is unbelievable.
You're being a fuss.
Get off me.
I clearly said I don't want to be around you.
One, two...
I'll kill you if you go to another reunion.
A reunion?
What's that?
You don't need to know.
Never find out forever.
Such events should be abolished.
Connections made in school are the ones I hate the most.
They should disappear.
Just look at that sweet face.
It got so much fun...
- since he returned as a twin. - That's right.
I watch this just to see Min Hyuk.
Me too. I want him to marry my daughter.
I don't have a daughter.
- If only I were 20 years younger. - Oh, come on.
Look at that.
My goodness.
("What's Wrong with My Mother-In-Law?" ratings)
Let's see.
("What's Wrong with My Mother-In-Law?")
Really? It's over 20 percent?
Master actor Seol Ji Hwan who's starring in a hit drama,
congratulations on going beyond the 20-percent rating.
Why did I eat so much?
Why won't he reply?
Is he that popular now?
I'll take this.
Wrap it nicely for me.
- I'll get you a new one. - Okay.
I didn't see the text.
I was about to call you.
I have good news.
Are you free?
Why... This is...
the same as yours.
You said it was pretty.
Can I really accept this?
What's the present for?
I have a real manager.
You signed with an agency?
Where? What other actors do they represent?
I signed with the agency that represents Hyun Bin.
Really?
Oh, wow, that's great.
Anyone with eyes would recognize my actor.
Congratulations.
You're the one who deserves a present...
and I got one.
You went through a lot for me.
Thanks to you, I signed with a great company.
Thank you.
I'm a fan who got a present from a celebrity.
A fan?
From now on, I'll act like a fan should.
Sorry if I confused you.
As a fan,
being able to do this with a celebrity they like...
is quite exciting.
Right.
Where do you shoot now? You aren't late, are you?
I'll drive you.
Ji Hwan, over here.
You have a car already.
Your company made quite a fuss.
They got me the car yesterday.
I'm all for that fuss.
Now I can relax.
Good luck with the shoot.
Thanks. See you.
Now I can be...
just a real fan.
The parents who raised me are Australian.
They were working at the Australian embassy...
when they adopted me.
So we lived together in Korea...
and then I went to Australia with them when they went back.
That's why you went to high school in Australia.
Are they good people?
I can tell.
They're really nice and really funny.
They're fun people.
I'm grateful for them.
I should be grateful too.
Tell me more.
Is there anything I don't know?
Actually, I met my mom today.
My birth mom.
Your biological mother?
You're in touch with her?
Yes.
My Australian parents found her for me.
When I was 20.
I'd met her after a long time...
and something upsetting happened.
My birth mom is a mom to someone else as well.
(Son)
(Mom)
(Park Morgan, student)
My mom's a professor.
It was a great disguise.
So I just felt...
a bit upset.
You weren't just upset. You were hurt.
It's okay.
Everyone either gets hurt by their parents...
or hurts them.
Back when I was young,
there was a time when I thought...
that I was forced to be born when I never really asked for it.
But if I think about it the other way around,
my mom might've given birth to me...
when she didn't really want to.
Back then, my existence alone was probably enough to hurt her.
She was only 21.
I'm sure she doesn't think that way anymore.
I liked how you told me...
that you felt sorry for me that day.
Ever since I was young, people tried to hide that from me...
because they thought they were being polite.
I acted like I didn't notice any of that...
and kept my manners as well.
But you just told me that you felt sorry for me.
And I really liked it.
I'm a pitiful guy, so I'm going to sleep over tonight.
Fine, I'll let you sleep over since you're pitiful.
I'm going to do more than just sleep.
Isn't that a given?
You're so sexy.
- This looks delicious. - Yes.
- What do you do these days? - I idle away.
We're getting attacked from all sides...
because we're trying to reform the main page.
But you seem like you're doing okay.
I envy you.
My goodness.
Do you think you're the only one who visits me?
The people who attack you come to see me every day.
Thanks to you, I'm busier since I left the company.
Gosh, I need to get my liver checked tomorrow.
The youngest members of each team are...
asking people to sign a petition to oppose your resignation.
Do you know that?
Yes, of course. People visit me every single day.
You must be happy.
I envy you for having such a strong fan base.
That darn fan.
Well, anyway,
I think it'd be a good idea to add something new...
as we reform the main page.
But I can't think of anything.
Other than reorganizing categories and changing the design,
I want there to be an issue that people can talk about.
Issues always arise at the right timing.
Around 50 years ago,
you'd be front-page news if you wore a miniskirt.
So in the end, an issue is the middle ground...
of a particular time and value.
How would you apply that to our business?
Well, for example,
you could pick what will soon be picked...
in this current time.
And in reverse, you could discard what will soon be discarded...
But the crucial part is that you need to do it beforehand.
The right timing.
Timing?
The right timing is eventually what creates an issue.
What do you mean we exceeded the period of use for the web drama?
What's the certification of contents for?
Remember the original work of the web drama...
that you asked us to air when we launched Con TV?
The agency called and asked us not to air it...
because the license period expired.
When did it expire?
This April.
And you didn't know that?
Maybe we should've done more than just suspend you.
How is this possible? The launch is in less than a month.
We put in so much effort to cast all those actors...
so we could enter the South-East Asian market.
If this goes down the drain, it'll be useless to launch it.
I'm sorry. I'll look into what happened.
By the way, Director Bae...
was the person in charge of this project.
And you were Bae Ta Mi's direct boss.
Ta Mi would never make a mistake like this.
She definitely would've made sure we had enough time.
You seem to trust her more than you trust yourself.
If there's no written consultation, she would've done it via email.
How are you going to read her email when she no longer works here?
I'll get her consent so we can read her email.
Good going.
You'll have to beg an employee who caused a mess here...
and left to work at Barro.
Yes, I'm at the pub in front of the company building.
I'll see you here. Let's go together.
Okay, bye.
(Song Ga Gyeong)
(Consent form to view contents of intranet email)
Sign it.
Why do you need my email?
The web drama agency sent us a certification of contents...
saying we exceeded the period of use.
I discussed the term.
I knew the term was going to end...
around the time the drama was going to be made.
I figured that could be an issue, so I discussed it via email.
That's why I want you to sign it.
You made us get a certification of contents...
because you didn't leave a written consultation.
I added in the contract...
that we could discuss the terms via email or written consultation...
if there's a legitimate reason behind it.
Are you saying it's a problem that I discussed it via email?
The problem is that you made me come here for something like this.
Don't you get it?
Don't you know how sick I am of all the troubles you cause?
Is this seriously my fault?
This isn't my fault.
The agency's trying to mess with Unicon.
You must've done something to make them want to do that.
You left without even saying goodbye to our subcontractors...
just because you got fired.
Do you think this is the only issue you caused...
- by leaving without a transition? - You need to bear with that...
since I was dismissed unfairly.
And shouldn't you be asking me to sign the agreement...
instead of ordering me to do it?
You're here to ask me for a favor.
Why are you so angry when you're asking me for a favor?
You were never this emotional.
At least that's how I remember.
What do you even know...
about me?
Do you want to criticize me and tell me that I've changed?
Do you want me to go back to how I used to be?
- I just want... - Why do you always...
cling onto me as if we had a special relationship?
Do you think...
you've changed?
I'm scared...
that this might've been your true self all along.
I need to hand it in right now, but how am I going to do that?
But was it really my fault?
You wouldn't have dropped it if you had been more careful.
You wouldn't have stepped on it if you had been more careful.
Hey, what's your problem?
Why are you taking it out on her...
when you're the one who dropped it?
Look at how bad your painting is.
I guess you're here to slack off.
You shouldn't even call this a painting.
What? What did you just say?
Let's go, Ga Gyeong.
So much for that cute face of yours.
(Gyeongil Girls' High School, 11th Grade, Class 2)
(Bae Ta Mi)
(Search: WWW)
Just how much did you like me?
Now I want to know how much you hate me.
CEO Na of Unicon and the Vice-president of Barro...
are meeting Chairwoman Jang for a meal.
What will you do now?
What is it you can do?
Fans are supposed to watch from afar.
So you're just my fan?
Why don't you ask Da In to play the song this time?
- Aren't you going to get married? - I want to,
but that's not up to just me.
He's my first love.
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu's subs