Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I am a prosecutor, Lee In Ah.
Mr Nam,
this is Lee In Ah. She is in charge of your son's third trial.
Mr Tak.
What is she doing here?
I thought you wanted to change the prosecutor for his third trial.
I am the prosecutor in charge of Nam Kyu Man's case.
I will seek justice.
Mr Tak.
What is going on?
This means Mr Tak's business at Ilho Group is finished.
It was difficult for me to keep this secret.
I feel much more relieved now.
Mr Tak,
how could you...
Crazy jerks!
Gosh! Seo Jin Woo!
You are here.
Did you watch...
the video I sent you?
Yes, I did. You're dead.
It sounds like...
you did watch it.
Yes, I did!
Do you think doing this would change anything?
What will you get by distributing a video that has no legal force?
People will watch the video and then you'll see.
All you need to do is to wait for the law...
to give you the punishment you deserve.
I am a man...
who can play around with the law. Haven't you seen what I've done?
No, I've seen enough.
But the important thing is...
that you are not the one who is above the law.
It's the truth.
But will you remember the truth? I know you're ill.
You better focus on remembering yourself.
I may forget who I am,
but I won't forget the truth...
behind my father's death.
I'll see you at court, Nam Kyu Man.
I won't!
I will never go to court, you jerk!
My goodness! I will kill him!
This is killing me.
Does this mean...
that I have fallen into...
Mr Tak's trap?
You are an interesting man.
I hear that often.
I'm known for never working for anyone.
Do you think such a trick would destroy me?
What's your purpose of doing this?
It's to let the world know of the true faces of yours...
that have been manipulating the law with money and power.
I'd like to know...
that true face of mine myself.
You will see it soon...
when you go to court.
Now,
everything is over for you.
You should've let me know.
I'm a little upset.
I'm sorry.
I tried really hard to stop myself...
from punching you in the face.
I had to make you become suspicious of me...
to completely fool that old snake, Nam Il Ho.
That's true.
You will never know...
how sick I felt when I had to flatter Nam Il Ho.
Why wouldn't I know that?
You're right.
Here you are.
Cheers!
How does it feel to work as a prosecutor again?
I am Lee In Ah.
I recommend her as an experienced prosecutor.
She is very passionate and determined, too.
I heard you are...
the person who planted Mr Tak in Ilho Group.
I've always been a troublemaker for Mr Tak...
for acting hastily only on my passion.
I always thought the problematic ones were those who only...
care about how to please their superiors and acting complacently.
Please...
do the best of your ability.
I will do my best.
I'm not sure yet.
The prosecutor general supports you. Why are you worried?
What if I feel sceptical about the prosecution again...
and what if I have to compromise...
It wasn't the prosecution, it was a person...
that made you feel sceptical.
You should've seen Hong Moo Suk's face when he saw me.
What?
Come here.
You'll do better than anyone.
I'm looking forward to it.
- To what?
- I'm looking forward to...
your nosy way of solving cases.
Be bold and hold true to your convictions.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Sir.
It has gotten out of our hands.
We've done this before, haven't we?
Change Lee Jin Ah and the judge.
After the release of the president's video from five years ago,
no one wants to be involved.
Are you saying we can't make any changes?
No, Sir.
We'll have to go to trial with the assigned prosecutor and judge.
Is this all you can do?
Sir, the public is not favourable at the moment.
We need to find a way to gain popularity again.
First of all, we need to...
turn the public in our favour.
Are you telling me to step forward?
If a father comes forward,
people will sympathise.
If he's a man of conscience,
he should resign from being the president.
A murderer is the president. Does that make sense?
We don't know if it's true yet. It could've been fabricated.
Can't you tell?
Nam Kyu Man killed her for sure.
He's notorious around here for being a menace.
Congratulations.
Great.
You got it right.
I did kill her.
Sir... Sir.
Where are you going?
Let's get on the elevator together.
Wait.
- Gosh.
- I...
I am sorry.
I am very sorry.
Why?
Weren't you complaining about me?
Let's have a talk in my office.
No...
I... I have... no complaints.
Don't you?
You know what?
Now I have complaints.
I... I...
I am sorry.
Please forgive me.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Look at me.
I'm a murderer.
Then isn't it okay to kill one more?
How about you...
die from getting beaten up?
What? A murderer?
Did you say a murderer?
Die! Die, you idiot!
Die, you idiot!
I'm sorry, Sir. Please forgive me.
What? A murderer? Die!
You'll be killed by a murderer. Just die!
I didn't know a person would die so easily.
The confession video has been released.
The retrial is on.
They are in deep trouble.
Nam Il Ho and Nam Kyu Man...
won't be able to turn the case to their favour.
Kyu Man is completely cornered.
Now we need witnesses who'll help us finish him.
Wouldn't Gwak Han Soo be a sure witness?
We need one more.
Someone who knows about this case very well.
Someone who is close to Nam Kyu Man.
An Soo Beom.
It won't be impossible if we ask Judge Kang.
I heard you took over the trial in place of Chae Jin Kyung.
I am going to indict Kyu Man...
for all the crimes he committed.
I want to see him finished.
So...
Please go on.
Could you please help me call...
Soo Beom as a witness to the retrial?
It won't be easy.
But I will talk to him.
(AN SOO BEOM)
Your call has been forwarded to the voice mail service.
Hello...
Hello... I'm in here.
Help me.
I'm in here.
Please...
You'll be killed by a murderer. Just die!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stop the video from spreading.
But I had him drop the charges.
You won't be going to court for this.
Are you joking with me?
With the salary you get from me, is this all you can do?
You should've been careful.
- What?
- All eyes are on you...
because of the confession video.
What's the situation like?
With the third trial coming up,
we have to be prepared for the worst.
Okay.
I sincerely apologise for...
the trouble my son has caused.
As the chairman of Ilho Group and...
as Nam Kyu Man's father,
I ask of your forgiveness.
Please blame me.
It is all my fault.
Regardless of the court's ruling,
Nam Kyu Man will resign his current position as the president...
as well as all the titles he has...
with the subsidiary companies.
Ilho Produce will be...
reverted to the state.
I would like to apologise again...
and ask you for your forgiveness once more.
Gosh,
the years of experience under your belts are incredible.
You are quick at managing crisis.
Are you trying to provoke us?
You might have put out a small fire just now.
But it's too late to save your house that's burning down.
Don't think that...
my son and I will go down so easily, Dong Ho.
A son and his father are one, aren't they?
Jin Woo and I will put you two to jail.
Just consider it as taking a life lesson.
Get out of our way.
You're still deluded.
You're the one who's deluded.
You're Ilho Group's hound.
Don't trust...
Hong Moo Suk too much.
There's no one that can be trusted, is there?
Have a good day.
In Ah, you're here.
- Did you move all your things home?
- Yes.
Mum.
You know I'm back at the prosecutor's office, right?
You always do whatever you like.
What's the point of letting me know afterwards?
Mum.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Do whatever you like. An attorney or a prosecutor.
But I won't let you be with Jin Woo.
- Mum.
- In Ah,
Jin Woo will only get worse.
How will you handle that?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
In Ah,
go in first.
If Kyu Man is found to be...
the real killer at the retrial,
what will his sentence be like?
It'll be 20 years at most.
Once people forget, we can get him out with a special pardon.
Father,
how could you take away all my positions...
I had no choice. It was for the group.
The trial hasn't ended yet.
We don't know what will happen to me.
Your video has been spread all over the world.
Why are you still saying that?
The chairman is doing everything in his power...
to remedy the situation.
I'm consulting Mr Hong about...
the worst-case scenario...
that may happen to you...
after the trial.
I pulled you out of all of your positions...
to calm down the public,
so stay quiet and calm down.
Yes, Father.
I'm repenting.
Why do you keep coming here?
Detective Gwak,
how long do you plan to stay here?
Well,
I should stay until all of my sins are washed away.
The chairman can get you out immediately.
What does he want...
in return?
Say that the confession video that you gave Seo Jin Woo...
was made under coercion.
And at the retrial,
don't say anything and keep your mouth shut.
Where's Soo Beom?
This sounds like Suk Kyu.
Did you see my father's press conference?
I've been fired from my position as the president.
Is this what you wanted?
Where is Soo Beom?
Why are you asking me?
You're the reason I can't reach him, aren't you?
I am...
trying to calm myself down. Don't do this to me.
Don't try to hide anything else from me, and tell me where he is.
He quit,
saying he didn't want to clean up after me.
He should have landed in the States by now.
Really?
I really hope that's true.
I don't want to see how low you can go any more.
Good.
Ms Lee,
Soo Beom has disappeared.
Kyu Man says he left for the States.
Border control says...
he left this morning.
He didn't call you first?
No, he didn't.
But...
I think Kyu Man is behind it.
I'll look as well.
Okay, In Ah. I'll look too.
I think...
Nam Kyu Man did something to Soo Beom.
He's still causing trouble even during the trial.
Please look for places...
where he could be hiding An Soo Beom.
Okay.
The person you have dialled is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Gosh.
Why isn't he picking up?
Is something wrong?
Yes.
I can't reach Soo Beom.
- You can't reach him?
- No.
Maybe something happened.
Sorry?
He did say jokingly that...
Nam Kyu Man will kill him.
I see.
Something definitely happened.
Jin Woo must have Soo Beom on his side.
I need to repay my debt.
Call your boys.
I'll do it my way.
Yes, Dong Ho.
Hi, how have you been?
Hello. It's been a while.
What brings you by today?
Find this person for me like you did the other time.
Have some coffee while you wait. I'll be done in 30 minutes.
Forget the coffee. Get moving.
Soo Beom.
You can't sleep here. You'll get sick.
Kyu Man,
please let me live.
You want to live?
Then I'll give you one final chance.
Go to that punk Seo Jin Woo...
and bring the wine opener.
I will do...
anything other than that.
Since when were you so stubborn? How did you hide it all these years?
I'll live quietly.
Please, let me live.
You said you won't get me the wine opener,
so why should I let you go?
It doesn't make sense.
If you don't want to bring it yourself,
you can make Seo Jin Woo come here himself.
The person he needs the most...
is you.
Kyu Man. Kyu Man...
Kyu Man.
Kyu... Kyu Man.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What's this?
You're not Seo Jin Woo.
Nam Kyu Man,
you've gone over the edge.
What brings you here?
Why?
Did you want to see your friend who went ahead of you?
Come here. I'll send you to him.
Let's see how long you can talk.
Let me take...
Soo Beom.
Get rid of him!
My goodness, Kyu Man.
It'll take at least a month for me to recover.
You'll already get...
a hefty sentence as it is.
You'll make it longer. What will you do?
What will I do?
I have a lot of pent-up anger against you.
I'll pay you a hefty settlement fee,
so let me beat you today.
I will never...
settle.
Kyu Man,
let's follow the law.
Follow the law? Whatever.
Let's see who wins, the law or me!
Give it to me.
What are these gangster punks?
Sang Ho, what took you so long?
Dong Ho! Are you okay?
Look how many I'm against!
I got beaten up so much.
It's time for you to get my revenge.
Let's go, guys!
- I'll get you!
- Get him!
- Come on!
- Let's go!
I'll get you!
Take this...
and this!
You are both just gangsters,
but why is my gang losing?
Come on!
You idiots.
I'm done here.
Soo Beom.
Thank you for staying alive.
Sang Ho.
Thank you...
for saving my life.
My goodness, aren't you two just a pair of lovebirds?
Get a room, you two.
Right, Soo Beom.
How do you feel about staying in our office with us?
It's too dangerous for you to go home.
May I?
Dong Ho, he can, can't he?
Do as you'd like, Sang Ho.
Thank you very much, Mr Park.
And you are the only loyal man, Sang Ho.
Did Mr An really switch sides?
Yes.
What would happen if he stands in the courts?
The moment he witnesses,
your retrial will be over.
Then, Lee In Ah will accuse you for everything.
In that case,
you will be punished for killing Oh Jung Ah.
Hey, Mr Hong.
Save me.
I do have one solution.
This will be dangerous for me, too.
We need to proceed without your father knowing.
Without my father knowing?
Yes.
What do you want?
I'd like you to hand me...
the golf resort in California which is under your name right now.
All right, so tell me already.
You fake your death...
before you stand in the court.
Yes, Mr Song.
I just found out the last known location for Mr An.
- The address is...
- Are you home?
Jin Woo!
I just found a witness who'll bear witness on our retrial.
I'll call you back.
Weren't you just looking for Mr An?
Jin Woo, sometimes illegal ways get things done faster than legal ways.
Where is Mr An?
It's me, Seo Jin Woo.
I know it wasn't easy,
but thanks to you, we were able to get the crucial evidence.
I am prepared...
to pay for my crimes.
But it looked like...
Nam Kyu Man wasn't interested in paying for his crimes.
He's been hiding it for years. He wouldn't accept his fate.
That's why I'm here...
to ask you to stand...
as a witness for the retrial.
I will make sure...
Nam Kyu Man gets punished by the law.
I don't think I can bear witness.
Do you know what I've learned over decades of watching him?
If you fight against Kyu Man, you'll die.
Kyu Man may be cornered at this moment,
but I am scared and frightened.
- I will protect you from...
- No!
I won't bear witness...
as long as Kyu Man is alive.
What are you talking about? Are you telling me to die?
Mr Nam, calm down.
I'm talking about laundering your identity.
First, go to China.
Are you telling me...
to stow away to China?
And there, you'll become a dead man on papers.
And you'll launder your identity...
to become another person.
Becoming another person, you say.
After a while,
you can come back as a new person to restart all your businesses.
One thing is this.
I hope it doesn't take too long.
I hate living abroad.
You know how things are.
People never remember anything for long.
You, Mr Nam...
and Oh Jung Ah...
will soon be forgotten.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I'm sorry, Dad.
I couldn't sleep in warm bed...
when I get reminded of the difficulties...
you face in here.
Don't do that.
It would make me feel better if I know that you are doing well.
I feel like I have to rush, but things aren't really working out.
Can you guess...
what the most difficult thing about staying in here is?
It's the fact that...
I can't see you growing up.
That's what makes me sad.
I can only imagine, you know.
I wanted to make more great memories with you.
I'm really sad that I can't do that, Jin Woo.
I am truly sorry...
that I can't be there for you.
Don't worry, I already have...
many great memories with you.
Those are enough for me.
You've done so much for me since when I was very young.
What if...
all the memories...
of you...
vanish, too?
I can remember everything for you.
I will remember them forever.
All of your memories are...
left here with me.
Dad.
I'll do this well.
Again, I'll be standing all alone...
in the defence counsels' bench.
You can do this well without me, can't you?
I couldn't have done all this...
without you.
Attorney Seo Jin Woo,
your father is watching you.
Tell everyone...
the story you've been wanting to tell them.
Defence witness, please come forward.
(RETRIAL OF THE SEOCHON COLLEGE STUDENT MURDER CASE)
Please introduce yourself.
I investigated...
the Seochon College Student murder case five years ago...
and made Seo Jae Hyuk write up an affidavit.
I'm Detective Gwak Han Soo.
What did the affidavit entail?
The affidavit said that Seo Jae Hyuk...
killed Oh Jung Ah.
In the process of making the accused...
write the affidavit,
did you coerce or threaten him?
Yes.
Seo Jae Hyuk...
did not admit to the crime.
I made him make a false confession.
Objection.
What the witness is saying is...
completely opposite to what he had said in the previous trial.
Sustained.
Witness.
Do you know...
how serious of a crime...
perjury is?
Yes.
I know it well.
Let me ask the prosecutor.
Why would I be here?
I'm here to be punished.
I am here to...
ask forgiveness to...
Seo Jae Hyuk and Attorney Seo.
Witness.
Only answer the questions you're asked.
Yes, Your Honour.
Was there...
any crucial evidence that...
made Seo Jae Hyuk a suspect?
There was the wine opener...
which was the murder weapon.
But it did not have Seo Jae Hyuk's fingerprints.
What the witness just said...
is his personal opinion.
Witness.
Are there any grounds for your statement?
Yes.
The wine opener used as evidence...
in the trial five years ago was fake.
I will submit the actual wine opener that was...
used for murder as evidence.
Objection.
The evidence the counsel is submitting is fabricated.
I will submit the results from National Forensic Service as well.
The forensic results show that...
Oh Jung Ah's blood and flesh was found...
on the murder weapon.
The murder weapon found previously did not show...
the murderer's fingerprints.
But the wine opener you see here...
contains the murderer's fingerprints.
The murderer?
The murderer is...
Ilho Group's president, Nam Kyu Man.
Counsel,
how did you obtain the evidence?
I received a report.
Your Honour,
the origin of the evidence is not verified.
It must not be accepted as evidence.
Who is the informant?
Because of the circumstances the informant is in,
I cannot tell you, Your Honour.
If you cannot reveal where it originated from,
it cannot be accepted as evidence.
I'd like to call a witness.
Objection.
This witness had not been agreed upon.
This witness is the one who brought me the wine opener.
Is what the counsel just said true?
Yes. I...
gave that evidence to him.
I will acknowledge him as a witness.
I am Nam Kyu Man's chief secretary...
An Soo Beom.
Can you describe how you came to...
be in possession of the evidence?
On November 2, 2011,
Nam Kyu Man's welcome home party...
was held at Seochon Villa.
Oh Jung Ah was there to sing.
Very early in the morning after when the party was over,
I ran over to the forest after getting a call...
from Nam Kyu Man.
Oh Jung Ah was already dead when I got there.
Nam Kyu Man was heavily under the influence of drugs.
He handed the murder weapon to me and ordered me to take care of it.
He ran away from the scene.
So I...
hid the real murder weapon.
So...
the weapon that was presented five years ago,
was it fake?
Yes.
Why did you...
hide the real murder weapon?
I was afraid.
Were you afraid?
Nam Kyu Man...
could have framed me for the murder he committed...
if anything went the wrong way.
So...
did you hide the weapon...
in case of that happening?
Yes.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
An Soo Beom's testimony turned the trial against our favour.
An Soo Beom, that idiot.
Police will be on to you soon.
We need to move onto the next stage.
Make sure there's no setbacks.
Counsel, make your closing argument.
I am the defendant Seo Jae Hyuk's...
attorney and his son.
Seo Jae Hyuk was an ordinary father.
Five years ago,
he was framed for crimes he did not commit.
He passed away not too long ago...
without being able to...
clear his name.
Up until this retrial,
in order to prove his innocence,
I had to...
fight every moment.
During the time...
when Ilho Group...
completely destroyed Seo Jae Hyuk's life...
and Nam Kyu Man continued on...
with his evil doings,
I realised that...
the truth does not...
speak for itself.
For the past five years,
I tried very hard...
not to forget the memories...
my father had lost.
That is because...
I believed it was the only way to clear my father's name...
who was an innocent man.
Your Honour,
please find the accused, Seo Jae Hyuk,
not guilty.
The accused is no longer here,
but please use the justice of the law...
to show that...
he is not guilty and that...
he will not be forgotten.
That is all...
for my...
closing argument.
(DECISION)
I will announce my decision.
There is insufficient evidence...
to prove Seo Jae Hyuk is guilty of murder.
Thus, the original decision has been overturned...
and Seo Jae Hyuk is declared not-guilty.
Also,
on behalf of the justice system,
I express my deepest apology...
to the late...
Seo Jae Hyuk.
Jin Woo.
Good job.
Now, the entire world knows...
that your father was innocent.
You never know whether someone is a friend or foe until the very end.
You and I are...
I don't know what to say.
Do you need more time to see it?
I'm not asking for forgiveness. However,
I feel much better,
now that your father has been vindicated.
You should also...
live your own life now.
Jin Woo.
This is my life.
Paying penance for...
all the wrong I've done.
Have you...
been well?
Jin Woo.
Even if I lose my memory again,
you will remain...
in my heart forever.
I'm sorry it took so long.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Dad.
You were found not-guilty.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Did you need something?
What are you doing?
If Dad finds out...
I need to save myself first.
I can deal with the rest later.
Yeo Kyung.
I don't want to go to prison for nothing.
The thought of going there...
gives me a headache.
You didn't see anything.
Neither me...
nor this.
You understand what I mean, right?
Put out an all-points bulletin for Nam Kyu Man and track his car.
Yes, Ma'am.
Hi, In Ah.
Nam Kyu Man has disappeared.
We have a warrant for the arrest of Nam Kyu Man.
Your cooperation is appreciated.
Where is Lee In Ah?
Jin Woo, we located Nam Kyu Man's car.
He's headed towards a dock.
Okay. I'll head there now.
Okay.
I'll look into it, too.
There's a warrant out for Kyu Man's arrest.
He must be trying to escape to China.
Did you know about it?
I had no idea.
I advised him that if he went in for a while,
we'd get him out soon with a special pardon.
That useless rat...
ran away to save himself?
I put up with the humiliation...
and bowed my head...
just to save him!
Please calm down.
That rat.
That useless rat!
I won't accept him any longer!
Sir.
You punk.
(INSPECTION POINT)
What is it?
I think my brother is trying to escape to China.
What?
He had a Chinese passport and ID.
I'm sure of it.
Why are you telling me this?
It's my last...
ounce of pride as a prosecutor.
And...
it's an apology for all the wrong my family has done...
over the past five years.
Thank you.
I think Nam Kyu Man is trying to escape to China.
Step on it.
- Please hurry.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Mr Nam Kyu Man!
Are you going away on business?
This worm is here again.
You're finished.
Fine. Catch me if you can, punk.
You jerks!
I didn't get on yet!
You need to take me!
You can't go by yourselves!
Come back!
You jerks!
Turn the chopper around! Turn it around!
Shoot.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU